got eight bloody thumbs up. Oh gosh darn it. Yeah.
You little copy. You little copycat. At
least he admits he's a little copycat.
At least he admits he was being a copycat though
with the crowd. I was thinking about
that when I was doing my little washing.
Yeah, there's nothing wrong Indigo with
somebody wanting to fit in with the crowd.
UK signing. I don't know how we can sit
there and try and [ __ ] flex Natalie
G. Bro, the all of the women that I've
been with is [ __ ] better than [ __ ]
all of the women that he's [ __ ] been with. Silly [ __ ]
You know, I mean, mate,
don't bring me up in your [ __ ] [ __ ]
Don't get sloppy with me, you [ __ ] Yeah.
So, Indigo, why did you say that if you
don't like Shay?
Why did he say that again, Indigo?
Oh, by the way, my mom owned all of LJ's
um followers, by the way. I'll read what she said.
Yeah, Mommy F owned you all. I'll read
what she said when more people join.
Yeah. So why did So why did Nons say if
you don't find her attractive, you're gay then?
Yeah. But why so why did he say why did
he say it?
Yeah. So why did he say it then?
So why did he say it then indigo?
Yes. So why do you say I'm gay then if I
don't like her?
No. Go on. Why did he say UK signing?
Why did he say I'm gay if I don't find her attractive? [Laughter]
Yeah. Why did he Why did he say it?
>> Yeah. Why did he say it UK silent? Do
you know why?
He said, "If you don't find her
attractive, you're gay." Do you remember
why he said it?
Yeah. Laney owned you all,
by the way. She said, she said,
he said, she said, "Yay, tell your
friends I am watching the bold-headed
[ __ ] I report them for deformation of
character. Also, I'm more fit than any
of them [ __ ] They're welcome to
come tell me to my face, idiots. I will
slap them down without a second thought.
I wonder how they would feel if I was
their 65year-old mother. Oops. Sorry, they don't
They don't though. Lonely, low life, dysfunctional morons.
>> Yeah. Laney owned LJ's followers. Yeah.
This true though. They ain't got no
family. These people. Yeah.
Yeah. True though. Is it?
He says it because he wanted to fit in
with the crowd,
you know. He wanted to fit in with the crowd.
Yeah. Because he's a little copycat.
He's a little copycat. UK sign. He
wanted to fit in with the crowd, didn't he?
Yeah. He didn't want Yeah. He just
didn't want to feel left out. lesson
must be hard, you know, being new in college.
Yeah, he's a copycat. Yeah. [ __ ] madness.
I don't know why though. I've never
copied anyone. I've never feel felt the
need to copy
to fit in with a crowd. You know,
you called the noise. He's attractive.
Oh, by the way, I had a shower, by the
way. I had a nice little shower.
I was stinking, so I know. I need to get
a haircut. I know. I know. My hair is a
bit out of control.
It's all right.
It's all right, mate.
Just naturally dry. Had a little hair
wash and um Yeah.
So, what do you think of Monte?
But it turns out this woman I was
speaking to on Reddit is in a real is in a wheelchair. [ __ ] hell. Yeah.
What do you think of these Reddit
moderators? Do you think it's a power
thing with them, Indigo? I mean, they
don't get paid. They don't even get paid
to [ __ ] ban people.
They sit on there all day and they don't
even get paid.
How does that even make sense?
And not even get paid. That is [ __ ]
mad. And not even get paid.
That is a madness.
It turns out this person was in a [ __ ] wheelchair. 100%.
These old mongos on here aren't worth it.
none of these people in here got family, lad.
Yeah, that's what my mom was saying
that they're jealous cuz they got no
family. These people in here are loners.
They got like no family.
My mom said the same thing. If you
notice that the people on here, you
notice they've got like no family
and they're ugly and they're fat and
they're losers. Yeah.
But they're also ugly people that are
jealous that like I'm I'm younger than
them as well. It's a few different things.
>> Yeah. It's a few different things.
All right, Gregy. I had a KFC today. We
was waiting for you.
Laney owned these people earlier.
Yeah. Laney said the same thing that
they're jealous cuz I got like a family
and that and they don't. And it's coming
up to Christmas as well. So, they're
going to be sat at home Christmas lonely.
I went on a
I got a far peace meal and a popcorn chicken.
I got a far four far peace meal. Oh,
bless you then.
We've been waiting for you all day,
Grezy. We've been waiting for you. We've
been expecting you.
Do you think I'm better looking than Red
Star UK asylum?
Do you think I'm better looking than
Redshaw if he showed his face?
I said to my mom.
I said to my mom, I just think they're failures.
Yeah, I had a KFC. It cost me £20 with a popcorn chicken.
Do you reckon I'm better looking than Red Star?
Yeah, I think they're jealous of me,
bro. And I I don't think I'm better than
anyone. I said that I think they're
jealous because of what they do. UK is
hiding cuz what they do every day.
They're stalking on Reddit. They're
stalking every day. That's why I think it's jealousy.
Not because they're just older and I
think I'm better. It's because of what
they do every day for years. Yeah.
It's because of what they do every day
for years, bro.
It's not because I think I'm this that.
It's because of what they do for years.
Stalking, harassing, making videos every day.
If people are not jealous, they don't do
that stuff. That's what I was trying to
say. But Joseph Ferrar is a [ __ ] mong.
These people are very biased on it as well.
Same as that. Joseph, he's biased.
Yeah, but it's not about jud No. No, but
they're not judging my life, though.
They're stalking. They're actually
stalking what they do.
They're actually stalking.
But yeah, I'm not going to tell them
nothing from now on. Anyways, if they
had their own life, they wouldn't be
doing that in the first place.
I agree. See,
Monty man said he's not going to tell
these people nothing.
I think they're jealous cuz I'm younger
and better looking than them and have
family. That's what I think.
And obviously I can go out and do what I
want when I want. I'm free. I can do
what I want when I want. Think about it.
I can do what I want when I want.
Yeah, it's true.
Let me ask you a question, Greavves. And
I want you to tell me if this is biased
or not because
what's your opinion on this uh bouncer thing.
So they were saying to me, "Oh, uh yeah,
I went for a bouncer knowing that he
couldn't fight me, even though bouncers
beat people up all the time." But then
when this bus driver was shouting at me
a few years ago, no one called him a
coward for doing something when he knew
I couldn't hit him back. See, this is
what I mean on here. They're all biased
to what's you know the more you you
argue with these people you actually
lose brain cells. I've actually got a
headache. I've actually had a headache
for the past like day and a bit. Like
not like a proper proper headache but
like a how do I explain it? Like um a
sore head. I've actually got a sore head
because of these people
because they're you're arguing with a
bunch of disabled people. They're [ __ ] biased.
They are biased. Another video on that.
Joseph Ferrar. Did you watch the video
on Joseph Ferrar Griezy? Watch the video
on Joseph Ferrar and tell me what you
agree and what you disagree with.
Cuz I think you always disagree and and
and sometimes you agree but you agree. I
think you're the one to to I think
you're the most impartial person on here.
What's the Joseph for all even half of
it and then come back?
Did you watch the Joseph Ferrar
video UK asylum
and then apparently I get my clothes off Kana.
Why are they so hateful these people?
Cuz you can afford things that they
can't. Jeans, trainers.
Yeah. So, what did you think of it? What
did you think of the Joseph Ferrar
video? What did you agree with? And what
did you disagree with,
bro? Kana. Why would I use Kana? I've
got my own money. I can buy whatever I
want when I want. What the [ __ ] are you?
I was laughing. It's quite sad that you
you'd say that, but but what did you
think of the Joseph Ferrar video?
I think they are biased with the nonsle
thing, with the bouncer thing. They are biased.
And again, I don't think they're jealous
because they're older than me and I'm
better than them. I think they're
jealous because of what they do on here.
Yeah, he is. He's fast enough to not he
he's he's he's he's fast enough
to [ __ ] suck up Nons's dick when I'm
going at him, but nowhere. Uh oh, yeah.
Apparently, I've got a bad credit file,
but then I use Colana. Bro, I'm not
showing these people receipts. I'm not
showing them receipts. I'm not showing
them nothing. I'm not here to prove
myself to fat ugly people. If they show
themselves, I'll show these receipts and
I'll show money again. If they prove to
me they're not fat, ugly bums, greasy, I
will show receipts. I'll show again. I
have no problem. But until then, I'm not
showing them nothing. Nope. Never used
Colana in my life. Don't need to use
Kana. I bought my jeans and my trainers.
Both paid out full. Never paid off for
clothes in my life. Don't need to. I have money.
I don't use Colana.
I have my own money. If I used it, I'd
say I used it. Never paid off for
anything in my life. My jeans I got from
the mainline wear and the trainers I got
from Foot Asylum. Both receipts.
Yep. both both got receipts for
and I am not showing nobody nothing.
They're just jealous because they're ski
people that can't they can't listen they
can't fathom paying £200 for jeans
because they can't afford it. So they
hate on anyone else that can afford it.
You know what I'm saying? So they they
they can't fathom that someone can pay
£200 for jeans
and then when they get proven they're
just they're just little losers on here,
bro. That's what they are. They're just little losers.
They care so much about others cuz they
ain't got a life of their own. See, the
thing is UK asylum, if they were just
people that were in their 40s doing
their own thing, I wouldn't say they're
jealous. I say they're jealous cuz what
they do, you understand? I wouldn't sit
there and say, "How hard can it be? He's
jealous of me cuz he's 45 or 46."
Because he's 45, 46. It's what they do
on here. It shows that that it's an act
of a jealous man. It's what they do on
here. It takes a lot of time, a lot of dedication.
So that's why they've got nothing.
That's why I say that
if it's a if it's a channel, right?
Okay. Like for example, I'd say Lem is
not Lem is Lem isn't jealous of me.
So I mean that's why I say this stuff.
So, what did you agree with on the
Joseph Ferrar video and what did you
what parts you agreed with and disagreed
with? I want a summary.
I'm mad. Oh,
I'm going blind, bro, if I'm looking at
the screen too long.
So, what do you agree with and disagree
with on the Joseph Ferrar video?
They are bi they are biased
because if a bouncer beat me up they
love it. So they are they are biased and
he's biased with the nonsle legs thing.
He's biased with the nonsle legs thing
as well. Yeah, I'll be there Saturday.
Don't you worry. He's also biased with
the nonslegs thing. They are they are
biased. They are biased on here.
They are biased on here, bro.
They're 100% biased on here.
Maybe they don't even realize they're
doing it cuz they're that disabled.
Yeah, that nonsleg thing run me up, bro.
It's fast enough to his rescue like
Superman. Because he says that you don't
prove yourself to these people. Yeah.
Prove I've had more. Prove I've had
money. Prove I've had sex with people.
Prove I've had women.
And then they still talk [ __ ] But he
says that I forget things.
What are you on about, bro?
Yeah. Yeah. Exactly. It's it's it's
excuses because when that bus I don't
know how long you've been on here, but
when that bus driver was having a go at
me, I got called a [ __ ] for not saying
anything back to him. And then when you
say something back to them, oh, they're
at work. That's what I'm saying. It's
it's part of their biasness. That's what
I'm saying, bro. Cuz this bouncer was
running uh sorry, this bus driver was
running up his mouth. I don't know. It
was like four or five years ago. It was
a few years ago, bro. It was about four
or five years ago. He was [ __ ]
chucking up his mouth, bro. And I was
quite younger, so you know, I didn't say
anything. And they all call me a [ __ ]
But now if you reply back then,
but then when you go back, but then when
you give it back to them, then they they
say that they're at work. And then
they're always they're always full of excuses.
I think UK silent these people don't
like you if you're not fat and ugly like
them. I think they make problems with
people that are not fat and ugly like
them cuz they get a bit jealous. No
family and [ __ ] That's that's what I
think it is, bro. I generally generally
think it I think it is that. I think it
they hate themselves cuz they're old
failures and they're jealous of people
that are younger and better looking than
them that's got a mother and [ __ ]
That's what it is. So
pretty much. Yeah.
Get a job. Get a job. Get a job. Get a job, mate.
So yeah, um the jeans was 20200
pound and the trainers were £210. So yeah,
so that means I've got So that means I
would have had over£400 colana credit.
Really? Over 400 colana credit for
someone that's got bad credit. Really?
Really, bro? Really? They always talk
[ __ ] Do you remember they used to call
people's clothes fake?
They used to call people's clothes fake.
I don't know if you remember, but
they used to call people's clothes fake.
Yeah, they used to call people's uh clothes fake.
Yeah, but then and then they say that
you buy stuff from Kana. That's funny, bro.
They don't think I've got money. They
think that Oh, they think they [ __ ] me
with the sub sublet thing when it wasn't
even them that stopped it. Um, but
either way, I've got money anyways.
These people don't know about anyone's life.
They don't they don't they don't know
about anyone's life. And I don't need to
prove myself. I can go out every week
and go out twice a week if I want to. I
don't need to prove myself to these
people, bro. These sad, pathetic people.
Why is it always people proving
themselves to them? Why don't they prove
themselves to us? Why don't they come on
camera? Why don't Red Star do a live
stream and start talking? Show his face.
[ __ ] ask people to prove themselves to you. Yeah.
They're just sad people in here, bro.
What's the reason?
UK asylum. These women are [ __ ] [ __ ] in it.
probably this person on Reddit was
[ __ ] disabled, bro.
You had a shower and done some washing.
Yeah, it's bad, bro. Bad. I wonder.
Could you imagine I was a virgin, lad?
Imagine I was a virgin.
What would I do at uh UK aside if I was a virgin?
I'm a [ __ ] I'll be [ __ ] It Yeah.
Yeah. I'll be in bed.
Yeah, but it's not the same. I don't use
escorts, bro. I don't use escorts,
you know. I don't use escorts. Me.
People on Reddit say you can easily get
sex UK asylum.
Rice wants to know why I have not met
anyone yet. He Rice wants to know why
I'm not settled down. UK asylum.
I don't know what got into me the past
couple of days. I was just pissed off,
bro. I didn't lose money. I don't gamble
only on football every two weeks. I was
just pissed off, bro.
[ __ ] [ __ ] women, bro.
I think when you think about your
experiences and the amount of money
you've spent and No, no, no, no, no.
You've you've got nothing for it.
It's madness, bro. [ __ ] mad.
I still got my nice trainers and my nice jeans. Um, yeah.
Yeah. I don't know.
I told uh Chinese Izzy that I hate
women. She always says come to
Manchester. I said dude, [ __ ] you.
Yeah. So, what do you reckon the chances
are of getting a date now that is UK
asylum? If you're starting off fresh
cuz you imagine like just starting off fresh.
Probably take you a very long time in it.
You wouldn't get a date. It would I
don't know. I don't I like I said, I
haven't had one since April.
March and April, I think it was the last time.
March and April is the last time I had a
date and I've been out multiple times.
Uh last month I went out three weeks in a row.
Yeah, I went out three weeks in a row,
bro. Three weeks in a row.
>> Yeah, I went out three weeks in a row.
Remember, bro, I went out I've been out
a lot since April.
That's why I don't bother. That's why I
don't bother with it. UK signing because
all that's going to happen when you go out is
I'm not interested. I have a boyfriend
or they give you D and lead you on.
I was having an argument with this woman
earlier. She says that all men are the
same and I'm saying all women are the
same. But when she says all men are the
same, it's all the men that she's
choosing because I've gone out and I've
approached people and if they were truly
looking for someone normal, well then
they would have went on a date with me.
some of them. So don't there's no way
that these women because the thing is right
the thing is these women have got
options. So even if there if there's 99
shitty men there's got to be one one out
of 100 that's like normal now there's
got to be like one guy out of 100. So
they've got options to pick from. So if
you have no options then that's the end of that.
Obviously, they have to like there's got
to be one in them actions that are
normal. You know what I'm trying to say?
And and obviously people approach and
stuff. There's no way they can't find
anyone that's normal even even if it
took time. So that's why I've got no
sympathy when they say that all men are the same.
That's why I have no sympathy
because it's like
I've approached people and they've said,
"Oh, you're this. You're that." and they
still won't get with you. So, it's like
it doesn't make sense. They have options.
So, even if it took three months, they'd
still find someone.
Someone with no options is not going to
find anyone. Think about it. It's common sense. So, yeah. Yeah.
What do you reckon will happen if I go
out Saturday talking to people? UK asylum
think any any changes.
I can't be doing that [ __ ] anymore, bro.
I ain't got the energy.
I wish I could say I ain't got the
money, but I do.
I haven't had a date since April.
I don't need a wing woman, bro. I can I
can I can talk to people myself. I don't
need a wing woman.
I don't need a wing woman. I don't need
a wing man. I don't need a wing woman. I
can do I can approach myself by myself, bro. Ah, Coffee cats Oh, no. I'm finally for Mhm. coming in.
Well, it will never change, will it?
Will it will never change, will it?
Why change up the time? Mhm.
Yeah, I love my flagship phone. It's quite cool. Gosh.
One second. UK Asylum. When do you
reckon this phone is going to pack up?
It's a flagship.
Would you say probably never?
Yeah, these little fat ugly mongos don't
don't bother me. Do you reckon this
phone will ever break? I don't think so.
I've had it a year and it's a flagship.
It's a fold. It's a fold phone.
Cost me 1,700 quid.
It cost me 1.7k quid.
I don't think it's going to pack up, is it?
That's how much it cost me.
It cost me one. Yeah, but it cost me
1700 quid. This mobile phone.
My mama actually got it from me
from the Samsung shop
a year ago.
Nothing lasts forever.
I don't know. I think it will. I think.
Yeah, the battery doesn't seem to [ __ ]
up on it either.
I think that's why they call them
flagship phones, though.
What phone do you have, Captain?
What phone did you say you had? captured. Oh,
you jump away in that chicken.
Yeah, my mother 1.7,000. Yep.
It was quite fine.
Yeah, my mama saved me saved up for it.
Cheers for the flagship phone, mama.
Thanks for the phone, Baba.
What's bro? You're [ __ ] What kind of
question is that?
What a weirdo.
My mama bought me it from the Samson shop. Da da. 1.7,000. Yeah, dusty.
I got uh I've had this phone a year now.
This Samsung Fold. I think it's going to last forever.
It's still quite fast. The battery is
still quite good on it. It was It was 1.7,000.
My mama bought My mommy bought me it.
My mommy bought me it from the Samson shop.
Yep. It was 1.7,000 quid. Saved up for it.
Well, mommy Oh man. forever.
I had a wash, Dusty. I had a wash and I
put my clothes in the wash.
Yeah, I've got a sore head, bro. From
this community gave me a sore head. I
need to stop. I need to take a break
from this because it's hurting my eyes.
But I've been looking at the screen for so long.
They're [ __ ] my eyesight up. Yeah.
No, I am leaving for a bit. I have to,
bro. I have to.
It's the same. Was
he uploading? Has he uploaded again?
Yeah, you. So, same as you. Same as you.
Same as you, bro.
Yeah, I've been on it since I was 22.
I've done a lot of stuff on here, though.
Did this community Yeah.
Did that Hey, did this community ruin
Monty's life? Dusty.
How did I [Laughter]
Yeah, but he could have easily got off
it though, could he?
Can't deny she's attractive.
>> Yeah, but he could have easily got off
it, didn't he?
Yeah, you can watch Bill and Yeah.
Did I lose everything? Nah.
I don't have
I don't have long-lasting effects over
this website. Do you get what I mean? I
don't have longlasting
where she's like lost kids and like
relationship that it
no about the [ __ ] thing. No, it's not true.
It's pathetic. Pathetic and immature and made up.
No, it's [ __ ]
Absolute [ __ ] bro. It's made up.
It's completely made up.
It's made up. Dusty,
why did he say that was attractive again? Dusty.
Why didn't Nex say that again? Did you
Why did he say that again? [Music] Yeah.
Only losers do that though. Is it that
have to follow
Don't leave me alone. My [ __ ] They keep
obsessing over me and harassing me and stalking me.
I'm banned forever, lad.
I'm banned from Simmons as well.
They ban me for Simmons for approaching
for mass approaching.
Yeah, you can actually get banned. You
can actually get banned for approaching people.
Yeah, long story, bro. That O'Neals I'll
always be banned until they change the
staff, which I don't think they're ever
going to staff. They're never going to
change the staff, bro. that that that
place, bro. They've been there years.
They're never changing the stuff.
Um, and like Simmons, like I I can tell
you what happens in some of these
places. Well, maybe other ones. Like, say you
have the up with a security lad.
Oh, that nose joke is so boring. Now,
come up with something original. Uh,
it's boring. Listen, Dusty. If if if if
a if if a member of staff yeah says
something to you and you say something
back, they'll just snitch to the
security and they'll just ban you.
Like it's uh it's that it's that much.
I'm still finding someone to try to do
it to, bro. I'm still trying to find
someone to do it to. It's not hard. It's
not easy. I tried earlier. Someone was
talking to me, but they just been
[ __ ] It'll be worth it when I do
find someone. Maybe the tenant. But
listen there if they saying like say a
member of staff gives you attitude right
there was a Simmons right I was in a
Simmons bro listen and this there was
this Canadian and she was a stuckup [ __ ] brouck
up like you should saw the face on her I
said oh yeah she's just like being a bit
of a [ __ ] and someone must have heard me
and then they they they grasped the
security right and then the security
banned me literally bam me bro. Yeah,
just for that. Like the that's how
[ __ ] up it is this country. Like you
can get banned for just like nothing basically.
Um so basically the staff hate their
job. They walk around with attitude and
if you say something they don't agree
with or whatever, they'll just they'll
just tell the security to ban you, bro.
They'll just remove you. They'll remove
you and then uh you know blacklist you forever.
Yep. Forever. And no one no one knew I
went to Simmons either. So when I go in
now, if they scam my ID, it will it will
come up as blacklisted. All cuz I said
that someone's acting a bit of a [ __ ]
Yeah. Really, bro? Cuz no one no one on
YouTube knew about it. Obviously, if you
get in there a bit early, then you could
kind of get away with it. But yeah,
literally for nothing. And the other one
I got banned cuz I was approaching
people. Uh, I approached about three
people and yeah, they they they they
grasped to the bouncer and I said,
"Well, I'm a single guy. I'm allowed to
go and speak to people in in a social
acceptable place." That's why I don't
really go out anymore, bro, cuz it's
just like too toxic.
Um, the Simmons,
Lester Square, Simmons,
Simmons in Leicester Square, bro. Um,
and they'll just move mad. Like me and
this black guy was talking about this
and the other one was Oxford Circus cuz
I was approaching and I'm thinking, bro,
it's a free country.
It It's a free country, bro. You're
allowed to go and speak to It's
literally a free country.
Like, what the [ __ ] So, it's not
against the law to go and speed someone.
So, that's why I don't really go out
anymore, bro. It's just too toxic.
Well, the O'Neal's one was people on
YouTube, so that's different. The
O'Neal's one was people on YouTube. Um,
yeah, it was people on YouTube. Yeah.
But the other two had nothing to do with
YouTube. And I'm thinking, "Oh [ __ ]
I haven't been out for a month.
How can I go out all the time if I
haven't been out for a month?" But yeah.
Um, so that's why I don't really go out
much anymore, bro. Um, there is a place
I do go in central. Obviously, they're
right. Obviously, I go to places, but
yeah, they can Well, yeah, I was in a I
think it was about 7:00 p.m., right? And
I think I I think I was live. I
approached three women. None of them
complained about me. None of them did.
Even though they try and say they did.
No, they didn't because I've been
approaching for years. And I was in
track two bombs. I can't. And And a guy
comes up and this is what started it
with a bouncer. Yeah. And he says, "Oh."
I said, "Okay, let me just finish my
drink." No one complained about me, bro.
I was sat I could see everyone, right?
So, that's what happens. The staff, the actual bartender
will just chat [ __ ] and then the
security and then they'll just then
they'll just ban you. Um, I swear to
God, bro, that's how that's what happens
in London. So, that's what made me say
that it's just a country designed to
annoy you. So, that's why I just don't
bother. I don't bother with it. like you
can go on the street.
No, I just approached three people.
There was a few people in there. It was
like I can't remember what day it was.
Maybe I think it was a Friday. It was three people
and yeah, they just uh
um and it's not even like they said, oh,
like, yeah, can you just like not do it
like so much? Like, can you just stop
for like a bit? They literally said, no,
you're not coming back.
where no one complained. No one on
YouTube knew where I went. So, it was it
was it was definitely the staff. It's
the staff behind the counter. If they've
got any problems with someone, they'll
just grasp on them and then the security
will just chuck you out. That's Simmons.
That that is Simmons, though. I don't
know about other places, but that's
Simmons. Um, and obviously the one where
I called the woman like she I said she
was acting like a bit of a [ __ ] and then
they banned me for that for that. So,
they're two separate ones.
Um, so they walk around with attitude
like the staff bad bad attitude and then
if someone says that they're acting like
a bit of a [ __ ] you you ban someone forever. Really?
Really, bro? And then if you weird,
no, they don't. But it's the only way to
find someone if you wanted to.
It's the only way to find someone if you
really wanted to, which I don't want to anymore. I mean, you know,
it's the only way. It's the only way of
getting someone 1% chance.
But yeah, it's not worth the effort.
It's not worth the effort.
It's just that's why I don't bother
anymore. It's just not worth the effort
because all that happens is they're
going to say, "I'm not interested. I
have a boyfriend." Give you attitude.
Dude, I'll lead you on. And where it's
so toxic, you just don't want to get
back into it.
Because it's so toxic, you just think,
"Nah, there's just no point." Nah,
there's just no point because it would
always be the same. It gets to a point
where you just think like,
"Yeah, well, what else can you do in it?" Fine. Yep.
It is bad though, especially after like
the USA thing and all the other things that happened.
No, I wouldn't pay the bill. I wouldn't
pay the bill. I don't want nothing to do
with them. I'm trying to [ __ ] him over.
I wouldn't do it. I'd [ __ ] him over.
I've had too many bad experiences to
last me a lifetime.
Too many bad experiences.
No, I would leave.
I can't believe the amount of money I
spent and time traveling I did to try to
meet someone. Mad.
Still never met someone.
I think they're all [ __ ]
I think leading people on should be illegal.
I think so.
Cuz that way they can't get a sick
through out of it. I think I think
leading people on should be illegal.
We're not equal. How can we, bro? How
can we be equal when people defend women
for just being a woman?
If if people defend women for just being
women, how can we be equal? It doesn't
make sense. They defend women for just
being women. It's been proven multiple
times. So, how can how can it be equal?
You have a man on the train defending
someone because they've got a [ __ ] in
between their legs. You've got people on
podcast [ __ ] defending women for not
lead apparently not leading people on
when they know they're leading them on.
They just don't want to admit it because they're women.
They can't take accountability for anything.
They can never do wrong. They can never
do any bad things to these people. It's mad.
It's not it's not it isn't existent
because they they defend them for just
being a woman.
They defend women for just being a woman.
But yeah, this woman on Instagram, she's
trying to say all men are the same. All
men are the same. I don't know how they
can say all men are the same though. I
don't know how they can say that cuz
when they're given opportunities to meet
genuine downto- earthth people,
they um they're not interested. So, I
don't understand how they can say that
all men are the same. I don't get it.
One out of 200 men must be different
about, you know, the options that
they've got flooding in their DMs. Think about it.
So, it just doesn't
they just don't make any sense whatsoever.
They pick three or four bad men and
generalize all men based on the men that
they pick. They've hardly even met men.
These people have hardly even met men.
Like I said, they might have met three
or four people.
They might have met three or four
people. Three or four men. That's it.
Then they generalize all men based on
the men that they pick. Weird. No.
these biscuits are nice, bro. So, yeah.
No, it's just bad exper just it's just
it's just bad experiences. Dusty
I should have gave up from them really
is it? It's just bad experiences. We
just talk about bad experiences.
I just don't It's just toxic bad experiences, lad. Nope.
No, it didn't go out the weekend. Triple H.
I can't believe Monty's life got ruined
on here. My mom said that you're too
faced, Triple H.
My mom said that she caught you on other
channels being two-faced and stuff.
My mama told me, you know,
have you seen that account, Dusty? Have
you seen that Ricky Millington account?
I wonder who it is.
Have you seen it? You've seen it any Ricky Millington. [Laughter]
You said you've been
You said you've been on on here a while. Yeah.
Yeah. It is a real person that account, isn't it?
Oh, Greavvesy, you're right. My flagship
phone is still going strong, Grevy. My
mommy bought me it. My mommy bought me
this phone. It was 1,700 quid. She
bought it from the Samsung shop.
Yeah. So, who's that Ricky Millington?
Do you reckon it's a real person
or is it like a robot, do you think? Or
do you think it's a real person typing
behind that account?
Leave Laney alone.
Lay me alone.
Yeah. But who do you think it is though,
Dusty? Like what do you think they look
like in real life? Cuz they seem like a robot.
Ricky Millington is it Grey do love that
account Ricky Millington you silly sausage lovely
I saw this woman on um Instagram Greavves
had like big big boobs and stuff for baby Peter
for me greasy for my vitamins and
I think I need to go to the restaurant again. Greavvesy,
I think the restaurant is good. Is uh
Yeah, if money didn't come on it, he'd
be in the same relationship with Kaye.
Elephant and Castle where Peter Belly
found his mama
is where he found his mama.
Graves Age. Remember Elephant and Castle
is where Peter Bddy was re reunited with his mama.
Have you seen them kind of comments? Dusty.
I wonder who it is typing these things,
bro. I wonder what they look like in
real life just sat there writing it. It
could be anything. It could be a
construction worker on break. It could
be fat ugly old man. It could be a Jack
the Lad with tattoos. I wonder who it is
greedy behind these accounts. You know,
it could be anyone in it.
Could be your neighbor.
Dusty, they said that Peter Belly can't
get attached anymore because he already
found his mama.
You know, because he already found his mama.
But why are they typing stuff like that?
Mocking me. I don't understand why they
mocking me, Dusty.
And when I said about taking a baby away
from its mama, they started like copying
it. Taking a baby away from its mama.
Yeah. I don't know why I said that, bro.
Do you remember Grezy?
Oh, can I get attracted then? Can I get
attracted easy then? Um, Greasy.
So, can I get attracted again?
Do you reckon?
But think about it. Imagine Monty
weren't on here, right?
And the virgin on here, it would just be me. It
would just be me. Imagine that. Just me, you know.
Can you imagine? Did I want to bring
Bonnie down with me, Grezy?
You know. O Grey, did I want to bring
Bonnie down with me? Nah, [Laughter]
no. Basically, you want to know how I
got mod? Yeah. So, I used to watch Timmy
a lot. Yeah. And me and M stopped talking.
We fell out. We used to fell out and
stuff and we was talking on PS4 again. Um
um I was like, "Oh, Ruby, this is how I
start." I said, "Oh, do you want to come
on this YouTube? There's this guy called
Timmy Elders. You'll you'll love it." I said, "Oh,
do you want to come to this YouTube?" He
said, "Oh." I said, "Like, you know how
you like the drama that back on
PlayStation? This YouTube this YouTube's even funnier."
So, he's come on. So, so he's come on
with his So, he's come on with his name,
right? He's come on with his name.
So, he's come on with his name. All of a
sudden, you started getting all of these
accounts, his mom, his dad, like his
mom, his [ __ ] you know, they're
making mom brother accounts.
And that's when it started, mate. That's
when it all started. That's when it all
started. Grezy. Yeah. I said this community.
Yeah. Madness in it. Madness. Madness, mate.
They say without me on it, it would have
been a peaceful community. Crey,
because he's already found his mama. Dusty. [Laughter]
I'm No, no, no, no, bro. You can't just
blame me. Yeah, cuz he could have got
off it. He could have got off it. He
could have got off it, though. He could
have got off it.
He actually could have got off it, bro.
See, if I was in a relationship and
[ __ ] you know, if I was in a
relationship and whatnot with with
someone, man, I I wouldn't I wouldn't
have been on here.
So, he had his choice and he made his
bed and he had he just couldn't get off it.
Greasy. He could He just couldn't get
off it, could he?
He He wouldn't get off, would he? No. [Laughter]
Why? Do you remember when they were
[ __ ] contacting Social? [Laughter]
Do you remember when
you remember when they were contacting
social services? Grezy, [Laughter]
you thought that was funny, is it? Nah.
No, that ain't funny. That's That's not
No, that's bad. Yeah, it was that tra it. Yeah. [Laughter]
lady said it's not funny. I'm immature.
She said I'm It's not funny. It's immature.
So, Gregy, this place could have been a
It could have been peaceful without me.
It could have been peaceful without me, ain't it?
You You said I was the root cause um for
the for the LT [ __ ] isn't it? Do you
remember that weekend
when I uh
Do you remember that weekend, bro, where
I started on the bouncer and it caused a
load of [ __ ]
And it caused a load of [ __ ]
Remember me just posting that video when
it was my own [ __ ] caused a load of [ __ ] in it.
That Timmy arguing with people. Yeah.
Lovely weekend. Lovely. Yeah.
Did you like the poem last day? It was
sweet, wasn't it? Oh,
it's very sweet. They're very addicting and biscuit.
>> Yeah. Would you Did you go for some?
>> That was over there. I haven't had that
for a while.
You know the washing's coming out in a
minute, mate. I'm going to do it, mate.
You all right, mate? Yeah.
>> All right, mate. Hold on, mate.
What do you call them? idiotic morons, in it. >> Yeah.
>> Why they why are they trying to pick on
a 65y old woman? >> Yeah.
>> Is that fair?
>> They ain't got family in it. >> Yeah.
>> Did you say that?
>> Yeah. See through it now.
>> Yeah. You got your relationship.
>> Yeah. It's true, isn't it?
Who did you say? Who did you say is too
faced? Triple H.
>> I don't know. >> Okay.
>> I see one split from your channel to the other. >> Yeah. >> Yeah,
I guess so. Laney.
All right, Laney.
You're L. Can I call you Laney? Why?
>> Yeah, they call you Laney cuz I call you Laney.
But that's my little nickname.
>> Yeah, that's true. Is it? They're fat,
ugly. I bet.
>> Would you say these people are skin? >> Yeah. on YouTube.
>> Yeah. It's from the Yeah, it's from the
time they wake up to the time they go
dead in it.
>> Yeah. That's what I said the same thing.
>> Yeah. I said
>> do it.
>> Yeah. That's what I say. If they've got
And it's not about what It's what they
do. It's not the fact that they're on
there. It's what they do. It's not like
they're on here at the end of the day
for like an hour or two or they've got a
week off. They've been doing this for
they've been doing this for years.
>> Yeah, but I'm not going out though. I'm
chilling for a bit. I'm not saying my
life's better than everyone else's. I've
took three I've took weeks off of YouTube before.
>> Yeah. Well, every day hating.
>> Every day hate him. So, yeah. I don't go
in there hating, do I?
>> That's what I'm saying. So, they
obviously have nothing in it.
>> I think they want my ass.
>> I know. Yeah. I think they want my ass,
man. It's It's kind of dangerous, isn't it?
>> Yeah. Yeah. His body gets [ __ ] as well,
you said, is it?
He's moved house and he's still on YouTube.
But why is he on YouTube if he's moved? [Laughter]
>> They're going to find them again. >> What? >> Why?
>> Straight in the end.
>> Why? But like if he moved, he's moved.
>> No, no, no. He's moved, right? He's live
streaming in the new house. [Music]
No, it's it's him. I don't know if it's
her, but he's moved and he's on YouTube
and he's moved, but he's just moved. [Laughter]
>> You said I've been trying it
>> cuz it doesn't make sense cuz he moved,
didn't it? I don't know why he moved.
Why did he move?
Never like before that.
>> Yeah, I got him. I got him there. No, I
got him there a couple of um I got him
on there a couple of couple of years ago
because I had I met him on the
PlayStation and he didn't know about
this YouTube and I said, "Do you want to
come on this YouTube?" Cuz there's some
guy on here called Timmy Eldridge. He
said, "Yeah, you'll love this community
cuz it's drama." He used to love drama.
He's come on it now. They started making
accounts of his mom, his brother. I
didn't know they were going to do that
cuz they did they done a lot of the
stuff um to him before they done it to
me. Before they done it to me and I was
on it longer than him like the letters
and stuff, they done that to him first.
They done mad stuff to him before they
done it to me. Yeah. So, it's not like
they had done this stuff to me then I
had brought him on here. You understand?
They done it to him first. They done it
to him first. Yeah. Like the whole like
the windows and the Monty was already on
here so it never all happened and then I
was like come on it. Obviously I
wouldn't put him on it if I do that obviously.
>> Yeah. But you understand what I mean is it?
>> Someone like you.
>> Yeah. I'm talking to Grees.
>> You're not
>> Yeah. Luckily, you're noting. >> Yeah,
>> you can leave now.
>> Yeah, I'm just talking to cuz I like to
talk to Grezy.
>> If I if I cuz if I don't But if I don't
go on YouTube, then Grey doesn't get
content. The poor [ __ ]
You know what I'm saying? The poor
[ __ ] The one that goes on my live
stream. The poor [ __ ]
>> Yeah, he's a he's he comes on my live streams.
uh planet Mars. Um up north somewhere,
>> but but the poor [ __ ] won't get any
content and then he'll be bored out of his head.
>> No. Okay, fair enough. But he likes the
Indian restaurants and stuff.
>> I need to take my wash out. One sec.
Oh, greasy. Poor [ __ ]
Then he doesn't get content. The poor [ __ ]
Yeah, they done all that stuff to him
before they done it to me.
They They really did, bro. They really did.
Sounds like a copycat statement.
>> You little copycat.
>> Are you a little copycat?
Mom, are you a little copycat?
I might do my bedding actually.
What's the most?
One off, one on.
You little copycat. Meow.
You copycat. They're copycats because
they're copying people. Mommy. Ma.
How do you know that I done my traveling and that?
I said, "How do you know that I've done
the traveling and stuff?"
You watch the videos, isn't it? You used
to like the videos, didn't you, Ma? Oh,
I got some lovely clothes, ma. Oh,
I was telling everybody how you bought
me my my flagship phone.
It was £1,700. I told them that my mommy
bought me it.
Is that true?
You did buy it for me, ma
back last year, huh?
No, you bought it for me £1,700.
You c you you £1,700 mama
from the from the Samsung shop. All right. Oh,
my [ __ ] underpants.
How many errors do we have? Huh?
All right, I'm going to need that as
well for my other bed.
I'll put 20 in the ley, darling. No problem. You little
no mind of your own.
You got no mind of your [ __ ] own. I
hate people that ain't got a mind of their own.
That's to say people attract him to fit in.
He says he says he was attractive. He's a copycat.
>> Yeah. He likes to fit in with the crowd.
Bless him. It must be scary being new,
you know. One second. I'm just doing my little underpants.
Where's my little sock?
I've lost the sock, mama.
Oh, there it is.
Well, I need to I need to take a break
off the phone, you know.
It's starting to affect my eyesight.
Uh the looking at the screen
looking at the screen.
Yeah. I need to rest my eyes. M
because I could die
and you have to come to my funeral. Mama,
what are you sat there doing, man?
You're being good.
Oh, do you want a lost kebab? Do you greasy? Bless you.
You want a kebab, do you?
Yeah. I'm going to put my bedding in the
wash, I reckon.
Therefore, that needs to be washed. A bed.
Move that a bit more that way. Perfect.
Yeah. One second.
So, what you I don't reckon you're going
to last more than a couple of days. You
you silly sausage.
Hello, M. I'm going to do my bed now. I
don't mind putting some money in the lei
if you want.
All right. I put some Huh.
>> I have money. M.
Okay. Cuz I need to put the I need to
put the bed in the wash.
All right, Mom.
You're that cute.
I'm just putting my bed in the washing machine.
You want to know how I do it?
No, she's all right. She's a bit tired. Right.
Right. This is how I do my washing.
So, I boiled a kettle.
Well, I filled a kettle.
Okay. And then we boil the cow. And we wait.
You You wait.
Yes. Until it's until it's been boiled.
Got my little bed.
I got a couple of flat sheets.
So, you do this,
right? Show you what you do. How I do
it. I always use two bombs with my bed. Right. So,
you stick a bomb in. Oh. Ah.
All right. One bomb.
And then I do it a special way.
Want to put on a 20 because I'm boiling the turtle.
I've already had a shower.
I get another bomb.
I lost my picker
in the shower. Oh,
and now we Right.
No, I was doing something. Hold on a
minute. What do you mean froze? My phone
don't bloody freeze. It's a flagship.
>> Well, that just went on my beard. That
did. So what you do Greavvesy is one second.
This is how you dissolve a bomb.
See? And then you dissolve it. Lovely.
The smell is lovely.
Why Dusty, are you still there?
You still there, Duster?
Da, these people on Reddit say that I
should shine up to like a hobby class.
What do you think? H
They should they should join up to like
a hobby and meet people that way. Dusty,
what's your unbiased opinion on that? Huh?
That's what this person said. I'm ready.
They said sign up to like sign up to
like a hobby class,
something that you're interested in to
to meet women, dusty.
No. What? No. What? You're just being negative.
No, you're just being
>> Oh, mama, you ate the cheese. You see the kiss?
>> You're just being negative.
>> I think you're just No. So, what's going
to happen if I join up to like groups
and stuff and try and speak to people? Huh?
What do you think?
If I try to like Don't do that again.
So, if I try to if I sign up to like a group.
Yeah. But people on What do you think,
D? What do you think, Grezy?
Join like a group like a hobby. A hobby
group. That's what Reddit people on
Reddit told me to do. Huh?
That's what people on Reddit told me to do.
Just finish doing my washing. Really greasy.
What do you reckon will happen though?
This woman on Reddit say try like
hobbies and stuff.
Do they dismiss my struggles?
Do you remember when you told Lexi to
stop dismissing my struggles?
You don't like that Lexi, do you? He's
an oable, horrible [ __ ] in it.
He's an honorable, horrible old [ __ ] Horrible. Horrible.
Why don't you like Lex?
Why? Sorry. Why don't you like Lex?
H is it because he dismisses people's struggles?
Yeah, but did they dismiss my struggles,
do you reckon?
>> I'm sick of this [ __ ] phone going off
every [ __ ] 10 seconds, man. I need to
change the settings again on it.
to keep changing the time out. It keeps
timing out every 10 seconds.
Every [ __ ] 10 uh every third every 30
seconds it times out. Greavves.
Did you Who did you think was going to
win? Me or Lex?
Did you Did you actually think he was
going to beat me? Music.
Yeah, the mods keep banning me. That's
the They keep banning me.
Oh, this smells This room smells lovely.
Greasy. The washing smells lovely. Oh gosh. Really?
>> Oh, why is this phone not charging? This
charger is [ __ ]
This [ __ ] charger.
Oh, this charger is so annoying, bro.
There you go. I think I just saved it. Would
you want to be a Reddit mate? I But do
you know these Reddit moderators? Yeah,
they do do it for power. They do do it
for power. Do you know why, Grezy?
Because they don't get paid for it. Why
would someone want to sit on a site all
day and mod and not get paid for it? It
just doesn't make sense. So, it is
definitely a power thing.
They want they need to feel in control.
Joe said, "Yeah, Joseph Farer said that
anyone that has to
have power for something like has to do
something that gives them power is sad.
Any kind of site like that where they
have to be in control and that is sad.
Would you agree?"
I didn't know they didn't get paid for
it. I used to think they get they got paid.
Yeah. It's definitely definitely
people that have got no life because
if they don't get paid for it then what the [ __ ]
Why would they mod if they don't get
paid for it then
what the [ __ ] bro?
That doesn't make no sense. Joseph Ferrar.
Joseph Fra is a bit biased though, isn't he, Dusty?
He's a bit biased.
I think he's a Do you know what I think
he is, Greavvesy? I think he's an undercover hater.
You might laugh at that, bro. You might
laugh at that word. Yeah, but I
generally think he's an undercover hater. Yeah,
I think he's an undercover hater. I
don't know. I get that vibe. I don't
know. I don't know.
What do you think, Dusty? About Joseph Ferrar.
I think he's an undercover hater. You're
not wearing your boots back, mama. I
bought them for you. They cost me £165
and you return them back to me. You
should bloody appreciate it. Ma ma,
what are you doing? M
you didn't take your back. just get. Mama. Hello, mama.
Yeah, I reckon Joseph Ro is an
undercover hater, lads.
What do you think, Grezy?
I think he's an undercover hater. Oh, mama.
>> yeah, Monty shouldn't have [ __ ]
money shouldn't have started on me and I
wouldn't have done a video to him
[ __ ] trying to He thinks being
without Natalie G is is something to brag about. Yeah,
which kind of points? I'm not say I'm
not disagreeing with his points. I'm
saying that he's biased.
No, no, no, no. But I'm not uh I'm not
disagreeing. What points did you agree with?
I'm saying that he's biased.
I never said his points are wrong. I'm
saying that he's biased. That's what I'm saying.
With the non legs thing, um the bouncer
at work. I explained it all in the video.
He is biased. He is biased.
Uh he is biased, lad.
Oh, and you don't think he's biased with
the nonsle thing. So, when I'm calling
him a virgin and he's coming on my live
stream a million times saying, "Oh, how
can he be a virgin? He's got a
girlfriend." But yet when people are
going at me, he's nowhere to be seen.
But you you don't think that's a bit biased?
What do you think, India go? Do you
think that's a bit that is biased? It is
biased because I'm sat here responding
to nonsleg saying that he's a virgin.
He's coming up my ass saying, "Oh, well,
he's got a girlfriend. He got a
girlfriend." A good six, seven times,
but when people are going at me, he's
nowhere to be seen.
So, he's being biased. Yes, he does
watch him. He comments on some of his
things. So, I'm thinking, hold on. So,
he can't be a virgin because he's got a
girlfriend, but I'm a virgin even though
I pull up a porno that got his channel banned.
So, and he's biased with the whole uh
bouncer thing as well because it like
that bus story I told when a person was
working on the bus and and he was having
a go at me, everyone call me a [ __ ]
Now, if you can't hit people that that
are at work, that would not make me a
[ __ ] That would make him a coward. So,
it is all biasness, which is why I say
he's an undercover hater. He is biased.
because if that bouncer whooped my ass,
no one would have a problem.
Um, and LT had a problem cuz the guy was
black. So, yeah, they're biased. He's
biased, but because the guy's black. So, um,
yeah, they are biased, bro. So, yeah, he
does watch him. He comments on some of
his stuff. He's not blocked by him,
though. That's the thing. He's not If it
was blocked by him, it'd be different.
But he's not blocked. So you don't think
somebody can be a virgin that's got a
girlfriend, but you think somebody can
be a virgin that's proved they've had
one night stands that's put a porno up.
So it is biaslessness. So why do I want
someone biased on my channel? And then
he's biased with the law J thing saying
about how other people call. We're not
talking about other people called. We're
talking about you being biased. You are
biased. Yeah. Why are you talking about
two or three people when we're talking
about you? So he's not very smart. He
might make good points, but he's not
very smart. He a He ain't smart at all.
And he also spelled a load of things
wrong as well. But then he talks about
my punctuation. Okay.
I don't get it, bro. biased. Yeah.
Yeah, he is biased.
Cuz you don't say anything, Greavves. I
would say that you're unbiased.
I think that you agree on things you
agree on and you disagree with things
that you disagree on. You're not biased and
Yeah, Stephen. Yeah. Yeah. Like I don't
think you are. No.
But yeah, they're biased, bro. They are biased.
Why is he sticking up for a nons? But
then they say they don't I don't get it. It's weird.
And they don't even like him. It's so weird.
I don't know why they I don't know why
they do it. But yeah, they do. They are biased.
Shag is biased as well.
I don't know why. I don't know why they
do it, bro. Really don't >> weird.
And then he says, "Oh, they're not je
they're jealous of your life.
We're no one jealous of your life, but
then it's what they do on here that
makes me think they're jealous."
So, yeah. It's like my mom said, "If
they got all this money, why are they on here?"
And then she's like, "Oh, you're on
here, but I'm on here because I'm not
going out and I just can't be bothered
to do anything." So, I mean, I'm not
going on it. Like, I've done my [ __ ] and that.
Anyways, [ __ ] them, bro.
thing is grievy this women thing
shouldn't affect you. Yeah, but it's
hard not to let it affect you sometimes
if that makes sense.
It's hard not it's hard with somebody
with my history to not let it affect you.
But it shouldn't. It's never going to
change. It is never going to change. It
shouldn't affect you, but it does
because of my history and [ __ ]
It shouldn't affect you, but it does.
Sometimes it can't be helped every two
months or something. It does. It is bad, bro.
It ain't like you ain't tried. It's not
like you've not done mad amounts of [ __ ]
Yeah. Affected. Effected.
Cuz all of the advice that they give
people, they're not me. So, uh,
100 p.m., bro,
that Jamie Thompson is definitely disabled, bro.
That Jamie Thompson is defo disabled.
this guy I met from Red and he added me
on Facebook, man. The one from a month
ago. Yeah, he's a cool guy.
He's a cool guy, bro.
see there's normal nice men out there. I
meet these I see these men. I don't know
what these women are on about. I meet
nice men all the time. That would be
good to them.
Grieves you. I just don't I just don't
understand how these women can't find good men.
I just don't understand. I don't
understand it, Grezy. I really
just don't I don't understand them.
I really don't understand how they can
sit there and say all men are the same.
I really really don't.
I really really really don't, you know.
I think, like I said to you earlier,
Grizzy, I think they pick three or four
bad men and then generalize all men.
That's what I think. I think they pick
like three men maybe and then they
generalize all of them.
It doesn't matter why I consider myself
as bro and [ __ ] talking about me. What
do you think? Cuz cuz Greavves, right,
they've got so many options
that surely one out of a 100 m men would
be normal. No, there's a woman Grezy
Antman showed me this article. You
wasn't on it earlier. There's a woman
with a man on death row
with a man on death row. One sec.
Uh, let me put the link up. She's dating
a man on death row, bro. She She's
actually met him in prison. She She She
met him whilst he was in prison. Yeah.
Not together. And he killed like an elderly woman.
Does that not tell you about women, bro?
They're all the same, bro.
That's not Does that not tell you?
One second. I'm trying to put this link
up. Why is it not letting me? One second, please.
Oh, here we go. Sir, Yeah. So,
but then they say they want a nice guy,
but then they go for them greasy.
People that are on death row.
I might do a video. Yeah. Saying I might
do a video titled All Men Are the Same
and explain how their logic is so [ __ ]
I I don't believe them, bro. I generally
generally don't I don't believe them.
I don't believe that these women can't
find good men. I'm sorry. I don't believe it.
I really I just can't believe it because
of like, you know,
because of how many women I can go by by
my experiences with how many people I've approached.
So it doesn't um Noah,
I don't believe they can't find good men.
It banning people again, Grezy.
I think they get some kind of hard on
when they ban people. [ __ ] nerds.
Yeah. No other site does it. No other
site bans for no reason. No Instagram,
no Facebook, no YouTube. No site bans like Reddit.
That's why that's how you know it's a
power thing with them because no other
site does it.
No other site like YouTube. You can
basically do what you want.
That's why I like YouTube. I like
YouTube. I like Facebook. If you say
something mad, then Instagram will ban
you for like seven days. But with
Reddit, if you disagree with anything
they say, they'll just ban you. They'll
delete they'll delete your account and
they'll they'll ban they'll flag your um device.
Does that sound like a power thing to
you, Greavvesy? It sounds like a power
thing to me.
It sounds like they get off on the power
of banning people.
It seems that way, bro, cuz no other
site bans people then they definitely
don't IP ban them.
Do you understand, bro?
I don't know. I think it is a power
thing with Reddit.
Yeah, but they didn't IP ban me.
Yeah, but they didn't IP ban me and they
didn't and they didn't shut my account
down. But I can come on here every day
talking about women, talking about
double standards and I will never get banned.
I mean, that's different. That's a
that's that's you showing your dick
getting sucked. It's a bit different.
Reddit will ban you if you say anything
bad about women and they will literally like
uh they will say, "Oh, you're suffering
from a victim mentality." an icon will
pop up saying you're suffering from a
victim mentality. I think it's just a
site designed to annoy people
by people that have just been bullied
their whole life. It kind of reminds me
of this a little bit to be honest. I
think it's just a site Yeah. designed to annoy you
because of the like
the IP B. I don't know. No other site
does it. No other site bans for silly reasons.
Never in my life have I known it.
And they ban you. They they they
actually ban your they flag your device
so it flags up every time you make an account.
I think it's a power thing, Dusty.
Yeah, they dismiss them. They dismiss them. Yeah.
No one ever No one ever is is is is
thrown back by Greavvesy. Oh [ __ ]
that's [ __ ] up. That's what I want
people to to to be like, "Oh, that is
mad." I don't want anyone to like
feel sorry for me and [ __ ]
Yeah, but I just want to But no one's
ever like, "Oh [ __ ] that's [ __ ] up.
What the fuck?" Even though I show them
videos on my other channel, they don't
really seem bothered by it. They just
dismiss it. Yeah.
Yeah, they do. I think they're just
simps that I think they're virgins, you
know, them Reddit moderators. I
definitely think they're virgins. I
actually think they are virgins, bro. 100%. Yeah.
And they try to ban people without
telling people as well. Uh
my friend said he doesn't use it because
they ban people for no reason. Greasy,
he says that like he says that uh he
doesn't use it because they downvote and ban.
That's why he says he doesn't go on Reddit. >> Yeah.
I like sh.
I like show.
Think think the thing is uh Dusty they
say that having a partner in life is a bonus
but you literally would have to approach
every single day for like a month to find someone
but they say that you know finding
someone is a bonus but you won't find
someone unless you make it your life to
find someone unless you literally made
it your life to find someone. You won't
find someone whether it's short-term or
long-term. But they say in life, Grezy,
that it's supposed to be
it's supposed to be a bonus. Having
having a relationship is supposed to be
a bonus, but you will never find someone
unless you made it your whole life. You
your life would literally have to be
dedicated to finding someone, otherwise
you would never find someone. And even
then, you still might not. [ __ ] Yeah.
Yeah. But you're not going to find someone. though
unless you made it your whole life.
You're not going to find someone in this
country though. That's the thing.
Unless you approached every day for like a month.
But even then, I don't think you'd be able to
deal with it to be honest. So yeah. So yeah,
and obviously if people work dusty,
where are they going to find the time for dating?
Where are they going to find the Where
are they going to find the time for
dating? If they're working,
you're not going to find the time. You
need to make it your whole life.
What do you think about these women that
say they can't find normal guys with
you? I think they're full of [ __ ]
Of course, they can find normal men.
They just don't want normal men.
Oh, yeah. You meet people through work,
so they say. Well, I won't be meeting
anyone through work. I did actually make
some friends when I was when I was doing
Uber. I actually made a couple of
friends and they were nice people as
well because most of them were from
third world countries so they were they
were no [ __ ]
Yeah, I met a Turkish guy. Yeah, they
and they were nice people cuz like I
said they weren't uh they were from
third world countries so there was no
attitude problem or anything with them.
Yeah, but but it doesn't mean they're
going to be interested.
But Grezy, no. But no, no, no. But
Grezy, the thing is No, no, listen. The
thing is, I'm saying this because I have
I have been trying for years and I have
never met a a woman that's different.
So, I have met 500 times more women than
they have met men. My my my
uh generalization is warranted. Theirs
is not because there is no way that they
can't find a genuine guy with the amount
of options they have. Even if they had
to weed out 100 people,
um, you know, one in a 100 men have got
to be different.
So, I'm not buying it. And with the
amount of options that they have,
there's no way there's not one man that's decent.
There's no way in hell. And I'm saying
it because I've been all over the
country. So, their experience is not like mine.
Their experiences is not like mine
because I've met thousands and thousands
and thousands of women. So at the end of the day,
I've met thousands and thousands and
thousands of women. They've not met
thousands and thousands and thousands
and thousands of men. So they can't even
relate. And the thing is, the thing is,
right, and what I say again, what I'm
saying as well, Grevy, is I have met
women that have said to me, "Oh, you're
sweet. Thanks for coming up to me." But
they're not interested. So which
contradicts the whole thing of they
can't find men. And even though uh that
you know some of them might generally
have not been looking there's there's no
way not some of them wouldn't have went
and complained about men. So they have
men that are different coming up to them
and they're still not interested but
they're moaning about men. I've never
been shown a good woman in my life. So
in that case, the the I it's uh the
generalization is warranted
in my case, and I doubt it is in their case.
And it's not about men. I don't need to
defend men. I don't give a [ __ ] about
men. I'm saying that if if if they if
someone has no options and they've got
loads and loads of options,
there's got to be three and 300 men that
are different. There's got to be. if
they re weeded out all of them people.
So there's no way. There is no way. Even
if they have to go through 300 creeps,
there's a man out there that's
different, bro. There is a man out there
that's different. I've approached people
and I've been different. So what what
was the excuse then? What was the excuse
then? So it's and obviously I can use
myself as as an example because I've
gone out talking to people. So,
um I'm not buying it. They go and and
the thing is they haven't met many men.
They've been with about three or four
men that they've chosen to go with.
So, I don't believe them when they moan
about men. I don't believe they can't
find someone. I don't believe they can't
I really can't believe that they can't find someone.
The thing is right uh Grezy they they
put it like this right as a man trying
to find a woman is like water
is trying to find water in the desert
and trying to and a woman trying to find
a man is trying to find clean water in a
swamp. So you that's what they say
but they're eventually going to find
clean water. That's the analogy that they use.
I don't believe that they can't find a
nice man. I can't believe I can't believe it.
Cuz then you'd be getting dates all the
time. Something is not ringing right
with what they're saying, bro. I'm
telling you, it can't be.
And then they say that they don't know
what these men are like.
You're with him. You're dating a man on
death row. You got with him whilst he
was in prison.
You got with him? Um,
you got with him while she was in prison
and he murdered an older lady.
Yeah, that actually happened. I can show
the article if I want. So, they know
what these men are like before getting with them. Uh, so yeah.
Well, have they have they Okay. Have
they met Have they met Have they met
Have they met thousands of men?
Have they met thousands of men? No, they haven't.
So, what? I don't believe them, bro.
There's no way they can't They can't
find a man that's normal. They don't
want a man that's normal.
The moment it goes tits up. So
I don't believe it.
I have I've had sex. I've had sex. I've
been on dates with people. I've had
chances of being in relationships.
But not recently. No.
Not recently. I have had but not
No, I haven't. So, yeah.
So these women,
it is sex is something. Yes, it is.
I like [ __ ]
Which I'll probably never get a [ __ ]
ever again in my life because even if he
was to get sex again, you probably never
they might not even give you a [ __ ]
I think them days are done. Dates and
getting sex, I don't think it'll ever happen again.
So, best get used to it. Lucky we're not
three years younger.
It is for me. I used to like getting a I
used to like this person coming around
giving me a [ __ ] I never had sex
though. I didn't have sex. I didn't have
sex after like the second time. So
what? You don't care about sex, Dusty?
See, there's this guy in America. Have
you seen the Oreo man? He doesn't help
himself, though, because he could have
easily got an escort. He's 36. He could
have easily got an escort. His videos
are right about what he's saying about
women and stuff, but he could have helped himself,
you know? I'm like 10 years, he's
[ __ ] senior and I've done a lot more
than him. He could have helped himself,
bro. He could have helped himself
more. He could have helped himself a lot
But I don't know why he still hasn't got
an escort to lose his V card,
his Valentine's card.
He's [ __ ] He's Valentine's card.
He's When are you going to lose your Valentine's card?
When are you going to [ __ ] lose your Valentine's card?
And it's the lie and the dishonesty from
these women as well, Dusty. I even had a
friend that lied to me. And you're and
you're thinking to yourself, who do
these people think they're lying to?
Bro, you're not born yesterday.
now. Who do you think you're [ __ ]
lying to, bro?
Do you reckon that Ricky Milling will
ever meet me for a uh for a beer?
These people are [ __ ] Yeah. [Music]
Do you reckon if I never approached I'd
be a virgin without escorts? Dusty
like or do you reckon I would have met someone naturally?
Yeah. Not from tomorrow. I won't be.
Bro, you know that's cap.
What? Why? Why? What? What do you mean?
Of course. How do you know? Maybe I
might have met someone through my sister
or something. Bro, but you know that's cap.
You know if I you know if I don't you
know if I didn't come on here
you know if I you know if I don't come
on here for a week, you're going to be
on here every day. So what's the point
of saying that, bro?
What's the point of even saying that?
Because you know if I come off of
YouTube for a week.
Yeah. Yeah, but I' I've been going for
it since April and I haven't got a date,
Dusty. I haven't had a date since April.
They all keep saying they've got
boyfriends and giving me attitude.
No, it definitely is impossible to find
someone. The fact that I haven't had a
date since April,
you're not just going to go out and it's
going to change. I've already changed my approach.
It's not going to change the fact that
they're stuck up with unrealistic standards.
This is what these people don't
understand before going to Thailand that
the problem is not you. The problem is them.
I've used I've used different I've used
different approaches. It's not about the
approach. It's them. They're not
interested. All these people before they
go to Thailand, they question themselves
for years. Ant-Man does it. Um Antman's
friend does it. Other people, they
question themselves. They're changing
this. They're changing that. They're
changing this. They're changing that.
They don't know what's wrong. Let me get
this haircut. Let me get that haircut.
They'll change they change their
approach. They do this. They do that.
Nothing works. And then in the end, they
just go Thailand and then all the problems end.
So, it definitely is them, bro. It It's
not about your approach, whether you're
nervous, whether you're confident.
You can get girlfriends in Thailand.
Even ones that are not after your money.
You can you can get girlfriends in
Thailand. Yes, you can. Plenty of them
want money, but they do. You can get
girlfriends. So, it's not about the
approach because it's the women that are
the problem with their unrealistic
standards. So, you can No, you don't.
No, you don't. Not all the Not all the
women you do. No, you don't. No, you
don't. There's You can go on Tinder on
Thailand in Thailand and the woman just
come straight to you without you paying
a penny. Trust me, I know.
And man showed me his Tinder.
A lot of them you got to pay. Yeah. But
if you go on Tinder and if you go
Philippines, they're people that want relationships.
Yeah. Well, guess what? Anyone that
wants to deal with these westernized
women have got no respect for
themselves. And guess what? Anyone
anyone that deals with women in this
country have got no respect for themsel
dealing with their [ __ ] and their
lies and their toxicity. That's people
that have got no respect for themselves.
So, you're either desperate or you've
got absolutely no respect or dignity for
yourself. So, you pick which one.
So, trust me, I know I approached 50
women about a month ago. I know exactly
what they're like. And even though I
done it for a laugh, I was like, "Oh
shit." Is this what you got to go
through? This attitude, this [ __ ]
with these women, you know? So, I'd
rather be a desperado, bro, than never
have to deal with that ever again. And
the lies and the [ __ ] It's not even
about it. It's things over text as well
they do. The attitude. You got to be
really desperate to want to put yourself
through that [ __ ] mate.
So, yeah, you can do different
approaches, Dusty. It's not going to
make a difference whether you talk
normally, a pickup line, they're not
interested in this country. Simple as that.
cuz they've got unrealistic standards.
I mean, when you're seeing Tik Tockers
that have got loads of followers, loads
of money getting rejected, you just know
there's no hope. You just know there's
no hope. And the fact that you don't
even get dates now as well. Like if you
got dates every two weeks
or like kisses, then they'll be like,
"Okay, yeah, the stove's warming up
here. The stove's warming up." But I
think pretty much the fact that you've
not had a date since April, there is no
hope here. There's not even like minor
successes now. So the the chances that
the next time you go out is suddenly
going to be different. No chance. See,
back like 2 years ago, April, you'd be
getting dates. Dates just normal. You'd
be getting dates like how you should
should be getting dates. Now you can't
even get that. You go through 600 pound
over a weekend and get nothing.
and then you'd want to gamble and then
the whole toxic [ __ ] starts again.
That's that's what happens. So,
it is them and their unrealistic
standards. Definitely, it is 100% it is them.
There is no chance. There is no chance
in this country.
That's why after I got the 10 numbers
and I didn't get a date, whatever
happens, I know. Yeah. There there's no
there's no hope here.
There's no hope here. So, anything that
happens now, I'm like, "Yeah, okay,
whatever." Cuz I know there's no hope.
So, it's nothing that surprises me
because you already know there's no
hope. So, if you go out and you try,
it's just just you, you know, you're
doing it to yourself.
No, I won't be on tomorrow. My eyes are
hurting, bro. Staring at the screen all day.
Yeah. And there's a lot of men's
experiences as well. I see men approach
women all the time and they seem to get
the same [ __ ] It annoys me just
watching it. Well, I don't watch it
anymore. I used to watch this guy in
America, a few guys in England, and I
stopped watching it cuz it just it's
just annoying their attitude, the
entitlement. That's why I stopped watching it.
That's why I stopped watching it because
it was just annoying.
But I don't regret getting the 10
numbers like a couple of months ago, not
getting a date because now I know
there's no hope. So, anything that happens Yeah.
It's like, okay, whatever,
which is good on
some of them are, but there's ones on
Instagram that's not, and they say the
same old [ __ ] I'm not interested. I
have a boyfriend. I'm seeing someone.
It's just the same [ __ ] they say.
And it's just boring. I hate watch I
don't even like watching it.
I don't like watching it, bro. It just annoys me,
even when it's not me. So, I don't watch
them anymore, you know? Yeah. They
So, yeah, that's why I don't watch it anymore. Yeah.
Because when it's happening to more men
that that it's not happening to,
you know, I mean, I don't even know why
why we have this argument, bro.
Yeah. It's like one in a million.
You don't need to do that. You just need
to leave the country.
You just need to leave the country.
That's all you need to do. go to South America, Asia,
or somewhere. That's all you need to do.
Cuz whenever you go out, you should be
getting a date that next week. Doesn't
matter if the date doesn't go anywhere
or not. If you go out and you do
approaches, there's no reason why you're
not getting a date. But you won't get a
Very unlikely, bro. Very unlikely. I
mean, like I said, I haven't had a date since April. So,
you're not going to meet a woman that's suddenly different.
It's not happening, bro. It ain't happening.
See, back after that USA thing, I was
having one night stands, dates, kisses,
fingering. So, I mean, yeah, that's why
I used to go out a lot. But now, you
will never get anything,
which is why I don't ever go out cuz you
don't get anything.
You just go out, spend what a couple
hundred pound and you don't get fuckle. Pointless.
Pointless. Pointless. Pointless. Never changes. So,
you notice as well when you when you
stop dating, your mental health is a lot better.
That's that goes to show you that it's
women because when you when you stop
dating for like 2 weeks, you change as a person.
You're constantly toxic and depressed
when you're trying to date women cuz all
the [ __ ] they put you through, the mind
games, the [ __ ] the attitude.
You're constantly depressed.
But then when you give up, you feel a
lot better after like 2 weeks.
It's down to social media.
And uh I don't want a relationship. If I
was desperate for a relationship, I'd be
approaching every day.
I'm I'm really really not. I'd be
approaching every day. If I was
desperate for a relationship, I would be
approaching every day or at least every
week. I'm really really not
because I could go out and approach. I'm
not scared to go out and approach.
So I don't want a relationship
and I don't even think I want sex
anymore either. So
yeah, because I'm traumatized from my
experiences, bro. What the [ __ ] I'm
traumatized by my bad experiences with women. you know,
they really are evil people. So, that's
why I talk about it cuz I can't I can't
get over how mad it is. If I wanted to
find someone, I would be approaching
every day and trying to find someone.
If I have something in my head, I would
do it. You know, I'm that kind of
person. But I don't do it. I won't do
If I really wanted someone, I'd be
trying to. I don't know if I would find
someone, but I would be trying every
day. But then you realize all women are
the same. They're no good. So then now
I'm saying it. I'm not contradicting
myself. You see,
they're all the same. Women are
literally all the same. So
So yeah, if I wanted to find someone,
I'd be trying every day, bro.
I'm going to be making money soon. Like
I said, if I wanted to put my mind to
something, I would do it.
I mean, I could try every day if I wanted to.
I mean, I could try to meet a woman
every day if I wanted to and maybe find
someone in a month, but I'm not doing
it. So, actually, it's not by choice.
It's by choice that I don't want to deal
with them every day. I don't want to
deal with their [ __ ] So, it is a choice
that there's no there's not even a 1%
chance for me because I don't want to
deal with their [ __ ] So, it kind of is by choice
because I'm choosing to not deal with
them because of how what they're like.
So, therefore, there's no chance because
I'm not dealing with them. Simple. Which
is my choice to not want to deal with
them to even give me a 1% chance or 2% chance. So
the last time I done it when I was bored
uh and I was like how people put up with
this [ __ ] is mad. These women are stuck
up. A lot of them need telling about
themsel. I'm not doing it. I don't need
to. And then that's real life. This is
not Reddit. This is women that we're
talking to in real life. And then they
do and say and act the same.
But then people sit there and say
they're not all the same. I mean are
these people living in the [ __ ] real world?
you know, so it kind of is by choice. If
I was a virgin, I would get laid. If I
was like non-sleg,
um, I would approach every day until I got laid. So,
there's nothing stopping me. Where are
we today? There's nothing stopping me
going out tomorrow and approaching. It's
Wednesday. If I really wanted to, I
could, but I don't want to deal with them. So,
My ego is too big.
So it's not it's not by choice. It's
where my ego is so big,
right? I wouldn't want to disrespect
myself. And I haven't thought and and
the only time I did do it is cuz I was bored.
So, and I don't have the energy. I can't
be [ __ ] bothered to deal with their
[ __ ] I can't be bothered to get led on.
So, I'd rather just hate them instead.
It sounds like the easiest thing. Hate them instead.
Get so many bad experiences where you
don't even have a sex drive anymore. So,
you can only give people the benefit of
the doubt for so long.
And what's so mad about me is the
traveling I've done. Like, you've heard
my mom earlier, the amount of people
that I've approached.
Like, I am in my rights to think the way
that I do. I'm not like a normal woman.
I'm not like a normal man. A normal man
or woman would have met a few people and
be like, "Oh, they're [ __ ] They're
shit." But I am telling you, I've met
more people than 90% of people in the
world, bro. At least that's the way it feels because
of what I was doing for years. So, it's
like how how anyone can try and tell you
different. See, people like this people
like this Oreo man, I don't understand
how he can complain. He's never tried
with women. He's never tried. He never
tried to better himself. So, I don't
understand how people like that can sit
there and explain. I reckon if people
have actually tried like me, they they
can't even be called an incel, bro. I
reckon they they they should be barred
from even being called an incel. See,
people like this Oreo man has never
tried. Never ever tried. He will tell
you he's never tried, but yeah, it
annoys him. So when you look at someone
like me who has actually met so many
different women, bro, you're like barred
from being called an incel, bro. You
can't even [ __ ] call someone like me an incel.
I can understand if you hadn't tried or
you tried a few times and you know
I've met a lot of [ __ ] women, bro. A
lot of [ __ ] women. So when you
compare that woman saying all men are
the same to me, it's just like, bro,
you've probably been with three men that
you picked. You haven't been meeting
men. You haven't been meeting loads and
loads and loads and loads and loads and
loads of men
because you would have found someone.
You would have found someone that's not
that's not a bad person.
Cuz like I said to you before, they say
all men are the same.
But yet they've got options. We say all
women are the same, but we don't have
options. We have to disrespect ourselves
to even get a date. So yeah,
it is sad though that people that have
kids or people that want kids would have
to deal with that every day.
Bad, isn't it? That must be really bad
if you actually wanted kids. You know,
it would that is really bad, bro. Like,
say you actually did want children, you
know, at a young age. Like, what if you
actually wanted kids? Like, no, all
jokes aside now. Yeah, let's talk
serious. What would you do?
Like, you could adopt, but it's not
going to be a biological child. So, what
would you do? Just sit and watch
everyone else have That must be
heartbreaking, bro. If people actually
wanted kids, cuz you know you're never
going to meet anyone.
And um you know, there'd be other people
having kids. Like what you what would
you do, bro?
That's really bad. That is really bad,
bro. Could you imagine?
Yeah, but Oreo man's never tried
anything. He's just been whining for
years and he's never even approached anyone.
It is strange. It is strange.
So yeah, if I wanted to try to get laid,
I could try every day, but
it wouldn't be it wouldn't be worth it.
I'd rather make money and leave. I'd
rather put out time and make money and leave
to be honest.
It's [ __ ] up, bro. Virgin boy,
have you ever been to Red and Dusty?
So, what's the what's the best night out
in England? I reckon it's I reckon it's
Newcastle for me.
But I've been everywhere except from Glasgow, Southampton.
Uh, and Blackpool.
I've only been to Liverpool once.
I can live without sex. I haven't had
sex, bro. I went without sex for ages,
bro. I I was just getting [ __ ] I can
live without sex as long as I got [ __ ]
No, that's in the uh that's in the West
Midlands, isn't it?
I've only been Liverpool once on a Monday.
I'd have to go back.
Yeah. Well, maybe not now.
But I did back then. Maybe I did back
I think I did back then.
I wouldn't have sex at at the church.
I don't know why. I just went there. I
was bored, so I just went to Liverpool.
Yeah, I preferred a [ __ ] over over
sex. For a long time, I didn't have sex
for like a year. I just had a [ __ ]
Yeah, Antman just Antman just reply back.
I might do a video on this.
and man replied.
He said, "Yeah, I know, mate. That is
true. They say they want a down
to-earth, genuine man, a good guy, yet
shoot them all down straight away. So,
what's a good guy supposed to do exactly?"
Yeah, it is the truth. And I can speak
from my experiences when I've approached
people as well. So it's [ __ ] cuz
even if they're genuine and they're
saying about what you're like, they
would be getting with you. Some of these
women would be getting with you, bro.
It is the truth because they would these
women would be getting with you sometimes.
Like that one on Snapchat saying, "Oh,
you're nice. Thanks for coming up to me
and talking to me. You're making an
excuse not to get with me." It doesn't
make sense. If these people generally
want a nice man, they would they would
they would give you a chance.
At least they would at least give you a chance.
So it doesn't make sense when they try
to generalize all men. It doesn't make sense
cuz I'm probably the most down to earth
person at 11 without bigging myself up.
Um, but and then and this is another
thing when you this is another thing
that the they do. When you say that
you're a nice guy, they basically mock
you. There's a whole like meme on it
where they basically mock you. Um,
because women prove that they don't like
nice guys, so they try to erase it by
saying, "Oh, you're a nice guy. Are
you?" They try to mock you in a way to
get out of it. But they don't want
normal nice guys. Definitely definitely
definitely definitely definitely not.
So don't sit there. That's like me me
going for women
that I know is going to cheat on me then
complaining about all women. That's what
they do. That's literally what they do.
Yeah, they do shoot you down straight
away. They don't want a normal down to
earth nor normal person. So I don't know
what's the cap why they talk [ __ ]
I was speaking to this guy today, uh,
Dusty. Uh, he I spoke to him. I met him
10 years ago when I opened my bank
account in Barclays.
He gave me his number when I I think I
was 18. Yeah. I opened my Barclays
account and he messaged me back today
and yeah, he's a cool dude.
Yeah. From 10 years ago, man. He's He's
a cool dude. That's what I'm saying.
Men, there's no way these people can't
find normal men.
There's no way. I've got people that are
friends. Just I know so many down to
earth people, bro. I know so many men
that are down to earth people. I just
don't understand how they can't find anyone.
I can tell you three of the nicest
people, bro, that I know. I know are
good three people. When I went to Wales,
right, I met this guy and he was from
Pakistan, bro. Been here ages. Nice guy,
bro. Wasn't ugly. Wasn't he wasn't ugly,
bro. He's just like a he was like a
handsome looking guy. And I said, "Oh,
can you help me get in?" They're not
letting me in by myself, bro. We was
talking. I met his friends. I still have
to go back to words. I just haven't
They're nice people, bro. There's nice
people out there. There's nice men out
There were nice men out there. So, I
don't know how they sit there and don't uh
Well, I can tell you white men if you
want. I mean, that was just an example.
So, how they say they can't find
normal men, I don't know.
Cuz my mom's like, "Oh, it's it's the
women you're going for." But it's not.
It's every woman that I come across.
Every woman that I seem to come across
from approaching or from all angles,
they all seem to be the same. Mind uh
attitude, pretend they got boyfriends,
say they're not interested, lead you on.
That's all I ever get. It's like opening
a box and then the same thing happening
over and over. It's like opening a
mystery box, but the same thing's coming
out every time.
These women are not just coming across
these the these men.
There's no way. I'm going to do a video about this.
But yeah, there might be a lot of
creeps. They might have to filter out a
lot of creeps. Yeah, maybe. But well,
they do. But
I'm sure somewhere along one of them
million options they've got, there's a
there's a nice guy. So yeah. >> Yeah.
So, it's like there's no point going out
now if if you can't even find something that's normal.
There's this woman from Brazil that I
met, Dusty. I showed her my dick and
then she blocked me and then she
unblocked me and she said, "Oh, just
don't do that again otherwise I block
you." So, why have you unblocked me?
Yeah, I've done it, mate. I've done it
before. I've done these social experiments.
Yeah, I've done these social
experiments. I know how it is. I've done it before.
Yeah, they have more options. But the
thing is, they've got options, but
they're creeps. A lot of these men are
simpy creeps. So, I'll give them that.
They are creeps. They don't have they
don't have genuine options. They have
men messaging them, desperate men that
are not going to stay with them and
whatever. A lot of them. So they're not
genuine options. They're just desperate
men that are probably not even going to
meet them. And if they do, they're not
going to stay with them. So they're not
genuine options. However, however,
um you know, they they obviously can
find someone in the end because they have options.
Yeah. But they're not but they're not
genuine options, though. That's what I'm
trying to say to you. They've got more
options, but they're not genuine
options. They're just desperate simps
that will just creep people out.
However, they've got options. They
still, nonetheless, they've still got
options. So, even if there's three
decent men out of 300 men, they've got options.
Do you understand? Which is what I'm
trying to say to you. Even three out of
300 is good.
So, the men that they have, they're not
genuine options that will stay with them
and [ __ ] So, they're not genuine
options. cuz they're just desperate simps. So,
think about it like that. Um,
she didn't rate it. She just blocked me.
She said, "Don't send it again." She
Yeah, I sent her my dick. I sent her my
dick cuz she was being a [ __ ] So, I'm
thinking, "Okay, why have you unblocked
me?" It's always games with these
narcissistic women. She lives in Brazil,
by the way. So, why have you unblocked me?
It's just [ __ ] behavior, ain't it?
That's why I sent her my dick because
it's just [ __ ] behavior.
Yeah, these women are hypocritical, man.
They pretend they don't like sex and
dicks are gross, but then they have sex with people.
I I've never understood them kind of
people, Leanne. Never understood them
kind of women pretending sex and common
dicks is nasty. But then then they get pregnant.
They weren't South African, they were
South American and it wasn't funny.
That's what narcissists do.
She said, "I'll talk to you later."
Okay. When are you going to talk to me, [ __ ]
They're a South American. Yeah, she was
being a [ __ ] I said, "Stop ignoring me,
otherwise I'm going to I'm going to spam
your [ __ ] page." Cuz I just wanted
her to block me. So, I spam her page and
then she blocked me and got other people
to message me, coward.
There were no good women out there, bro.
No good women out there.
There's no good women out there.
But they can't say there's no good men out there.
They can't say there's no good men out
there, bro. They they they've been
they've been approached by people that
are normal and nice and they're not
interested. So, stop complaining.
That's like me getting chances and then
complaining about women. That don't make
sense. That's like people giving me chances.
That's like women giving me chances and
then complaining about women. That
doesn't make sense.
That doesn't make no sense.
That's like different women that are
average looking trying to get with me,
but then me complaining about women. It
don't make sense.
It was on Instagram and Central London.
When I met, they were in central London.
Women in central London.
Nah, there's no good women out there,
mate. There is no good women out there.
I've been to most cities in England.
I've been approaching for years. Trust
me, there is no good women out there.
That's why I don't bother with them
anymore. I've been giving them the
benefit of the doubt for years. Trust
me, I'm not somebody that's judging
women based on 10 people. I'm not a woman
judging men based on 3xs. I am talking
about thousands of women. Like the
amount of approaches that I have got on
my phone, it's disgusting, mate. I've
got so many. And they all seem to say
and do exactly the same [ __ ] So, I
mean, I don't know how long or how much
longer you're going to keep giving these
people the benefit of the doubt. You've
been approaching for years. They all do
and say and act the same way. So, it's
clear that then there's no good ones out there.
They're all the same.
And I was trying to explain to this
woman as well. She's like, "Oh yeah,
maybe people have boyfriends, but again,
it's not about the boyfriends. It's not
one thing. It's all of what they do.
They're leading on the toxicity, the
attitude. It's not one thing.
So it's like
it's not one thing that they do, bro. Do
you understand? So there are no good
women out there. There is no good woman So,
I've met more women in the world than
any man that's complained. Put it that
way. Facts. I stamped it. So, you know,
I could go out on Saturday and I'd know
exactly what would happen. I could I
could tell you exactly what would
happen. Now, do you think you could say
that if women weren't all the same?
I could tell you exactly from start to
finish what would happen and I could put
money on it and be rich.
Yeah. Yeah. That's how bad it is. So, do
you think that somebody could be so confident
knowing that if they did if women
weren't all the same? I' I'd happily
gamble, I'd go back to gambling.
That's how confident I am.
So unless a woman's been going up and
down the country for years coming across
shitty ass men, don't complain.
Don't complain. Would never happen,
mate. It would never happen. So
I mean, again, when you're saying that
there's good women, bro, you're talking
to someone that's been up and out of the
country for years.
Like you need to remember this when when
people are saying this stuff they're
talking to me. They're not talking to a normal person.
So do you really think that if they were
I would have found someone by now?
Cuz if a woman's been if if a woman went
through exactly what I went through, I'd
be like, "Yep, you can generalize all
men." I'd literally say, "Yeah, they're
all shit." I'd say, "No cap." I'd be
like, "Really?" Yep. They they are all the same.
I would generally generally say that
they're all the same.
I would say, yeah, you can say they're
all the same. But with you people, you
still say that they're not all the same
when I don't know how many more women
you have to [ __ ] I don't know how
many more women you got to [ __ ] meet.
How many more bad experiences you have
to keep having before how many times you
have to keep putting your [ __ ] hand
on the stove before you realize that no,
they are all the same. and then not go
out and then you know it's it's obvious
they have too many they have too many similarities
they have too many similarities for
people that are all the same and men
don't do any of these things which which
I'm comparing them to women so how can
they say that look I spoke to that guy
from Barclays today right and he don't
even remember me and he was he was down
to earth nice guy gave me his number no problems
No problems. I was speaking to him on
Facebook now. Why is it you never have
any of these problems with men?
Do you not find that a bit odd how you
don't have any of these problems with men?
Not saying that women don't have bad
experiences with men. I'm saying that
obviously they [ __ ] do. But I'm
saying and obviously they're going to
come ac across creeps and that. But
we're not saying that. But I'm saying,
do you not think eventually you would
have found someone?
I just don't I don't understand it.
Cuz I can very much do an experiment and
I can tell you I can find a man within a
week. I can tell you that I could find a man
nope, I don't like men. I'm using it as
an example. Nope. I don't like men. I'm
using it as an example because they're
saying that all women aren't the same.
So why is it that you can come across
normal men, no problem, right? But all
of these women, there seems to be
problems, yet all women aren't the same.
Generally wondering why this this is
happening if women aren't all the same.
I'm generally generally wondering why.
I really really would like to know why.
I met some guy from Red and I can easily
go for a beer with him, have a chat,
have a laugh. With women, you can't do
that. They're just [ __ ]
So, it's definitely women. No, it's
definitely when it when it comes to me.
Like, it's definitely women. No. No. So,
I'm not going to do a video on this, I think.
titled to all these women that say that
men are all the same. Yeah.
They have not met enough men to to to generalize.
generalize all men. I have met way more
than enough women to make a a good generalization.
I'm comfortable with generalizing. I am
very comfortable with sticking with to
what I'm saying
because because I've I've given people
the benefit of the doubt for years. Like
I've made it my life. I've basically had
no life doing it. So when someone sits
there and talks to me and says, "Oh,
women aren't all the same." It's like,
"Really, bro? You're you're talking to a
guy like me, mate, in in the 10% minority." So yeah,
we all got the same similarities.
You all have the same They all have the same similarities.
Yeah. But it's not just my experience.
It's very It's a lot of men. It's more
men deal with it than me. So I mean more
men have these experiences than don't. I
mean I'm seeing big Tik Tockers getting
rejected. So it's not I'm not in the
minority dealing with this. More men are
dealing with it than not dealing with
it. So that in itself is a problem. If I
was the only one dealing with it, I'd be
like, "Okay, this is weird." But you
will see that majority, I don't know
about majority, I don't [ __ ] know the
statistics, but there's a lot of men
dealing with this. A lot of men. And if
women generally weren't the problem, why
are more men struggling than not
struggling now trying to date now?
um or people that approach. I mean even
I mean just people that approach anyone
that goes and approaches seems to get
the same [ __ ] So
there's a black guy I follow from
London. He goes to the gym gets the same
[ __ ] Guy in America gets the same [ __ ]
If they weren't getting the same [ __ ]
I'd be like, "Okay, this is a bit dodgy.
Now let me look at look at myself now."
But when you see so many other people
that are getting the same [ __ ] it's
like it's got to be them.
It's got to be them, you know? And
also the men that do get dates, they're
like fat, ugly women as well.
Uh, so yeah, and this guy's a black guy.
So more people will deal with their [ __ ]
then. That's how I know it's them.
That's how you will know that it's them
because you'll see different men. I've
seen it before, right, where
I've approached someone in in in a club,
right, and then they said they have a
boyfriend. And then you'll see other men
approach and I'm thinking, "Oh yeah,
they're going to go for them obviously
cuz cuz uh because obviously I don't
know, they might think they look better
or whatever." They're going to go for
one of these guys, bro. I have seen a
good three men approach women
um three and they get the same old [ __ ]
and they get the same old [ __ ] They
might speak to them for a little bit
longer, but ultimately it's the same
result. So you got to ask yourself, bro,
if the problem is not them, then
why is it that they're doing it to show
other different men? So obviously it is them.
He needs to get laid. You're banned.
Bye-bye. You're getting banned, you
little you little nerd. We're not
letting you up nons legs so you can try
and get the police involved, you sad little bastard.
You're not going to get the police
involved, you little sad [ __ ] You
actually posted as well that you you
tried calling the police on me the other
day. Yeah, you're not coming in, you little nons.
>> Nice try. Trying to get the police involved.
He's trying to get the police involved,
you [ __ ] idiot. I've just I just told
you what he's trying to do. He's a grass
and you're trying to and you're telling
me to let him on knowing damn well he's
trying to get the police involved.
Whether it works or it doesn't work, I
don't want a little grass on my channel. Simple.
Dusty knows the score. He's just trying
to get police involved.
It's B. It's boring, bro. Boring. I
don't like grasses. Of course, he
follows the crowd.
Um, again, I'll repeat myself for the
second time. He's trying to get the
police involved. For [ __ ] sake,
he is trying to get the police involved.
He's a little police boy.
Do you know what? I'm actually going to
screenshot some of this
what he's doing. I screenshot the other day. Actually,
I'm going to screenshot some of this. I
screenshotted something the other day as
well. He's going to be [ __ ] if this
ever goes to court, which he definitely won't loser.
Yeah, he follows the crowd. Dusty. Yeah,
he he says then he tries saying he
didn't say the chevel thing. He did say
the she call thing.
He's a little copycat. Yeah, he's not
coming in. He's a little informant.
Yeah, he's a little police boy.
Oh, yeah. He's a police boy. He's a
little police boy. Otherwise, I would
let them in if they weren't a police
boy. He's trying to get me to argue with
him so he can get the police involved.
He's a loser. He's a sad, jealous little
virgin loser who needs to get laid and
lose that Valentine's card.
Lose that Valentine's. God, you're
[ __ ] running out of time. When are
you going to [ __ ] pop it? Jesus
Christ. If I was a virgin like you, I'd
be [ __ ] approaching every day. Know
what I'm saying? I'd love to let this
[ __ ] up, man, but I can't. Sorry, bro.
Cuz he's he's a little police boy.
He's a little police boy.
So, I'm basically [ __ ] basically, bro,
with this whole women thing.
Every time he types, I'm going to
screenshot it as well.
Then he tried saying that he didn't say
if you don't like Chev Cole, you're gay.
Yeah, he did. Of course he said that. He
did. He did say that. Now he's trying to
Now he's trying to reverse it now,
Dusty, because he knows he's been caught
being a a copycat.
Yeah. Last time. Yeah.
Yeah. About a week or two weeks ago.
Yeah. Yeah. He because he knew he got
caught being a copycat,
but now he's trying to change what he
said. Uh, Dusty
cuz he knows he's a little copycat.
Yeah, I know, bro. I've got I've got
[ __ ] I've got Yeah, bro. I've got uh
I've got everything he's done anyways,
mate. I've got pages pages full.
I'm not calling the police on him.
I'm not calling the police on him. I
don't call the police.
He's a loser, bro. He's a [ __ ] loser.
He's an absolute loser, man. Calling the
police cuz he's getting owned on
YouTube. He's such a jealous, obsessed
[ __ ] And you don't understand, Dusty,
right? To be doing this police stuff, it
it's a form of obsession because you
know how much effort it takes to call
the police. I tell you what, bro. Yeah.
When I got out of the court, they
suggest they said to me, "Oh, like you
need to call the police. You need to
call the like you need to call the
police to help your case." Bro, I done
it about three times and I was like,
"Fuck this. I'm not doing it again cuz
they told me that I had to do that and
he is literally on here every day trying
to get me done. He's a jealous little
[ __ ] I think he's jealous because my
mommy didn't starve me.
I think he's he's a jealous little [ __ ]
cuz my mommy didn't starve me and he's
still he still ain't lost his
Valentine's card. That's what I think, bro.
I think it's cuz he's still a virgin.
That's why he's bitter.
Yeah, he did.
Anyways, get banned,
[ __ ] virgin. Get lied. Lose that
Valentine's card. You don't want to die
a virgin. Don't die that virgin. You're
better than that, virgin boy. Yeah. So,
I done it about two or three times. Then
I was like, "Fuck this. I'm not doing this again."
to basically cover my back. So, the fact
that he's doing this,
okay, if you say, okay, you right, if
you if you're saying about [ __ ] the
police, contact me on WhatsApp right now.
Contact me on WhatsApp right now and
I'll let you in. If you want to say [ __ ]
the police, you contact me on WhatsApp
right now and then we'll know that
you're not called and let and really
void that order if you want if you want
to come in.
That would [ __ ] the whole thing up,
right? That will [ __ ] the whole thing
up. So you you're saying right now about
forget the police. Okay. Why don't you
why don't you message me on WhatsApp right now? Then
we know that you're not going to call
the police. That's a way to get dusty.
Cuz when someone contacts you, it voids the order.
It voids the order.
You see, it's like a restraining order.
If you've got a restraining order on
someone and you contact them, the the
order becomes void. Ah,
yeah. The posters were lovely, weren't they?
They were absolutely marvelous. I hand
posted them as well. So, yeah, if you
message me via WhatsApp,
of course, I've got a smart hat on, bro.
I know exactly
what I'm doing. So, if you message me on
WhatsApp and you try to call the police,
I will show them where where where
you've messaged me. Basically, I can't
call the police for you messaging me,
but if the police come and I show them,
you're [ __ ] Your whole case is
[ __ ] So, if you really saying [ __ ]
the police, message me on WhatsApp.
That's the most encrypted thing
uh that you you can do.
Message me on WhatsApp right now
and send me just send me a voice note.
Send me a voice note just saying, "Oh,
hi, it's me." So you can't get out of
it. You know
Peter B is very smart in he
Why are you going to lose your V card? One second.
One second, bro.
One second, lad.
talk [ __ ] on Reddit, man. They say that
you meet people through friends, Dusty.
I've never met anyone through friends.
I have never met anyone through friends,
bro. I used to hang out with a load of
army lads. I'm not saying that people
don't meet people through friends.
Obviously people do, but you know it
doesn't happen for everyone.
I've had loads of friends.
I've had loads of friends, bro. And I've
never met anyone through friends.
Yeah, I do have friends. Of course I've
got friends, you silly goose. Of course
I've got friends, bro.
I do. I do have friends.
And you can get rejected
by women even if you meet them through
friends. Like you don't you do realize
you can still get rejected. No problems.
You do realize that. I do have friends, mate.
Well, I don't meet anyone anymore, but I do.
And everyone's out for themselves
because that's just nature, isn't it,
Dusty? That people are just selfish and
they're out for themselves. Like even
your whole family.
Even your whole family, bro. Like even
your family, right? I'm not saying my
family. Anyone's family could [ __ ] you
over at any time.
Yeah. It's not going to work. Like I
said, if you want to message me on
WhatsApp, I'll let you on.
Uh even your family could [ __ ] you over
at any time. Anyone watching this, even
your family could snake you? So, you
really think a heterosexual man is gonna
set you up with a woman?
Nah, you'll be waiting till you're
[ __ ] dead, mate. I'm not saying
people haven't met anyone through
friends. Obviously, I'm not saying that.
I'm not saying that. People obviously
people have, but I'm saying for a lot of
people, it's not the case.
And then they say, "Oh, you got bad
friends." And then, yeah, it's not going to work.
Like I said, message me on WhatsApp.
and then I'll let you in. That's a smart
idea, isn't it, Grezy? Cuz that way you
broke the order, so there's no way you
can get the police involved. There was
no way. So, if you're not willing to
message me on WhatsApp,
then I'll let you up. If you message me
on WhatsApp, I want one message and I
want you saying hi. Then I let you up.
No, I'm not forgetting the police for a
moment. You message me on WhatsApp. You
message me on WhatsApp. One message and
a voice note and I'll let you up
and I'll let you up and I'll let I'll
let you say whatever you want to say. So
if you want to call the police, I'll
show them where you contact me and then
you're [ __ ] and then the whole thing's
[ __ ] But I can't call the police with
you just messaging me. You don't have
the order. I've got the order. You
don't. The order is not on you. The
order's on me. But it will void the order.
So yeah, I've got your number on my phone actually.
>> Oh, I'm blocked. Are you blocked? One second.
>> Yeah, if he really he would have no
problem break uh voiding the order. If
that's the case, Peter Bell is too smart
for you. Believe me, mate. Yeah,
he he he needs to get laid. He needs to
lose his Valentine's card. He's gonna
die of virgin. He's gonna die of virgin,
dusty. He's going to die of virgin. He's
fighting one soon. He's still a big virgin.
He's still a massive virgin.
Massive massive. Cuz I would like to I I
want him to be in here so I could ask
him why he said Sher Cole was attractive
to fit in with the crowd. I would like
to know why he's why he's a copycat.
I would love to know why copy the crowd.
You know, Dusty, it doesn't make you
look good. It makes you look like
someone that has to copy. You know, no
one likes a copycat.
Look what I ate today. KFC. Then he's
trying to say that he didn't call me
gay. You did call me gay.
You literally said that I was gay if I
don't find her attractive. Yes, you did.
You said it to fit in at college. To fit
in with the crowd.
to fit in with the crowd. Oh my god.
No, he doesn't. Well, like I said, if
you message me on WhatsApp,
then you void the order, don't you?
You little police boy.
You little police boy. There's a lot of
police boys on here. Just for age,
what did you say? You've got a week off
work, triple, I'll let him on when he
messages me on WhatsApp. I'll let him on
when he messages me on WhatsApp. What's
so hard about messaging someone on
WhatsApp? You got my number.
And he and he and he's and he's trying
to put news up as well. He needs to get
laid. He's going to die a virgin.
You can get off of YouTube and lose your
Valentine's card. Bro, just message me on WhatsApp.
Greasy, what's so hard about messaging
someone on WhatsApp? If you're not
trying to get the police involved,
message me on WhatsApp.
Message me on WhatsApp.
Message me on WhatsApp. And then I'm
going to I'm going to screenshot it and
I'll keep it in my little evidence pack.
And then I'm going to keep it in my
little evidence pack.
P evidence pack in case I need it.
You'll void the order. That's all you'll
do by messaging me is void the order.
But you won't do it because you're
trying to get the police involved. I
know you better than you know your
virgin self. I know all the things that
you you tried with Tom Woods as well.
You You done the same thing with Tom
Woods as well. You was a little police
boy then. You [ __ ] virgin. I can I
can say it louder now than you, could I?
You [ __ ] virgin.
and my voice is [ __ ] you know, a lot
a lot deeper and stuff. But yeah,
message me via WhatsApp and I'll let you in.
Bro, I've just told you a million times
that the guy's trying to get the police involved.
All he's got to do is message me and I
will let him up.
You know, it's boring. This guy keep
going to the police over and over and
over again cuz he gets owned on YouTube.
So, at the end of the day, if you
message me on WhatsApp, I'll let you in.
What's What's I don't understand. It
takes two seconds.
You know, that way we know he's really
not trying to get the police involved.
Simple. I don't just message me on
WhatsApp and I'll let you up. You know,
you know, mate,
you know, I'm sure you've already, you
know, avoided it, but I want to make
damn sure you, you know, you avoided it.
You know, I want to make damn sure.
And then the whole thing's [ __ ] And
then we know that he's really not trying
to get the police involved.
But why are you not why why are you not
messaging me, mate? you know. No,
no, no, mate. I've just read your
messages and all I can say is No,
no, no. That's all I can No, no, no.
That's all I can say. She all like, "No, no, no, no, no.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no.
no. I'm a coward, says the one that
calls the police. You absolute virgin.
Where's you and your virgin f friend
friend [ __ ] Christian.
You pack of virgins. I want to see the
pack of virgins together. That would be good content.
The two biggest virgins.
the all time virgins. You know
where you and you where's the two
virgins? I used to like you together.
Pack of virgins. Like a pack of bags.
The two virgins.
Yeah. I I I had you I made you stop
going to events though, didn't I, mate?
I made you stop going to your little
events for for a couple of weeks. I done
that. One second. Oops.
I done that. This face did. Hello. Hi.
I done it, mate.
This face went to your area and stopped
you doing stuff
cuz you had to be taught. You had to be
taught a lesson, you naughty boy.
You naughty naughty naughty boy, mate. I
I had to I had to I had to teach you a
lesson. Do you remember the video,
Gregy? When it popped up on the notification,
I said, "This [ __ ] virgin's driving me mad.
You're driving me [ __ ] mad, mate.
This absolute burgeon that's never been
laid is driving me [ __ ] mad.
No, no, no.
I even done one on the train.
Cheryl Cole was attractive. Copycat.
Do you know what I'm going to do? Yeah.
Whenever I see when I find that you're
going to an event again, I'm gonna find
out the event and I'm going to scream
copycat. He's a copycat. Everyone fits
in with the crowd.
Please do that. Please message me. I
want to do that. I'm going to be like
copycat. Would you like that video?
Grezy, you're nothing but a copycat.
That's to fit in with the crowd.
I'm going to I'm going to I'm going to
be like, "You copycat with the Cheryl
Cole thing." You literally did call me
gay. You said if I don't find her
attractive, I'm gay. That's literally
what you said. No, that is literally
what you said. You did say that. You
literally said it not so long ago as
well. You literally did say that. You
said I was gay. You literally said that
You literally said that I was gay
because I don't find her attractive. You
literally did say that. You said it not
so long ago as well. You little copycat.
Yeah. You're going
I have a Okay. Can you Okay. Do a do a
uh video on your channel inviting me and
I'll come there.
I'll come there and I'll be like
everybody. He's a copycat.
He's got no mind of his own. He's got no
[ __ ] mind of his own. You little copycat.
Do you want me to tell more [ __ ]
stories about your [ __ ] father?
He's nothing but a copycat.
Copying the crowd. Remember you you you said
you you you said that if I if I don't
find her attractive, I'm gay. You're a
copycat. Now you're trying to say that
you didn't say that because you've been
caught out for being a copycat.
Yeah. You you caught out for being a
little copycat. You little copycat.
No. Yeah. No, but you said that I was
gay if I if I don't find her attractive.
You might say that. You think I'm gay
because I don't I don't find her attractive.
No, you said if I do not find her
attractive, I am gay. Yes, you did. You
said that you're a homo. Yes, you did.
You said if you don't find her
attractive, you're gay. Yes, you did say
that. You're nothing but a little copycat.
You're a little copycat. Would you like that content?
You're Let me guess. You're waiting for
your next copycat statement. You're a
copycat. You're a copycat.
You got no mind of your own.
I was speaking to Britney about you the other day.
And she was telling me that you're
she was telling me that you earn her cup of tea.
Do you like my little eyes? They're
cute, aren't they?
I might get the bun soon.
But do you like the bun when I have the
little bun? Grezy,
I can't leave Greasy without content.
Poor [ __ ] What's he going to do all
[ __ ] all day?
Who's Britney? Oh, some [ __ ] girl in
Canada that he stalked. I didn't want
him. That didn't want to know.
You was crying over someone that didn't
want to know you.
Dude, you actually made up a story about
me being bullied by something about car name. That was
uh No, no, no. You was No, you went you
went to college and there was two guys,
right, named Ben and Jackie. I remember
exactly their names. And you were saying
that they were bullying you, you know,
because of the way that you was
dressing. And it was a time where I was
having problem with my sister and then
you said that they're like they're
picking on you and then they thought
that you was gay. No, that's what you
did say. That's why there was days you
didn't attend college. That's what their
name was. And then
literally he must have been on the
internet or something. The next day he
was saying, "I like I like
I said, oh yeah, I've heard about that one. Uh
Do you like her? I was like, not
particularly. He's like, you're gay,
homo. Um, and then you literally done
that. Uh, and then you then you dropped
out of college. Um, which I didn't judge
you for being a copycat to be honest
because it is quite scary being new.
It's quite scary being new, you know.
So, I mean, it was the copycat trend
back then, wasn't it? that he
you told me loads and loads of stories.
Loads of stories. Yeah.
Your dad's got a very very dark past.
A very very dark past.
Very very very very dark past.
Yeah. He was a brick layer. He went to
Germany for work. Um
yeah, he was born on the 1st of September.
um kidnapped a kid. You even told me uh
you said that he kidnapped a kid once.
Um now I don't believe that for a fact,
but that's what you told me because he
he'd be [ __ ] in prison if if he done
that. Said that he he kidnapped the kid,
which I'm thinking I don't know why you
were saying that [ __ ] You told me some
weird ass stories.
It was It weren't the first time I met
you. It was It was the second time I met
you. When we went to the Indian Yeah.
When we went to the Indian uh cuisine,
told you about that bindaloo, mate, you know.
Yeah. You said that they were copying
each other, but then you was copying.
Yeah. Cuz they're copycats like you.
Yeah. And they were copying each other like you.
You told me a lot about your dad.
No, we did eat in an in the end and you
literally shack your pants.
No, I'm joking. You had the shits the next day.
I told you, you know, you can't handle
that [ __ ] vinder leg. Yeah. And also Aisha's dad
owned a barber shop and your dad went to
that barber shop. Your your dad actually
met Aisha's dad.
Yep. Gary, his name was
Pakistan. But uh very westernized. It
was very westernized. And you absolutely
did not sleep with her even though your
dad met met her dad. Absolutely did not
do anything with that girl. Absolutely
nothing. Uh, you didn't stick your dick
up her? You you you did you didn't do
anything, mate. You you you didn't do
So, you're saying that?
Oh, you never you never went anywhere
near that girl sexually? I spoke to her.
Mate, your story is not even believable.
I knew then you was an absolute virgin
that you [ __ ] you went to a park and
you started [ __ ] someone on a bench.
You [ __ ] didn't do nothing. You
absolute virgin. Shut up. You absolute
virgin. You didn't [ __ ] anyone on a park
bench. I haven't I haven't even done
that. Jesus Christ. You absolute virgin.
You could have made like a better
[ __ ] story up that you know you went
to a hotel. You didn't [ __ ] anyone on a
park bench. For [ __ ] sake, shut up,
you [ __ ] absolute virgin. Uh, she
asked you for [ __ ] uh £300 for
trainers and you didn't give it. Yeah, I
remember that. You absolutely did not
[ __ ] [ __ ] her. You absolutely went
nowhere near that girl sexually.
Um, you absolutely did not go anywhere near her,
you know. Oh, nice try, mate. I know you
better than you know yourself, virgin boy. You know
you didn't [ __ ] her. You didn't go
anywhere near her, mate.
Tell me what her boobies look like then.
I can tell you what you say Izzy's
boobies look like.
I can tell you exactly what her boobies
look like, but you can't tell me what
hers look like cuz it never happened.
What does her [ __ ] look like? Tell
me. Tell me the color.
Because you didn't [ __ ] her.
You didn't [ __ ] her.
Right. Who thinks that that this guy
[ __ ] some [ __ ] girl on a park bench?
I think he's I think he's a fantasist,
mate. I don't think it happened. It
doesn't even make any sense. You go to a
park bench. No mate.
No. No mate.
No. It never happened.
Tell me what her boobies look like. I
can tell you what USA is boobies look
like. He's got brown nipples.
She's got brown like brown little nipples.
I can tell you. Why can't you tell me?
Cuz it never happened.
It never It never happened. You didn't
go anywhere near that girl.
What do you think? Does anyone believe
this guy has has [ __ ] a girl on a park bench?
One if you believe him. One if you don't
believe him. Two if you believe him.
Just going to wait
till the votes come in.
I reckon he's lying as well. One, we all
think you're lying, mate.
We all think you're an absolute virgin.
No, it's not all. It's not. Look,
it's not me.
They don't believe you. They don't Anyone else? Dusty rage.
They all think you
who who think who thinks he's a virgin.
Press one if you think. Press two if you
don't. Votes to win.
Vote to win.
They look mate, I can't I They all think
you're a virgin, mate.
Look, dip right. Tom Woods.
Look, they think you're an absolute virgin.
Right. Seriously though. Yeah.
Can I ask you why you're scared of likes
and dislikes? So, what I mean by that is
when people dislike your videos, why why
do you uh why do you delete the video?
Or when I comment something, can I get
thumbs up? Why do you delete it? Are you
literally scared of thumbs up? Now, let
me tell you something, right? When I
done that video showing women being
[ __ ] that comment got 25 thumbs up. I
didn't delete it. I'm not scared of
likes and dislikes. I literally don't
care about any of these people on here,
what what they think, if they want to
agree, whether they want to disagree
about me. I didn't you you were
literally scared of dislikes. They're
not fake accounts. This is another
thing. This is your problem. You think
anyone that disagrees with you is fake
accounts. You literally think anyone
that disagrees with you is is is fake
accounts or me. This is what I'm saying.
You're scared of likes and dislikes. You
think anyone that you you f you you're
telling me [ __ ] Ricky Millington is
me? You were saying that Ricky
Middington fellow was me,
you know. No, you're scared of dislikes.
You're scared of dislikes.
You've got a thing about dislikes.
Yeah. He gives me you vibes when I was
arguing with him all day. Yeah. Okay,
mate. You're scared of dislikes. You're
scared of dislikes. And you were saying
that anyone that dislikes the band
playing is disrespectful to the band.
People allow their own opinion, mate. If
they don't like a band playing, they're
not allowed. They They can dislike it if they want.
You're scared of likes. You're scared of
dislikes. What the [ __ ] man? Who the
[ __ ] is scared of dislikes? No,
you're scared of dislikes.
You're scared of dislikes.
Yeah. So, do you still talk to them two um guys in college?
Did you make up
Ben and Jackie? Yeah.
Horrible [ __ ] They were, weren't they?
Horrible [ __ ] You version [ __ ] No.
Do you remember when you said you tried
killing yourself over Britney? Why?
Because you didn't tickle her fancy.
Cuz you cuz you didn't cuz you didn't do
it for her.
You didn't do it for that girl. You know,
you didn't do it for that lady.
Nope. Not over your mother.
No, not over your mother.
No, it wasn't over your mother.
It's cuz Britney didn't want to know.
Didn't want to know you. Didn't want to
know you in life. You know,
do you remember when you went to
Amsterdam? Because I went to Amsterdam.
You are nothing but a copycat.
Yeah, I'm allowed to generalize women.
My generalization is warranted.
Yeah, I generalize. I generalize women.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no,
no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no,
no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
The first place you went to was Amsterdam.
That's the first place you went to,
mate. There's literally
over 200 countries out there. The first
place you went to was Amsterdam.
He's nothing but a little cupcake.
There's so many different cities, so
many different countries.
But the first place that you ended up in was
was Amsterdam because you're a little
copycat. You're a little copycat.
Now, at the end of the day, if I went to
Blackpool, it would be because that's
the one of the only places that I've not
been. Big difference. Your first trip
was was in Amsterdam.
You little copycat.
It doesn't matter if I went with my
girlfriend or I went by myself. You went
cuz I went. You're nothing but a little copycat.
You little copycat.
I want to literally get your cheeks and
be like, "Oh, you little copycat.
You want to fit in?"
You didn't want to feel left out, did you?
I've been to Great Yarmouth.
Yes, I've been to Great Yarmouth.
You're a little copycat. You've never
been to Manchester. You've never been to
Newcastle. You've never been to Cardiff.
Did you want to fit in with a crowd? You know,
you've never been to Cardiff, you've
never been to Newcastle, you've never
been to Manchester, you've never been to
Middlesbrough, you've never been to Scotland.
Should we keep going, mate? Should we keep going?
Should we keep Oh, you have been to Brighton. Yeah.
No. Never been to Manchester. No. No.
No. No. No. No. Never been to Never been
to Milton Kees. Never been to Leeds.
Never been to Sheffield. Even though
your stepdad is from Leeds. David Campbell.
That's your stepdad. Uh, where else?
I've been to so many places, mate.
Would you Would you agree? I've been to
more places than you.
Would you Would you agree? I've
definitely been to more places than you.
You've never been to Cardiff. You've
never been to Scotland.
I've been on an airplane.
Not the nicest experience, but one that
you don't have.
I've I've been to more places than you
know. I've been to the country Wales. I
have been to more places than you know.
You have to admit I've been to more
places than you
think. You've been to more places than you.
I've been to
You've never You've never been to
Bournemouth. You've never been to Bristol.
You've never been to Bristol. I've been
God, I've been to so many places, bro.
It gives me a [ __ ] headache. I've
been to more places than you and I'm
younger than you
and I've been on an airplane.
I've been to Belgium. And you've never
been to Belgium, have you?
No, no, no. Next.
No. No. Have you been to Leeds? Have you
been to Sheffield? Have you been to Cardiff?
You've been to Have you been to
Edinburgh? I've been to Edinburgh.
I remember I went to Liverpool.
I remember I went to Liverpool. But I've
been to more places than you know.
I've been to more cities than you.
You've never been to Scotland. I'm in
I I went to see Scotland. I went
I I went Scotland, mate.
I in Scotland.
Oh, we've been live for almost four
hours. Jesus Christ.
No, I've never been to Scotland, mate.
You've never been to Scotland, have you?
You You can't afford it. You bit skinn
bit tighter money.
I have been to Comry.
Yes, I have been to Commentary.
Yes, I've been to Commentary.
I went there with Timmy. Yes, I have
been to Commentary.
Yeah, yeah, I have, mate. Well, I have.
Well, [ __ ] I have. I got a [ __ ] in
Nottingham and she was from Commentary.
She sucked my Willie. Yes, I have.
You've not been to Leeds. You've not
been to Sheffield.
You've not been to Cardiff. You've not
been on a plane.
You've not been to Scotland.
You ain't been to [ __ ]
You ain't been to So you ain't been to
Newcastle. You ain't been to Middlesbrough.
I've been to way more places than you,
mate. Peter Belly's been about. So I
don't know what you're talking about, mate.
Yes, I have been to Highwickham.
I went to But the first time I went to
Birmingham, I went to meet uh Jack the Ripper.
What do you mean? No, I haven't. I've
been to more places than you have. What
do you mean? No, I haven't. I've been to
more places than you. You skin flint.
You don't go all You go all over the
country. You go all over the country,
but you've not been to Leeds. You've not
been You've never been to Yorkshire.
You've never been to Scotland. You never
been Yorkshire. You never been Scotland.
You never been Cardiff. But you go all
over the country.
No, you don't go all over the country,
mate. You've never been to Scotland. You
never been to You never been to the
Northeast. You've never been nowhere
near the Northeast.
You've never You've never been
Newcastle. You haven't been all over the
country, mate. I've been all over the country.
You've actually never been. You've not
been all over the country. Nope.
Nope. Nope. Nope. Nope. You've never
been Yorkshire. You'd never been Newcastle.
You never been [ __ ] Scotland. Nope. Nope. Nope. Yeah.
You've never you've never you've never
been with women that's got bigger
boobies than the ones I've been with.
I I can tell you that. Yeah.
Sig told you to [ __ ] off.
Sig told you to [ __ ] off, mate. She blocked you,
didn't she? Yeah.
Yeah. Sig blocked you definitely.
Marvel's boobs. No. No, no, no, no.
Yeah, but yeah, but USA Izzies and and
and and Sigs were bigger.
You didn't get to you didn't get to play
with Laura's boobs.
She rejected you.
I I think that's why you were so sad you
was missing the boobs.
I know. I understand now cuz you never
like got to like play with them and stuff.
That's why you were so sad.
You You was missing the boobs. I know.
I've been there before, mate. Been there before.
You do like big boobs.
You do. You do like big boobs, mate.
Yeah, you do. Everyone likes big boobies.
Yeah. Ben and Jack used to [ __ ] bully
that [ __ ] mate. Ben and Jerey. Yeah.
There were two Scottish lads,
Ben and Jackary. They were from
Scotland. I can't remember where in
Scotland. Where in Scotland were they from?
No, I don't like ass.
I I like I like boobies.
I've never I never I've never cared about ass.
Yeah, they Yeah, they're they're Scottish. Yeah.
Yeah. I wonder what happened to them. He
said he doesn't talk to them anymore and
there were two Scottish lads.
Do you remember that Stephen King
that was stalking you?
Do you remember? Do you remember that Stephen King?
He made you [ __ ] your pants. He made you
[ __ ] your knick-knocks on PlayStation.
Remember on PlayStation Stephen King?
Was it Ste? Yeah. See, he said he was
going to go to a college.
He's going to [ __ ] you up.
Yeah. There were two Scottish lads.
Yeah. They used to bully you for being
gay, didn't they? They used to call you gay.
They used to thought you were gay,
didn't they, mate? Yeah.
Do you remember when everyone was
obsessed with that Hannah Aris?
[ __ ] obsessed with Hannah Arish.
Jesus Christ. I'm surprised you weren't
on her. You [ __ ] virgin.
You were like 19 at the time. Hannah Harris.
Surprised you weren't on her, you [ __ ] virgin.
That's when you That's when you got your
own [ __ ] place, was it?
Yeah. Your mom your mom starved you and
you got booted out.
Do you remember? Yeah.
No. How was that? Yeah.
Yeah. I met you. You were still a
virgin. You still You're still a virgin
now. I lost my virginity before you to an escort.
Yeah. You used to make up these mad sex
stories, man. And it was so obvious that
you were a virgin.
Biggest virgin going.
You're the alltime virgin. Like the hall
like the hall of fame, is it? Yeah. You
didn't lose your VC card. Shut up.
Monica never existed. You didn't lose
your Valentine's card.
You didn't You would never lose your
Valentine's card. That's yours truly forever.
Your little Valentine's card.
That's your little Valentine's card.
It's yours to keep forever.
Yeah. You You make up sexies.
You tried it on with USA and she rejected you.
You tried it on with Morgan and she rejected you.
You could have her, mate. You You could have her.
You'll probably be a hundth by now,
mate. 100 time lucky. You're losing your virginity, mate.
You tried You tried hooking up. You
tried hooking up my man, didn't you? [ __ ] virgin.
You're a lifetime virgin, mate.
with Morgan. You want You tried to get
with Morgan. You tried to get with USA. Is he?
You tried to get with her. You fancy
No, it doesn't matter if you got a
girlfriend. You fancy her. You want her
little You want her little punani?
You want her little punani, mate? Yeah,
but she didn't have a boyfriend then. Yeah.
Do you know?
So what if she likes black dick? You
could still lose your V card.
Yeah. Your girlfriend likes black dick as well.
She sucks black dick when you're not
looking, doesn't she?
Doesn't she, mate? Yeah.
She sucks your dick when you when you
suck black dick when you mate [ __ ] madness.
[ __ ] man. I need to go to bed in a minute. No,
she's not with a black guy. She's with a
guy that's got brown skin. I told her
I'd slap her up in front of her
boyfriend. Her [ __ ] friend thinks
she's [ __ ] hard.
I said I'll slap you up in front of your [ __ ] boyfriend. Yeah.
boyfriend. I'll do it in front of any
man. You [ __ ] little [ __ ] I'll slap
you up in front of him, mate.
The guy's got tattoos. Did that guy have
tattoos? No. Hold it in front of your
boyfriend and make you watch
and make you watch. All right, Triple H.
Do you remember what Monty said about Pat's kids?
He said, "I'm going to make you watch." Mad.
Like I said, message me on WhatsApp.
Message me on WhatsApp and I let you in.
What number is your number? Tell me your
number and I'm going to I think Are you unblocked?
No, I won't report you. Won't report
I won't I won't report you. When is your
number ending? I've got two of your numbers blocked.
Nope. I'm not messaging you. You can message me.
You can message me, mate.
Well, like I said, you messaged me on uh
what's what what number are you on and
then then I'll let you in. I need to
know your number. I need to know your phone number.
I need to know your phone number. You
got two numbers. What number are you on? Come on.
No, I'm not I'm not friends with I Do
you know what? I can't be friends with virgins.
Oi, I was going to invite you to the uh
the pub about 3 weeks ago, right? But
the manager said there's no it's a no
virgin zone. Absolutely no virgins. So
So you couldn't come with me.
Doesn't allow virgins.
I don't know what the [ __ ] this guy's
problem is, mate. But he he said no
virgins. I said, "What do you mean no
virgins?" He said, "Nope. Nope. Nope.
Got like a [ __ ] ginger beard." So
obviously no. It's a no virgin zone.
He's like, "No, they're not for It's not
for virgins like you." Virgins like you. Yeah.
Virgin. I'm going to make myself a bowl
of cornflakes. Actually, >> [ __ ]
hardly agree to our content for [ __ ] you virgin.
So, you're you're going to and you're
going to message me first.
All right. And you're and you're going
to message me first. Yeah. All right.
I might I might have to contact the old
Bill if you do. I'm only joking. No, I
I'll let you in. If you message me, I'll
Trust me, I'm not up to anything fishy.
That's not how it's going down. Okay,
then. Because you're trying to get the
police involved. You're an absolute virgin.
You're an absolute [ __ ] virgin. You
absolute virgin. That's why you're
trying to get the police involved.
Yeah. I was I wanted you to come to the
um the cow. I wanted you to come to this
pub, but the manager was like, "It's a
no virgin song." I said, "I wanted to
bring somebody that I met." And he's
like, "No virgins.
It's It's a no virgin zone. No virgins.
And I said, "What do you mean no
virgins?" People allowed a drink. He
said, "No, no virgins alone allowed."
Sorry, mate. No virgins.
No virgins, mate. No,
no virgin, mate.
No virgin, mate.
Yeah. I don't know what his problem was.
He says it's a no virgin zone.
Remember when you got ID?
Little bit of ID, mate.
Can't go wrong with a little bit of ID.
Do you remember when you got IDed?
Bit of ID, mate. Bit of ID.
Bit of ID in life.
You said you got IDed once and the guy
because the guy was showing off or something.
You said that there was a place that you went
and you said that he's normally fine. I
wasn't with you and you said that the
guy was showing off. I don't [ __ ]
know. You said he was showing off.
Yeah, they wanted your ID, mate. Bit of
ID. Bit of ID.
Bit of ID, mate.
Yeah, you said he asked you for ID.
you said he was he weren't showing off.
That's what the rules are.
You need to show ID, mate. That's why
you got an ID. Show it.
I think your girlfriend fancies me.
That's what Ricky Millington thinks as well.
I reckon your girlfriend fancies me.
Ricky thinks it as well. Yeah.
cuz she knows that
you can't give her normal babies.
That's why she wants me.
That's why your girlfriend deep down
wants me, mate.
That's why his girlfriend wants me, mate.
Cornflakes. Can't beat him.
Um, no he hasn't. He wants me to message
him. He's trying to get the police involved, bro.
All right. Triple H.
You remember that Ricky Millington?
You love that account, is it?
That Ricky Billington is it
I wonder where that H guy went.
You remember that H guy that went on
mine and went on Monty's? He just disappeared.
Yeah, but he is biased though.
Yeah, but he is biased. He might be an
all right fella, but he is biased.
Yeah, but he is biased though. ugly person. Bro,
you only say that I'm ugly
cuz you know deep down I'm better
looking than you and your girlfriend
fancies me. Bro,
everyone knows this now. Your girlfriend
loves me. That's why you call me ugly
cuz you can't handle it.
You look like a rat, bro.
You look like a [ __ ] rat. You rat looking bastard.
My dad would throw you out the window,
bro. Would he really?
A fat old man would throw me out the window.
And there you go calling me a virgin
again. Even though I proved I' had sex.
You're insecure, bro. You know this
every day what you do.
It shows that you're insecure.
That's all it does.
I'm [ __ ] way better looking than you.
I've had more women than you. I've had
more sex than you would ever have. I'm
still talking [ __ ] bro. Insecure virgin.
All he had to do was message me, Trip H,
and I would have let him on. He just
wants to get the police involved. Yeah.
He calls me ugly cuz he hates that I'm
better looking than him and his
girlfriend fancies me. virgin.
I mean, anyone that has to call the
police over YouTube is a loser.
Think about it. Trip. Yeah.
Where's Mr. G's crew? Too great.
Remember the GTA live streams? Me, you,
Mr. G's crew. Um,
who's the other one? U Goodson.
Who else was there? There was other
people, bro. Who was it again?
You remember when Goodson used to go live?
Good thing to go live. Yeah. J,
you absolute virgin.
Absolute virgin, mate.
What did my mom say? She can't fathom
why I'm on YouTube in it. She said
you're not fat, ugly, and disabled. You
should you should get off it.
Yeah, he won £100. [ __ ] hell.
Do you remember when I went on Izzy's door
the breaks and they all come on my Oh,
You remember that?
Cuz I knew where she lived. I went on her door
and everyone went on it. Tiger.
I said to him, "Can you be my mama over
the winter?" She said, "You're sick." No. Yeah,
some account said to me, yeah,
some account said to me, you touch
Isabelly's boobies. That's immature, is
it? That is so immature. I said to LT, I
told LT about it. He said, that's just immature.
He said that's just immature.
They said, "Did you touch his belly's
boobies?" Bro, that is [ __ ]
perverted, isn't it? Yeah.
Who do you think it is behind these accounts?
Who do you think is behind these
accounts, bro? Like, just Millington and
that. Who do you think it is, bro?
Seriously, like what do you reckon they
look like? Do you reckon they're old people or Yeah.
Yeah. But you like it though, is it?
You like this community.
You [ __ ] virgin. Oh, [ __ ]
Well, I'm going. Yeah, I'll be on tomorrow, maybe.