Yo, I'm not going to I'm not going to be live long. Um,
I just want to know Yeah. why you people
can't take one day off of YouTube.
Already have day and a half. Already
proved proved my point. [ __ ] went on
Timmy went live. I literally had come
back. I clicked on it and it's the same people typing.
same people typing away
which is strange because
I don't know it just something is not
right. I know in my gut feeling
something is not right with these people
that can't take a day off of YouTube. It
it is strange, you know. I I come back,
Timmy was live
and then I went on Timmy's Timmy's live
for like and it's the same people and
I'm thinking like, bro, [ __ ] They say
that they've got all this money.
Everyone else is this, everyone else is
that. Okay, whatever. So, why is it the
same people every day? I wasn't on
YouTube today. Uh, so yesterday I went
on YouTube and I've been busy today. I'm
just about to go to sleep. So I thought
I'd go live and ask like
what is it? Why can't you take a day off for YouTube?
It's boring. It is generally boring.
Look what I done today. I'll tell you
what I done today. I won't tell you
everything. Yeah, I went got myself a haircut.
Ready to go out in uh two days. I'm
ready to go out in two days. You know,
I've been busy. Why can't you people
take one day off of YouTube?
I I I don't get it. I seriously
seriously seriously ser like do you
still find it enter? It's [ __ ] boring.
It is [ __ ] dead. Like I've only I've
only come alive to ask you like why
you're doing what you're doing.
Like I'm generally I'm generally
curious. Like [ __ ] bro. No insulting.
I'm genally I'm generally Yeah.
I'll be out Saturday. I'll be out every
week after Saturday as well cuz it's
December now. So,
but apparently I can't afford to go out
every every uh
every day. Sorry, every week apparently.
So, you say? Well, I bet you I [ __ ] can.
But then they say, but this is what I
don't understand. And it's like you see
this account Smokey B
saying how he's got all this money and
that he works and you see him everywhere
you go. Anything that you click on,
you'll see him typing away, typing away,
typing away, typing away.
I guess it hits these people harder this
time of year, you know, December, it
hits these people like a ton of bricks.
I, you know, it hits them badly, you
know, in in December.
cuz they realize they got no family,
no friends, no money. So the only thing
they they can really do is just self
project on here. I get it around
December time. You get it?
No, I never said I went to the gym. Why
would I be going to the gym?
And I'm do you know what I'm going to do
now? I'm not even going to say what I'm
doing, where I'm going, how my nights
out have been. Nah, cuz this is what I
don't this is what I'm this is what I'm generally like.
This is the bit that I don't understand.
Yeah. Right. Is you saying that you got
all this money, right? But yet you'd
rather be on here all day every day. You
can be on here at the end of the night
an hour, 2, three hours a day. Yeah. But
these pe what what these people do on
here and I've seen it because when I've
clicked on on, you know, channels, it's
the same people. So realistically,
right, if these people are coming on
here calling people skin every day, right,
then how did that make sense when
they're on here all day? It doesn't make any sense.
I'll be out every week anyways from uh
next week. So, I just figured it's
better than this. It's actually better
than this, lad.
No, I don't care about the self-p
projecting haters. They're just self
projectors. They don't bother me at all.
I just I I just find it a bit strange to
be honest how people that claim they've
got all this money will sit on it all
day every day.
He doesn't have no six grand. The guy's
[ __ ] skint. You really think if
someone had all this money they would be
on here all day every day the way this
[ __ ] is? He ain't got no six grand. He's [ __ ] skint.
Don't believe a word he says mate. Trust
me. anyone that's got a good life would
not be on here all day every day the way he is.
I'm out every week from uh this week.
So, you know, that's that.
You know what I'm saying? So,
you can't have all this money and this
perfect life if you're on it all day,
every day. It doesn't add up. Something
fishy is going on
cuz even going out every week drinking
is better than being on here.
So it shows what they do, how long they
do it that they really ain't got a life
on here. I'm on and off. I'm on and off here now.
I'm on and off here.
That's the difference. I got my hair
done today as well. Yeah.
Just added some lotion to the old. You
know what? So, ready, bro. Ready.
Yeah, that Smokey Bee is one of life's losers.
Just like that account I responded to.
All of a sudden, you realize that like
they're doing it more and more now cuz
they ain't got family. They're going to
be lonely Christmas. What is it today?
The 4th. Right. So, it's Christmas in uh
21 days. These people are going to be
all alone and they're going to be alone
on YouTube as well. Don't let them try
and tell you that they're not going to
be alone on YouTube because they are
going to be on YouTube. They are they're
going to pretend they're not on YouTube,
but they are going to be on YouTube.
I'm going to prove it Christmas Day, you
know. I'm going to turn the live stream
on and I'm going to walk away from the
phone and come back in a couple of hours
and see how many people typed and if
these people really have got a life, right?
then no one will join.
As simple as that. No one will join. I'm
going to I'm literally going to go I'm
going to turn my live on, go shop, leave
the phone here, and come back just just
to see who comes on the live stream.
And I better hope I don't find one of
you on these bloody live streams, mate,
cuz I'll go [ __ ] mad.
It's like what my mom said. I've got no
reason to be on here.
I'm off and on when I want to. You know,
only fat disabled skin or skimp people
come on here doing what they do like
Smokey B and that sad people.
I bet they're doing nothing side. Eh, no.
They can't even create They can't even
create They can't even create their own [ __ ] content.
That's what makes me laugh. They can't
even create their own content. Oh yeah. You know, mad.
It is madness.
Make myself a coke in a bit. Maybe a
tea. Actually, getting colder now. Is it?
Well, I quite like this weather. I'm
quite weird, you know. I quite like this weather.
Snuggle up into bed. Oh,
that subline was lovely.
So, I'll be out anyways on that.
And that's another thing, Indigo. He
says, "I don't go out every week now
because I can't afford to." You don't
know my life, bro. You don't know how
much money I have.
You seem to guess. You don't know what
money people have, what money people don't have.
I'll be out every [ __ ] I'll be out every week
now. Depend. Uh I'll be out every week
and I'm just going to switch the days up.
So, Saturday, Friday, Thursday.
Well, I'm not going to do Wednesday, but yeah,
because it's better than being on here
talking to a bunch of self projectors. So,
and that smoky be is a big self projector
proper proper self projector, bro. Proper.
Cuz if I'm if I'm a single person, right, and
and I'm not working and I'm now finding
I'm finding it hard to find a time to be
on here. How do all of these people seem
to find all the time in the world to be
on here every day? I'm just I'm just
wondering. I I don't I don't really
care. I'm just wondering how they find
the time to be on here all day, you know? Yeah.
[ __ ] morons, bro. [ __ ] morons.
That's what they are. More on that. Yeah.
I said to Jo for
Yeah. We called you jealous because of
what you do on there. Not because what I
think of myself. is because of what you
do on here.
It's because of what they do.
If no one hated and stuff, people would
would never think anyone was jealous.
They would just think they're normal people.
That's that basically. Yeah. Gosh,
myself a tea in a minute. Poof.
I won't be live long anyways. Yeah,
I was on Reddit yesterday. That's
another thing. These people can't find
me on Reddit now cuz I use different subreddits. But um
still not admitting uh people's um faults and [ __ ]
I have left. I'm just coming on here
asking why you people can't take a day
off of YouTube.
I'm just wondering why you people can't
take a day off of YouTube.
I just want to know why you come on here
every day saying about how people are
this and they ain't got that and they
ain't got this when bro, you're
everywhere on this community. Like Timmy
was live earlier. I clicked on his on
his uh live stream was there for two
seconds same people typing away.
It just doesn't make sense. I mean the
lies on here by you from you people is
ridiculous you know
typing away typing away typing away
but apparently you've got jobs you've
got money you've got this. It just
doesn't make sense.
You know, I was I was You know what? I
was I was thinking about this, right?
Uh I can take I can take a day off of
YouTube. You can't. I don't need to ask
myself that. I can take day I can take
weeks off of YouTube. You can't. So, I'm
asking you people that that are sat on
YouTube every day. So, no. I'm asking
you that. I'm not asking myself that.
I'm asking you people that can't take a
day off of YouTube.
I'm asking you people why you can't take
a day off of YouTube because I already
have multiple times and I wasn't on
YouTube yesterday and so a day and a
half weeks I've been off of YouTube but
you people can't take one day off of
YouTube. So I'm asking you people why
you can't get off of YouTube. Everyone
else's skin, everyone else's all of
these things. Why are you sat on YouTube
every day? It's that bad. And I'm just
going to go out drinking every week.
Now, I was thinking about this, right?
We slag off going out drinking and how
toxic it is, but think about it. It's
It's better than better than being on
air. Better than [ __ ] being on air.
Going out drinking. It's better than
being on air.
No, you don't. Okay. Well, we'll see if
you're off. We'll see if you're on in 15
minutes time then, won't we? We'll see
if you're still on here in 15 minutes time.
So I can leave anytime I want. I don't
live on YouTube like you people. I went
on Timmy's earlier for like 10 seconds.
Same people typing away.
Same people typing away. Smokey B, all
of these people. So you with that bit of
evidence, we can tell who the skint ones
are. We can literally by what these
people do on here every day. We can tell
who are who's the skint ones, who's the
ones that ain't got no life. We can tell
by what we can tell by this bit of
evidence that we see what these people doing here.
Cuz if I'm a single guy that don't work
and now I'm finding it hard to find the
time to be on here, how are these people
on here all day every day?
It's strange, isn't it?
Very, very strange.
So, yeah, I'll be out drinking every
week now. Anyways, so starting from Saturday.
So, you know what I'm saying? Like, you
see the same people, Clint, Smokey B,
you see the same people. Any kind of
live stream you click on, you will see
the same people every day.
All day, every day you see the same people.
Kind of funny in a way. Same people, same comments.
Same people, same comments, lad.
Joseph Ra's been quiet.
Joseph Farrar has been very quiet, hasn't he?
So it tells me that these people are either disabled um
and or skin.
That's that's the only thing it can be.
It can either be they're disabled and or they're skin really.
>> Yeah, man. I've got a nice trim. I've
got my hair a bit shorter this time cuz
of uh it growing back so quickly. So, it
should last longer this time. Uh oh, I
made my bed as well. I'm going to have a
nice sleep today. Nice sleep.
My little clean clothes as well. Oh [ __ ]
Uh, I'm live asking you people why
you're doing what you're doing.
Yeah, I I mean I'm I'm live. Okay. Was I
on YouTube yesterday? No, I wasn't. You
people was. So, there you go. You've
already proven that you can't take a day
off YouTube. Was you people on YouTube
yesterday? Yes. Was I on YouTube
yesterday? No. Was I live yesterday? No.
Was I live earlier? No.
So, I would understand it, right? No.
No. Do you know what it was? Do you know
what it is? Do you know what it is?
Right. I could understand it. Yeah. If
if you didn't come on here hating every
day the ways the way that you do.
That's what makes it makes you just look
silly. Because you come on here every
day. Everyone's this. Everyone's skin.
Everyone's no no. We hear this [ __ ] But
you are the little clowns that can't
take a day off of YouTube.
If you didn't say any of that stuff,
then we'd be like, well, but then when
you're saying that stuff, then you're
thinking, well, hold on a minute, right?
If you've got this such perfect life and
you've got all of this money, why are
you [ __ ] on here every day? You know,
right? And I'm telling you that you
can't take a day off of YouTube,
right? And I'm telling you people that
you can't take one day off of YouTube.
I can't leave. Bro, you can't take a day
off of YouTube. Let Let's take one step
at a time, right? You people have
already proven that you can't take one
day off of YouTube. [ __ ] leaving. [ __ ]
if I can leave or not. You can't take a
day off of YouTube. So,
mate, one one step at a time.
I don't know where he is, bro.
See, Gregy will come on here and say,
"Oh, yeah. I'm getting to this stone. I
don't need the house. I've got anxiety.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no. So
Steven Howard when he's on here every
day when he's on here every day right
um we're like okay well he kind of said
it but when you see these people like
Clint and Smokey be saying that they've
got all this money and everyone's this
and everyone's that yet you'll sit there
and see them typing away typing away
until the cows come home with their
little others because They ain't got
nothing. So obvious. They're
self-projecting little bastards.
That's what I was saying. I'm not
pressed, bro. I'm just I just went live
to say it to be honest. So
it is weird. It's just [ __ ] weird. So
I mean Greavvesy says, "Oh yeah, I'm I'm
on a diet because I'm fat. I'm uh I
can't leave the house. I've got anxiety.
That's why I'm I'm going to be out
drinking every week now. I won't be on
it. I'll be on and off here when I when
I want to be on and off here
cuz smoky beer
is [ __ ] skin, you know?
Yeah. Okay. No, everything that you say
is about your own lives. Otherwise, you
wouldn't be on here every day hating.
That's what shows you up. That's what
shows you people up. When you sat when
you're sat on there calling people skip,
but you're on him every day. You're
showing yourself up. Your YouTube
activity gives you away.
He's only got six grand in the bank.
Bro, the guy's skinned. For [ __ ] sake.
He He showed 1700 pound the other day.
[ __ ] hell, bro. The guy's a [ __ ]
joke. I can show money. I have no
problem showing money, but I I don't
need to prove myself to sell projectors.
Same thing with the receipts.
I don't need to prove myself to self projectors,
fat, ugly people.
That wasn't why I was uh born.
I wasn't born to prove myself to fat
ugly weasels. They [snorts] ain't got a
life. So So yeah, it's like um
yeah, uh I come back from the barbers.
I was chilling for a bit. I saw Timmy
was live. I clicked on it. It was the same people
that's got all of this money that lives
is better than everyone else's.
Makes you wonder, doesn't it? Really
makes you wonder.
Makes me wonder. Anyways, so
yeah, I went to the barbers earlier. Yeah,
I'm going out Saturday, but I thought I
might as well just get it done today.
and I'll be out every week from there
on. But apparently I can't afford to go
out every week according according to
Indigo. Even though he doesn't even
know, he doesn't even know how much
money I have. But I can't afford to go
out every week.
Just weird these people are there. Is it very weird?
So yeah, I'll be out next week, the week
after that. Figure it's better than
being on here, isn't it? Yeah.
I don't know what I'm doing yet.
I don't know what I'm doing.
I might not even go out. Well, well, I
will be going out New Year's Eve. I'll
be out every week. I don't know.
I was thinking of maybe going Paris New Year's Eve.
I don't know. I could either stay in
London. I could even stay in London. I
could either go Wales. I could go Paris.
Maybe I was going to go Paris. I don't know.
Yeah, I got a trim, bro. I got my
eyebrows done as well.
Yeah, just somewhere else for New Year's
Eve, you know. I got some lotion on my
face. I don't know, bro. I don't know
what I don't know what I'm doing.
You're getting a timeout.
See you later.
I don't know what I'm doing. I'll be
out. I don't know. I will be out. Maybe
I might not be out New Year's. I don't know.
It's too busy. Yeah. I don't I don't
know, bro. It's Maybe I'll go out Maybe
I won't go out New Year's, but I'll be
going out every week until then. Uh
why? Why would I might as well go out,
bro? It's busy. It's It's just
pointless. You don't need to go out New
Year's Eve. Why Why would it Why would
it be might as well go out?
Why Why would I might as well go out New
Year's Eve? That doesn't make sense.
Yeah, it doesn't matter if life's short.
I've done my living, bro.
It's not a good night to go out. It's
very, very overrated.
Prices are more expensive.
It's not a good night. It's actually one
of the worst nights
to be honest cuz it's just overrated and
overpacked with [ __ ]
Yeah. It doesn't matter if there's only
one. It's just another day, bro.
Yeah, it's just another day.
It's just another day, bro. New Year's
Eve is just another day,
but it's commercialized, but it's just another day.
No, no, no. I can do large crow crowds.
I'm not scared. I've been everywhere by
myself. I can do. I just don't want to.
I'm not scared. I don't have anxiety.
Don't try and turn it into an anxiety
thing. It's just there's no point bothering.
So, don't try and turn it into an
anxiety thing. I don't need to prove
myself to you. Let's not let's not turn
this into another where people need to
prove themselves to you again cuz we all
know what happens with that one.
I can go into crowds. Well, I was out
New Year's Eve before
stuck in a crowd. So why would I be able
to go in crowds?
It's overrated. Simple. It's just
overrated for the [ __ ] It's simple as that. Yes.
Yes, it is. That's why sometimes I go
out Thursdays in central London.
Yeah. It's better.
Yes. Because that's my preference. It's
not that I can't do large crowd. is cuz
I don't want to. So, it's not can't do,
it's I don't want to. Can't do is making
it seem like it's an anxiety thing.
There's a there's a big difference.
Yes, because you said can't do which
makes it. Anyways, moving on now,
right? So, yeah, that's that. So, I
don't know what I'm doing anyways.
Uh, New Year's Yeah,
maybe. I don't know.
Just another day, bro. It's just another day.
Just another day. It's all it is.
I think I went out last New Year's and
the year before that. Yeah.
Skin and a [ __ ] skin flint.
Skin and a [ __ ] skin. Yeah. So,
I'll never go in Scotland ever again.
I've already been twice.
I think the furthest I'd ever go now in
this country is probably Nottingham.
I would never go I don't think I would
ever go or Cardiff maybe. I don't think
I'd ever go further than that ever again.
There's just no there's just no point.
Might as well just leave the country for
spending that kind of money. To be
honest, I don't think I'd ever go as far as that. ever again.
You know, I was on Reddit uh UK silent
talking to someone yesterday.
They're still making excuses for women.
Oh, [ __ ] hell. I need to I need to
stop this, bro. We need to break the
cycle, man. This is pathetic. Now,
we really need to break the cycle.
is [ __ ] with wickedness.
I think people should just stop asking
people for [ __ ] um advice, you know.
It's ridiculous cuz all they're ever
going to do is dismiss people's
struggles. So, it's [ __ ] The whole
thing is just stupid, isn't it?
You know what makes me laugh though is
that you people can't like you can't
create your own content
like you know LA the spasia they can't
create their own content
so they wait for other people's content.
I find it [ __ ] weird.
I still can't get over that Sher Cole
thing. I just I just can't get over that.
Sorry to be a repeater, but I just I
just don't know why someone would want to copy other people.
I'm wearing a [ __ ] six silk coat. I'm
wearing vapors. No one wears what I wear.
I just don't understand the need to
copy. I just don't understand. It's pathetic, you know.
Never never never never understood
people like that.
Never did, you know.
People that follow the crowd.
I think people do you know where I think
it used to come from? I think where I
think people used to bully each other
for being gay.
You're gay. You're gay. You're gay. And
then people I think they used to bully
each other for being gay. And that's
where they used to come out with I can't
I can't be gay. I think that's where it
comes from. You know, pathetic.
He's [ __ ] ugly. I've had more women
than him. [ __ ] had more women than he
would ever have. [ __ ] virgin.
I've created a song for the virgin by
the way, but I'm not I'm not going to
sing it. I was I was singing it all the
way to the barbers. It was about a 25m
minute walk and I was I was singing it.
Yeah. I'm I'm good at singing. I'm good
with lyrics and [ __ ] Yeah.
I'm a [ __ ] [ __ ] mate. Seriously. Yeah.
Yeah. I don't know why they copy though.
It's just stupid. Have a [ __ ] mind of
your own. Buy a mind of your [ __ ] own
for Christmas, you know.
Autumn can be my mama for the winter.
And this is how you know these people on
here ain't got no life because uh
cuz they all go for you Autumn. Yeah.
Saying, "Oh, you look good. You look
good. You're Oh. Oh, message me off
here. I seen your little white knights.
I said that you was my mama as a joke.
I've seen these little white knights.
Now, if these people weren't ugly and
had a life, do you think they would care
about some woman on the internet?" No.
That's another way to tell that, you
know, these people ain't got no life
because they wouldn't care about some
[ __ ] random ass woman on [ __ ]
YouTube if they weren't ugly and had a
life. They could just go out and meet
someone. Like, I'm not saying they'd
find a um not like they'd get sex and
find someone like that, but I mean like
they'd find someone that they could talk
to. Like, they might get a number of
someone that would talk to them back.
They might not get a relationship
obviously, but you know.
Oh, he tried Oh, that's another thing.
He tried [ __ ] retracting um his
statement by the way, trying to say that
he didn't say that because he got caught
red-handed by Chief Wigan being a copycat.
So, because Chief Wigan caught him,
right, being a copycat,
he's trying to say that he didn't say
that. out. You [ __ ] did say that,
mate. You [ __ ] did say that.
You said if you don't find her
attractive, you're gay. Yes, you [ __ ]
did say that. But now you've been caught
out being a copycat. You got caught red-handed.
He got caught red-handed, Dusty. He got
caught being a copycat
by Chief Wigan. Wigan.
Is it Wigan or Wigan? He got caught in the act copying
only because there's no um there's no
way there's no coincidence
that if you that these people are saying
the same thing as you.
They're copying each other. That's what
I'm saying. There's no coincidence, Dusty.
There's no uh there's no coincidence. Copycat. No.
That's what cats do.
I'll make myself a copper [ __ ] in a minute.
But yeah, if Smokey Bee's got this such
perfect life with all this money, why is
he on YouTube all day every day?
Yeah. From the Simpsons. Yeah.
Yeah. So, he caught non legs being a
copycat and now he's trying to say that
he he didn't say that when he did say
that. You said if you don't find her
attractive, it's homo vibes. Yes, you did.
Yes, you [ __ ] did say that. You got
no mind of you own, you [ __ ] virgin.
So, I made I made a song about the virgin.
I might sing it to you one day if you're lucky.
It didn't take me long to think of a little song.
Where's the nonsl lover Joseph Ferrar?
Where's the bias nonslover?
He rarely comes on here anymore, does he?
Nah. Come on, bro. No, not not yet. You
need to earn it. You need to earn it, mate. Yeah.
I'm going to go live on Christmas and
see who comes on.
I'm going to go live.
Yeah, my sister used to be obsessed with
um her Autumn. Yeah, but it's it's a
trend. Do you not understand? It's a
trend. Yeah, my sister used to be
obsessed with that. Michelle Keegan me.
I think what it is, bro, is that these
celebrities, you can see better looking
people on the street.
So, I don't I don't know. I don't see the
Oh. Oh, I tell you what, though. There's
a porn star that I like. She's old now.
Saying that though, there's there's a
there's a German porn star that I like.
She's from the um 80s in the ' 90s, but
obviously she's she's she's 49 now. I
was watching it yesterday. Oh my [ __ ] god.
No one knows who she is.
So yeah, definitely not a copycat.
Yeah, it's a porn star.
No, I I don't I don't watch. I watch
Vintage Born, but that just come up. Yeah.
No, I watch vintage porn.
Ant-Man's like, "That's strange. Did you
watch porn from the from the 70s and the
80s? I said, "Yeah, it seems more real then." Yep. Nah.
Gre said autumn could be my mama for the
winter. I'm dead. Can be your mama for the winter. No,
I don't know how people watch that. Johnny Sins,
you don't watch porn, do you? Steven Howard
by that Ricky Millington commented on my finger yesterday.
That cow makes me die. Bington.
Jesus Christ, man. Uh,
launch leg watches child pornography.
Michelle Keegan. Yeah, I uh
I know who that is.
It's not an accusation. It's facts.
It's set in stone.
It's set in stone, mate.
People on Reddit say you'll meet someone
because I know these things.
I know these things, lad. You're not. >> Yeah.
Don't forget it. It he was younger then. Copycat.
What did you say, Dusty? He likes to
follow the crowd. Did you say?
I've never been one to follow the crowd.
No, I've got a mind of my own. That's
what I was born with.
No, I've never had to copy.
Nah, I like being unique. You know,
someone on Reddit said, "Well, you can't
get someone pregnant because then I
said, "I can get someone back by getting
them pregnant, Dusty." But then they
said, "But then you're going to have a
kid and then it's going to backfire on you.
I said, "Yeah, but it doesn't matter." You know,
I was 17 years of age.
Yeah. I was 17 years of age.
Why didn't Virgin Legs just meet for a
fight? You never know. He could beat me.
You never know, Dusty. Think about like
all the credit he'd get if he if he
could beat me.
Definitely, definitely. Definitely not.
I didn't even meet Jack the Ripper on uh
PlayStation. I spoke to him after
Uh, he was 20, 21.
He could You never know, Dusty. He might
be able to beat me in a fight.
Yeah, I didn't meet him on PlayStation.
I met him after. I didn't know all the
[ __ ] he done until after. What the [ __ ] [laughter] Did I? No. No.
Oh, I love it here. Look, I've made my
bed. I'm ready to go to sleep soon. I'm
having a whale of a time,
you know. I can't wait. I got my face,
my beard done. I'm going to sleep like a baby today.
I'm going to sleep like an actual bubba,
you know, as soon as my head hits the pillow.
I just fancied I don't know why
I just fancied the savoy chips today.
Dusty, I could have had anything.
Indian. I could have had well this was
from the Chinese but I could have had
like a proper Chinese. I just wanted the
sublo and chips.
I don't know why just fancy sub
you know have a different
he probably did the [ __ ] virgin gosh [ __ ] Yeah.
Nice to have lion chips.
You can't go wrong.
I remember when Savo used to be 99.
Yeah, they used to be 99. Oh man,
Laney had a go at me, Steven Howard,
when she woke up. So, there was a bit of
milk left and I was hungry. So, I made
myself some cornflakes and Laney has to
have tea in the morning uh to be able to
function. And obviously, there was no
milk left, so I drank it all.
the corn flakes.
She had a guy at me.
I love corn flakes with lots of sugar.
Love it. Seriously? Yeah, I did.
I like corn flakes.
No, I like cornflakes.
So yeah, Laney was a bit mad, but we got
him in the end.
I was thinking about himself and it Yeah.
Yeah. It took uh about an hour and a
half to get my haircut. I had the full service
cuz it smells so nice. M
I'm going to have some Turkish food on
Saturday before I get another drink.
Oh. Oh gosh. No.
No. I was just chilling at the barbers.
What do you think of people on Reddit?
Steven Howard. People on Reddit say
you'll meet someone.
People on Reddit say you'll meet someone.
Hey, he's asleep. Bye-bye.
Yeah, Lane is asleep.
I'll be asleep, Finn. Oh gosh.
Yeah, the mods. Me and this woman both
agree that it's a power thing with these
Reddit moderators because they don't get
paid and they still have to manually ban
you even when it flags up. So, you need
to you need to ask yourself this, right?
Who that's got a life would sit on a
forum all day,
right? Who would sit on a forum all day and
mod it for free and not get paid? It's a power thing.
The the only people that do that are
people that have been bullied cuz they
don't get paid for it. They literally
don't get paid.
So, and they still have to manually ban
you even when it flags up. So, yeah,
they're definitely bully victims. I hate
using the word, but they definitely
definitely are. It's a power thing.
It is a power thing. Definitely. Defa. Yeah.
I never I always used to think they got
paid for it, but apparently they don't.
So yeah, they're sad bastards doing that for free.
Why Steven Howard? Joseph Ferrar is a
non legs lover.
He's a nons legs lover. Remember
Yeah, he's a non leg lover
and he's not blocked by non legs either.
Never see him defending me against that virgin.
Quick enough to be up his ass, though.
Hey, [ __ ] little [ __ ] Anyone to
try and say that I'm the pathetic one?
Yeah, they're biased on here. It's a
shame to be honest cuz he he he was all
right. He made some good points and
stuff, but I just can't stand biased people.
Not my cup of tea, you know.
Yeah, they definitely like nonses on
here, bro. Defer.
Timmy was calling Monty man a virgin.
They seem to love nonslegs on it. I
think it's because he's an actual pedo.
That's why I think people on here are
loveing because they love actual pedos.
like people that actual pedos, not not
just people that have said stuff. [snorts]
It's a pedo community in it. I think I
think they just love nons lad. Yep.
There's a lot of self projectors on this
community, Stephen Hard. A lot of self projectors.
Money would even tell you that there's a
lot of self-reflectors on this community, lad. [sighs] It's a
Where's Greasy? I hope he's all right.
Maybe he's had a heart attack.
I'll be looking for a new mama on Saturday.
Yeah, cuz they love they love nonslegs
on here. They lick his ass. Stuck up to
him like Timmy Joseph.
And it's not because he goes at me
because even if I come off of here, they
will never go for him. Maybe three
people might. So that's what makes me
think they love pedos on here.
That's why I think it's a pedo community.
Cuz if they're saying right that they hate Monty, right?
If they're saying that they hate Monty
cuz if they think he's a pedo. Yeah. So
why they not going for [ __ ] nods?
And even if Monty was going at me,
right, if Monty was going at me and I
was going back at him, people would
still be taking my side.
So that's what makes me think they just
love nonsense on here.
You know, proper like it's a proper pedo community. That's no no.
What do you mean? Because I fight back.
That Jamie Thompson is jealous of Peter Belly.
Belly. That's a fact.
My little weasel.
Little weasel. Fat weasel. Why am I
saying little weasel? [ __ ] fat weasel. Yeah.
Right. I'm going to make a cup of cont.
What do you mean? because I fight back.
So that Joseph Ferrar, right,
says that these people are not jealous
of me, right?
Okay. Well, look at Jamie Thompson and
then look at me.
Look at him and then look at me. I mean,
his picture's up there.
I mean, look at him and then look at me, bro.
Look at [snorts] this self projector.
This one on his channel. He so
desperate. He's transmaxing on Reddit.
He's react react. He's rejecting from
women or turning him into a homosexual.
This is the same virgin I was telling
you that was self projecting the other day.
Use this colon to buy fruity clothes.
Oh my god, these people on here are so
funny, bro. So much selfjecting.
Even though this was 3 days ago, they're
such self projectors. But I I don't
blame them to be honest. Like I said,
it's almost Christmas, man. They got no
family. So, what else do they have to do
then to be on here?
Steven Howard, you've been on here for
many years. You should know what they do
on here now. Every December used to do
it as well. The projection gets stronger
because they know that they're going to
be all alone Christmas, no family. They
can't say the same thing about me. They
literally can't. So, there's only one
family member that I don't talk to out
of choice. So,
you know, so you'll notice it gets a lot
uh a lot more in December. Around
December time, the self projection gets
gets more and more more and more.
Then it just goes back to normal.
Did you ever notice that or was it only
me that noticed it? Yeah.
Yeah. December they go mad, bro, because
they know that they got no family.
So they they they self projection gets
worse. You ain't got no money. You ain't
got this. I can't believe that guy the
other day telling me, "I've never had a
girlfriend." But he don't have a
He doesn't have a girlfriend and he
doesn't have any money.
Self [ __ ] projection. I've been with
more women than these had hot dinners. Self projection.
That's all it is with these people on
here. Self projection.
How can they be single, fat, ugly,
lonely people and try and tell you about
having a girlfriend when they're sat
alone, single, lonely people that's
already been proven that they they can't
get off of YouTube.
Madness, isn't it?
These people are just self-p projected
little losers, bro.
See, look at this.
And it's the same people that have never
been with a woman.
Look at all of the women that I've been
with. All the sex I've had, all the
women I've been with, they are single.
They are single, lonely people.
These people need to [ __ ] look in the
mirror, bro. Really, really, really need
to look in the mirror.
They're sat lonely, skint, and single
trying to talk about other people. And
they ain't even got a life. They ain't
even got a [ __ ] life. That's That's
the thing, bro. Madness. Madness.
It is madness, isn't it?
Come [snorts] second, bro.
Sorry about that, bro.
Yeah, sad people. They ain't got nothing in life.
They've got nothing in life. These people, Steve. Ah,
I can't wait to close my eyes, bro. My little
my little nasty calls.
I want to turn off.
I've got one. Yeah. But I'm not using
that at the moment.
Yeah, I'm not using that at the moment.
Yeah. [clears throat] Those
are for all the little uh bias launch lover. [clears throat] It is.
I can't wait to go to sleep.
Right. I said, "Yeah, Reddit mod have
got to be sad and pathetic." Yeah, for
sitting on a forum all day modding it.
One one replied saying, "Cool. So, you
looking for advice or just rage baiting?"
This person was like, "Not as sad and
pathetic as people not being able to
read the rules of a sub before posting.
It's a thank It's a thankless job, but
someone has to do it. They're not all
bad though. Chill." Not really.
Not really. They don't really need to be
bod. Not really.
Not really, bro. I mean,
nah, not really, bro. It's definitely a power thing.
We've read Reddit. It's definitely a power thing.
Definitely. Definitely. Definitely.
Definitely is a power thing.
I never said they're all bad. I just
said they're sad on modern site.
Similar title there modern it. It is sad.
I just had a big [ __ ] Yeah.
Yes. You can imagine
Why is Joseph Fro so biased? Steven Howard.
Well, a cup of cont. [clears throat]
Yeah. You say Izzy's is a fatty, ain't she? [laughter] >> Yep. >> [snorts] [clears throat]
>> Yeah. Joseph Rosen
the bias non lover. Yeah.
Did you see it Steven Al
when he's so um fast to be up Virgin boy
to Virgin boy rescue
but when he slated me no one says
Yeah. Did Did you notice it, Stephen?
That like when I was calling like non
legs a virgin, he he would be so fast to
be to his rescue saying he can't be he
can't be a virgin. He's got a
girlfriend. He comes straight to his rescue.
But then when he was talking when
they're calling me a virgin, he's
nowhere to be seen. That's why I got rid of him.
That's why I got rid of him, bro.
And started calling him
or anyone else calling me a virgin for
that matter. No one comes to my rescue. You know,
that's what makes me think they're like
pedos in this community, bro. That's
that's what I was saying. And then it
had a like they had a problem with it.
I said, "I don't see you on his channel
backing me up. You're not blocked. He
hasn't got you blocked."
You know what I'm saying? Stephen How?
He hasn't got him blocked. So,
I don't see you on his live stream defending me.
You [ __ ] nonsel loving [ __ ]
Why isn't he [ __ ] defending me? You know [ __ ] idiot. Yeah,
protecting that [ __ ] virgin. So he's
got a girlfriend that proves that he's
not a virgin, but someone that prove
they've had sex is a virgin.
And he said, "Oh, no. I said that you're
a virgin." I said, "Well, you're not
backing me up on his channel like you're
backing him up on my channel.
You [ __ ] nons."
I called him out for being a non-slaver, bro.
Yeah. How about if you don't want to get
How about just don't get involved?
A few of them have done it as well
cuz they're biased on here. It's like
Kieran said, it's cuz they're biased. Oh,
you [ __ ] skin virgin, can't you? I
need to take my washing out. Your skin
virgin, can't you? No.
Did you notice that with Joseph F indigo?
Did you notice it, lad?
What Joseph Ferrar used to do.
Did you notice it? Indie guy what he
used to do with that nons legs.
Oh, we're just talking about Joseph
Ferrar that when I used to uh well when
I call nons leg as a virgin he's
straight to his rescue like Superman
saying he can't be a virgin he's got a
girlfriend but then when he's calling me
a virgin Joseph Ferrar's nowhere to be seen
yet he's not blocked on the channel
that's why I [ __ ] him off bro being a
little bias nons lover
[ __ ] proper pedo community in
Yeah, it is, bro. It's a proper proper uh
it's a proper pedo community, lad. [snorts]
>> Proper [ __ ] Po community. One second.
boy won't see it.
He's like a virgin.
He's going to
He's going to He's going to die.
He's going to die down. He's going to
You went nowhere near that girl.
Absolutely nowhere near.
You went absolutely nowhere near
because I've spoken to her myself.
You went absolutely nowhere near that girl sexually.
You went nowhere near that that young lady, you know,
and you still remain a virgin.
Maybe next year, mate.
I just done my washing.
Are you going to lose it? Are you going
to lose it? Oh gosh.
Start want to know you. Want to know
you. I always said to him though, Indigo.
I always said to him, Indigo, that uh
you would be you'd be a good author,
like good at writing books. And and I
said that to him as well, like when I
used to meet him. you'd be a good
author. The amount of stories that you tell.
The amount of stories that you tell,
man, they're quite uh
they're quite interesting
about like um how you had sex. And none
of them are true, you little virgin, but
it'd make it make a good, you know, it
make a good author.
So, Indigo, you didn't answer my
question. Why is it when I call him a
virgin, Joseph Farrar straight to his
rescue saying, "How can he be a virgin?
He's got a girlfriend."
But Joseph Far's nowhere to to be seen
when he's calling me out. It's a bit
biased, isn't it?
It's a bit biased, isn't it?
Indigo, when I've actually put a porno
out there, it's a bit biased.
It's not really fair, is it?
No, Joseph Ferrar is not Ricky.
Ricky's on my side. Oh, I've got a bone
to pick with [ __ ] Ricky, right? He he
he wrote a little um paragraph
on my thing saying, "Oh, you're not uh
he forgot to mention that uh he's
obsessed with you. The Virgin's obsessed
with you, and he's jealous of your looks
and stuff." I agree with. And then he
was trying to say he's the one that's
obsessed with PJ bullying him every day.
That [ __ ] [ __ ] don't bully me. That
[ __ ] that [ __ ] skint virgin don't
bully me. I had him [ __ ] run into the
police about me [ __ ] hiding in his
area because he was scared to leave his
house. [ __ ] don't bully me.
Apart from that, Ricky, I [ __ ] uh I
agree with uh everything you said that
[ __ ] don't bully me. People that hide
behind a keyboard, run into the police,
don't bully anyone.
That [ __ ] [ __ ] Don't bully me, mate.
I [ __ ] beat him with one hand. A
[ __ ] lanky string of shitty piss.
No, he's he's not Joseph. Joseph,
I don't have a mama. I'm an orphan. Virgin.
It's a virgin.
The big virgin.
You're a [ __ ] virgin.
You [ __ ] virgin.
You should tell him to meet me. He might
beat me in a fight. You never know. The
virgin might beat me in a fight. Who knows?
All I'd have to do is give him one uppercut
in that [ __ ] skin rat face and he'd
be a goner. Yeah,
you went absolutely nowhere near that girl.
I shot, you went nowhere near her, you [ __ ] virgin.
Nowhere near us sexually.
Yeah, I remember eye shot.
You nasty virgin.
You nasty bird.
You nasty skin bird.
I'm going to be going out drinking every week, Indigo,
from this week. I thought you said I
can't afford it.
You're going to be proven wrong.
I'll be going out every week.
Every week having a piss up.
We'll see who can't afford it, mate. Not me.
I got my eyebrows done at the barbers as well. Look,
I got them threaded. You like them?
I'm a bit tired.
Yeah, you did.
Yeah, you [ __ ] did. You can.
Oh, get out of the car.
Get out of the car, Frankie.
Where's Greavvesy? He doesn't feel the
same without him here.
Greavves said Autumn can be my mama for
the winter. Indigo.
No, I don't need a mama. >> [snorts] >> Bye-bye.
See you later, mate.
No autistic. No autism on this channel.
No autism on this channel, mate. These
people are so autistic, you know. on
this community asking me if I book
tickets. Bro, you don't need to book
tickets in advance to leave London. You
do realize that? Unless you're going
somewhere like Scotland. These people
are so autistic.
They're so disabled in this community,
bro. Like, honestly,
you know, if you go Manchester Yeah.
with a rail card, it's always £64 there
and back. It's £64 there and back.
Always £64 there and back.
always. Like always, doesn't matter how
whether you went today or you went in
six months time, you don't need to book
an advance to leave London, you [ __ ]
retards. That's how disabled they are.
They don't they don't know anything of
this community. That's how you know they
don't leave their house.
They're [ __ ] retards.
Steven, they're retards, lad.
proper retards, man.
[ __ ] retards. Bye-bye now.
Some blue contact lenses. Why?
I hate blue eyes.
My eyes are greeny brown. A
Yeah, I got my nose waxed as well today,
so there's no hair.
Yeah, I got a little trim. I was looking
quite homeless, wasn't I? Oh gosh. >> [snorts]
>> It's a virgin.
You [ __ ] virgin. You [ __ ] virgin.
Where's Joseph Ferrar?
Oh, Monty's live.
I'm going to go watch Monty and then come back.