Yep. So, the Christmas projectors are
back. Oh my god. So much self projection
on Joseph Farah's channel. Look at all
of these people going at me. Just cuz
I've got family and I'm younger and
better looking than them. [ __ ]
pathetic, bro. Ladies detest me, bro.
I've had more women than you. This is
what I mean with these self-p
projectors. It gets worse during
December. I'm telling you, I've got
something that they want, bro. I'm
telling you. These middleage sad, fat,
ugly men, I've got something that they
want, bro. Why are they so jealous of
me? Why are they so jealous of me? What
have I got that they want, bro? Like,
you tell me that I'm not good-look. You
tell me that I'm not this. So, why are
you so jealous of me? I'm asking a
question. I really want to know why
these people are so jealous of me, bro.
This fat, ugly, smoky bee, all of these
skinned people. Why are they so jealous
of me, man? I didn't [ __ ] come on
this community yet for a bunch of old
men to be jealous of me.
Why are they so jealous of me? I just
see myself as a normal person, bro. Why
are they so jealous? And I'm And I'm
saying that word, bro, when I I know
that I've got family, bro. It's not my
fault that I've got family over Christmas.
It's not my fa fault that I've got
family over Christmas. I'm not going to
be lonely like these people and skint
like these people. Like, I don't
understand. It's not my fault, bro.
He's the same fat, ugly, familyless lurs
that have got no money. And and to
answer your question, Joe, the reason
you people call people skint is cuz
you're skint yourselves. It's been
proven many times. This is a disabled
community, bro. This is why I I don't
even want to come back on this
community, bro. Yeah. The only one or
two channels that I go on, it's just the
same fat, ugly people taking out their
familyless, lifeless losers lives out on
you, bro. Every single time these sad,
ugly people on YouTube ain't got a life.
Every [ __ ] time, bro. This is why I
wasn't on here the other day. This is
why I can't be bothered with it. Arguing
with a bunch of hateful, jealous, fat,
ugly people that ain't got a life. And
that's what these people are in this
community. They're jealous of anyone
that's better looking than them, that's
got family. I'm telling you, it is, bro.
100% it is with these people.
They're ugly people, single people with
no women trying to talk about me every
day. These fat skinned people are trying
to talk about me, bro. Every day. I've
got something that they want. I know it,
bro. I'm telling you 100%, bro. The fact
that you have got these middle-aged slobs,
gravitating towards you every day. Bro,
you're better looking than them. You're
younger than these people, bro. This is
why these fat ugly people don't come on
camera. This is why these fat, ugly,
skint losers do not come on camera, bro.
This is what I mean, bro. Look at this,
bro. You reply to me. Yeah. And you've
got about six fat slobs that are
replying back. It's because they've got
no family over Christmas. You can see
the projection is strong. Even an old
woman like Laney could figure out why
why you people do what you do. Yeah,
bro. You're the one that's living up
north. You're the one with a pension.
You're the one with a [ __ ] pension
living up north. You poverty ridden
[ __ ] You poverty Joseph. Joseph poverty
living up north. Yeah. Living up [ __ ] north. Right.
Know what I'm saying? These fat ugly
projectors need to get money and need to
get laid. They're [ __ ] losers. It's
not my fault that you got no family over
Christmas and your family hate you
haters, bro. Again, I'm not talking
about the genuine people. You can tell
these people are going to be lonely this
Christmas. My man literally replied to
me to and he's got about how many
comments from the same fat ugly slobs?
No, it's not even. Do you know what it
is? It's you fat ugly people. I can't
believe how jealous, right? You fat ugly
people can be of someone that you don't
know. I do you know what? I find it
impressive a bunch of fat ugly skint
people on YouTube every day being
jealous of someone half their age. I
think it's I think it's interesting to
be honest. I think it's interesting.
Bro, these people are going to be lonely
Christmas, bro. Lonely people. It hits
them this time of year, bro. It hits
them this time of year. Yeah. That's why
there's so many comments on [ __ ]
Joseph Ferrar's um community post.
They're fat, ugly people jealous of me
cuz I'm younger and better looking than
them. No, it's you people don't destroy
me. You fat ugly people. I laugh at you
at your jealousy every day on YouTube. I
laugh at you ugly jealous people. You
don't destroy me. You [ __ ] fat ugly
people. Do not destroy me. Bunch of fat
ugly people that have been bullied all
their life. You don't destroy me. But
otherwise, I wouldn't be on here. I
think it's strange how jealous fat ugly
people with no money can be of someone.
I I I I find it strange. Sorry, bro. It
just shocks me. You people do not
[ __ ] destroy me.
You fat ugly skinned people living your
worst lives. Don't destroy me. Coming on
here every day with your jealousy.
Especially around Christmas. Even Laney succ
knew that it's around this time
Christmas. They got no family. It's the
truth. You little losers ain't got no
family. Again, I'm not talking about
you, Triple H. And you know what I'm
saying, bro? You know what I'm saying?
You little fat losers ain't got a pot to
piss in, which is why you come on here
every day calling people skin cuz you
skin yourselves. Everything is about
your own lives. And that's why you come
on here every day doing this. You're
sad, disabled, lonely people. Lonely,
lonely people that ain't got no family,
no mom that loves you, no sister that
loves you, just a bunch of ugly, fat
people that have failed in life. And you
know it's true what I'm saying as well.
Doesn't matter how I say it, you know
it's the truth.
Bro, bro, I'm talking about you people
being lonely. You've never been seen
with a woman. Your mom don't love you.
What are you talking about, bro? I'm
talking about you lonely people on
YouTube that can't get off of it. I'm
talking about you lonely people. I'm
talking about you lonely, fat, ugly
people that can't get off of YouTube.
That's been proven multiple times. Do
you want me to prove it again? Do you
want me to come off of YouTube again
from today and prove it again that you
can't come off of YouTube?
Bro, you are the ones that are lonely.
Ugly people never been seen with women,
never been seen with friends. Bro, you
are the ugly ones. You are the fat ugly
ones that come on here every day to feel
special because your special needs and
you don't even realize that you're selfjecting.
End of the day, bro. It's you little
bongos. You're all loners. Look at you.
Look at this Jamie Thompson. Fat, ugly,
fat, and ugly. Ugly people that are
lonely bully victims in the real world.
Not this YouTube on the real world. You
do this because you're fat, ugly,
jealous people. And you can't even admit
it to yourselves. Come on, bro. Let's be
so real about this right now. Yeah. You
come on here every day. You claim you
got all of this money, yet you're sat
here typing away on YouTube. On YouTube
every day. And I've seen it. And I have
seen it as well. I have seen it as well,
bro. I have seen it as well. Yeah, bro.
You people don't have friends and family
otherwise you wouldn't be on here every
day doing what you're doing.
It's your YouTube activity
shows what you are. Okay, let's put it
this way, right? What you do on YouTube,
it shows that you've got nothing. It
gives you away. Your YouTube activity
gives you away that your skin ugly, no
family, no friends. The fact that you
keep coming on here for attention that
you don't get from your family, bullied
all your life. It It is true about you
people. It is true about these people.
If it is true about you people, you're
sad, ugly people that are jealous of
someone that's younger and better
looking than you. And the sooner that
you admit it to yourself, the sooner you
can move on. The sooner you admit that
you're fat, ugly, you failed at
everything in life. Yeah, triggered.
You're repeating yourself again. Stop
repeating yourself. You're not at work.
Wanking your little dick waiting for
your £300 a month does not mean that
you're working, bro. You're a repeating
little [ __ ] You don't have the brain
cells to have a job. Stop lying now,
bro. Just just admit to everyone that
you don't work. You don't work. You're a
disabled [ __ ] Just like triggered
triggering. Same repeating with you
disabled people. Same repeating with you
familyless disabled people. It's the
same repeating. You don't have a job.
A job is not wanking your little dick
waiting for your £300 a month. That is
not a job.
You know, you sad, ugly, familyless
people. This is why I don't come here
anymore, bro. This is why I didn't come
on here the other day trip ra with these
fat ugly people you know you actually lo
you know yeah when I was on here the
other day I had a headache bro for two
days arguing with disabled people really
takes its toll really takes its toll
yeah you got this job but yet you're
typing away on YouTube fantasy you need
to give your head a wobble bro and go to the doctors
no you people don't have a job you're
skin loners on YouTube you don't have a
job no 90% of you people don't have a
Yeah, 90% of you ugly fat virgins ain't
got a job. Yeah, I can't comprehend it
because you're on YouTube every day
typing away. Again, your YouTube
activity gives you away.
Yeah, your YouTube activity gives you away.
Fat, ugly, lonely, and that's why you
come on here. Just admit it to
yourselves. Just admit it to yourselves,
bro. Your fat, ugly little self-p
projectors. Admit it to yourself. Your
life will get better, bro. Simple.
I'm on here because [ __ ] I I had to
respond to this show for
Oh, bro. Stop the self projecting. Stop
the self projecting. I'm with my mom
right now. You people ain't got no
family. This is why you're doing what
you're doing. You'll notice it with
these people, right? Uh to break. Every
December, maybe you weren't on it last
year, bro. Every December, these people
go for it. It's cuz you got family. They
ain't got no one. And Laney was not the
only one that caught this. I caught this
as well. The bombs used to do it as
well. Every December, the hatefulness
and the jealousy towards me gets worse
and worse and worse. This is why I come
off of it, bro. This is why I come off
of here. You know, you know what I'm
saying? These people ain't got no
family. They're going to be lonely
Christmas. They're going to say to you,
Trip, bro, I'm going to go live on
Christmas and I'm going to walk away
from the phone, bro. I'm going to go
live and I'm going to walk for 10
minutes and I'm going to come back to
the phone, bro. And I'm going to end it
and we'll see how many of these people
are on here Christmas Day, bro. You
know, I'm going to tell show you how
many of these lonely people with no
family are going to be on their
Christmas day. [ __ ] losers. Self-recting losers.
Nah, bro. I just don't I just don't like
you people. You don't destroy anyone,
bro. You just you your lives have
already been destroyed. You're fat,
ugly. Look in the mirror, bro. Your
lives are already over. This is why you
do the [ __ ] that you do every day, bro.
You're already destroyed. Fat, ugly, no
money. You've already been destroyed,
bro. You've already been destroyed by
life. You ugly monsters on YouTube.
Now, I'm just sick of these people,
Charlie, bro. These little
self-reflecting fat ugly people, bro.
This is why you don't really see me on
here anymore, Charlie, bro.
Like, you know what I mean, Charlie,
bro. Like this is why I don't really
bother with this [ __ ] anymore, bro. I
only come live to [ __ ] just reply to
this Jo. They're just fat, ugly,
disabled little mongos. Bro, I got I
almost developed brain damage the other
day, bro. I swear to God. Yeah, I had a
Hey, do you know what? Yeah. Hey, do you
know what? Uh uh Charlie. Yeah,
I had a head. Not like a headache. Yeah.
But I saw a headb for like a day and a
half, you know. And then when I come off
here, I was like, "Oh, I'm normal
again." They They're so disabled, bro,
that they actually turn you disabled.
Arguing with them.
Uh ex got to go to my sisters and have
some food. Bro,
I was thinking of coming to Nottingham
New Year's Eve. No, it weren't even a
migraine. It was just a sore head. Like
a bit of a sore head. It weren't like a
full-on headache. It was just like a
sore head. Bro,
damn idiot. Yeah, I'm lonely. You're
talking Yeah, you're talking about
yourself, bro. Same back to you, bro.
You need to come on YouTube. Stop
pretending that you got a job, you
fantasist. You are lonely. You do need
to get a hobby. Yeah, man. Right back at
you, self projector.
Same. Back to you, you little self projector.
Same thing goes back to you, you little
self projector. Yeah, I used to suffer
from migraines, lad.
No, no, no. Because it's arguing with
disabled people, Joseph. When you argue
with disabled people like you, disabled,
fat, ugly people like you, you're
arguing with disabled people. So when
you argue with fat, ugly, disabled
people with nothing in life,
you know, this happens. But yeah,
Charlie, I used to suffer from
migraines, bro. When I was like 15, no,
17. I used to get them bad, bro. Yeah, I
don't really I don't really get headaches anymore.
is arguing with disabled people time and
time and time and time and time and time
again. It's a madness.
Jesus Christ, lad.
What are you doing New Year's Eve? Uh,
Charlie, and you don't need to call me
Poverty Pete Joe, just cuz I said that
you're a nons lover, you do defend
nonslegs. I wasn't lying. You were
straight to his rescue like Superman.
What? What? Where was the lies? There
was nothing malicious in saying that
you're so far up his ass.
You're so far up his [ __ ] ass. And
also the the amount of comments that you
got, it just shows how jealous these
people are. Sad, fat, ugly, lonely,
single people, no family over Christmas. Yeah, man.
Yeah, I know. I know. I need to stop
going on that Joseph Farage channel.
Otherwise, I wouldn't have come back. Um
I wouldn't have come back. Bro,
just leave the fat, ugly single virgins
to do what they do every day.
And to answer your question, uh, Joe,
the reason these people call me skint is
because they're skint themselves. Again,
we've we've been over this a million
times. You call people skint because
you're skint yourselves.
Uh, not in noting Nottingham, bro.
Listen listen, uh, Charlie, I was
looking to go Edinburgh. Yeah, it was
like £500. £500 for hotels. Like, I'm
not paying that. But in Nottingham, it's
like 97. So, I was thinking of going
there, but I might just stay in London.
I'm not paying [ __ ] £500 for a [ __ ] hotel
in Nottingham there. Okay. In Cardiff there, right?
No, I don't cuz I can't I just don't
understand why I've got so many people
jealous of me. Middle age people that
are jealous of me. It gives me the ick.
You know, you fat ugly people on here
every day jealous of someone that you
don't know. It's It's weird. And you are
jealous. And don't make me go over the
whole thing again because I'm not I'm
not going over it again.
and shut the [ __ ] up about rising to it.
Even if people ignored you. Oh, it's the
same argument. It's the same conversation.
[ __ ] hell. Bye. Right. Let's have a
normal Let's have a normal conversation
now. Yeah. So, yeah, in Nottingham,
right, a fourstar hotel was like 92 97. Charlie,
bro, I'm more educated than you will
ever be. You can't even spell properly.
Bro, you can't even spell properly. Do
not try and tell me about education,
bro. Do not let me do not make me go
back on your thing again. And Joseph
Ferrar, I'm telling you, you people are
jealous because of what you do. Your
actions show jealousy. It shows
bitterness and jealousy. Like Jamie
Thompson stalking me every day, won't
leave me alone. It's acts of someone
that's jealous of you. And if you want
to keep saying that these people are not
jealous, you just make a fool of
yourself. Writing away, writing away,
writing away, writing away. It's cuz
you're jealous of me. You are jealous.
You are [ __ ] jealous of me. I'm
younger than you, better looking than
you, and you want to bring me down to
your skin, ugly level with no family,
and you're not going to do it this
Christmas just cuz you people ain't got
no family, no life, no money. Don't
[ __ ] take that out of me.
It doesn't, mate. Listen, you can't even spell properly.
Anyways, shouldn't you be sucking Lance
Legs' dick? Shouldn't you be on his
channel sucking up his dick? You [ __ ] fat [ __ ]
You [ __ ] biased [ __ ] fat [ __ ]
Nons lover. He got a girlfriend. He's
got I swear if I ever see you in real
life, I'd love to punch your teeth down
your throat just for that. I would love
to punch your teeth down your throat.
Well, do you know what's so mad, right?
Is if you was really, really, really,
really, really, really educated, you
wouldn't be gambling. If you was really,
really educated, you wouldn't be
gambling unless you were a [ __ ]
billionaire. So, if you was really
educated, you wouldn't be gambling. I
don't need to state the [ __ ] I don't
need to state the obvious, people. If
you was really intelligent, you wouldn't
you wouldn't be gambling,
bro. I would love to punch your [ __ ]
teeth down your throat, you biased
non-slaver. Go and suck your boyfriend's
dick. You got a girlfriend.
You got a girlfriend. Why? Why are you
not sucking his dick? You [ __ ] fat
[ __ ] You and your fat ugly misses,
mate. Your misses. I would never go
near. Yeah. Even if she was the last
woman on earth. Yeah. Fat sausage
fingered fat [ __ ] And I can tell I can
tell by her [ __ ] hands that she's a
fat [ __ ] [ __ ] you. You fat [ __ ] [ __ ]
your fat [ __ ] Go and suck nons legs
dick. You biased northern [ __ ]
We got a girlfriend.
Oh, I got a girlfriend. You [ __ ]
biased little nonsing [ __ ] [ __ ]
Oh, they got down. No. [ __ ] [ __ ]
Biased [ __ ] [ __ ] dick sucker.
[ __ ] bastard. Suck my [ __ ] dick.
You [ __ ] [ __ ] [ __ ] and all. [ __ ]
you. [ __ ] your misses. Stupid [ __ ]
You poverty ridden bastard.
If you was educated, you wouldn't be gambling.
gambling. Simple. Well, unless you're a
millionaire, then you know, I'm sure
there's footballers that gamble that
gamble. You wouldn't, bro. If you was
educated, you wouldn't be gambling
knowing the risks and what will more
than likely happen. If you if you was
intelligent, you wouldn't be gambling.
I mean, on on on slots and roulette and
[ __ ] So, you're really not smart, lad.
Oh, cuz he's just a biased [ __ ] uh
And I think Greavves has got a bone to
pick with you as well, Joseph. About it. You know,
I've got more disposable money than you.
have. So, anyways, why are you so fast
to suck up his dick? Why do I not see
you on his channel backing me up,
Joseph? You little nons lover.
Oh, you little nonslover. Why do I not
see you on his channel or live stream
bringing up the porno that I put out?
You [ __ ] little nons. You little nons
lover. You're f You're so far up his
ass. Oh, he's got a girlfriend. Oh, he's
got a girlfriend. Why do I not see you
on his channel? You little nons lover.
Why are you nons lover? Why do I not see
you on his channel talking about the porno?
You [ __ ] nons lover. Two nonses think
alike. Two nonses think alike. Think
You know, oi you little nonslover.
Oi, you little fat nonslover. Why are
you so fast to suck up his dick? But I
don't see you wring about me on his
channel. He's a non-sl uh Charlie. Yeah.
Yeah, bro. Yeah, he's a nons lover. He
likes nons legs.
He's He's so far up his ass to his
rescue. But again, two nonses think
alike. You probably are a nons to be
honest. Now I'm calling you a nons.
Yeah, it's probably a good thing you
don't have children. We won't get into
that. Yeah, you Yeah, you are a n.
So again, why do I not see you on these
channel talking about the porno Joe? I'm
asking you a question.
Well, no, Greavvesy. Greavves, am I not
making a good point about what I'm
saying? Grievy, am I not making a good
point about what I'm saying?
Well, I I thought I think I'm making a
good point. When I go in on launch legs,
he's so far to his rescue. Oh, he's got
a girlfriend. He's backing him and
everything. And then when he's talking
[ __ ] about me, I don't see any Joseph
Ferrar. That's the truth. That is the
truth. That is literally the truth. It's
cuz he's a little nod. And two jealous
people think alike. Ever since I I saw
your biasness, I got put off you.
You know, I don't like biased people.
Nons bias. I don't like that. Yeah.
Listen, you little [ __ ] Why do I
not see you on these channel talking
about Sig and talking about the woman in
Manchester, talking about the 19year-old
and talking about the PO?
Why do I not see you on these channel?
You [ __ ] nonsubber. Am I not lying,
Grezy? You're so far to Oh, he's got a
disabled girlfriend that he's never
proved that he's had sex with. Oh, they
got a girlfriend. Oh, why do I not see
you backing me up, you non-slber? You nonsloving [ __ ]
No, he hasn't. No, he hasn't. He never
has. I've never seen him back me up on his channel.
You [ __ ] jealous little nons lover.
Oh, after what I've said. Okay. What
about him talking about getting with 15y olds?
What about when he said that he's
getting with 15y olds? I mean, he's
already proven that he's a nons. So,
what? So, you're saying that you you'll
back up a non, but you won't back up
someone that said things? You fat nons
lover. So why are you backing him up
then if you don't like him? Why are you
sucking his dick? He's more than happy
to defend himself. No, no, no, no, no,
no, no, no, no, no, no. It's not There
you go. Because this guy Right, right,
right, right, right. So if he's So what?
So you're saying he's a nons?
Wait, wait, wait. So you're So you're
saying he's a nons? So you're defend So
you defend a nons, but you're not going
to defend someone that said Nazi things
but not not a nons. It's not end of
discussion because what you're saying
don't make sense. You've just said that
you don't like him. So why are you
sucking his dick every time I'm going at
him then? If he's a non, why are you
defending a non? You just said that
you've called him nods legs. You keep
saying about how he he he can't be a
virgin. He's got a girlfriend. But where
are you defending me when he's calling
me a virgin?
So you so you're defending a nons? It
doesn't make sense. So it's not end of
discussion. So, he can't be a girlfriend
because he's got a disabled girlfriend,
but I can't be even though I proved I've
had sex, but yet he's a nons and you
don't like him. Make it make sense. You
said that you've got a degree, [ __ ] [ __ ]
He's got a disabled girlfriend, so that
must means he's had sex more than
someone that's actually stuck their dick
up a woman on video. Up a woman's mouth,
been seen in women's beds. Why are you
defending a nons?
Yes. Okay. So, Okay. Okay. Okay. So, why
have I not seen you So, why have I not
seen you on his channel talking about I
don't see how someone can be a virgin
when they've been in women's beds when
they've recorded them getting a [ __ ]
I don't see you saying anything about me
on his channel.
H because you're a biased nod. So, it
just goes that you show that you like
nonsense. And I don't need anyone to
back me up. I don't want anyone to back
me up. I'm just saying. Why are you
straight? So, so you can't see how
someone in a threeyear relationship
hasn't had sex, but you can see how
someone that's had one night stands
ain't had sex. You little dodg. That's
what you are, you little dodge lollver.
Go and mate, listen. You and your
[ __ ] ugly misses, go and have a fing
with him and these misses. Like, it's
getting out of hand now. It really is
getting out of hand. Why don't you all
just [ __ ] each other and get off of this
[ __ ] community, you know?
Get off of YouTube. go and [ __ ] each
other, all four of you, and get it over
and done with. You know, it's [ __ ]
getting ridiculous now.
It's [ __ ] mental.
But then this is what I mean. They they
go at Monty, but this is what I don't
understand, bro. No, no, no, no, no. But
he hasn't said it to him. No, no, no,
no, no. But he hasn't said it to him. He
hasn't said it on his channel when he's
gone live going about me, you know.
Yes, but he hasn't.
No, Mr. Lotty. But he hasn't because
he's never gone on Nleg's channel saying
about how I'm not a virgin. So, no, he
hasn't. He's saying it now cuz I've
called him out on it. Yeah.
So, yeah. You're just a little non-slover.
But you haven't. Okay. When did you go
on Non Leg's channel and say that I
can't be a virgin? Okay. Okay. Then you
you you link me where you have gone on
Nons's channel and you have said that
I'm not a virgin and then I and then
I'll say okay. Yeah. Okay. Yeah. You
you've said it. Yeah. Okay. You tell me.
You show me on one of his live streams
where you've said that and post it on
your channel and then come back to me.
You've said it, have you? Okay. Show it.
No. No. No. No. No. No. What? You said
it to him. What? You said it to him. He
hasn't had sex. He's a virgin. Why do
you keep saying that he's had sex? He
hasn't had sex. He's a complete and not
a virgin. And it doesn't matter how many
times he shows a disabled girl, it
doesn't mean he's had sex. There's no
proof that he's had sex. There's proof
that I've had sex. How do you know he's
had sex? Have you been in the bedroom
with him like you have with me? Have you
been in the bedroom with him like you've
been in a bedroom with me? You've
literally been in the bedroom with me.
Have you been in the bedroom with him
and he's disabled girlfriend? So, no,
you haven't. So, shut the [ __ ] up. Simple.
Anyways, you're just a biased
non-slover. End of.
So, yeah. Get a life, bro.
Seriously, get a [ __ ] life. Honestly,
I'd go out today, but I'm save myself
for tomorrow. So,
yeah. I I'm going to get some fried
chicken. Greasy. I'm going to get it
fresh. So, I might have to wait like 20
minutes for it.
Get some fried chicken. [snorts] Yep.
He is a [ __ ] virgin. This is what I
don't understand. Like, you'd go at
Monty, but no one ever goes at him. This
is what I don't understand.
This is what I really don't understand.
Like, you say that you don't like like
you say that Monty's a nonchair. This is
what I don't understand. Greavesy. Yeah.
If Monty was going at me right now and I
was to go at Monty right now, people
would be on his side and people would be
on my side. Yeah. With this nons legs,
they would all go his side, which he's a
nons. It doesn't make sense. So, it's
not the fact that someone's going at me.
You know what I'm saying? It's not the
fact that that they're going at me, bro.
Cuz if I was arguing with Monty,
oh, you love their screams. I was on a
Reddit yesterday. The woman was being a
a struggle dismisser.
She was trying to say, "Oh, I don't
really know them." And tet and tet. And
can I ask you a question, Joseph Farra?
Do you think people dismiss my struggles?
Yeah, they do. They do dismiss your
struggles, bro. It's [ __ ] annoying.
We need to stop complaining now. We got
to stop complain. We have to stop
complaining now, um, Reevesy, about this
because we actually go around in circles
cuz all they're going to do is keep
dismissing people's struggles like they
always do it.
I don't know what to think, Grezy. I
People on People on Reddit says I'm
going to meet someone. Grieves, what do
you think? People on Reddit say I'm
going to meet someone.
Yeah, he's back to the same episode on his channel.
Yeah, but they are Yeah, but Joe, do you
think it's a gender thing or no?
Would you say it's a gender thing? Cuz I
I don't mind being wrong. I don't I
admit that I'm wrong. As long as it's
not a gender thing, Joe, I I would I
don't mind being wrong. But we need to
make sure that it's not a gender thing
and I haven't been able to do the experiment.
Uh because um
because the the mods keep banning people
because they like to feel powerful.
They like to feel powerful. So I don't
know. I don't mind being wrong, but are
you sure it's not a gender thing? Yeah.
So, are you sure it's not a gender thing, Joe?
You sure? You sure it's not a gender
thing? So, if I if I if I go if I go as
a woman now, Joe, and I start
complaining about men, they're going to
make excuses for the men, right? Fingers crossed.
They're I'm just going to pretend to be
a woman and say, "Oh, yeah, a man's lead
me led me on." And they they're not
going to make excuses, are they? Like
they like they you know,
they're not. Do you reckon they're going
to make excuses as they do women or No,
I just want to make sure it's not a
gender thing. That's all. I I need to be
100% sure cuz then that is not fair and
that is not equal.
And that is not equal. legs.
Oh, that Aisha thing is a true story, by
the way. He actually did meet someone um named Aisha,
but did didn't sleep with her. Didn't
sleep with her at all. Went nowhere near
that girl. Triple H. He went nowhere
near that girl. No, I'm not coming
across as pathetic. I'm I'm curious
about this. Right.
There'll be a new episode tomorrow on Saturday.
Stay tuned. I'm not coming across
pathetic. I'm saying that when I've
shown women leading me on and stuff,
Joseph Fra, they all make excuses for
the women that oh uh they change their
mind and so I want to see if I pretend
to be a woman moaning about men if
they're going to make the same excuses
just so like so it's fair. I just want
it to be fair, you know?
I don't get triggered when these people
call me a virgin. They're calling
themselves a virgin. They're virgins themselves.
They No, they don't they don't they
don't trigger me, bro. They they they're
talking about themselves. Just like when
they call people skin, they're just
talking about themselves, lad. They
don't trigger me. I find what they do very weird.
They're virgins themselves.
sat on here every day the time they wake
up to the time they go to bed.
These people are the virgins.
So anyways, are you sure it's not going
to be a gender issue then? Joseph Farah,
I'm just playing some Franklin.
Yeah. And I want to pick my pieces as
well. So, I was going to go Nano's
Grezy, but I was like, I don't know. I
don't know what I fancy, actually. Um,
I'm having a restaurant tomorrow, so I
might just save myself with a nice
restaurant tomorrow. Yeah, I'll just
stick with a fried chicken,
but it has to be fresh. Otherwise, I
can't eat it. I can't eat it, Grezy. I'm
going to have some fried chicken from
the chicken shop. If it's not fresh, I
can't eat it, bro.
If it's if it's just come out like 10
minutes or like 15 obviously, but I mean
like I I get them to like cook it fresh
and it and it keeps the chips warm as
well, you know. Lovely.
That savoin chips was nice
yesterday. Did you see it? Groovy. I had
a savloin chips. Yeah.
So yeah, I think I'm just going to have
chicken and chips. I think
and I'm going to a Turkish tomorrow. I'm
going to get on a drink tomorrow. So, yeah.
Yeah, I went to a Chinese yesterday, but
I just I just wanted to have ling chips.
I didn't want a Chinese. I just just
have lion chips.
Um, I could order five guys, but that's
No, I need to go out anyways. I need to
get some drink.
So, and by drink, I mean Coca-Cola. Coca-Cola drink. Yeah.
Yeah, it's still it's all right. Waking
up about 12, so it's not too bad. Could
be better, but could be worse.
I went to the barbber's greasy. I got my
little haircut. I slept like a baby
yesterday. I changed my bed in. Had a
nice shower. Oh, as soon as my little
eyes closed, I was asleep.
Can't beat waking up with a nice fresh
haircut, can you? In a lovely cozy fresh bed.
No, I need to get the Coke from another
place because the Coke in the chicken
shop is foreign and it tastes like [ __ ]
So, I have to get the Coke from a from
an actual branded shop. You know what I
mean? Don't you, Grezy?
No, I have to get it from like a Yeah,
I don't know. I think Yeah, fried
chicken. I think I would have. What do
you What do you think, Greavvesy?
Five guys is nice though to be fair.
I don't know.
Busy today. It's Friday.
I don't know. Go on his channel and go
and ask him. Did Hey, Monty. Hey, Monty
went to uh court today, Grezy, and he's
not come out.
So, I wonder what I wonder what's
happened to him.
Maybe he got sent down, is it?
So, maybe he's he's been sent down. Yeah, [laughter]
he's not laughing now, is he? >> [laughter]
>> What? Just a normal chicken shop. Yeah,
I'm going to get one leg, one fire, and
one middle breast.
Yeah, I was talking to this person on
Reddit uh and I said that women are
hypocrites and stuff, greasy, and they
said that you just want to get a woman
pregnant. I said, "Yeah, that will show
them in it if you got someone pregnant."
And they said, "Well, they won't show
them because then you're going to have a
kid." I said, "Yeah, but then I can just
ignore the kid." Grieves. I said, "I can
just ignore the baby and stuff."
We was talking about pregnancy and stuff
and boobs and stuff.
Yeah, we was talking about that kind of stuff.
Is that cute? Greavvesy.
What do you mean that's stupid?
It will show. We was talking about like
women that have boobs and stuff
and then how like they will get bigger
if the person gets pregnant and stuff
and they'll need like a different bra.
So how comes if a woman don't have big
boobs you don't approach them? H
surely I should just approach anyone
like depending on what they look like in it.
You you would have thought in it. [snorts]
You would have thought so, would it,
Grezy? I love your little comments,
Grezy. Autumn can be your mama for the
winter. You and your little comments.
You know, you wasn't on YouTube
yesterday. It felt really
weird without you being here.
Yeah, it felt really weird without you being here.
Welcome back. It's good to have you
You and your little comments. Bless you.
Oh, what is to my little thing?
What are you having for Are you still
You're still in your little diet, aren't you, Grezy? [snorts]
This is the [laughter]
buddy said it's just the same people
doing the same [ __ ] on here. Grezy.
He said it's just the same people doing
the same [ __ ] Same shitty comments.
I didn't even know the football was on today. >> [snorts]
>> Maybe I'll get a kebaby just to tease
you. What kind of kebab? A don or aish.
I'm Oh, I'm having a kebab tomorrow. I'm
going to a kebab restaurant tomorrow, Grezy,
before drinking. So, I'll do a little
video for you. Oh,
yeah. I'm not really keen on the Donna,
Grezy. It's kind of greasy.
Yeah, it's kind of greasy. Less [ __ ]
than if you're on a little diet. You're
better than me, mate. I'm not sticking
to no [ __ ] diet. [ __ ] that for a game of soldiers.
You know why I prefer going to the
chicken shop? Cuz you can pick your
pieces. Whenever you order from KFC and
you get pieces, they always try to pour
you off with a [ __ ] wing.
Like a little wing.
You know what I mean?
So yeah, going to go to the chicken shop
in a minute.
Okay with you, boss. I'm going to tell
them to make it fresh.
Nothing worse than dried chicken, eh?
Why don't you get the shish, Grezy? It's
a lot better for you and it tastes
better. Instead of getting the donor,
you should get the the shish.
[ __ ] silly goose.
You silly goose. Oh, bless.
Oh, bless you. Then if you fancy Oh, no.
[ __ ] McDonald's, bro. I a McDonald's for ages.
Yeah, but the shush is nicer. It's just
more expensive, isn't it? Won't take long.
Yeah, it is. But it's a it's it's a lot
nicer. It is a lot nicer. The don is all
right. The chicken don is all right, but
the lamb don is stinking. It's too greasy, Greavves.
I like a I like a tandoori chicken me. I
just want some fried chicken today.
Yeah. You know yesterday, Greavves, I
just fancied some chips. You know when
you fancy just some salt and vinegar
chips, Greavves. Some salt and vinegar chippies. Chipilates
with a nice Do you like Savoy Greavvesy?
I probably don't imagine that. I can't
imagine that you do. A lot of people don't.
I do like Saboy. I haven't had it for a
long time. I like Sablo and chips.
Yeah, I don't think a lot of people like
it to be fair. I feel like I'm the only
one. No, I got my haircut, Graves. You
don't. Does it look better?
Does my hair look better now? Does my
face look better?
Oh, what are you doing, you little goose?
Yeah, I went to the barber shop uh yesterday
cuz my hair and beard was getting out of
control. I'm going out tomorrow for some
Guinnesses, BC, and I'm going to cause
mayhem. I'm going to cause mayhem in the town center. Oh [ __ ]
What was it, Dad? Oh, cheers.
Where was you yesterday, Grevy? We was
waiting for you.
We were waiting like the like like the
like the guy in the shop. All he was waiting for your appearance.
Your hair looks skin, bro. Oh, you need
to stop them comments, bro. It's repeating.
You know what we need to do, Grezy?
Yeah. From next year, we need to change
up the content. No more skin talk. No
more virgin talk. We should change up
the content. Is it?
Yeah, that would never happen, bro.
These people repeat themselves every
day. Do you remember when Monty man said
that, Grezy? And I'm getting sick of it.
It's like that. I think they're robots.
Are these people even humans? [laughter]
Oh, bless you then. We was waiting for you.
I need to go out and get some [ __ ] food, man.
I'm so cozy in my nice little clean top
and my basketball shorts. Greasy. I
don't want to go out in the cold,
but I'm going to have to.
I wish they could bring the food to me, Breezy.
You know, like bring the food to me.
No, he's not.
So, what do you think? 2026, Greasy. Do
you reckon these people will still be repeating?
What if I came back here in six years,
Grezy? Do you reckon it would still be
the same [ __ ]
Oh, do you reckon people would have
changed the words?
Why do they do it, bro? I saw I saw
someone on Timmy's. Yeah. And they're
always on on these channels, Greavves,
and they write skin like that's why why
do they do it?
Have you seen that account? It's called Pip Something.
It just says skin. That's it. That's the
only word it says. It just says skin
with nothing else.
I asked Monty and I said, "Why do they
do this?" And he says, "It's cuz they're skin."
Grievy. He said, "It's because they're
skin." Is it or what? I don't understand
it. I don't understand why they do it. I
don't know why they do it.
I don't know why they do it. They must
be skinned themselves, isn't it?
Yeah, these people are skin. Yeah, defo
say I'm not reacting to these clowns anymore.
That's what you said, didn't it, Grezy?
I'm going to have a nice can of coke.
I'm uh I'm going to have a nice can of
coke with my chicken and chipsy.
I like it with a nice can of coke. Is that cute? You know. Yeah.
How did I for chicken and chips?
Uh, I don't have to pay for anything. I
get everything for free.
Yeah, they give me food. I get food for free. Grievy
cuz I'm known in the local area so they
give me food for free. Greavvesy. Yep. [snorts]
Elephant and castle. Grezy.
Yeah. Something like that.
A I need to pop to the shop now. Oh sh I
don't want to. I'm so
I'm going to go in my little shorts,
baby. I'm going to go in my little shorts.
My little basketball shorts.
[ __ ] sake, man.
Going to get some nice chicken and chips.
One leg, one thigh, one middle breast. >> [snorts]
>> Gosh darn it. You like to pick your
pieces as well, Greasy.
I like the middle breast.
It gives me vitamins, Greavesy. [snorts]
Well, you [ __ ] can. I just say I want
leg. I just want one leg, one thigh, one middle breast
or a side breast.
So, Grezy, in 2026, are we going to stop
hearing the word skin? No, it doesn't
trigger me. It's just boring cuz it's
just repeating, you know? It's like
watching the same film over and over again.
Why wouldn't you think to do that, Greasy?
Because if you if you order from if you
order from KFC, they give you a little
wing. I ordered four piece meal. I got
one leg, one middle breast, and two
wings. There were two small wings as
opposed to pieces.
That's why you have to like Well, mate.
Yeah. Because if you if you go KFC and
you like whenever I used to get the six
piece meal, it would be two fire, two
leg, two middle breast. Two thigh, two
leg, two middle breast. Done.
Because if you don't pick the pieces,
they're going to give you [ __ ] so little wing.
They will and they always do it, which
isn't a piece.
It's like a wing. It's like a wing piece
and it's tiny.
So that's why I say Yeah.
No, I like KFC.
What's your favorite What's your
favorite videos of mine Greavves? Is it
Is it the Indian restaurants?
Oh, they're lush. I can't be bothered
going there today having I'm like I
said, I'm going to eat tomorrow, is it? So,
yeah, it's okay if you um Yeah, I'm I'm
going to a restaurant tomorrow, so I'll save myself. Virgin.
Yeah, I'm going I'm going in a minute to
get some food. Uh, Triple,
I'm going to find a candidate for Baby
Peter tomorrow. P.
Yeah, I want I want the chicken fresh, bro.
I am getting free pieces. So,
I don't know why I get free pieces cuz I
can only eat two, but I always get free.
What do you mean? I've already found my mama.
See, look. Triple H is saying it now. Greavvesy.
Imagine him saying mama in his little in
his little Jordy accent. [laughter]
Yeah. I could have had Natalie. Yeah.
When I was 22. Yep. Peter, buddy,
is he live? Yeah. Yeah, he has caught
today, don't he?
Yeah, he's got caught today. So, if you
don't if you don't see him live, we know
why, isn't it, Reevesy? [laughter]
We know why.
But if he get if he gets
if he get [laughter]
if he gets sent out right, I'm not the
root cause, am I? Not really. Nah,
I didn't do anything. Can it? [ __ ] [laughter]
No, not really. Is it? There's no way I
could be the root cause for that. That [laughter] No way.
No way. [laughter]
Greavves. You know when the police You
know when the police come and arrested
me at 5:00 p.m. at the old house a
couple of years ago, I I woke up with a
load of old bill in front of me and I
was just watching the sidemen. I fell
asleep. Yeah. Watching the side men on
the same [ __ ] website and let the
[ __ ] police come on my door over. [laughter]
Literally, I must have fell asleep. I
woke up and the side room was still on the screen.
It was still there was they were still
on the screen and I've got a load of
copies in front of me. Gy, a load of copies.
Uh, no. No, I didn't.
No, it was you little clowns. Gosh. Hey,
everyone likes a little voices, isn't it? Hello. [snorts]
I sound like less. Well, that's not possible.
My chin is huge. That's self projection.
Shut up, you little self projector.
My chin is huge. No, it's not.
They don't pick on me, man. They just
pick on themselves. Thank you, man. No,
the haters don't bother Jame. Oh my god,
this Charger. The haters don't bother me.
The haters don't bother me, Jamie,
because they're just talking about themselves.
I've been on here longer than everyone.
Oh [ __ ] Why is it not working? They
just talk about that. Do you not do you
not know why these people are doing this?
Do you not understand why these people
are doing this, man? Come on. You're not
new to this community. You know why
these people are doing this? What month is it?
Yeah, they bully themselves. But the
thing is, Jamie, that they don't bully
anyone. They bully themselves.
These are fat, ugly people that ain't
got no family, no life. They don't
bully, though. That's the thing. They
don't bully anyone. They bully
themselves. Oh my god, this child. Why
ain't it working, man? They don't bully
anyone, though. They bully themselves.
You have to meet somebody to bully
someone. You have to come on someone's
door to bully someone. You can't bully
someone behind a keyboard. them
self-reflecting doesn't mean they're
bullying. They're just talking about
themselves. I can go on a channel and
start calling people behind the
keyboard. That's not bullying. You can't bully someone.
Because they're jealous.
Because it's jealousy.
Do you understand? They're fat, ugly
people in no life that have been
bullied. They've been bullied their
whole life. So that's why they come here
to feel special.
These people don't bully me, bro. How
can they bully me if I'm on here every
day coming back for more? A bully
doesn't come back for more.
No, it's not bullying. They don't bully
anyone. So, you feel wrong because if if
they were bullying, you wouldn't be
coming back for more. What does what
does a what does a bully do? A bully
tells these teacher that I'm being
bullied. I'm being bullied. These I'm
keep coming back for more because they
just keep embarrassing themselves.
They bully themselves. That's all they
do. They've been bullied their whole
life. Fat, ugly, skinn, no family.
They're living their worst life. So,
anything that they do on the internet,
no one really cares.
So people, if they were bullying, you
wouldn't be coming back for more. If a
kid gets bullied at school, they don't
come back. Yeah. It doesn't matter what
the videos are me. I'm still better
looking than them. I'm still younger
than them. I've still got more money
than them. They can make what videos
they want. They can do whatever they
But until someone comes to my door and
does something or until someone meets
me, they don't bully me. You have to
meet someone in order to bully them.
Being generous to someone does not equal
bullying. You have to actually meet
somebody to bully someone. You can't
bully someone over a website.
Anyone can talk about themselves and
make videos. I wouldn't keep coming back
for more. A bullied person don't keep
coming back for more. I haven't called
the police on any of these people yet.
They've called the police on me. I don't
have a crime reference number. So
clearly their bullying isn't working if
you keep coming back for more.
So I mean yeah that's that. Definitely
definitely don't bully me, mate. I hate
that I hate that [ __ ] word bullying
cuz they definitely definitely don't
bully me. They're fat ugly old people
that are bullied. What kind of bullying
could they do on the internet?
You know, it's December. It's almost
Christmas, bro. These people are going
to be lonely Christmas.
This is why they're doing this.
This is why the community's peaked up
because they realize they're going to
have no family Christmas and they're
just self projected. So, yeah.
Yeah, that's that. So, yeah.
Uh, [sighs] I just go back on Reddit one second. Yeah.
Nothing. But I'm just going to get some
food in a minute.
Yeah, I'm just going to head to the shop
in a minute and get some food, I think. [snorts] Yeah.
I don't understand with this Reddit. Why
do they ban people?
I was going to ask this woman a question
and then they uh
bam me. I was going to ask I need to
make a new account. Now I want
do women moan about men and they can't
find normal people. This is one thing I
would love to know.
Not for somebody to answer me it. Maybe
a woman could answer it.
Why? I want to know, Bob, why they say
they can't find normal men and they
struggle with men, but then when someone
comes their way, they're not interested.
I'd love to know.
Just out of curiosity. I've always I've
always wondered it because it seems a
bit like mocking.
a normal guy that they go on about.
[snorts] Maybe I'll ask her this.
It is strange, isn't it? They contradict
himself by going with somebody in prison
whilst they're in prison. [ __ ] idiots.
We're not going to overthink it cuz
we're still going out tomorrow no matter
what. So, we're not overthinking it. But
be a waste of time. But yeah,
just like it always will be. But that's done it. One sec. [snorts]
Good. One second. I need to go in a bit.
be live on Christmas Right.
Sorry about that. Anyways, I'm gone.
I'll be back uh later. So, yeah.
I don't want to see any of you people on YouTube either.