[Music]
What a loser. I've just gone on [ __ ]
uh Jamie Thompson's [ __ ] channel.
Yeah, because [ __ ] idiot keeps me.
And guess what? Virgin Legs is running
to the police again. I've whooped his
ass again. I've made him go to the
police about me again. Yeah, he's the
one that bullies me. What a loser. They
always go to the police in the end.
These losers. These YouTube losers. I
literally have to leave in about 20
minutes. I've got this date to go on.
These YouTube losers always run to the
police when they get home owned. Have
you noticed that? Every time these
little losers get owned, they always run
to the police. Oh my god. [ __ ] what a loser.
Loser. And let me tell you something,
LT. Yeah, that Terry is no different
than any of these people. and his family
is no different than any of these
people. So the more you talk to someone
like that, yeah, trust that Terry is not
about nothing either because he bigs up
when people get nicked. These bro, you
know, these YouTube losers, right, are
all the same. I'm I'm I'm literally
telling you they're like all the same,
bro. And all of the ones that was all of
the ones that aren't the same, they're
not they're not any um they're not on here anymore.
Yeah, it's a madness part. You want to
be talking to people like that team,
bro. They're all the same. They're
literally all the
same. They're all the same, bro. These YouTube
losers. Oh, he's running to the police
again. What a loser. Oh my god. They
always run to the police in the end. Oh
used to do it as well. They are They are
such losers. Oh my
god. They're [ __ ] They don't even
understand the law either. They're so
stupid. Oh my
god. Honestly, why why do you do this to
yourself? You come on YouTube every day.
Like let's let's let's let's just like
talk normally for a minute. Yeah. Yeah.
Cuz I got to go in like 20 minutes. Why
do you come on here every day with your
ugly rat face acting like you're some
sort of hard man with your string of
pissed body with your no teeth in your
gum and then as soon as somebody owns
you, you run to the police. It doesn't
make any sense. And the police will
never believe you. The police don't
care. Listen, let me tell you something.
The only reason, right? The only reason
the police come out last time is cuz you
used your disabilities. I didn't use my
disabilities. I've never told the police
I'm disabled. You told the police that
I'm disabled. Yeah. The only reason the
police come out last time is cuz you use
your disabilities. And guess what
happened? Nothing happened. Why? Because
they've seen your YouTube channel,
Virgin Boy. You got nothing better to
do. Oh, I'm just saying I'm I'm going to
put up posters of this [ __ ] Virgin.
And guess what? He's run to the police
again. All they do is run to the piece
when you own them. They're losers.
Terry's no different, bro. Even that
Terry, I lied the other day, bro. I was
cussing his mom. I was cussing his dad.
And he won't meet anyone. I'm telling
LT, they're no different. These YouTube
losers are all the same. Sean, Terry,
they're no different, bro. Trust me.
Trust me. He's so stupid. Like, listen.
Never say never that the police would
never come out. No, they haven't come.
No, he just said that he's reported me.
But the police are going to see your
channel and then they're going to let me
go, Virgin. Like, okay, the police are
not going to come. If the 1% chance that
they do come, they're going to see your
channel and see what you've been doing,
virgin boy, and then they're going to be
like, "Oh, you're both as bad as each
other." And then they're going to let me
go. It literally could never go to court
because if it went to court Yeah. It
It's like It's like Morgan, for example,
right? If she was harassing me every
single day and I was harassing her back
and she tries to take me to court and
then they go down my [ __ ] phone and
they see that everything she's done,
bro. It would never happen. It would
never ever go in the doors of court. He
doesn't understand like it's madness.
Why would you even waste please time
when you're going to lose in the end?
Even in the short even in the short
time. This is how bad his autism is,
Gary. This is what I mean. like his
autism is so bad that A, he can't leave
people alone. B, when someone owns him,
he has to run to the police knowing damn
well he's going to lose. It's stupid. It
is stupid. Oh, also I've got his
blackmail as well. I've got his
blackmail. I've got his videos calling
um um Goden and Goden and Goden and
Goden and Goden which I've sent to the
to the to the police woman. Last time I
got nicked for like 30 minutes. You're
never going to win. you will never ever
ever ever ever ever
ever win. And I've also got years of
things that you've done as well. So, it
doesn't make any sense. Like, it's all
well. It's good, man. Have a YouTube
channel, you know? Am I going to be
lifted? Nah, never going to be lifted,
mate. But what I'm saying, have a YouTube channel,
right? Imagine having a YouTube channel,
right? Showing your [ __ ] ugly face
round, trying to call people out, and
then you run to the police. Good luck
with that, buddy. The police are going
to ignore you. Like, it doesn't make any
[ __ ] sense how somebody can break the
law and then try to be a victim
themselves. [ __ ] off, you little
virgin. [ __ ] off, you little virgin. No,
bro. I'm just because it's to me it
sounds mad, bro. To me, bro, it's like
I'm I'm trying to explain this to LT. I
don't understand how these people work.
I'm I'm trying to Well, again, I would
never understand autism. So you come on
YouTube, right, every day with your ugly
face, with your ugly rat downy face,
trying to call people out and act the
big man, right? And then you run to the
police. Does Does that make sense to
you, Gary? Does that make sense to you?
It doesn't make no sense to me, bro. It
me. Oh, we're just talking about
nonsense. Like, you're you're such a
[ __ ] loser. Like, I say that. Yeah.
With with my hand on my heart. You are
one big loser. Literally, you really,
really are. Get a life, man. I'm going
on a date in about 15 minutes, so I
can't be here long, bro. So,
yeah. [ __ ] loser,
lad. It's a
madness. Got a football bet on today.
Madness to get one on [Music]
delay. It's [ __ ] weird, bro. Like,
you would have thought these people
would would just give it a
break. It's mad.
He doesn't bully me. He's never bullied
me at all. He's He's the one that's
running to the police about me. He does
not bully me, brother. You [ __ ] mad.
I went to his area and made him run to
the police. I had him stop going to
events for like over an hour. That Sha
Virgin has never bullied me. Go on that
[ __ ] Jamie Thompson channel right
now. He's the one running to the police
on me. Doesn't sound like a bully to me
when you have to run to the police.
Doesn't matter what teams are
on. No, bro. I'm just talking about
these losers. You think that lanky
string of piss little virgin who I've
made run to the piece about me three
times has ever bullied me? You can't
bully a guy like
me. You can't bully a guy like me,
bro. And you No, obviously they've not
been around, you know, but the thing is
I want them to come. I want them to come
and show them all of these harassment. I
want I I've got everything. the
blackmail. The blackmail from the Do you
know that? Did you Did you see it the
other day, um, Harry? Did you see it the
other day? But this little [ __ ] he was
like, "Oh, um, if you don't
comply, if you don't comply, your
messages," I said, "You don't [ __ ]
blackmail me, you [ __ ] ugly rat
virgin [ __ ] Are you [ __ ] mad?"
That's screenshotted. You think you're
going to sit there in your virgin bedset
with no [ __ ] woman and [ __ ] try
and blackmail me with that ugly inbredad
face of yours? What was I was I was
looking at myself. I was like, "No, this
can't be real. This ratfaced little
virgin keyboard warrior spacker is going
to try to blackmail me. Are you [ __ ]
mad?" Anyways, go self-reflect on
another channel. You are autistic. I was
like, "What? He doesn't torment me. He
doesn't torment me. None of you people
torment anyone. You're just little self
projectors. You people don't torment no
one. I live in your heads rentree. You
don't torment no one. I'm still on
YouTube. At the end of the day, yeah, at
the end of the day, bro, if you knew if
you tormented me, I wouldn't be on here.
You people don't torment no one. I
torment you every day being
alive. Every day on YouTube, you can't
get me out of your head. I torment you
just by existing. I assure you, you
people have never bullied no one on
nothing. And I tell you that for
nothing, mate. And I give you the whole
bet of money. You people do not bully no
one. You are the bully victims. Look at
the ones. Yeah. Who's the one that has a
light? And who's the one that don't have
a light? Yeah. You people don't torment
no one. Listen, mate. If he he I've I've
had him go to the police about me again.
I've made him run to the police about me
again. I've made him run to the police
like the little [ __ ] he is again. You
people don't torment no one. Your little bully
victims. You [ __ ] ugly people don't
bully no one. I will say it clearly
clearer than Monty. You people don't
bully no one. A [ __ ] four or
fiveyear-old can come on YouTube every
day doing what you do, but you people
are not about it in real life. You
people will never meet anyone because
your little housebound anxiety bully
victims. Any kind of bullying that you
think that you do on YouTube. Yeah.
You've been you've been bullied every
day of your life. You're being bullied.
90% more that. You know what I mean? Now
we're doing posters, Lord J. We're doing
posters. We're doing posters, mate.
Simple. There's no going to gigs. No,
there's just straight up posters. You
No. Like, bro, it's not tormenting me. I
just It's the cowardness. It's the
cowardness of it. It's not tormenting
me. It's unbelievable how somebody can
be so much of a loser. I'm I'm
surprised. No, no, no, bro. It's
absolutely surprising me, bro. Yeah. How
somebody can be so much of a [ __ ]
loser their whole life on
YouTube. I've got a date with this Yanka
LJ. We're going to be making some love.
I don't give a [ __ ] if I'll get nicked
for it, mate. I'll get nicked for it and
they'll let me go. How about that one?
That's fine, bro. I'll show the police
that he's harassment. Bro, listen.
Listen. Did it work the last time? Did I
get put in prison the last time? No, I
didn't. I don't give a [ __ ] if I'll get
nicked. I'll show them all of his
harassment and he'll get nicked for
that. And I'll keep reporting it and
reporting it and reporting it.
Simple. Yeah. I will show all of the
stuff he's doing and he'll get nicked
for that. How about that one? And he
will do it, bro. And I'll say to the
police, and this is what I'll say to the
police. Yeah. If you do not nick him,
I'm going to keep doing it. I'm going to
keep doing it every week. Every week.
Every week. If you do not do anything,
I'm going to keep doing it every single
week. I'm I'm going to say that as well.
Simple. So, that's it, bro. Yeah.
Simple. So, they're going to have to do
something, bro. Simple.
Yeah. That's it,
lad. Yeah. No, Timmy's all Timmy's all
right, man. To be fair, man. Timmy's all
right compared to this [ __ ] stupid virgin. Yeah,
simple. No, if the police come on my
door, I'm just going to show that all of
these harassment and he's been trying to
blackmail me as well. Yeah, it does. No,
no, I tell you what it does changes. I
tell you what it does change. It changes
me getting done for it. Yes, it does. It
changes me getting done for it. He
doesn't torment no one, mate. Listen, I
pull up areas I pull up areas, right? I
put up post this area tormenting him in
real life, mate. I made him go to the
police about me, mate. I made him stop
[ __ ] posting for three weeks, mate.
I've got him going to the police on me,
mate. Do you think anyone on YouTube
could ever make me go to the police
screaming I'm not a fighter? Listen, I
tell you what, it does change, and I'll
explain it to you, [ __ ] mate, has
anyone ever made me stop posting about
them for free [ __ ] for free um um 3
weeks? I made him go to the police about
me as a victim. No real bully goes to
the police. Lord J, you tell me. Right.
You tell me. You tell me. Right. Does
any bully run to the police as a victim?
Does any bully go to the police
screaming how they're not a fighter? Cuz
I have known many bullies in my time and
I've never had them run into the police.
Oh, and I'll tell you what it will
change, LJ. I tell you what, it will
change. Yeah. Let's just say the 1%
chance the police come on the door,
right? And you know what? They don't
even put you in handcuffs. They don't
they don't hear you. Uh, he's so jealous
of me. I know, Gary. He's such a jealous
little virgin. He's a jealous little
virgin. Listen, I tell you what would
change, Gary, right? Is if the police go
down your phone and they see all of his
[ __ ] guess what's going to happen? No
further action. No further action. No
further action. That's all that's going
to happen. That's literally all that's
going to happen. He's such a jealous
little virgin. Just cuz he can't get
laid and lose his virginity and he has
to be a virgin on YouTube, he's a
virgin. Um trolling. Um that's not
breaking the law. Uh that's not breaking
the law. And you know what the police
actually said to me? They like, "Oh, why
did you do it that?" And they was like,
"Oh, um they was like, "Do you know what
they said? Do you know what they said?
Do you know what they said, Gary? Do you
know what they said? You know what they
said, Gary? Yeah. Do you know what they
said? They was like, "Oh, well, you you
know, we kind of understand it that it
stopped it. It stopped it, mate. What
you're doing is against the law. You're
blackmailing people. You keep harassing
people every single day. You are already
breaking the [ __ ] law. So, shut the
[ __ ] up." Yeah, you little virgin. And
you don't try me, you little [ __ ]
You have me going to Do you have me
running to the police about people? Do
you think anyone could ever make me run
to the police about them, bro? Are you
[ __ ] mad? And that Terry is no
different. That Terry is no different
either, bro. Yeah. And I've had to warn
LT about that. Terry is no
different. Oh, he tried to say, do you
know what he tried to say? And I've got
his blackmail and blackmail blackmailing
is illegal. A lot of police have been
done for it as well. Right. And um yeah,
so uh what he tried to blackmail me
with, he said, "Oh, if you don't
comply," he said, "If you don't comply,
right, I'm going to uh get you um" He
says, "If you don't comply, I'm going to
put all of your messages out there." I
said, "Fuck off, you [ __ ] ugly [ __ ]
Go suck your [ __ ] dad's dick about
complying with you, little [ __ ] [ __ ]
off, mate. I would rather literally
record my face out there posting up
posters than comply with you. You
[ __ ] virgin. Don't [ __ ] do videos
about me. Don't [ __ ] make videos
about me. I'm leaving in 10 minutes when
it gets to
25. I'm leaving at Yeah, I'm leaving at
2:00. Go get there for 4. I got some
stuff to do. So, yeah. This little
virgin thinks he's going to blackmail me
in his little bedsit. He can [ __ ]
suck his dad's dick. He's got more
chance of his dad taking up his
virginity than me complying with him.
Are you [ __ ] mad? Yeah, you've got
you have got autism, Red Star. You have
got autism, boy. And you can't come and
do anything to me, boy. And I own you
every day, boy. You're on YouTube
triggered every day. Raging, should we
show everyone your channel again, Red
Star? But should we show everybody your
triggered channel? your triggered
channel of your obsession. But you can't
meet me in real life cuz I bully you in
real life. Big nose bullies you. Big
Nose bullies you. You can't meet Big
Nose. Big Nose owns you in life. Big
Nose owns you. You can't do nothing to
Big Nose. You can't even show me where
you are. Guess what, Red Star? You can
say whatever you want behind the
keyboard, but I have got a power over
you. You can never show me where you
are, lad. You will never show me where
you are cuz you're scared of me. You're
scared of me. You can have your little
channel online. You can have your little
channel online, Baldi, but you will
never meet me in real life cuz you're
scared of me. You're scared of me. Woo!
You're scared of me. You can never show
me where you are. You're a little
keyboard warrior. Keyboard warrior
bothers no one. You don't bother no one.
You little keyboard warrior. You can't
show me where you are. You're scared.
You're scared of me. I've got that power
over you. I've got that power over
you. Anyways, I'm going at 2 o'clock.
anyways. Anyways, I'm leaving in 10
minutes. I can't entertain these little
[ __ ] [ __ ] basement dwellers all
night, man. I can't
[ __ ] I can't entertain these little
basement virgin dwellers [ __ ] all day
long, mate. I'm going on a date with an American.
Got that 19year-old coming over today as
well, LJ. Uh yeah, she text me
yesterday. They always come back for
more. I suppose she's supposed to come
over yesterday, but I fell asleep. I had
some jalapino uh pizza. I'll show
you. Yeah, they gave me two cuz I had to
wait 2 hours for it actually. It looks a
bit [ __ ] now, but yeah, it was very
tasty, man. It's sort of a hangover right now. Right
out. Yeah, we'll be out all night, mate.
There you go. Look. Papa John's. Papa
John's. Papa John's. Papa John's. There
we go. You can't beat the Galapino pizza, man.
Yeah, I am getting a ride, mate. I'm
making some babies from um babies from California.
LJ. L. We was together for over an hour
and I'm going to say right at the end,
do you want to make
love? Yeah, of course you did. Yeah, of
course you listen, we're not all little
basement dwellers like you little
virgins. We're not all little virgins
like you that sit on YouTube all day.
I'm talking about that account, by the
way. We're not all the same as like you
people on here yet. You seem to think
everyone's got the same life as you.
That's why you call people skin. That's
why you call people these things because
you think everyone's got the same life
as your own life that you're living. And
I'll say to some of these people as well
like what what are you? Are you my
personal banker or
something? Um we're going to be together all
night. We're going to be together all I
need to go in 6
minutes. So yeah, I'm gone, bro. I'm out
of here. Try not to be too
jealous. Try not to be too jealous. Yeah.
Yeah. And it's not legal. It's like if
that Morgan lived in England, I would
have been nicked. If I if I if she lived
in England or I lived in America, I
would have got nicked. Yeah. Bye-bye,
Red Star. Go make another account, you
borrowing obsessed little keyboard
lawyer. Bye-bye now, bud. Stop talking
about yourself. But I would have been
licked by now because it's actually not
legal. Yeah, stop talking about
yourself. It's no good for your mental
health. It's not nice to call yourself
all of these
things. These people live. They're
basement dwellers. They're literally
basement dwellers. Actually, the date is
actually at 4, but I'm leaving at 2:00.
You know what it is with these people?
They're basement dwellers. Think of
think of it, uh, Gary. Yeah. Do you
remember when I was in the pub the other
day when I was drinking Guinness? It
triggered them. Think of it. Think of
their lives, bro. Listen. Listen. I went
to a pub and I had a Guinness and they
were trying to get me kicked out of the
pub and they didn't even know what pub I
was in. These that should tell you what
these people are about on YouTube.
They've got nothing. They got no one.
They can't even go down to the local
boozer and a fool of Guinness. That's
how [ __ ] their lives are. Like get they
get jealous of a Guinness. Like it's a
madness. Their little bro. They're
little basement dwellers. I'm telling
you. I swear. Who's a 19year-old? Uh the one from
before. Duh. Hopefully I can win this
football bet today,
mate. Probably won't though. It's a
double. Both teams to
score. Come on, you [ __ ]
Yeah, cuz I need to go get my hair done
and I go out and it's going to take me
like 40 minutes to get there. I need to
get my I need to go to the barbers.
Yeah, you wouldn't know about the Versus
LJ because you don't have any
hair. You don't have any [ __ ] hair.
Yeah, man. You people are [ __ ] man. I
swear to God, you people are [ __ ] on here.
Literally, you shouldn't be jealous of
people. You shouldn't be jealous of
people. Do you know what I'm saying,
Gary? You know, if he actually went out
and he was normal, he'd actually be able
to pop his virginity, Gary. He'd
actually be able to pop his V
plate. It's not my fault you're still a
virgin. Yep. Got the old shorts on,
buddy. You know, I've got basketball
shorts on, Air Jordan, LJ, and that's
not going to stop me booging the night
away. That's not going to stop me
boogying the night
away. I got the old trainers as well.
Most of my stuff, my moms, I just ain't
bothered. They just ain't bothered going
back to me. But yeah, man. I'll dance the night
away with the shorts on. You think
that's going to stop the madness? I went
out Thursday with shorts and I was
boogieing the night
away. Boogieing the night away. All
long. All night long.
L all night long. Having a little
pig. Having a little
pig. Man needs to go in uh in a minute. That's it,
bro. Few minutes. E, it's at
four. Best not get there,
LJ. You know. Yeah. I lost 20 pound on
the property. It wasn't having nothing.
It weren't having It wasn't having it
for toffee. Lj, it wasn't having it for
tough. This is how rigged these machines
are. Yeah. I'll tell you what happened.
Yeah, I put 20 in. Yeah, I got one spin
and the ball was on 30%. I put another
20 in, up, down for about 5 minutes. And
guess what I took? I took £21 and then
20, which means all in total I was £1980
down. Yeah, £198. I'm not even going to
put this last 20 pound in it. Are you
[ __ ] mad? I swear to God. I swear to
[ __ ] God, bro. I was like, I'm not
even going to put I'm just going to take
1980 down, bro. I can't justify losing
any more of this [ __ ] [ __ ] It kept
going on 25,
LJ. They kept going on 25,
LJ. What's that all about, LJ?
Yeah, bro. So, I just I was just call it
19 and I done a 40 football bet as well.
Oh, it's actually
£41 because obviously I got to change it
for myself. It's £41 on this football
bet and it better [ __ ]
win, which it probably won't. Anyways, I
need to go anyway. So, I will A see you.