[ __ ] more projection.
Do these self projectors ever get bored? But
do ever get bored
of talking about themselves?
They're not nice, bro.
Do these self projectors ever get that
of talking about themselves? It's madness.
There's so many things you could be
doing in the world, you know,
or talking about yourself,
right? from past to chicken
instead of calling yourself a B calling yourself skin.
So what can I say with you little
mongos? Yeah, you're obviously watching
my channel. So why don't you why don't
you join the hangouts? I play the money
game. I play with you show your face.
So you obviously watch a video cuz I've
gone back on Joseph Far channel. So why
are you not joining the panel then?
You fat projected ugly nerd with no
family. You know exactly who I'm talking
to as well. The box
the link was there. I'll put the link up
in a minute. Everything
all these little selfies
in their lives. Anyways,
if any of these people got to say they
can come, they can come in the hangout
in a minute. Let me just let more people join.
So, you're watching me. You're being a
little nerd. So, I'll put the link up.
Skin cell projectile
all these accounts
self-reflected every day on YouTube. Let
me put a link.
See if anyone will join.
Or is it just the same self-reflection
[ __ ] that we've been doing for years?
Well, shout out people.
I mean, the link's there. So, if anyone
wants to join,
I'm more than more than happy to put
this to bed, bro. Not a problem. You
show me what you look like.
I'll show you receipts and I'll show you
money. It's not a problem.
Instead of being a little coward by the cable warrior
being a cable warrior there little birds
come on the boxes there
I don't care about the usual generous
people but I just want to see if
anyone's enjoy that actually join the panel.
I didn't realize they watched me. I
didn't thought they saw.
So, you watch, but you won't join the panel.
Join the panel, man. The link's there.
And you're all self-reflected. Ain't got
no family, no money, no life. The link's there.
Come on. Don't any selfies. Yeah.
I made the same thing to you. I said if
you if you show what you look like, I'll
prove that you're a M and I'll show you
money. I'll show you receipts. But they
can't do it cuz they are the mother. Cuz
any any people that are not ugly would
just come in and shut you shut you up
once and for all
cuz they're not intelligent. cuz >> cuz
they want to every day repeating. So, I
mean, they can't even say they're intelligent anymore.
They're the self-reflecting little
skinned little fat. Nobody is. That's
why they can't join the hangouts.
And yes, I'm talking about you. You know
exactly who you are. So, join the hangouts.
Oh, the box for you.
You little nerd. You little weasel
trying to tell someone the other day how
they don't have a girlfriend when you
don't have a girlfriend and you've never
been anywhere near a woman. You sad
pathetic loser virgin. Anyways, the box
is up there. I'm not a coward. So, you must be
trying to talk about girlfriends when
you don't have a girlfriend.
That's the definition of an oxymoron. She's self-reflected.
I'm sure like
they're just [ __ ] losers. Failed at
everything in life and the only thing
that they've got left to do is to come
in here and try to bring better people
down. I'm sure it is with these people, you know.
And if it's not, come in and explain yourself.
You're more than welcome to come in and
explain yourself. The link is there for
anyone who wants to join.
Any little self-reflector. No UK
signing. Come off. Come on. Just right.
Just said one second. Well, he said
one second now.
You know, you talk about people being
skinned and whatever. Join the hangouts
and put your camera on. The link is
there. I don't know what what you
waiting for. I said to you, I'll show
you money. I'll show you money and I'll
show you receipts. If you show your face
and you prove everyone you're not a mon,
I'll show you anything you want. Even my
ass if you want.
These people are serial self-reflectors.
That's what they that's that's all they
are. They're just they're just fat
people that ain't got no nothing to life
that just come in every day calling
people that they don't know. How is a
how is a man in their 40s that's never
been with a woman trying to talk about a 28-year-old?
They're all self-reflectors. This is
what I mean with these people. They're
self reflecting fat ugly people that
ain't got no life. And I will be coming
off here soon anyways. Like I only come
back on today because of because of Joseph.
They're the sad self-reflective fat ugly
losers. Most of them are virgins.
Despite what they say, they're just sad
people that need attention online
because they ain't got no one. Just like
Smokey B is another sad loser. What I'd
like to know UK is silent is
that they call people skint every day,
right? I don't care why they do it, but
we see these people everywhere. Any live
stream you go on, you see them typing
away, typing away, typing away. You go
out for 5 hours, you come back, they're
still there. So, I just don't understand
with people that's got this great life
and all of this money why they sat on
here every day hating.
But the link's there. If anyone wants to
uh come and explain themselves and show
their face, you're more than welcome to
or another couple if you want.
Cuz if I'm wrong, explain why you do it.
Again, I don't mind being wrong. Maybe
there's something else I'm missing.
You've been on this community now for 10 years.
self projecting every day talking about
other people when it's your own life. I just uh
I want someone to I want someone to join.
What the [ __ ]
You want L J to go live? That just goes
to show you a [ __ ] You want L J to go
live? Another self-reflector.
You You want L J to go live?
I mean, Timmy, I can understand. M, you
you want Lord J to go live. Another self-reflector
that's got self-reflecting people that follow him
that self-reflectness getting this onto
people every day that causes autism.
That channel, if you spend enough time
on that channel channel, you're going to
end up like them. You know, you're going
to [snorts] end up with a sore head and
brain damage. That's why I don't go on it anymore.
on a repeat. No, there's no point in
that channel. It's just the same people,
same pictures, same same repeating, same
self-reflecting, same hating on different people.
That channel was totally gone. It's just
the same middle-aged nerds that ain't
got a life that failed at everything in
life. That's why you shouldn't get
annoyed at these people. You shouldn't
get annoyed at these people because
they're just people that are that are
failures that ain't got no hope. people
that never made it that come online
every day self-reflecting.
That's why these people shouldn't even
annoy you to be honest.
They hate themselves. They hate that
they're failures and they got nothing in
life just like the bombs. Just like all
these other people.
Why would anyone want Lord J to go live?
It's the same. It's the same. This is
what makes me laugh at. Yeah.
You say that you don't show your face
because you're smart. You got this IQ,
right? So then if you've got this IQ,
why do you come on here every day
creating the same atmosphere and
repeating the same old [ __ ] the same
old comments? If you're smart, why do
you constantly repeat the same [ __ ]
every day? No new comeback. We ain't had
a new comeback in since I've been on it.
I think that skin thing has been going
on now for like seven years. six and a
half, seven years. So if you're that
smart and you got this IQ, why do you
want to every day repeating
with your grain to get off here and get
a life? Well, actually like um like you
can't even like you can't even create
your own content.
You can't even create your own content.
You have to bounce off other people's content.
That's another thing.
Sad people in this community, sad sad
losers on this community.
So, you got all this money. You sat on
YouTube every day self-reflected. Can
you explain it to me, please? It
actually make a good uh it would make a
good um it' make a good live stream if
somebody could come up there. You got
licks there. Anyone's welcome to join.
You got a lot to say behind your face
about people being skinn and everyone
else is apparently what you are. So, you
know, come here.
Any of these people, Clint, all of these
people come, come in.
They're fat, ugly people that ain't got
no life, bro. So obvious,
they make it so obvious,
you know? It couldn't be any more obvious,
right? If if if if they tried, you know,
same self. I just don't understand with
people that's got all this money
and and this life and
and to be honest it's not even is about
money as well but it's not really
because they come on here right? Yeah.
And to be honest with you if they weren't disabled
why don't they get off and get a life?
This is this ain't even me hating. This
ain't me raging. This is me asking.
I want the answers and I'm I'm more than
happy to listen to the answers. You
people got all this money.
Everyone else is scared. So why are you
on here every day hating? Why don't you
get off and get a life?
Is what I'm saying wrong or what? I just Yeah. Oh
yeah. And this guy trying to put a nude
up. Why are you trying to put a nude up, bro?
trying to put a nude up. No, come on.
You said about how people need to prove
this to you. People need to prove that
to you and you're trying to put a nude
up. Put your camera on and show your
face and we'll see the M cuz the M ain't
me. No, no, no. The mon is definitely
you people, you haters. The M is
definitely definitely definitely not me.
And I'm more than happy to prove that if
you turn your camera on and you show
your face. You're another one that wrote
on your channel you wanted receipt. You
wanted people to show this. You wanted
the people to show that. I'll show you
it once you show your face and you show
everybody that you're not the mun all
along. But you can't do that because you
are the m.
And that's why you people do this every
single day. You're m lives
hating on people that are younger,
better looking than you, got more family
than you, and sit there and say that
ain't the case. But what what do you do
with your life? Do we need to prove
again that you're on here typing away
every day? Can I prove it again if you
want me to
tell us why Shaunie lost her children? I
will I will answer all of your
questions. Uh once you put your camera
on and you show us your face, I will
show you receipts. I will show you
money. Um I can show you my online
banking. Not a problem at all. You said
that you wanted to see things. Sure.
Show your face. Put your camera on and
show your face and stop trying to porn bomb.
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Go on.
Bringing up kids again. Nons. Tell us
why you people on YouTube every day
self-reflecting your ugliness and your skddness.
Tell us that. Tell us that and then show
your face and then come on here.
You are the m. You don't answer mas. You
are the m to call me a m, bro. I'm
better looking than you. I've had more
women than you. Don't make me put up all
the videos again of all the women that
I've been with and make you jelly again.
Bro, it's pretty sad when you're saying
that I'm a M when a M has had better
looking women than you and you can't
show your face. Take the L, bro. Take
the L all day long. You are the M. And
I'm willing to prove it. I'm willing to
prove that you are a M once you put your
camera on and you show your fat, ugly, disabled face.
But you can't do it cuz you're ugly.
Just like me. If I was to go on a
community right now and say, "This black
guy is ugly. This white guy is ugly. I
would have no problem showing my face. I
You can't cuz you're ugly. And that is
the most uh normal way to put it with
you little mongos. You're ugly fat
people that are not wanted by no one.
And that's why you're on here every day.
Think about it. You Why can't you people
take one day off for YouTube?
Why can't you people take one day off of
YouTube if you've got all of this money?
I I want to know. I want to know. I want
Sure. Yeah. Yeah. You keep telling
yourself that. Anyways, we're not we're
not self-reflecting on other people.
We're talking about you fat ugly people
that can't get off of YouTube.
We're We're literally talking about you
fat ugly. Bro, you didn't have plans.
Stop talking [ __ ] Stop the clap. You
didn't have plans. Okay, fair enough.
So, where's your relationship?
Why aren't you in a relationship?
Where's your girlfriend? Shouldn't
Shouldn't you be using you as an
example? Exactly. In the private chat,
because you've never had a girlfriend
because you're ugly. That's why you have
to talk about other people. You've never
had sex. You've never had a girlfriend.
You ain't got no money. You're just an
ugly little bully victim. Yeah, bro.
You've been coming on YouTube bullying
me for seven years. But if I was being
bullied for seven years,
bro, 28 and never had a relationship.
Bro, you're 48 and you've never had a relationship.
And you've never had a girlfriend and
you've never had sex. I've had women.
I've been with women.
You know what I'm saying? Bro, you're 48
and you've never had a girlfriend.
Again, this is this is part of your
disabilities. So, why don't you join the hangouts?
Stop projecting. You're in your 40s and
you've never had a girlfriend. What do
you mean you've never heard that before?
You've never been seen with one woman.
And you know what? I love that. Yeah.
You're saying about being bullied for
seven years. I assure you, you clowns
don't do anything but bully yourselves.
All you people do is bully yourselves.
Again, you're getting yourselves mixed
up. Who's not the ones that are on
YouTube every day, middle-aged, ugly,
nobody? That's the definition of being
bullied. No matter how many times you
want to come on the internet and try and
say that you're not, that's the
definition of a bully victim. Someone
that has to come on the internet every
day, no money, no girlfriend like you,
never been seen with women. That's the
definition of being bullied. Doesn't
matter how many times you come on the
internet and you try to talk about what
other people have and what other people
don't have, you're talking about yourself.
You're in your 40s, no girlfriend, never
been with a woman. Look at your own
life. [ __ ] a 28-year-old. The
28-year-old has hope.
The 28-year-old has hope. the
40-year-old virgin like you don't. The
28-year-old has hope. The 40-year-old
bully victim's life is over. And that's
why you people do what you do.
You're in your 40s. Still a virgin. No
girlfriend. Look at you. Look in the
mirror. Like, I know your skin. I know.
Listen, bro. I know you people in here
are skin. I know you Kevin. Listen. You
didn't even come to London when I came
to your city. Don't get me started on
you again, Mr. Autism. Listen, Kevin.
Kevin. Kevin. Kevin, if you was really a
man, you would have came to London, but
you didn't. Yeah. One second, ghost, and
I'll answer you in a minute. Shut the
cat. I went to Liverpool. LT went to
Liverpool. You made excuses both times.
Two times you made excuses not to come
out. Yeah. If you was a man, you would
have come to London the next day, bro.
The only one that shot it is yourself,
you [ __ ] Mong. Cuz why haven't why
you been to London? This is what I mean.
There's no talking to these autistic
people. There's no talking to these
bongos. There's no talking to these
disabled people because you become like
them. The more you, you know, interact
with disabled people, the more you
become like one of them like this Kevin
Murphy. No one's shut it. I went to your
city and you didn't come out, you little
mong, you little spaz. I went to your I
went to your city, you little spaz, and
you didn't show up when I went to
Liverpool. Don't make me put the video
back up. You [ __ ] scout spasticated
[ __ ] This is what I mean with you
people. You're [ __ ] Mongs. This is
what I mean. Your Mongs. This is why no
one bothers coming on here anymore.
Kevin, I went to your city.
Listen, I went to your city.
Listen, Kevin, I went to your city and
you didn't come out. And then they want
And then they wonder why people don't
waste their time with them anymore, you know?
You know? Yeah. Okay. Whatever, bro. I'm
a coward. Okay, good for you, man.
>> Yeah. Yeah, I'm a coward. Whatever.
>> So, again, Kevin, I've already gone to
Liverpool. This is what I mean. There's
no There's no getting through to these
disabled people. They're not worth it.
This is why I don't come on anymore.
This is exactly why I don't entertain
these clowns anymore, bro. There's no
point with them. They're just fat, ugly,
jealous losers that ain't got nothing in
their lives, repeating the same old
[ __ ] ignoring everything. This is what
I mean with these people.
This is what I mean with these people,
bro. There's not They're not even worth
it, bro. They're not even worth it, these people.
So, yeah. They're just fat, ugly life
losers living their worst life. Just
allow them, bro. Like, every every time
these people wake up, Yeah. out of bed. Yeah,
bro. I don't I don't come on every day.
I've I've gone off of YouTube for weeks.
You people on YouTube every day, bro.
Repeating calling yourself skin. I've
seen it with my own eyes. Coming on here
every day, calling yourselves autistic,
putting yourselves down, but then you
wonder why the community is dead. You
name me one person on earth here that
wants to come on here and sit on here
looking at people bully themselves,
putting themselves down, calling
themselves autistic, calling themselves manta.
People putting themselves down, you
know, cuz that's what you do. You talk
about yourself. You put yourselves down.
That's why you can't. Okay, Kevin.
Kevin, Kevin. Okay, join the hangouts
then. Okay, Kevin, join the hangouts.
Okay. Okay, join. Right, join the hangouts.
My pissed himself again. No one pissed
himself at all, mate. A bit of piss went
on me when I when I went for a piss
again. Making up stuff again. This is
what I mean with you little clowns. This
is what I mean. You little [ __ ]
aren't worth it. You little disabled
little clowns ain't got no life. Just
ain't worth it. This is why people don't
bother with you people anymore, bro.
People don't bother with you disabled
failures. You're something to learn by,
bro. Not to interact with. You're
something to learn by, not interact
with. And that's it. 40year-old virgins
that ain't got nothing in their lives.
There's something to You're something to
learn from. So, you're you're not
actually pointless coming on here every day.
Kevin, again, I'll repeat myself for the
last time. I've gone to Liverpool and
you didn't come out, Mr. [ __ ] Pants. I
traveled to your city and you didn't
come out. That's the last time I'm
saying that. Shut up. And so did London
Taylor and I'm not even trying to bring
him involved. But yeah, listen, I
wouldn't, bro. I've already gone to
Liverpool to see Oh, okay. I'm not going
around in cir. You're [ __ ] disabled.
There's no point with these disabled
people. All right, listen, Frank. Just
just just leave them, bro. Just leave
them. Just leave them, bro. They're
They're just disabled.
Just leave them, bro. Just leave them.
They're never going to take They're
never going to admit L's and [ __ ] Just
just just leave it, bro. With these
people, bro. Honestly, just leave it, man.
Yeah. Cockney or soft. Yeah. Yeah. Good.
Cook up. Yeah. Whatever. Just leave
these people, bro. Just leave them.
Just leave them, Dad. Stop wasting your
time with them.
How does it feel that you're going to be
a lonely monster for Christmas?
How does it feel? Yeah. The UK biggest
monster that you're going to be a loner
for Christmas with no family. You can't
say the same about me.
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Okay. Anyways, we're
moving on from these plastic. And this
this is why I come off of here, Mr. B.
This is why you don't see me for like
weeks and days because there's no point
with these jealous fat ugly people.
They're not worth nothing.
They're just fat, ugly, disabled people.
I'm sure you've noticed that as well
when you come off of here. Yeah, there's
there's no point with them. They're just
disabled, bitter little old people.
Don't waste your life on them, bro. I'm
I'm gone after tomorrow. Anyways, bro,
after today, now I'm gone after today.
It's the same atmosphere. This is why
you don't you know when you don't see me
on here, bro. This is why because it's
the same autistic atmosphere by old ugly
people. It's a It's a waste of
everyone's time. Literally, it is. It
literally is that.
Yeah. It's a waste of everyone's time, bro.
Uh from today. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. I'm
scared, bro. Yeah. Yep. Yep. Scared.
Whatever you say. Yeah.
With your sister. That's what what Bro,
you don't have a girlfriend.
Yeah. Nobody wants a bun. That's why
you're alone. That's why you're in your
40s and you ain't got a girlfriend. Cuz
no one wants you. You are the bunter. I
can assure you, mate. Yeah, I'm talking
to the private chat right now. A
28-year-old that's better looking than
you is not a bunter. Nowhere near as
much as a bunter as you. Where's your
girlfriend? You sexist little virgin. I
notice every time I say these stuff
about these people, I hit a nerve. Bro,
you're sat there with no family, no
girlfriend. Don't talk about me, bro.
Don't talk about me, you little sad
logo. Where's your girlfriend? Why don't
you come on here right now and show us
your girlfriend, lad?
Why don't you come on here right now and
show us your girlfriend, you little
bully victim. You little 40-year-old
virgin trying to talk about a [ __ ]
28-year-old lad. Yeah,
bro. They don't online bully. They bully
themselves. That's why that's why I'm
not banning any of them because they
just make a fool of themselves.
They're not doing anything but
self-projecting. They're bullying
themselves. That's why I'm not banning
them. If if if they were bullying me,
I'd be banning them. I'm leaving them
because they're bullying themselves.
They're making a fool of themselves.
That's why I'm not banning them. They're bullying themselves.
Yeah, I know what they're doing. They're
bullying themselves. That's why I keep
coming back for more because everything
that they say is just the same repeating
[ __ ] Same repeating bully victim [ __ ]
because that's what they are, bully
victims. They're bullying themselves.
That's why I'm not banning them. We all
know that these people behind these
accounts are fat, ugly 40s, bully
victims. I'm not banning them. I'm not
banning them, bro. I'm not banning them.
They're fat, ugly losers. They can type
what they want. They're only bullying
themselves. They're only hurting
So, I don't give a [ __ ]
They're not They're not working me up,
bro. Bro, they're not They're not
They're not They're not getting me
They're getting all worked up. They're
the ones that are typing. You are the
ones that keep typing to me. I'm not
getting worked up. I'm not banning
people. You're typing getting yourselves worked up.
You fat, ugly bully victims. You're
getting yourselves all worked up. You
keep [ __ ] typing to me. So, you're
getting worked up reacting to me.
You're getting all worked up. That's a
lot of typing. You keep typing, isn't
it? Simple, bro.
Mate, you don't need to help.
These people just keep bullying
themselves. You need to help them.
They need to stop coming on here keep
bullying themselves. You need to stop
them bullying themselves. It's a serious serious thing
because we all know behind these
accounts they're fat ugly bongos and
that's why they can't show their faces.
They've always been bullied. They're
bullied in real life. Not just the
internet, just you know, real life. You
don't need to help me. I'm better than
these people. I'm younger. I'm better
looking. They can type what they want.
No one's bothered. That's why I'm not buying them.
Bro, they don't do anything to my mental
health. I'm still here. I'm still here
laughing at them. They're not doing
anything to my mental health. I'm
laughing at these fat ugly losers. I'm
laughing at them. They can keep doing
what they're doing. They're only hurting
themselves cuz everything everything
that they say is just about their own
lives. So, they're only [ __ ] themselves.
No. Yeah. They're bullying themselves.
Yeah. Yeah. They're bullying themselves.
Yeah. Yeah, they're only bullying
themselves. They're not bullying me. Not
mocking me. I'm still here. If they were
bullying me, I wouldn't be here. A kid
that gets bullied in school. I'm coming
because you don't bully people. I'm
laughing at you people bullying
yourselves. That's why I'm here. I'm
loving it. If I was getting bullied, I
would end the live stream right now. I'm
laughing at you people typing and
bullying yourselves. That's why I'm
still here because you're clowns.
Because we all know that you're fat,
ugly, lonely people. Loners. I'm not
ending the live stream. I can take it. I
know that none of you people can come on
the hangouts and show your face.
I literally know that none of you people
can come in and show your faces cuz
you're ugly. Cuz you're ugly, lifeless,
skin losers. That's exactly what you
are. Anyways, the link's up there. Is
anyone going to join or what?
But I mean the link is up there, lad.
You know that's it,
Joe. Okay, about my word means nothing.
So does your boyfriend's word mean
nothing. O, you fat northern [ __ ] So
does your boyfriend's word mean nothing.
When he said that he was going to go on
Jaden's door and he never. When he said
that he owns property and he doesn't.
Said that he was going to come and meet
someone in England and he never. So does
your boyfriend's word means nothing.
Stop sucking dick, you little biased
[ __ ] Yeah, so does your boyfriend's
word mean nothing, you dicks sucking
northern [ __ ] Sorry about that one. I
had to react to that one. Sorry, this
guy's spamming it. Listen, bro. Listen,
listen, listen. No, just like your
boyfriend's word means nothing. Lord J,
the horrible father. His word doesn't
mean anything. His word means even less
than mine. So, and that's No, it's not
bullying, bro. Yeah, they're bullying.
They're bullying themselves. I'm not
blocking them because they're not
bullying. They're showing themselves up.
These 40-year-old loners are showing
themselves up. I don't need to block
them. I don't need to because they're
bullying themselves. So, I'm going to
leave them to it.
They're bullying themselves. Yeah. I'm
not blocking because it's not affect
it's not affecting me. 40year-old losers
don't affect me. I put the link up, no
one's joining. Like, okay, put it this
way. You've got the link up. No one's
coming in and saying anything
because you're 40y old skeptics. You
don't bother no one. This is why I keep
coming on here because you don't bother
no one. You're unbothering me. This is
why I keep coming on here because you
don't bother me. Unlike a bullied kid
would would not go to school, snitch on
the teacher. You're not bothering me.
This is why I'm still coming on here
talking about what you people do because
you're not bothering me. This is what I'm saying.
You disabled ugly people don't bother no
one. You bully yourselves. You're
unbothering anyone. You do not bother no
one. I don't know how many times I have
to keep saying this. Like think about
it, bro. Listen, listen. Someone comes
on this community. Yeah. How old are
they? 19, 20. Yeah.
And say a load of people go on them and
you keep going on them every day.
Effective. Second day effective. burn
affected. Same old, same old, same old,
same old. But you do realize after a
while, you know, when we've heard the
same thing over and over and over again,
it's boring. What do you have to say?
Skin. Use your skin. Ugly. You people
ugly. Bully victims. You people bully
victims. You've been saying the same
[ __ ] for seven years. So come back when
you actually think of new things to say
that's not about yourself. And maybe
they might actually start hurting
people. If you actually started saying
new things that don't apply to your own
life, then maybe you could actually
bully someone and you could actually uh
achieve your uh achieve your goal. But
all we see here is just the same
40-year-old spastics repeating
themselves, which why we remain unbothered.
Not ending the live stream. I'll put the
link up again.
What the [ __ ] does this mean, bro?
Anyways, we're ignoring these stupid comments now.
These little self-protecting comments.
So, is no one going to join the hangouts
then or what? I'll put the link up.
[ __ ] stupid [ __ ]
What does that word mean? I don't know
how that works.
That's weird, lad.
Anyways, I'm not reacting to these
little clowns anymore. Anyways,
if anyone wants to talk, the link's up.
Yeah, if anyone wants to join.
Oh yeah, if anyone wants to join and
talk, you're more than uh welcome to.
Isn't Yeah, Joe is Wasn't Wasn't LJ
supposed to go on Jaden's door? [ __ ] sucker.
But like like I said, I don't mind it,
Joe. Like I understand it now. You know,
you're both fat. You're both ugly.
That's why you suck each other's dicks.
I don't have no problem with you being
biased no more.
I'm a fantasist.
You're not I you fat ugly people are not
worth the time. I'm off I'm off here
after tomorrow as well again.
And I won't be on your channel again
reacting to you because I realize you
fat ugly people ain't worth the time.
Simple as that. You're not even worth it.
I considered going out. I'm going out
drinking every week now
just to um not be on air. That's even
better than this. You fat ugly people
ain't worth the time. Seriously
caused him [ __ ] brain damage. Oh, you
cause you cause brain damage. [ __ ] idiots.
Hopefully in 2026 you people will get
off of YouTube and get a life. today. We
could only hope.
We would only hope, bro, that you know.
Yeah, of course he is, bro. He's been
doing it for years. Good for him.
They're sad cases. I don't go on their
channels, bro. They're wasting their
life on me cuz they hate me, bro. Let
them crack on. Where's my remote? [ __ ]
I don't care about these little clowns.
I'm off tomorrow. Anyways,
that's what these That's what their uh
uh New Year's resolution should be. Get
off of YouTube and get a life. How many
of them do you reckon could do it? Not many.
Not many. Not many at all, mate.
I can't even I don't know, bro. Why
don't they just come out with new
things? It's always just the same
self-reflecting repeating with these people. Yeah,
these people need to get a life, bro.
Need to get a job and get some money, bro. Seriously,
they really do.
They really, really, really do. These people
ain't got nothing in their lives, bro.
But again, it is an autistic community.
So, I mean, what what what do you expect
in it? Autistic community.
You either leave the community. Yeah. Or
you do videos
and you just like disable the uh comments.
I was thinking of doing traveling videos
again just to wind these people up to a
breach. Just do videos and just like ban
the comments and [ __ ]
Like disable the comments and likes and
dislikes and [ __ ] Just do like madness.
You could do something like that
if you wanted to stay on it. You could
just like post content and just not go
live. That would kill him even more
because there's nothing they'd be able
to do about it.
We're thinking of doing that. You know,
it's it's a good idea, you know,
because then they can't comment and it
will be killing them even more that
you've got a life and they they're sat
on YouTube every day doing nothing and
just don't go live or maybe go live like
once a month and they can't comment. So
all they're going to do is just put on
your channel where you've got a better
life than them if they want to post your content.
I mean, I'm thinking about it, bro. Yeah.
Don't tell them anything about women.
or like anything about anything. Just
show like hotels, food. They'll be
[ __ ] bro. What could they really do?
They'd be [ __ ] then, wouldn't they?
on that Red Star. Yeah, I don't go on
that Red Star channel. Triple H. I don't
go on it.
The same loser. He's been doing it for
years. Yeah, that loser's been doing it
for years, bro.
Yeah, we know what they look like. It
doesn't matter. We know what these
people look like. That's why they do
what they do. Look at Jamie Thompson.
stalker. Fat ugly stalker
ain't got a life. Yeah, we know what
they look like, man.
That's why they do all of this. Cuz
you're better looking than them. You're
younger than them.
Just like what Ronald Pump said, younger
than them, better look. No, he said
younger, better life.
Younger, better life, and more money and
it kills them.
I might get a tattoo of that, you know.
I might actually get a tattoo of that.
Uh, buy or pump. Yeah, I might get a
tattoo of that cuz truer words would
never spoken. Truer words have never been spoken.
No, no, no, Joe. Don't talk about Triple
H. Why don't you join and talk some
sense into me? Leave Triple H the poor
[ __ ] out of it. Leave Triple H the
poor [ __ ] He's just had his tea. Why
don't you come in and talk sense to me?
Why don't you come in and talk sense to me?
Leave Leave Triple H alone,
[ __ ] He's just having his tea.
Well, I just had his tea. We want you to
talk some sense. Come on. You make all
of these community posts, these videos.
Why don't you come in and talk? And you
know what? You don't even have to show
your face. I just want you to talk. Come
on. You're not scared, are you?
Remember, my word means nothing. What
are you scared of? What are you scared
of? Are you scared of your own shadow?
Are you scared of your own voice? What
are you scared of? Come on.
Come on. Join the hangouts and then you
can try and talk and then you can try
and talk some sense. What? Don't ask
Triple H what to do. No, no, no. Come in
the hangout to talk sense. You said link
for Triple H. No, I'm going to I'm going
to put the link for you. I'm putting the
I'm getting a tattoo by the way.
Better looking, better life, and more
money than them. And it kills them. I'm
getting a tattoo
by Ronald Pump.
Yeah. Why are you telling Why are you
telling Triple H to join the link? Why
don't you join the link?
Leave Triple H alone. Maybe he doesn't
want to join. Why? Everyone knows what
Triple H sounds like. Let's hear you.
Let's hear you. You'd have a similar accent.
You have a similar accent. No.
Yeah, I'm going to get that tattoo. Yeah.
So, you're trying to get So, you're
trying to get him on, but you won't even join. Really?
This is mad.
Come on. There you go. There's link. Join him.
Uh Jamie Thompson.
He's the worst looking and he's the most obsessed.
Yeah, Jamie Thompson obsessed with me.
Won't leave me alone. But it just goes
back to what Ronald Pump said, isn't it?
Better looking, better life, more money
than them. It's the truth, isn't it?
That was facts. Like sometimes I'm
arguing with these people and I'm
thinking, "Bro, remember what Ronald
Pump said, you know? Remember what
Ronald Pump said a year and a half ago.
No, that Jamie Thompson is the worst
looking. They're all [ __ ] ugly." So,
you know. No, that Jamie Thompson is
really, really ugly, bro. Peter Griffin,
come on. The link's there. Come on,
join. Joseph Fra, what are you scared
of? You don't need uh Triple H fighting
your battles, do you? You know,
I think I'm going to start doing this.
I'm just going to start doing content
videos and disabling the comments.
That's what I'm going to do. Disable the
comments and the likes and wind these
people up. Going to do something New Year's Eve.
I'm going to start winding these people
up. I think
they don't want to join the hangouts.
They don't want to talk. They don't want
to meet you. So, yeah.
Oh, well, Triple H is scared of me as well.
Yeah, Triple H is scared of me as well.
So, if I called if I went to if I went
up north and I called you out, Joseph
Ra, would you say any of this stuff to my face?
Would you say any of this stuff to my
face? Oh, you're gonna be a coward.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no. Stop deflecting.
No, no, no, no, no. This is nothing to
do with ghosting. This is me. This is
you joining the link. Come on.
Yeah, I think I'm going to do this. Uh,
what I said I was going to do to be honest. Yeah,
you're just going to watch content videos
and you won't be able to do anything about it.
Joseph Farra is is trying to get Triple
H to join the hangouts, but Joseph Far
won't join the hangouts.
You're lucky I didn't You're lucky I
gave you all of this attention to be
honest. You don't You won't even join a hangout.
You're that scared you won't even join a hangout.
Yet you want to be a hater every day.
You want to be an undercover hater, but
you don't want to join.
You you you It would be embarrassed to
be associated with anyone like me,
bro. Come on now. Have you seen yourself?
Have you seen your [ __ ] self?
That's ridiculous, man. Come on. Yeah. Boring.
So many cowards on this community, bro.
To be honest, you shouldn't even
entertain anyone that don't even [ __ ]
join the box. Jo,
you know, these people are not even
worth it on this community, bro.
Seriously, they're really really not [ __ ] idiot.
Uh, you people need to Okay, can you
people just say that in 2026 you're
going to think of some new things to say?
I'll be live on Christmas, by the way,
but I'll be walking away from the phone
and I better not see any of you people
on here cuz I will go [ __ ] mad.
These people are called Christmas projectors.
That's that time of year where they're
going to be at Christmas, no family, no nothing.
I don't know, bro. It's weird. This
community is so weird.
It We're not talking about money. We're
talking about you talking. Why? Why you
Why are you not talking? Are you scared?
Why are you scared to join the hangouts and talk?
[ __ ] idiot. £1,200
to last a month is a is poverty. By the way, people
Jesus Christ. How am I ever going to live?
I think I have about £1,500. How am I
going to live with £1,500 a month? What
am I going to do?
What am I going to do? £1,500 a month?
What? How am I going to live?
I probably have to start going to the
[ __ ] food banks. How am I going to live, bro?
[snorts] Uh, how am I going to live off that?
Jesus Christ. How am I ever going to
live off that? £1,500 left. Jesus
Christ. How the [ __ ] am I going to live off 1,500?
How am I going to live off £1,500, bro? Jesus Christ.
Jesus Christ. How am I going to live off that?
I have to start going to food banks.
I think you realize how stupid you sound now.
[ __ ] idiot. [ __ ] idiot, man. Yeah,
he was on earlier,
bro. Listen, listen, listen, listen. Oh
my god. This is This is what I mean.
They're giving me a headache again.
These these idiots, right? You people
have known where people live for years
and you ain't done anything. Let's not
talk about people being cowards.
Yeah. Like you people know where people
are and you don't do anything. Let's not
talk about cowards.
Let's not talk about cowards. Come on.
Yeah. I can't progress in life. Yeah. I
need a pension like you that I can touch
when I'm like when I'm like 80. Yeah.
Yeah. You can't progress in life with
it. Well, you can if you met someone and
you had a child. I mean, define
progress. I mean, you could easily meet
someone, have a child, and get a house.
Not easily, but like it could happen as
easy as that if it ever was to happen.
But you get what I mean? So, what what
what do you mean? You get house. Well,
define progress. I don't know what you
mean by progress. Elaborate what you
mean by that. You know,
do you know what, bro? You You know
what? Do you know the way I think about
you people? Yeah. is that
you people know where people live and
you don't do anything and you're still typing,
mate. If like I've said many times, I'm
not repeating myself. If I knew where
any of these people lived, Red Star all,
I wouldn't be typing. You are keep
typing. So, at the end of the day, like
just stop it now. Like, you're still typing.
You're still typing.
What do you mean? wanted ambition.
I mean, he Yeah, he'll be on YouTube.
Like I said, I'm going to go live on
YouTube and and go to the I'm going to
go for a walk and come back and come
back to the phone and see who's on here. You know,
I've been to Amsterdam, Joseph. You've
never been to Amsterdam?
I might be going to France New Year's
Eve. You don't know where I'm going to end up.
Yeah, it doesn't matter. Worry about
your own life. What is it with you
people? Why don't you just worry about
your own lives? This is what makes me
think deep down you hate your own lives.
Why you care about [ __ ] other people?
It's weird, isn't it? It's that's like
me going on going to saying, "Oh, you're
on £300 a month. That's poverty. I'm
better than you. I think these people
hate their own lives. Like Joseph Farra.
I I think that these people hate their
own lives. Insecure about their own
So what's wrong with having a baby, Joseph?
You can't live on 5,500 pound
for the month apparently. Oh,
to be honest, the only way you can get
quick big money is [ __ ] gambling. I'm
not doing that [ __ ] anymore. So, come to
think of it, that's where I got most of
the money from last time, but I'm not
doing it. There's no way I could be
doing that now, mate. Oh, [ __ ] that.
Doesn't matter how much money I had.
Cuz if I didn't stop, I think I would
have just ended up seriously hurting
someone. So that's why I had to stop, you know?
Yeah. What's wrong with having a baby?
Yeah. What's wrong with having a Yeah,
because by by progress, you're probably
talking about living by yourself, having
your own place. That's why I mentioned
that because you're probably thinking,
"Oh, well, how are you going to get your
own place?" And t
I mean I might move to Thailand and and
and work as an English teacher like what
Ant-Man does. Then what?
[ __ ] idiot, man.
>> You really are a clown. Joseph Harrah.
Really, really, really are a [ __ ]
clown. You got a stupid name as well,
like thing you said.
Oh, you're another little keyboard
warrior. Flash, I see you're another one
that's obsessed with me. You made a new
account. Oh, hey.
How's it like calling yourself a skint
every day? Are you going to have the
balls to join the hangouts?
Oh, I see you. You're on it every day as well.
Strange, isn't it? People that's got all
this money that ain't a m sat on YouTube
every day hating.
Makes you wonder, doesn't it? It makes
me seriously wonder about these people,
though. It really does. It really does.
You got all this money. You're not
skinn. You're way better looking than
me, but you're on it every day hating. [snorts]
That smells like fishy vagina to me.
Something's not right there, mate.
Something is seriously seriously
seriously seriously not right there, bro.
that these people can spend all of this
time when they're hating every day.
That in itself shows their life is worse
than anyone else's that they're talking about.
They won't hire me. What's the ne That's
another thing with you this community.
Why do you bring negativity as well
about they won't hire me? So much
negativity on this community, you know?
I just think honestly I think this
community is just a fat is a bunch of
fat ugly people that failed at
everything in life trying to bring other people down.
That's what I think it is.
I don't know about anyone. I I generally
think it's people that have failed at
everything. They're at their last legs
in life. They got no hope. So they just
come on here every day sad with their lives.
I think that's why they do this, you
know, bro. I think I genuinely think
that's why they do it.
And you being the prime you being their
prime target, younger, better looking,
free to do what you want, nice home,
nice mother. It does really, really,
really, really, really make you wonder
with these people, doesn't it?
Smells fishy to me, mate. Smells fishy to me.
And none of them will join the hangouts either. madness, bro.
>> Like I said, your best off, anyone who's
watching this on this community, right,
is not going live and doing content and
disabling the likes and and the comments.
Just get out just get at them that way.
Just get at them that way,
you know? They're never going to meet
you. They're never going to join your
[ __ ] So, just get on them that way. So
don't show money to them because that's self-reflecting.
But you know, equally just just just
show them a life that they'll never live.
So that's that's your best way. You know
what I'm doing anyways from now on. So yeah, you know,
these people can't go out. They can't
approach women. They can't afford
hotels. They can't do anything.
They're just sad numpties. Moronic numpties.
Like what my mom said. Yeah,
change the content up. I reckon with these clowns. Oh, [ __ ]
Oh, my back is [ __ ] bro.
That hurt there.
So, yeah, that's what they do. Anyways,
yeah, I got three pieces of chicken and chips triple.
I'm going out tomorrow to a restaurant
and getting another drink. So, that's
why I went for the chicken today. I was
going to get Turkish today, but I
thought I'll just wait until tomorrow.
You're on it hard, bro.
Oh, you're right. Oh, you're wearing
your little jumper, mama.
What? Did you wear your Uggs? Oh. >> Oh.
>> Oh gosh. Did you have a fun day?
How How is it? Oh yeah.
Did you eat?
>> No good. Yeah.
>> Oh god.
>> Would you say you'll punch the [ __ ] out
of her? Um, [laughter]
>> you need to calm down, mama.
>> You need to calm down, mama. You going
You're very violent today.
>> What did you say? You're not the cut out. Who?
>> You have another.
>> But who am I going to have?
>> Why not? I want to join in.
I don't I want to feel I don't want to
feel left out. I want I want to follow
the crowd, you know.
But what could Charlie do, Mom? The size
of her, please.
What if she gets seriously hurt? Yeah.
>> Yeah. But what if you get hurt, Ma?
Yeah, but how do you know? Yeah, but how
do you know? Yeah, but how do you know
you could beat Stav though?
Yeah, but you you could. Yeah, but you
couldn't. Yeah, but do you remember the
time do you remember when we had problems?
>> But you can't beat your
>> Yeah, but do you remember? Yeah, but you
remember before in the old house when I
come up to you, you don't think you
could beat me though, is it? But that
Yeah, but what I'm saying Yeah. But what
I'm saying is maybe Stab could beat me.
You don't know people that are fat like that, Mom.
You don't know though, is it? I've been
back in the But you're getting a bit
older now. Ma
ma is very violent.
A woman could beat me up. You never know.
Oh, my back is [ __ ] bro.
I think it's that diet, you know, the
fried chicken and chips. Yeah. >> Yeah.
I'm having Turkish tomorrow. Ma,
I'm going for a big day out tomorrow.
That's why I had I had fried chicken of
Turkish tomorrow. I want to wait for
tomorrow so I enjoy it more. It's nice
that restaurant. Yeah.
Yeah. I have the shift.
Not really keen on the don. Oh gosh. Gosh.
>> All right. I think Monty I think Monty
went I think Monty went court today
>> well he hasn't returned.
>> Yeah. What could that mean? [laughter]
>> Like racism and stuff.
>> But he's not we haven't heard from him all day.
>> Oh, ages ago. What? It was
You know, he would go live, but he
doesn't go live. He hasn't gone live and
he was live yesterday and it's all stopped.
>> So what? He could have got a custodial sentence.
>> No, but you know what these [ __ ] are
like, mate? They'll [ __ ] make an
example out of someone.
>> I think he was just saying it. See what I mean? [laughter]
>> They do though, don't they? They do. Politician. >> Oh,
back in his day. He made 17. >> Yeah.
>> He made
remarks against Jewish people. M
>> he used to go up to one
go up to him and go
the sound of gas.
>> That's what they used to do to them. >> Yeah.
>> But anyway, these guys have come up now
and they can still deny it. Oh, so there
is a big hype about racism at the minute.
>> Yeah. You you said you don't know how I
got away with all that [ __ ] on YouTube
like years ago. Is it?
>> No, but do you remember like years ago?
>> But you know last year? Yeah. Last year
I was saying some mad mad mad mad stuff
last year. Do you remember? And they
never came. I think they put a Merlin on
me. I think they put a Merlin on me in it.
>> Yeah. Like where they don't but they
just know that it's just YouTube is it?
Because you remember last year, I'm
talking about last year, bro. I thought
they were coming. They didn't, did they?
>> I know. I know. >> Yeah.
>> The only thing The only thing I like the
police getting is them phone snatchers.
And they are cracking down on them now.
They've got like motorbike They've got
like police motorbikes. They should
because they're [ __ ] They're cowards.
They don't give people the chance to
like catch them. That's what that's my
problem with them. Cuz once they snatch
it, you're not you're not ch you're not
catching a [ __ ] uh moped, you know? Yeah.
It happens a lot in Oxford Street. You
need That's one place you need to be
careful of. You like my hair, mama?
We're going to be seeing the snowman and [ __ ]
>> Oh, what? Jack Frost.
Okay. Is there going to be snow this
year? Ma, is there going to be snow this
year? I want to build a snowman. I do.
I want I want to throw a snowball at you, ma.
I'll throw a snowball at you. Oh,
I like milk with my cornflakes. [snorts] What?
Little red [ __ ] with no B money in it.
Steven with [ __ ] No. Oh.
Oh, you know Eminem died.
I heard about when I woke up.
Yeah, he's dead. Overdose.
I'm making it up. [laughter]
Oh, you see how convincing I am. Triple
H. Yeah, he died.
He had an overdose.
Did I get something to drink? Uh, I got a cola.
Hey, I got a Coca-Cola for the co-op, if
you must know. [snorts] Ah,
Steven Howard. So, what should I do New
Year's Eve? I need some suggestions.
Should I stay in London? Should I stay
in Should I go Nottingham? Should I go
to Wales? Should I go to France? Should
I go here? Or should I go there? Or
should I go here? Or should I go there?
Or should I do that? I don't know what
to do. I might just stay in London. I'm
not sure. I'm not sure what I'm doing. Gosh,
New Year's Eve is over pri I don't know
what I'm doing, bro. It's hard. And
don't tell me I've got time cuz I need
to start planning this [ __ ] now.
I need to really start planning this
[ __ ] now, bro.
I can go to France, but then I was
thinking just going France in March.
It's better, you know.
I might be able to find a new mama in France.
Blackpool Laney. No, lady won't go to
Blackpool. You silly goose.
No, she won't go to Blackpool.
She won't go Blackpool, mate.
Oh, [ __ ] No.
Why did [ __ ] nonsex go to Amsterdam?
Why was the first place he went to
Amsterdam? Steven Howard.
That's the first place he went to was
Amsterdam. That's weird, isn't it? Why
did he go there?
I went to Amsterdam.
Why did he go to Amsterdam? That's the
first place I went.
Why did he go there as well?
Maybe. What? It's weird, ain't it?
Copying me, is it?
But he used to say that he hated people
that copy and people that don't have a
mind of their own. That's what he used
to say. He doesn't like people that copy
people and stuff.
That's what he used to say.
They got like no substance and stuff.
But all all he's done so far is prove
that he copies
copies copies the crowd
likes to follow the crowd.
Why though? It's just that's just boring.
Who wants to who who why would somebody
want to copy? You know,
I never said shovel car was attractive
because I've got a mind of my own. I
never ever followed a trend.
Never ever ever follow the crowd.
Hey, you're right.
How can I help you?
How can I help you? Black Blackpool boys,
what can I do for you this evening? [snorts]
But no, seriously, man. Like, [gasps]
have I popped my cherry? Nah, never.
No, I'm a virgin.
Do you know what it is with you people
on here yet? We We don't get triggered
by your comments, but it's just so stupid.
That's why we say that it's repeating
because the the comments are so stupid.
That's why they don't even get ignored
because they're such stupid
self-reflecting comments. It doesn't
even get people mad. It's just stupid.
It's like watching the same film over
and over again.
I've never been with a woman. I'm a virgin.
Never. I'm a virgin. I don't know what a
woman is. I'm a virgin.
I'm getting a sore head again, bro. I'm
getting a sore head.
Good brakes. I'm getting a sore head
again. Good brakes. Fingers crossed, lad. 2026,
there'll be no more repeating on here.
There'll be no more repeating.
Fingers crossed. 2026. No repeating. No
more skin talk. No nothing. Please. New
year. New everyone.
What do you think? Triple H.
Have you seen that account that goes on
Tibies and and write skin? It's called
Pips I think. And they just write skin.
What the [ __ ] bro? Is it like a robot
or something? It just types the same
word skin. Nothing else. Just skin. He
goes live and they write skin. If you go
on large, they write skin.
Yeah. They need to think of some new
things though, man. Come on. Cuz if they
don't, I'm just going to do I'm just
going to do traveling videos. If these
people don't stop their [ __ ] I'm just
going to do traveling videos then.
Because if they if these people just
keep repeating and it's just killing the community,
then why do they do it though? Like,
think of some new comebacks, bro. You
know what I mean? I just want some new comebacks.
Why don't they just think of some new
things to say?
They just write skin. It's just skin.
Like, that's all they write. It's just
Why don't they think of some new things to say?
just some new content,
like some funny content. It's just repeating. So
So I'm just going to do some traveling videos
and turn off the likes and I might I
might leave the comments open. I'm not sure.
Don't even know what that means.
It's um Yeah, you remember trips. These
people repeat themselves every day and
I'm getting sick of it.
So, my haircut, I like my haircut. I
really do like it.
My mom pay for it. Yeah. Right. Call.
Never heard of it.
These people These people repeat themselves.
What do you mean no? Fade. There is a fade.
Look, it's there.
There is a fade, Captain. It's right there.
You can't see cuz the lights off, but yeah.
Fade, bro. Look, it's here.
Captain Captain Punt. Ah,
no. Your mom cut it when she was giving
me a [ __ ]
What's the need for these hateful [ __ ]
comments from you people? You know, why
can't you just be positive for once?
Why are you always trying to bring other
people down, you clowns? Huh? Always
trying to bring other people down.
Madness. Absolute madness.
Rice gets more women than me. Yeah. Okay, bro.
Yeah, you keep telling yourself that. We
get more women than both of you. Well,
guess what? Me and Rice gets more women
than both of you.
I'm coming off here after um after
Christmas, bro. After tomorrow, I'm off
a little bit. I'll just be on and off
when I want to come on, but after
Christmas, I'm coming off, bro.
But I'll just be on and off from now on
whenever I feel like it.
Yeah, I think so, bro.
Same self-reflecting people every day. Same atmosphere.
Do you remember when Monty said that,
Stephen? Same atmosphere. Same Mongos.
Hopefully Monty's live later.
Hopefully Monty's live. Yeah,
those are for all don't think that you
can live off £1,200 a month when everything's paid.
Oh, [ __ ] hell, bro.
He really is an idiot, isn't he?
I'm not sure, bro.
You don't miss the gablin videos, do
you? Steven Howard,
I might put 20 pound on Frankie
tomorrow. I put 20 pound tomorrow on Frankie
just to see if I can pay for some drinks.
Yeah, there's a Frankie machine. But you
don't miss you don't really miss the
gambler videos too much, do you?
I [snorts] can't do that anymore, bro,
because of um
the mood swings and [ __ ] So, yeah.
Yeah, it ain't good.
Do I still approach women something that
you ain't got the balls to do? Yeah, I
do. Do I approach women something that
you can't do cuz you got anxiety? Yeah, I do.
Yeah. Yeah. That's how I've had more
women than you. Yeah.
It wasn't good, bro.
It has worked. Ask your mom.
You people are idiots on this community.
I'm going to ask Ley.
what she thinks.
Sad, self-projected people.
Oh, she's talking to someone.
by Steven Howard.
You reckon virgin boy is going to lose
these Valentine's cards?
Well, it has worked and I've had more
women than you and I'll keep harassing
women on the street cuz I can and it
gets me more women than you.
I can do it because I'm not scared like
you. That's just jealousy, bro. You're
just jealous that I can approach women
and you can't.
It's the same atmosphere. I'm going to
feel after today, bro.
I'll be live on Christmas and I don't
want to see any of you people on
YouTube. I don't want to see any of you
people on my live stream on Christmas.
I don't want to see any of you on
YouTube cuz I want to know what I'm
going to want to know why you're on YouTube.
I'm going to want to know why you on
YouTube. You should be with your family
and stuff. You know, I might steward.
Yeah. When's he going to lose his Valentine's? God.
You get it? Stephen, he's [ __ ]
If he keeps this up, you're going to die.
Going to die.
You're going to die.
You know what I might do? I might go
into a bar and do karaoke and sing the song.
Yeah. I just think he needs to get laid.
The sooner he loses his virginity
and he's not so much of a virgin
anymore, I reckon he'll be a better person.
I generally think when he finally pops that Jerry
when he finally pops that make up I
think he'll be a better person.
I've always said to him, when are you
going to lose it? When are you going to
lose it? When are you going to lose it?
that Aisha Bouti bouty went nowhere near
him. Steven Howard,
he went nowhere near that girl sexually.
Aisha is a Muslim.
She's a She's a religious Muslim. So
they can't have sex without uh being
married. He absolutely Oh, did not have
sex with her. He had nowhere near that girl.
[ __ ] the [ __ ] [ __ ] [ __ ] vue. He's a
He's a big big thing.
Leave Aisha alone.
You went nowhere near that girl.
Stop making up sex stories about her.
He said he he said he they [ __ ] in the park bench.
He didn't [ __ ] anything. You're a typical virgin.
Dozer frost says that he can't be a virgin. Steven Howard. [snorts]
Yeah. Joseph Fra says he can't be a
virgin because he's in a relationship. Madness. Madness, bro.
He says that he can't be a burden
because he's got a girlfriend named Steven Howard. Another loony [ __ ] virgin.
>> Yeah, but I'm off anyways. Uh, busy
tomorrow, bro. So, should I do a
football bet tomorrow? I'm not sure.
I might do a football bet, Stephen
Howard. I might not.
I'm not too sure. You nasty.
You nasty B.
You nasty virgin B. [clears throat]
You nasty skin. Virgin.
I'm playing Frankie tomorrow. 20 quid. 150p spins.
But I've never been so much of a But
I've never been so much of a [ __ ]
virgin. Steven Howard.
virgin. I've had to resort to that. You
know what I mean? Steven Howard
never never understood them virgin guys.
Never never did.
Never never did understood them virgins.
Never did. Never did.
Never did understand them virgin guys.
Never did. Never did. Never did
understand them virgin guys. Never did.
Never. Never did. Never did.
Why did Why was everyone so obsessed
with that Sher Cole Steven Howard?
Why were they all saying the same thing?
Why were they all saying that
copying each other is it? [ __ ] Why copy? H
Oh, look. LJ is live. Repeating same repeating people.
Mont says nobody knows what money he
has, but he says everyone else is skin.
He's not the sharpest.
Yeah. I I say that you people are
skinned because you're on here all day,
every day hating.
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. You're on here all
day, every day hating.
Yeah. Yeah. So that means you're skinned.
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
Yeah. I mean, you're on here every day
hating from the time you wake up to the
time you go to bed. I mean, that's clear
evidence that you're [ __ ] skinn. If
you're not skin, why are you on here all
day, every day doing what you're doing?
Ask yourself that question,
do you know? I just went on it quickly.
It's just the same repeating people.
Same repeating people.
Who eats a burger at 7 in the morning on
public transport? None. one day he's not
accepted in society. Uh a lot of people
eat food and I don't want to be accepted
in this society.
I don't I don't want to be accepted in
this society where people are addicted
to their phones.
I don't want to be accepted by this society.
PJ confirmed he only got a haircut
because Elaine paid for it. Yeah, it was
a joke. These people really are disabled
on here, lad.
I'm just reading through these things.
He's so stupid. He says people on
YouTube because they are skid server. He
must be skinned. No, no, no, no, no, no,
no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no,
no, no. I've already explained this
before. I've already explained this
before. I'm not explaining it again. You
people are on here from the time you
wake up to the time that you go to bed
cuz you are skint. Yeah. I just didn't
want to go out for a little bit. I'm
going to be out tomorrow. I'll be out
next week and I'll be out the week
after. I'll just pop on and off here
when I when I feel like it. You are the
ones coming on here calling people skin.
So yet you're the ones that are sat on
here all day every day.
And that's when everyone knows he's
skinned because he's on it. You won't
see him on here for a few days. That's
No. Again, this is self projection. I
have not been skinted
in 3 years.
No. No. No. No. No. No. No. That's self-reflecting.
You people are on here every single day
cuz you're skinned. No, no, no, no, no,
no, no. That's self projection. I can go
out right now if I want to. I can get
drunk right now if I want to. I could
have went out yesterday if I wanted to.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Never had a girlfriend. Self projecting
again. All night Mike with his self
projecting comments. You've never had a
girlfriend and you're a virgin again.
another self projector. So,
I could go out right now and drink if I
want to. I could literally go on a night
out right now if I want to. Anywhere I
want. I can leave London right now if I want to.
I do not need to prove myself
to you fat, ugly losers. Moronic losers. Yeah,
that's that. Sad, sad people.
I'm not proving these people anything,
Stephen Howard. I'm not proving these
people wrong again. I've asked these
people to show their face multiple times
and they won't do it. So, I'm not
showing them anything.
Do you know what I'm saying, bro?
Okay. Okay. Okay. Right. You do not know
how much money I have. I wanted to stay
in because I wanted to stay in.
Yeah. That doesn't mean I'm skin. I told
you what I was doing and why I was on
it. You people come on here every single
day calling people skin. Yeah, you're
on. It's just the same argument, bro.
This is why I don't bother with this
Stephen Hard. This is why I don't bother
with these people, bro. I'm coming off
here tomorrow. It's just the same
projection every time with these people.
I'm off here tomorrow, lad. I'll be back
maybe next week or something. Maybe
later than that, bro. So,
it's just the same fat downy people that
ain't got a life. Same same self
objective, same repeated.
It's just the same fat nerds that never
made it. We need to we need to focus
about our own content now on this
channel now, bro. Seriously. Yeah.
Same [ __ ] provident loans, same
skin, ugly people sat on the internet all day.
It's It's mad how they got all this money,
but they're sat on YouTube every day.
You're not finding it mad, Stephen Hour.
Now, these people have got all of this
money, but you see them typing away all
day on YouTube.
Something's not right, bro. I'm telling
you, something is not right with these
people. Yeah. On here every day, hyping,
but they got all this money hyping away
every day from the time they wake up to
the time they go bed. You've seen it and
I've seen it.
But then they claim that they've got all
this money. It's not adding up. There's
something fishy here. There's something
really, really, really fishy. They say
that they're Look, look, I'm on this
channel right now. Yeah, they're typing away
all of this money. Everyone's skin, but
they're sat on YouTube. Anyone would
think these people are skin?
Why are they not out with their mates?
Why they not with their friends? Why are
they not with their family, bro? They're
typing away. If you go on Lord JS,
they're typing away, bro. They're typing themselves oblivious.
But they've got all this money. They're
self projectors. I told you, bro.
They're skint self-reflecting ugly
[ __ ] I'm off anyways um after today,
bro. So, I'll be back. Uh yeah,
remember. Yeah, it's just the same.
Look, look, bro. Triple H, go on LJ's
channel. It's just the same repeating.
It's the same repeating. They ain't got
no content. This is what I'm saying,
bro. They've got no content.
They've got no content on their channel.
It's just fat, ugly, skinned people that
ain't got no content. Look at it, bro.
You can go on the channel right now. I
know you're banned on it, but you can
read what they're saying. Elaine
generally hates Ma. This is what I mean.
It's the same repeating people. How can
people that are clever
be entertained by repeating people? They
say that they don't show their face,
right? They don't show their face
because they're smart. But they're sound
the internet repeating every day. Make
it make sense.
They are fat, ugly, life's losers.
The king of the loser and all the the lo
he's he's the lo he's the king of the
loser, right? And all of these people
that are commenting are losers.
They've got all this money. Why are they
not out drinking with their mates? It
makes you wonder, don't it? It really
makes you wonder these people that's got
all this money are sat on here every day
that are not disabled, that are smart.
It make it makes you seriously seriously
wonder, doesn't it? How
why they're on here?
I wasn't on here a day before yesterday.
I was on here once yesterday. At the end
of the day,
I'm chilling today, bro.
I want to know why these people that's
got all this money are sat typing away
and they're not out with their friends.
Self projection. Yeah, they're the ones
that are calling me, bro. Self projection.
Look at Joseph Ra. On a This is how you
know Joseph Ra is autistic. On a serious
note, how can you buy£300
jeans and then have your mom pay for
your haircut? Uh because my mom didn't
actually pay for my haircut, you [ __ ]
It was a joke. This is how you know
they're autistic with with people right
the first side of autism.
Bro, you people are low IQ. You little
repeating spastics. Listen all night.
Mike, I know you're watching this. You
are low IQ. That's why you repeat
yourselves every day cuz you're
disabled. That's the definition of low
IQ. You're very That's why you keep
repeating. You can't say two sentences without repeating
because you're [ __ ] autistic. ugly
autistic people. You are low IQ. That's
why you keep repeating and creating the
same atmosphere and you keep killing the community.
You are the manta and you are low IQ.
Why you're not out with your mates
having a drink, all this money, all this
life. Anybody would think that these
people have got nothing. Anybody would
think that these people have not got a
friend in the world and any because they
Why are they typing to each other all day?
Like I don't I don't I I really really don't understand.
Bro, these people are low IQ, lad. These
people literally are low IQ.
They are low IQ. Why do you think they
keep repeating every day? Because
they're so disabled. They don't even
have new comebacks. They're boring
repeaters. They've got nothing.
I might do a video on a screenshot. Like
a [ __ ] one minute screenshot. Look at
these people on a Friday night out on
YouTube. No friends, no money, nothing.
Typing away, making a fool of
themselves. It's the truth, is it, bro? Yeah. [ __ ] [ __ ]
Oh, I don't see that account.
It's because their skin, bro.
Their skin. It's evidence that their
skin. Look, it's Friday. Yeah. Triple H.
And they're sat on YouTube on their fat
ugly asses typing away. [laughter]
Typing away to each other. They ain't
got a friend in the world, bro. Look at
them. They're sat there typing away. No
friends, no money. All of the nose is
them. I told you, bro. I told you all of
the nos are them. No this, no that.
That's them. That's these people. These
fat ugly people. Mr. Lonely on YouTube. That's them.
[ __ ] off, bro.
And he actually believed my mom paid for
my haircut. So autistic
mantra again. Bro, you said mantra about
a million times. Stop repeating. It's boring.
Repeating ugly people. But they say that
I'm low IQ.
They say that I'm low IQ, but they just
keep repeating. They can't think of different words.
They must be must be definitely talking
about themselves. Bro, they're talking
about low IQ and all they're doing is
repeating. They keep repeating the same words.
The same words to be repeated every day.
And that's how you know anyone that
follows that channel is disabled.
It's fat, ugly people with no brain
talking about themselves repeating.
That's how you know anyone that goes on
that channel and types, bro, they're
just disabled like him. Yeah. >> [snorts]
>> [ __ ] Mongs disabled.
It's the disabled community full of fat
ugly people that never made it. All
right, bro. These people should all come
on my panel. Yeah. And show their faces.
They can't do it cuz they're ugly.
They're [ __ ] ugly. These people are
ugly low lives sat on YouTube again
repeating every day
repeating. Try try and say something without repeating.
Nah, these people. This is why I don't
come on it, bro. This is why I do not
come on it with these people constantly
creating the same atmosphere every day,
repeating every day, bro, because
they're [ __ ] disabled. I'm doing a
video on this, bro. I'm screen
recording. One sec. Hold on, bro. Let me
see if I can get it back up.
Look at these repeating people.
Repeating fat, ugly, friendless morons.
I'm doing a video. One second, bro. I'll
be right back. Two seconds.
Yo, these people are repeating again,
Dusty and Lar's.
They talk about people not having an IQ. Yeah,
but yet they're the ones that sat on
here repeating and they don't have
anything else to say.
These people really have been bullied in
life. You really can't feel bad for them
to be honest. You know,
they're they're just fat ugly bongs.
It's the bongo channel, bro. It's the
bully victim channel. I'm telling you,
this is where all these little bully
victims go hyping away on a Friday, but
they got all this money. They're better
looking than everyone. Something's not
adding up, Dusty. Something is seriously
seriously not adding up with these people, bro.
sat on YouTube talking about other
people's lives, repeating, and they
don't know anyone. And they don't know
anyone. These little clowns, [ __ ]
disabled people. Like I said, bro, Christmas projectors.
Like I was saying earlier,
same people, same atmosphere. Yeah, man.
Same people, same atmosphere.
Isn't it right? Same people, same atmosphere.
Hopefully next year it will be
different, isn't it?
Do you remember Triple H? Same people,
same people, same story. See you next year.
Same same. Remember Ben? Same story.
Same people. See you next year.
It's the truth though. It [laughter]
same people's same story. See you next year.
Look at these little nerds.
All right, Dusty. Go on, Lord J. Look at
these little nerds.
Look at the little nerds on YouTube
typing away. Typing their life away.
[ __ ] they're little Mongs. All
they're doing is going on about [ __ ]
people. Look, look, look. They got no
life, bro. You will know if they've got
a life if he goes live and no one goes on there.
Same repeating people
ain't got no life. Jealous of Peter Belly.
If they weren't jealous of you, they'd
shut up about you. They keep going on
about you. So, they [ __ ] obviously are jealous.
These little nerds. It's the same
people. It's the same little nerds.
None of these people have got the balls
to join a [ __ ] hangout.
You would h you would have thought, bro,
that you would have thought these people
would get bored. That's how you know
they're disabled. So when they're
talking about low IQ, they're talking about themselves
repeating every day.
And yet seeing next year, yeah,
it would always be the same with these repeating people.
If they're not skin, why are they sat on
YouTube every day? piping away
cuz they are skin [ __ ] skin flints.
That's what they are.
Same atmosphere, same people. I'm gone
after tomorrow anyways, lad. So, I'll be
back whenever. Yeah. Same people.
Low IQ, but then they're the ones that
sat repeating every day. Wow. Yeah.
Same. Yeah. Yeah. It would it would
always be the same old.
Just negative ugly fat lossers that
ain't got nothing in life.
Yeah. It will be it will always be the
same with these [ __ ] They've been
doing it. They've been doing it for 6 years, bro. [laughter]
They They've been doing it for 6 years.
They've been doing it for six years, bro.
See, look at this. I remember Flacker
turned up to the petrol station to
confront Kenzie. This is what I'm
saying. It's only old stuff they bring
up. They've got new They've got no new stuff.
It's just repeating, isn't it?
That's what I'm saying, bro. They only
bring up old stuff. They got no new
There's no new content on their channel.
Do you remember Triple H? What Monty Man
said about it? [laughter]
Sometimes I'll go live. Yeah. >> [laughter]
>> So sometimes I'll go live triple
and Monty's live will pop up.
Monty's live will pop up lad.
Same repeating people obsessed repeatedly.
Like I said, they're proving my point
even more that they're jealous cuz I've
got family and they've got no one.
They're still talking about me. Proves
I'm right about every It's prove I'm
It's proof It proves I'm right about these people.
Yeah, it's pro It's proof that I'm right
about these autistic sad people.
Do you remember what Monty said? Right.
When are you skinned people going to get
off YouTube and get a job? Yeah.
Working girls I know would pay him not
to do the deed. Yeah. Okay, bro. We've
seen me with multiple multiple women
that weren't escorts. Again, self-projecting.
Same fat ugly losers. Just like what my
mom said. Same fat ugly losers. Cuz they
ain't got a life.
That ain't got a life. Self projecting.
Self projecting. We all know that. Use
the ugly ones. Same autism. Same same projection.
They're just ugly people that failed at
everything. And they're trying to
they're trying to bring other people
down to their level. They're just fat ugly nerds.
skinned people that ain't got a life.
That's why they do this trip rates.
They're just lonely, sad people. Trip, lad.
Same repeating people every day.
What did Monty say about Triple H?
What did Trip uh Trip Race? What did
Monty say about it, lad?
These are proper nerds on here, lad.
They're proper proper nerds. Nerds.
just laughing at the same jokes. [laughter]
Triple. These people have been laughing
at the same jokes for like seven years. [laughter]
They've been laughing at the same jokes
for seven years, bro. But everyone else
is low IQ. Oh, triple.
These people laugh at the same jokes and
their own jokes [laughter]
for seven years,
you know. [laughter] Self projection.
Self projecting. Ugly people with no Five.
bastards. No life.
I'm just going on my main channel. What's that? [snorts] Tired, boss. >> [snorts]
>> Madness, lad. Madness. Same atmosphere.
When all are these ski people going to
get off of YouTube and get a job.
What's up about that, bro?
Oh, Monty did go live once >> [laughter]