[ __ ] the middle button up, bro. Oh,
good old Franklin.
A good old nesticles.
Back in the good old nestles.
Your phone's going off.
You might want to get it. >> Yeah.
Did you Did you answer it? No.
Hey, I'm back now. [ __ ] day as I knew it would be. Ah, [ __ ]
good old England, eh? Never changes.
I would have been a millionaire today if
I would have been an absolute millionaire today.
I would have been a [ __ ] millionaire today.
Did you answer it? >> Huh?
Sorry about that. I did go out and don't
tell me welcome back, bro. You can't
even [ __ ] You can't even take a
[ __ ] day off of YouTube. You can't
even take an hour off YouTube. So, don't
tell me welcome back. Uh, actually,
well, I wasn't actually going to go out
to the Etsy. Um, I had to go out cuz
someone come on my door. So, and yeah, I
would have been a millionaire today if I
put money on it. I would have been a
millionaire because all the things that
I said happened would happen happened.
Yeah, literally, bro. It was It was bad,
bad, bad, bad bad. And it was more toxic
than usual cuz I was with people. I was
literally going to stay here, bro, and
live off 30 a week and leave the country
like a month and a half cuz I already
had some savings. That's what my plan
was. I was going to live off like 304
pound a week and [ __ ] off. I don't give
a [ __ ] me, bro. Like the thing is I can
save. I don't mind. I can save money. I
can live off 30 pound a week. I don't
smoke. I really really can, bro. I don't
give a [ __ ] Like, you know what I'm
saying? That's the thing. But yeah, it
was the same old [ __ ] today as always,
as it will always be. Just put it down
to the same old same old boring. Same
old pathetic [ __ ] Boring.
Yep. I literally had to go out today. I
woke up to I No, no, no. I didn't wake
up. Yes, S. I'm not going out today. I'm
not going out today. I am not [ __ ]
going out. Would have been the third day
I let someone out, bro. I was out and I come back.
I woke up today. I was like, I'm not
going out. I swear I'm [ __ ] done it.
I'm going to live for 30 a week for a
month and a half and I'm leaving. And
then then I literally someone come my
door. So, I kind of had to go out. Like
I literally had to go out otherwise I
would have been in [ __ ] went out. Same
old sad song, same old story. So, I
would have I would have been a
millionaire today. Um, predicted it and
I was right again. Not one number, but
yeah, it was bad, bad, bad, bad bad.
And it made it worse cuz I was with
people as well. So,
yeah, it was [ __ ] bro. Really, really
bad. But I kind of had to go out today.
So, I weren't going to go out, but I had
to. So, um, yeah, I'm back in uh my gown
now. So [snorts] yeah, back in my good old gowny.
>> Yeah, I wasn't in central London. What
do you mean only one? You couldn't even
get a number.
You couldn't even get one. I wasn't in
my I wasn't in my area that I was
normally in. About only one. It was a
dead area, bro. I weren't in the area
that I'm normally in.
About only one. It doesn't matter if
it's one or 10, bro. Same [ __ ] So yeah.
So, I wasn't in a normal area that I go
to. I think I done about six approaches
today. Only got one number.
Only one number. I got six. I done six
approaches. It was a local area and Yeah.
I wasn't going to go out today. I I said
it from tomorrow. Uh yesterday when I
was talking to Timmy, I was like, I'm
not going out. I just want to leave now.
I want to live off 30 pound a week and leave.
Um but I kind of had to go out. I
literally had to go out, bro. Trust me,
I had to. If it was my choice, I would
have went out, but I had to. So, really, really bad.
I'm looking forward to living off 30 a
week and leaving in a month and a half.
Not a problem at all. You know, you're
more you're more depressed when you're
dating. When you're in the dating game
trying to date women, it makes you
[ __ ] depressed. I woke up today,
Greavves, no words of life, thinking of
ways to kill myself because of this
problem. And I was like, I don't want to
go out. I don't want to go out. I don't
want to go out. I don't want to go out.
But I I had to cuz someone come on the
door and [ __ ] and I didn't want to let
someone down for the first time. Yeah,
it's really bad, bro. Really, really
bad. All jokes aside, it was really bad.
And it just shows that it's never going
to change. I think it was five or six.
Five or six approaches.
Same old [ __ ] Same old boring. Dusty,
listen. Before you say, "Oh, if you
didn't know there was no hope, you would
have went out." Uh, the thing is, Dusty,
I when I was talking to Timmy yesterday,
I said, "I'm not going out. I'm not
going out. I'm not going out. I'm not
[ __ ] going out. [ __ ] this. I'll let
someone down for the first time. Woke
up. I was still in the same mood. I'm
not going out. I'm not going out. I'm
not going out. I'm not going to go out.
But my sister's friend come on the door.
So, I had to come out. This is what I
was trying to explain to man. He's like,
"Oh, just come out. Just come out. Just
come out." Like, I couldn't say [ __ ]
no when someone's on the [ __ ] front
door. Otherwise, I wouldn't have went
out, bro. And yeah, I've done five
approaches. Got one number. It was bad.
I thought it would have been a little bit better.
Nah, I'm not getting a proy round. I'm
going to sleep. and I'm giving up a life
and I'm living off 30 pound a week for
one and a half months, two months and
I'm leaving which was what my original
plan was. But yeah, so I spent over £100
today on literally nothing basically
same old boring.
So I'll be living off 30 a week now
anyways. Booking these flights next week
ever 100%. I'm deadly serious. Um I
would have went out today.
I'll be back. Doesn't matter when I'll
be back on YouTube, bro. Don't worry
about me. You can't take a day off for YouTube.
It doesn't matter what I'm on. What? You
can't take a day off for YouTube. So, it
doesn't really matter what I do.
I'm on and off here. I'm on and off
here. Why? Why does it bother you? I'm
on and off here. This is my first time
on YouTube today. So, yeah.
And I stuck it on some [ __ ] as well,
bro. Um, I woke up in a foul mood, bro.
You don't understand. was a foul. Foul
as I'm not going out. I want revenge. I
want revenge. I want revenge. You don't
understand how I work up. You don't get
me. You really really don't understand
it. You think it's all funny. I I'm not
going out. I ain't going out. But I
didn't get five numbers. I got one number.
And I don't really give a [ __ ] if it was
one number. One number is one number. I
was in a local area. I wasn't in central
London and I was with people. So that's
why I got one. And it doesn't really
matter whether it's one or five or 20.
It's always going to be the same [ __ ]
So it doesn't matter how many numbers it is. So
I'm tired of it. I'm boring. I'm bored
of it now. [ __ ] I'm at my w I'm at my
wits end of it, bro. You don't
understand. I will commit. I will commit
a madness, bro. Like you laugh at it
time and time and time and time and time
and time and time and time again.
I tell you exactly the approaches that I done.
First one, they were just unenthusiastic.
Bear in mind, they weren't even good
looking. They were fat. I just done it
to do it. Attitude problem. Okay,
whatever. Then I done the second one. We
were talking, got their number. They
seemed all right. Okay, got their
number. And I think I done about four
after that. Not a sausage. Boyfriend,
boyfriend, boyfriend. Now, I thought it
would have been a bit different cuz it's
not central London. Nope. Cuz it was
nowhere near central London. I thought
it's a local area. And what made it
worse is I was with people and it made
it even worse. It made it even more
toxic. So, I guess if I was going to go
out, I would have just went out by
myself. But I don't really care if it's
one number or two numbers. One number is
one number. I was talking to them. They
met my sister in that and just so I
don't give a [ __ ] I don't give a [ __ ]
I said as long as I got one number. Yeah.
Yep. It's always the same old. It will
never change. That's why I want to
leave. I had no choice but to go out
today. If I didn't go out today, I would
have never heard the the end of it. I
was basically forced to go out. So yeah,
same old boring. Same. I I have given
up. I have given up. I have given up.
But I had to go out today.
Here we go with the gay jokes. So yeah,
>> this is depressing, bro. I woke up today
grieving thinking of ways to kill myself
and [ __ ] It's not even a joke. All
because of this dating thing. All
because of this dating thing. I'm not
even [ __ ] joking, bro. You should You
should have heard my mom. You know,
I like to be around with a victim
mentality. I don't like to be one of
these people that try anymore. I want to
be left alone and leave, which is what I
wanted to do. But instead, I got forced
to go out again. I don't want to go out
again. I want to leave. I want to get
the [ __ ] out of here.
I will [ __ ] [ __ ] watch cuz I already
had some savings as well. Like I was
saying this to Antman, right?
Like I was talking to the dude earlier.
Yeah. Greaves. And I said this to him
that remember when I used to gamble and
I used to get pissed off worse than you
ever could. And I used to and I
time and time and time and time and time
and time and time and time and time and time again.
And I thought I had no and I thought I
had no patience. Bro, Ant-Man has not
dealt with 5% of what I put up with.
What am I still doing here, bro? I was
thinking about this yesterday, right
before I went to bed when I was talking
to Timmy. I was thinking, why am I still
here? No, no, no, no, no, no. Why the
[ __ ] am I still here, bro? This guy has
not dealt with 5% of what I've dealt
with. He's gone and I'm still here. Nah,
bro. We're living off 30 a week and
we're leaving. Simple. We're living off
30 pound a week and we're leaving.
That's it. That is it, bro. I was like
then why is this guy left? >> So
more [ __ ] tomorrow. Yeah.
It will never change. It will never
I get numbers and walk off cuz they're
with their friend. Yeah. Yeah. I get
numbers and walk off cuz they're with
their friend. Do you want to go and get
a number? Do you want to go out and get
a number? Let's see how you do it, man.
Let's let's learn from the best. Cuz if
you're going to try and critique me, Cuz
if you're going to try if you're going
to if you're going to try and critique
me, I said to my mom today, if I go out,
I'm going to end up killing someone,
bro. You don't You do not understand.
Like, it took someone it took somebody
coming to me today and talking to me on
a level in my room, bro. Cuz I said, "If
you want me out, I'm going to end up
killing someone." Yeah. It's not a joke.
You laugh and laugh and laugh and laugh.
Yeah. I was in a I went to bed in a foul
mood and I woke up in a foul mood. Oh,
but go out. Go out. I'm not going out.
I'm not going out. I'm not going out.
Someone comes on the door, comes in my
room. Let's go out. What am I supposed
to do? Say [ __ ] no. I'm done. Done,
bro. [ __ ] off. Yeah. [ __ ] [ __ ]
bro. You don't understand it. And it was
[ __ ] as well. The whole thing was
actually [ __ ] I'm never going out with
people ever again. I'm I'm never ever
ever ever ever going out with anyone
ever again because I never do. So
So yeah, I'm done anyways, bro. 100%.
I was just going to stay in and watch
WWE. Bro, I was going to watch some
films, chill, and then leave in like
February, January, February.
It's not going to take 6 months. I
already had some savings. So, so I was
just going to chill, watch some WWE, and yeah,
I got one number. They seemed all right
enough. So, I didn't need to get any
more numbers. I didn't want to make it
all about getting numbers. As long as I
got one, that was it. And I did try to
get more as well in the end. and they
weren't having it at all. Anyone would
think it was in central London. So, it
will always be the same. Uh I don't know
how people think it will not. It will
always be the same here.
And then and the night was [ __ ] as well. Yeah. So,
yeah, I got one number. Yeah, maybe
I met some guy as well.
And I thought, yeah, she seemed all
right and I like the look of her, so
that was good enough for me. I don't
want anyone else.
Yeah, I've never had anxiety in my life.
Self projection. Do you know what? Me
and this guy was actually talking about
you people. Anyways, the other day, we
don't care about you little self
projectors. It's boring now. Get your
life. But anyways, so I just figured one
was enough. Anyways,
I bite my nails cuz I bite my nails. I
do not have anxiety. Self- projecting
again. We're not getting into this with
you people. You little self-reflecting comments anymore. Yeah. So, yeah.
Yeah. I don't know about six approaches
just stuck up just as they always are in this country.
But we'll see you tomorrow with this
lumber, aren't we?
Yeah, of course you never cuz you're biased.
Yeah, of course you've never seen that.
Cuz you're biased.
Yeah, you don't see a lot of things on
here cuz you're biased. So, I mean,
that's no surprise. Is that even a question?
Well, the Guinness was dis I went to a
Turkish restaurant Gree and I had some
Guinnesses and some [ __ ]
It's either suicide or you leave this
country. That's how bad it is getting
generally. That is how it's getting.
It's either someone ends up killing
themsel going to jail or leaving this country.
So, I would say just leave, bro. It's
it's a better life for anyone.
You know what I'm saying? It's it's it's
a better life for everyone, bro. to be
honest though and that's what we're doing.
You laugh at it time and time again, but
it isn't funny, bro. Cuz I had a go at
somebody today on WhatsApp.
She said, "Oh, dude, you're actually
insane. Get help." I said, "You're the
one that needs help. You're the one on
WhatsApp trolling people and you're
telling people that they need help.
You're telling people they need help
that you're the one you're the one
trolling on WhatsApp." Cuz I told her if
I if I met you, I would have [ __ ] you
over, bro. I would have [ __ ] you over
proper. I would have done it dirty this
time, bro. Yeah, dirty.
Dirty. I would have done it dirty, bro.
Yeah. Just like the other one. Yeah.
Yeah. Yeah. You'll know what I'm about,
you [ __ ] little [ __ ] When you
meet me, you little [ __ ] [ __ ] So,
yeah. When one of these one of these
people meet me,
they're getting [ __ ] over, bro. 100%.
I'm insane. Yet, you're the one that's
trolling people on WhatsApp.
You're the one that troll that's
trolling people on WhatsApp and you're
telling people that they need help.
I'm the one that's insane yet you're the
one that's trolling people over
WhatsApp, you stupid [ __ ] [ __ ] Really? Really?
So yeah, I was forced to go out today.
Trust me, creepy. I would have not heard
the last of it cuz my sister was like,
"This is the third time now come around.
There's nothing I could have done."
Yeah. I'm so tough, bro. I'm going to
I'm going to dine and dash them. I'm
going to dine and dash them. I'm very
very hard. I'm going to dine and dash
him. Getting by the pockets. I actually
ate in a restaurant today as well.
100%. So, that's what we're going
telling people they need help when
you're the one on WhatsApp trolling
people. Really, bro?
[ __ ] them over.
I'm going to [ __ ] them over before they
[ __ ] me over.
Yeah, I was I'll [ __ ] them over like
they [ __ ] me over. What's the day
tomorrow? Sunday. It is Saturday. Yeah.
Can't even keep track of the [ __ ] dates. So, so yeah,
good luck to you people in here. Anyways,
so I got this TV. I I can easily live
off 30 quid a week. I don't smoke. I
don't drink. I I'll live off it for a
month and a half. I really don't give a
[ __ ] I'm not bothered. I don't need to
go out every week. I don't need to earn
money every week to go out. I don't need
to like Antman. That's mad.
cuz I was telling him the same thing
about this same problem. Yeah,
looks like that's the only way
cuz obviously this area I thought it
would have been a bit better because of
um just down to earth people. It was
bad, bad, bad. It was bad. It was bad.
It's worse than central London. I was
happy with one, bro. I don't I don't
mind. I met some guy as well, so I made
some link. Whenever you go out with
people, they bring you down as well. So,
uh, he just said you just need to leave.
He said the only thing you need to do is
just leave the country.
Yeah. I just went around my mom's area.
You just need to leave the country.
There's nothing else you can do. You
just need to leave.
You either leave the country, join the
porn industry, or you use escorts for
the rest of your life. Those are your only options.
So, you pick one of them.
Sure. That's the one. That's it. But
yeah, I didn't mind. I didn't mind
getting one number. I didn't I was happy
with that anyways
>> because they seemed right there. Oh,
drop me a message. So, I didn't mind to
be honest. I don't I don't want to get
loads of numbers. One's enough for me, bro.
I just wanted to chill.
So, I was all right with one. So,
this guy messaged me. Anyways,
I always prefer going out by myself.
This see the thing is this is what these
people don't understand on here because
they don't have life experience. I
prefer going out by myself.
I 100% prefer prefer going out by myself
for various different reasons.
You could get cop blocked. There's so
many different reasons. I just prefer
going out by myself,
you know. I just prefer to go out by myself.
Simple. So that's that.
that's that in it. Same old. There's so
many different reasons. Like the person
that I approached in the end met my
sister and the other guy cuz we just
bumped into each other. It was all
right. But I was scared that he was
going to get the number and then stuff.
And yeah, anything can go wrong when
you're with other people. That's why I
always prefer to go out by myself.
Like if I was to go out on Saturday,
100% I'd go by myself.
100%. one person maximum and they'd have
to be a really good person, bro. Cuz I
could have easily got cop blocked.
And yeah, two's company, free the crowd.
Remember that, bro.
Two come. Yeah, I don't give a [ __ ]
about escorts. I don't need to use
escorts. I haven't used escorts for a
long time. I don't need to use escorts.
What's What's that to me, bro?
So yeah, anything could have happened
and I could have got [ __ ] royally and
then all the effort is for nothing.
That's what I'm saying. People should
just go out by themselves.
But yeah, they can smell anxiety. Well,
that's definitely projection cuz I don't have anxiety. So,
but yeah. How is this person trying to
tell me on WhatsApp that I need I'm
insane cuz I was going to die and dash someone.
I put her in her place, bro. Proper
proper. Put her in her place. And this
is why I stopped. This is why I stopped
going out because of these people, you
know. But at the end of the day, when
you're when you're not left any other
option, you have to go out,
you know. I I had to go out to
otherwise. I wouldn't have heard the
last of it.
You don't understand, bro. You really
don't understand. Just Antman don't
Won't be happening again.
So that's it. Five weeks done. Simple.
So going out by yourself is definitely better. 100%.
There's various reasons why I stopped going out.
going out. Uh the [ __ ] the stupid
rules, the women. Uh that's one of the
reasons why I stopped going out. So yeah.
But we'll see what this person does
tomorrow. See if they uh reply back.
And uh that's that is it.
So they're just [ __ ] everywhere, aren't they?
I know. I had to go out today, though.
I had to go out today.
It doesn't matter anyways. It's not
happening again. So yeah,
uh he does understand my struggles
because he left the country because of
it. He does understand. He definitely
does understand. He just doesn't
understand why I had to go out today.
Well, he does understand, mate, because
he left the country because of it.
I think it was a few times I have a
boyfriend. Oh, change the record. Would
you give me a headache? Heard it about
three times. I was like, "This is boring
now." I was going to dip. It's boring,
bro. Very, very boring. Very, very
Give me a headache.
I said to my mom as well, "Have you got
like the [ __ ] keys?" I was just going
to bounce, bro, straight away.
Yeah, it's really bad. It is really bad.
It will never change. Yeah. You're
always going to be depressed and miserable here.
More bad experiences
thing. He went out with an axe. I'm not
[ __ ] running out with a an axe. I'm
not killing someone. I'm just going to
[ __ ] him over civily.
I'm not going to do that all all that
madness with an axe and [ __ ]
That's mad. I'm just going to I'm just
going to go to a restaurant, [ __ ] him
over, make them pay that [ __ ] bill
and that's that
and that's it.
But yeah, I would advise anyone if
you're trying to meet people, whether
it's friends or women, I'd advise
definitely going out by yourself unless
you got a really good friend and only one person.
It was a [ __ ] night today, bro. [snorts]
I I much preferred going out by myself.
I don't know why people go out in
groups. That's [ __ ] dead. Might as
well just go by myself. I don't wait on
no one, bro.
You know, I don't have kids cuz I don't
want a responsibility. I don't have a I
don't have responsibilities and I prefer
it that way. So, but yeah.
I like to think this person is
different, but going by your previous
experiences, I can't imagine it.
Yeah, this person had red boots. I was
like, I'm going to go and send it, bro.
I'm going to go send it hard.
They're 26 and I'm 28, so that's perfect.
Like I said, if I'm going out to enjoy
myself, if I get one number, I don't
want to I don't need any more numbers
because it was only local, you see. So,
one, I don't care. Only one's good
enough for me. I don't I'm not going to
go and sit. I did do more approaches. I
did do more of them because I thought,
why not? But
that was more later on and it was just
the same old [ __ ]
I would have been a millionaire today. I
would have been a millionaire today if
that [ __ ] market on the [ __ ] thing.
So, it definitely isn't the area. I
think it's definitely the same
everywhere in this country.
I'll be staying in bed tomorrow hung
over and I'll be staying in bed cuz I
don't regret getting the trim. Like, I
might I might have spent £60 for my
haircut, but I don't mind, bro. I
literally don't mind. I I don't mind
paying to be groomed. I don't need to go
out just cuz I paid good money to get
groomed. That's fine. I I I don't mind
personal hygiene. I don't need to go
out. And it was [ __ ] just cuz I got groomed. So So
yeah, it's bad, bro. Really bad. Yeah.
Yeah, I definitely got the right number.
I've got some balls on me, bro, to do
that. I done it in front of my sister as well.
I got some massive bollocks, bro.
But I know that even if you got two or
three numbers anyways, it's always it's
going to be the same anyways. They're
all the same. So, if you're staying
locally, really, if you get one, you
should just give up that one.
Depending on the on the vibe, it depends
on like what what's going on and that.
Then you're local anyway, so you don't
need any more than one. It's not going
to change anyways. It will never change.
You're not going to meet a woman that's
ever different. They're all the same.
So, which is why I went against going out.
Let me message this woman. Anyways, uh
on Reddit saying, "Went out today. More bad experiences."
See the thing is Greavvesy right I was
lying in bed earlier
and the problem with me I'll tell you
what the problem is with me is right is
that you I'm sorry to keep repeating
this but this is the this is the problem
though this is the really big problem
with this is that you have tried more
than anyone in the world you can't even
blame yourself like you've done
everything that you can do you've tried
more than that man you haven't got
anxiety where you can't speak to people,
etc., etc. Like, at the end of the day,
you've tried all you can do, so you
can't even blame yourself.
Whereas, you'll get all of these people
that complain all day and they don't do
nothing. You have tried more than
anybody in the world. And this is what
separates you from 95% of people.
So, this is the problem that you're
going to keep h having cuz my history
makes it biased. Do you understand?
Because of my history.
So this is the problem that you're going
to keep having, you know, so
so yeah, I got one number anyways. So
they live about 40 minutes away. So,
we'll see what they uh
what they say basically.
I don't I mean, I've got 199 numbers on
my phone. I don't think this person is
going to be different somehow.
It's very very unlikely.
So, that's the way it's always going to be.
and [ __ ] gets so boring.
I wish I could laugh at it, bro. I
really wish I could sit there and just
laugh at it,
but it's not even funny. It's [ __ ]
boring. Bors the [ __ ] out of me, bro.
So, yeah, I spent £110 today for no reason.
Yay. That's lovely, isn't it?
Same old [ __ ] Some more boring.
Yeah. 110. Food drinking. Food. Drinking.
It was good to be fair. It was [ __ ]
good. You right.
Nine nuggets maybe.
I'm fed up today. They [ __ ] pissed me
off, man. Oh, they [ __ ] did, bro.
Yeah, I'm definitely not going out with
anyone ever again.
I don't wait on no one, bro.
I'm [ __ ] drunk as [ __ ] man. I said I'm drunk.
Yeah, just give me some nuggets. Just
No, no, no, no. This selects nine nuggets. [snorts] Yeah.
God, I select too much.
Well, you fancy McDonald's.
I knew you was going to do that. I knew
>> That kebab that kebab place is nice though.
Yeah, it's b it's way better when you
eat. It's way better when you eat in as
well. I But do you know what's funny is
the chicken was more was more chewy than
the actual lamb.
Yeah, it was. I had mix though. I can't
ever decide, so I just get mixed. So yeah. Yeah. What you >> good?
I'm going to bed in a minute as well to
be fair. I'm tired. Tired and fed up.
They done everything today to get me
out, right? And then when I went out,
he was trying to blame the music then
when there was nothing wrong with the music.
You done all that to get me out and then
you've done that when when you get
someone out. You don't like my trainers, is it?
So, what do you mean by I've still got muscle?
>> Well, I don't go gym.
>> Why do you think it's from the walking?
When I walk like Franklin,
how do you know who Franklin is? Huh? [ __ ] man.
No, but it was nice cuz I was saying I
think I've only had Turkish once when I
was with you in Ilford.
I don't I don't like Donna. I had I
can't have Donna. I don't. But to be
fair, the donor was [ __ ] fat as [ __ ]
to be fair. If you want to
I've never had like a proper Turkish, I
don't think except from when in Ilford.
There might have been Turkish, but I
don't think I had the what the Turkish
eat. You know what I mean? The shish is
the best. I can't have the donut. The
donut. I could have chicken. I could
have chicken donut if you eat in, but I
can't have lamb donut.
I was just shoving it in my mouth like
how comes I didn't choke.
>> I was thinking of getting a
cheeseburger. I bet the cheeseburgers
there were really nice in it. Yeah,
because it's it's but I just had kebab
in it. I like I like Turkish wings as
well. I said I don't know. I don't know
what I prefer that I don't know what
mine was 27 which were bad and I got
quite a lot. The Indians in Liverpool
[ __ ] are a lot in it.
No, he didn't eat.
He didn't eat. No. And I had to eat in
case cuz I knew I was I might have went
on the spirits.
>> For real,
>> bro. She's just a [ __ ]
Yeah. I was saying, "Oh, I'm going to
put 20 on Frankly." Franklin, he's going
to put 20 10. You want to put 20? Just
as fun. Like we only learn 20. And she
was like, "Oh, I don't have any cash."
Well, can't you get cash?
I don't understand it. I seriously
seriously don't. I can understand if
someone does something with their money,
>> but they don't. So, what's the problem?
>> You've got to realize.
>> Do you understand what I'm saying though? It's >> Yeah.
That remind that Marvel thing reminded
me of him. And how do I know that she
knew about the Marvel? She knew about
the Marvel because of him.
Because he's into Marvel.
>> Yeah, I knew it. Because how do you know
about Marvel? Huh? How does she knew about him?
>> I used to like Marvel. >> Yeah.
>> I like um >> just >> Yeah.
>> want to come out. You [ __ ]
>> I don't want to go out. Jason. >> Yeah.
>> Everything you do, Charlie, is for your own.
>> I'm not doing it again. I'm not doing it
>> Oh, are you? Yeah. >> Yeah.
>> What's his name? Timmy.
So, it's almost Timmy Aldra. Almost. No,
that's almost Timmy Aldra. Is it
>> few weeks back? Not in touch.
Brian's pleasant color
>> and said, "Look, if
uh Brian wants to see a every other
weekend, that's fine." >> Yeah.
>> But you have to wear me
blah blah blah. Yeah.
>> I asked her I asked her in the um
Turkish, "What month do you prefer,
October, December?" What do you think?
She said December. Really? Do you prefer
December? I don't. No, seriously.
Cold [ __ ] [ __ ] New Year's Eve. Yeah, October's better. Sunday
was supposed to see
>> the night before that that was when her
soal friend to Brian with the girl took
to the hotel.
>> She's definitely there if we read that. >> Yeah.
So I know sh
>> I was playing [ __ ] Paul all rummed
up. It was very hard. The drink went
everywhere once. One of their drinks
went everywhere. It just missed me. Just
m it went on me.
>> Yeah. Yeah.
But I'm just fed up with it. >> Yeah.
>> Why would you not say
But it is nice to kebabs.
It's up there with It's up there with
Indian, isn't it?
It's up there with Indian.
It's up. Yeah, it's up there with Indian.
Well, what did you always get the shish?
Sorry about that.
What a [ __ ] day I've had.
You're laughing about it, mate. But when
I die and death someone, you're not
going to be laughing. I don't find it funny.
I don't know why you laugh at it. It's
not funny. It's [ __ ] depressing.
Same [ __ ] in it.
Same old [ __ ]
Would you like to see that greasier
woman get D and dash? are dying and dashed.
Yeah, it's lovely them not being able to
pay and then getting nicked. That is [ __ ] lovely.
No prison time for Peter Bell. Absolutely lovely. [ __ ] lovely.
So, when are you going to meet any When
are you going to meet someone here,
Grevy? Because they keep saying on
Reddit that you're going to find
someone. And I'm not being funny, Grevy.
This has been going on for [ __ ] years now. years.
[ __ ] in it.
It's never going to change, is it, bro?
Never going to change.
It will never change, will it?
I had my bers on. Got my hair nice.
Yep. Same old Remember
the struggle dismisses Graves. The struggle dismisses.
Really? You can't tolerate it? I think
it's [ __ ] lovely.
I think Timmy hitting women is
absolutely lovely if you ask me. We lovely.
I think it's [ __ ] lovely, man. Lovely.
What do you think about this, bro?
Nah, bro. I'm just eating my nuggets and chilling.
M. They're nice and hot.
So, did you have sex today, Timmy?
That tastes like [ __ ] diet coke. That was
[ __ ] vile, mate.
But I come up today in conversation
about these little self projectors on this community.
We were talking about these little self-reflectors
um earlier Triple H on this community.
I've I've only come on YouTube just now,
bro, like not even an hour ago. >> [snorts]
>> What? You don't you joining or what?
No, I weren't going to do anything but
stay in bed
cuz of my bad experiences with women. I
weren't going to do nothing. I was going
to stay in bed.
So, I didn't do anything but go out
drinking because I had to put it that way. So,
nope. Not interested in nothing. No
gambling, no nothing. I just want to
stay in bed and do nothing.
But that couldn't have been the case today.
Yeah, I didn't do nothing. I put 20 on Frankie.
Oh, I did put 20 on Frankie in the pub,
but I didn't get a bonus
if that counts.
So actually today I actually only spent
80. If you took away the 20 pound
gambling. Yeah. It would have been 80.
Same as Triple H.
And I'll be in bed all day tomorrow. Depressed. Yeah.
I'm not put I'm not letting his voice
reasoning. I can't be bothered.
If Timmy wants to talk and have a
conversation, that's fine.
Yeah. 50p spins. Yeah. So, yeah, it was
actually £80 I spent. Yeah. Nope.
Not a sausage. Not even not even a sniff
of a bonus.
Same old. It will always be the same in
this country. You know this.
That's what Antman said, Dusty. It will
always be the same day. You know this.
Well, duh. That's why I don't want to go out.
Same old depression.
Every time you go out drinking, toxic, depressing,
waste of time. [clears throat]
Yeah, I saw double. Both teams have
scored today. They both scarred. I see
that both teams have score.
Well, at least you didn't go out today
getting the same old [ __ ] with women as
you always get.
Boyfriend, boyfriend, boyfriend. Anyone
would think he was on in central London.
It is boring, bro. So boring. Very
Same old [ __ ]
I wonder how virgins feel.
I wonder how virgins feel, bro.
But I'll be in bed tomorrow depressed anyways
watching some WWE. Yeah. Depressed.
I don't even think I'll go to a
restaurant tomorrow. So boring.
And I'm going to have a bad hangover as
well cuz I drunk some spirits.
No, just old school wrestling from 2010.
Yeah. Keeps me occupied. Makes me forget
the fact I'll always be single forever. And sexness
helps occupine occupy the mind.
I'm going to start in this [ __ ]
tomorrow on WhatsApp
telling people to get help when you're
the one on WhatsApp [ __ ] with people.
You stupid little [ __ ]
If you're going to say something on
WhatsApp, say something to someone's
face. If you're not prepared to say
something to someone's face,
uh if you if you say if you want to say
something to someone's face, I'm more
than happy to meet you and give you that chance.
I'll say that to her tomorrow if she
doesn't reply by tomorrow. I'm going to
tell you to your face that you need help
and you need to stop [ __ ] trolling
people on [ __ ] WhatsApp. You won't
say anything to my face in front of any
man. You will not say anything to my
face in front of any man. So what you're
saying on here don't mean anything.
[ __ ] [ __ ] bro.
I'm really going to start some madness tomorrow.
Watch when I wake up. I'm going to start some madness. [ __ ] idiots.
I didn't think it was going to be as bad
as it was today, but
clearly is. Um,
stop telling people to get help. You're
the one that needs help. What? Well, cuz
I said I was going to die and dash
someone. That means someone needs help.
Why does that mean someone needs help?
Well, cuz they want to die and dash you.
It's hardly crime in a [ __ ] century.
I told her, "You're so lucky you didn't
meet me as well." These people, it's
like they know. They're very, very lucky
because when one of these women meet me,
bro, they're going to know what time it
is. And all of the [ __ ] that they've
done in the past, they won't be laughing
about it when they can't leave that
restaurant with a 5,600 bill. They're
not going to be laughing. None of these
people are going to be laughing.
So, it's all well and good now. [ __ ] [ __ ] [ __ ] idiot. Yeah.
About you get out of the world what you
put in. Really? Really, bro? Really? [ __ ] off.
Nope. When I meet a woman, I'm I'm make
I'm leaving them. I'm ditching them.
I'm getting a last laugh.
I don't give a [ __ ] if I'll be on
camera. No one knows who I am. They
don't know who I am.
What are they going to do, bro? I really
don't care. I never said I was going to
pay. So, if I walk out, I never said I
was going to pay, did I? So,
I'm really [ __ ] a woman over, bro.
Please. I want I was trying with with a
tenant yesterday and she was ignoring as well.
I said, "You going to answer the message
or what? Watch when I just watch, bro.
Watch. The longer it takes, the more
this bill is going to go up when I
finally meet when I finally find
someone, bro. Trust me.
Trust me, the more when I finally find
someone, I need revenge.
I was speaking to some guy today. He he
reminded me of that damning, you know,
bro. He reminded me of that damning, you
know, proper proper splitting image of that damning.
Proper splitting image, bro. Another little clown.
I was going to start all of that up as
well yesterday again, bro.
I'm going to start a [ __ ] whole madness again.
So, it doesn't matter if I'm on camera.
What are they going to do? You never
said that you're going to pay, did you? So,
it's up to them to pay. If you leave
them in the bill, they're [ __ ] So
yeah, it really doesn't matter where you are.
And I'm never going out with anyone ever
again, which I've already said. So
that has made everything worse as well.
with Monty. It made it worse. You just
You're always better when you go out by
yourself. I've had it with Monty. I've
had it with Ant-Man.
Someone forgets the ID,
someone tries a cop block. You're just
better by yourself with these kind of
things. You really, you really, really, really are.
Which is mad because people make fun out
of it. You know, if you went out, if you
went out right now and you went for a
drink as opposed to going out with six
people, people would make fun out of it,
which is strange because you'll enjoy
yourself going out more.
You have no response. You don't have to
like it just it just is better. It's
just way better. Way way way better.
It's better in every way, bro. Trust me.
But yeah, I'll be [ __ ]
I'll be [ __ ] someone over.
Still still on that way to try and find someone. But
all the bad experiences they gave me
over the years, bro. Someone needs to
pay for it. Yeah.
Well, my morning jeans, my nice coat.
It's mad, Stephen. How would people on
Reddit still think that you're going to meet someone?
I just can't imagine it. I just can't imagine.
You go out, you everyone's got the same
attitude. They all do and say the same
thing. Another one to add to the [ __ ] collection.
How these people say women aren't all
the same. H I don't know. But yeah, hold on.
I just didn't have the energy.
I didn't have the energy to really do it as well. Yep.
Laney says it. Reddit says it.
Laney was saying to me earlier we was
having an argument that explain your
experiences. Nope. I'm not explaining
them to you. None of your business. I'm
not telling you nothing cuz everything
someone every time someone says
something to you,
all you're going to do is dismiss it. So
there's no point of the whole conversation.
You've clearly dismissed struggles. You
don't need to know what happens.
But I was I was going to start at diamond yesterday.
I was going to start madness, bro.
Madness over Instagram. And I'm not
going to be a keyboard either.
I feel like these people really need to
pay for what they've done
over the years, the time, the money, the [ __ ]
Someone needs to really pay, bro, for
all the [ __ ] they've done over the years.
And I'll be putting that [ __ ] [ __ ] on
Instagram in her place tomorrow as well.
They just still say the same thing that
you're going to meet someone.
So if you're going to say something to
me, say it to my face. I'll meet you
anywhere tomorrow. Bring any man you
want. You know, bring any man you want.
I'm going to say it as soon as I wake up.
Stop pissing me off, bro.
You're the one that needs help. You sick
individual. You sick [ __ ] Yeah.
You know what I mean? I'll meet you
tomorrow in front of any man you want.
Bring any man you want and I'll tell you
about yourself to your face in front of any man. [ __ ]
So, I better wake up to a [ __ ] reply
tomorrow, please, from this [ __ ] who I
met months ago [ __ ] messaging me.
Nope. Go away, you little white knight.
And this isn't actually revenge.
I was going to say this is actually
revenge for people not meeting me. Nah,
not really. I'm doing this cuz I need to do this
to be honest. I won't even put it on
YouTube to be honest.
But yeah, this diamond I might start
madness, bro. I really might start
madness and I will really finish it this
time for real.
One of these people really need to pay,
bro. One of them. One of them. Could be
anyone. USA people you met recently,
people you met 6 months ago. They really
need to pay for what they've done, bro.
Really, really, really need to pay.
You know, it's not normal waking up with
mood swings time and time and time and
time and time and time again.
So, yeah, I was just going to stay in
bed today and just save money. I weren't
going to do anything
cuz it's insane depressing. You know,
there's no one for you. You know you're
hopeless. So, what are you doing, bro?
You don't need to keep trying to meet
new people. You don't need to keep
trying to meet new people. you know,
there's no one for you. So, a wise
person would do the right thing and
leave or save up to leave, which is what
I was doing. You know,
you know that you're never going to meet anyone.
You don't need to keep meeting people.
They're all the same. They're all the same [ __ ]
But this person's 26. I'm 28. So, we'll
see if they reply tomorrow.
They didn't seem stuck up, but they
could be devious via message. They could
still be They don't come across as stuck
up, but who knows? We'll see tomorrow. Anyways,
I said I'm going to send it tomorrow,
bro. I said I'm going to send it right
now. I did.
Sad, isn't it? Really?
Really, really sad life we living.
Not spoke about enough.
It's going around in circles. Is it?
It's not like you ain't tried. It's not
like you've not looked your best. It's
not like you're in a wheelchair. It's
not like you're ugly. So, there's really
no reason for it. This is what I was
saying to this transgender in in
Scotland. There is no reason for these
experiences. You're not ugly. You're not
disabled. You haven't lost your arms and
legs. You're not blind. There is
literally no reason for this. There is
literally no reason for this. These bad
experiences, there is no reason for this.
Yeah, they do dismiss my struggles.
That's why I don't tell Laney anything
because it just gets dismissed. It's
annoying as [ __ ]
Yeah, the dismissing struggles is very annoying.
It's like, okay, so say you you you show
what a woman does and you say that you
want to get revenge. They will turn
around and say, oh, you need help. But
they will always dismiss whatever they do.
They will always always dismiss what
they do even though they say they don't.
They'll be like, "Oh, well, you know
what I mean?" So,
I had that earlier. I had that Well, I
had that yesterday.
prostitutes for the rest of their life.
UK asylum. Is that what people are
supposed to do? Use prostitutes for the
rest of their life?
Really, bro? What people do supposed to
use prostitutes for the rest of their
life? [ __ ] It's [ __ ] sick, mate. It's disgusting.
I didn't want to get out of bed today
when I woke up, bro. I felt like going
out and doing someone in.
Yeah, but you shouldn't have to use
escorts. I shouldn't have to use
There's no reason I'm in the position
that I'm in.
That's why we can't because there's no
reason for it. There's literally no
There is no reason for it. It's not like
you've not tried. It's not like you're
handicapped. It's not like you're ugly.
It's not like there is literally no
reason for it.
There's not one reason for this
situation. You're not scared to
approach. You haven't not tried
like Ario man 36 never approached
anyone. There's no reason for it. That's
the thing. There's no reason. And you
can't even blame yourself. That's the
That's the problem with it.
At least if you never tried, you can
say, "Oh, yeah.
I haven't tried."
Oh, whatever. But there is no reason.
There is no reason for this. You know,
it's not bad luck. It's the country.
It's not about luck. It will never change.
If something was about luck, it would
have changed. It's not about It's not
luck. They're all the same. So, it's not
about luck. It's It will never change.
Luck is losing 500 on roulette. Luck is
winning 500 on roulette.
So, so there's no reason for it. So,
I'll be in bed all tomorrow depressed.
Good. That's nice. Good for them, bro.
There's loads of virgins out there.
There's loads of single people out
there. Good for them.
There's some people out there with no
legs. There's black people out there.
There's white people out there. Good for
them. There's people that die every day.
There's people that have cancer every
day. There's people that are diagnosed
with cancer every day. Just one of them things.
Doesn't mean anything, does it?
What does that mean?
I mean, we can we can use so many different examples.
There's virgins out there.
There's people that have never met
anyone. There's there's worse people
than me out there is is What's What's your point?
What's your point? They They don't give me hope.
Just cuz there's people that get married
every day, they don't give me hope.
The only thing that can give me hope is
me getting better experiences.
So, which is never going to happen. So,
I don't really care about other people
when it's to do with comparing.
Nope. It would never happen.
It would never happen cuz I'm not like
Antman. I'm smarter than that. And if I
was ever going to chuck piss at someone
and really [ __ ] someone over, I wouldn't
put on camera.
I would never put it on camera. So yeah,
it's mad that it's even come to this.
Maybe. Yeah, maybe. I don't know what I
would do. Who knows what I would do.
They're just [ __ ] That's all they
are is [ __ ]
It's so bad that we're even having this
conversation, bro. You do realize it's
not normal, is it? We should have had
better experiences. We should have met
someone by now.
There's no reason for it.
What do you want me to do? And and the
thing I And the thing is, right, you
should have to keep trying again. You've
already tried. You don't need to keep
going out. You've already gone out time
and time and time and time again. You
don't need to keep going out. You should
have to keep going out and trying.
You've tried more than everyone in the
[ __ ] world. You don't need to try.
You've tried and tried and tried and
tried and tried and tried and tried and
tried and tried. You don't need to keep [ __ ] trying.
[ __ ] off. You know,
it is really sad. It is really sad.
Really sad. Sad life, isn't it?
Especially when someone's tried as much
as I have. I love to see people in a
world that has tried as much as I have.
They love my full sympathy.
I had it today. Three times in a row I
have a boyfriend.
Make believe that aren't with them. I
was like, "Okay, this is giving me a
headache. This will give me a headache
now." I messaged my mom. I said, "Is
there have you got the keys in the
boot?" I was about to bounce, bro.
Before it was really starting to wind me
up. I was just like, "I'm just going to
get a black cabin. [ __ ] off. Just go to bed."
It's that that depressing. You know,
we've heard all of this before. We've
dealt with all of this before. This is boring now.
This is boring now. You know, boring. Boo.
You know, so I was just going to go back to bed.
Well, I got one number that like drop me
a message and [ __ ] but who knows?
Like I don't really think it's going to go anywhere.
It's bad, isn't it? Really, really, really bad.
And the most annoying thing is as
someone with my history and the fact
that you can't do anything about it either
because you can't you tried more than
anyone in the world.
So that's one thing and B there's
nothing else you can do which is but try
and then get more bad experiences.
So this is where you'll always go around
in circles in this country. So even if
you you can I can live off £30 a week. I
don't mind living depressed £30 a week.
If it if I know I'm going to leave at
the end of it and have a better quality
of life, I'll do it.
Um because you're depressed when you're
dating women. Depressed, toxic, miserable.
You know, that's how you are when you're
when you're dating. Which is why I gave
up. And I think what I I knew I think
the reason I woke up in a bad mood today
is cuz I knew what I was in for. I knew
what I was in for, bro.
I was like, "Oh, no. Not this again."
So just stress that people don't need.
Yeah, they looked all right. Yeah.
Not that it matters anyways.
I don't want to sit here. And then they
met my sister and her friend, which I
didn't really want happening, but
not a problem. They didn't didn't get
their numbers. I got the number, so it doesn't matter.
I got the number.
So, we'll see.
But yeah, we'll see anyways.
I can't even remember.
That boyfriend is so boring.
Yeah, go away you weirdo. That line is so boring.
That I've got a boyfriend and [ __ ] is so boring, bro.
Oh, that is so boring.
No, it wasn't. No, it wasn't.
I think I just went up and said hello. I can't remember.
Yeah, you're going to wake up with a
hangover tomorrow. Yeah.
It's bad, is it?
I have a boyfriend. I have a boyfriend.
[ __ ] off. God, that is so [ __ ]
annoying. I heard it like three times. I
just wanted to [ __ ] off.
See, when you're alone, you can [ __ ] off
by yourself, you know?
I'm spamming this [ __ ]
Why does the Reddit mods ban on why do
they ban on Reddit UK asylum?
Yeah. Proper, proper, proper.
Cuz they don't get paid for it.
They don't get paid for it, do they? boring repeating.
We've heard all this before.
It's like what Monty man. It's just the
same people doing the same [ __ ]
Isn't that right, Grezy? Same people
doing the same [ __ ]
It's the same people doing the same [ __ ]
True, don't it?
This community needs to change, bro.
This is boring as [ __ ] Anyways, greasy.
Just another day to add to the [ __ ] collection.
Another day to add to the [ __ ] collection.
You can laugh at it. I'm not laughing. I
think it's [ __ ] depressing. I don't
even know how anyone can laugh at it.
What would happen if you hold your pee in?
Say you had to go to pee. Say you had to
go pee and you held it in. Would you
just piss yourself?
Do you reckon you would just piss yourself?
[ __ ] that. You can't hold your PM, bro.
Yeah, I'll be in bed.
I'll be in bed all day tomorrow greasy
because all the things I would like to
try in life
all the things that I would like to try
in life are impossible.
You want a new you want to if you want a
new episode, bro, I can get you a new
episode. You you you find a different community.
Yeah, bro. Try another community. If you
want a If you want a new episode, bro,
go find a new community.
This is always going to be repeating on here.
Repeating. Fat ugly people ain't got a
life. Get used to it or leave.
Low lives here, lad. Yeah.
Well, I mean, I went out Triple H. What
did you think was going to happen?
I mean, what did you think? Was the
women going to be different or I mean,
I'm not long come back home. What did
you think was going to [clears throat]
What did you think was going to happen?
So, even if this person messaged, I
don't mind traveling 40 um 40 minutes to meet someone,
but I'll probably just [ __ ] them over as
well to be fair. I mean, I went out and
I've not long come back. So,
why was it going to be a different episode?
We're going out approaching women in England.
It will never change. It has not changed
for five, six years. It will never
change. I mean, that's why I didn't want
to go out. But I got I got forced to go
out. Greasy. I basically got forced to go out. Forced? Hm.
So, good news. You You What? What did
you think? The women was going to stop
pretending they had boyfriends. Same old
boring [ __ ] What did you think, bro?
What did you think?
What did you really really think?
You're approaching in England.
What did you think was going to happen?
They weren't going to pretend they got boyfriends.
Well, you never know. This person might reply tomorrow
and, you know, meet up.
What the [ __ ] did you think was happen?
Well, it's never Well, I've got more
chance of winning the lottery.
Yeah, but why would it change? It's not
changed in 5 years.
So why would it change now? Is what I'm
is what I'm saying the truth. Grezy,
think about it like this. Right, Grezy?
You've been going out for years, right?
No changes. Years. Years. So, we're not
new to this game. Now, why? Why? How is
it going to change?
Well, this has been, like I've told you
multiple times, this has been going on for years.
If anything was going to change here, it
would have changed by now. You know it.
I know it.
Yeah, the incel. Yeah, it's boring now.
Yeah, the incel [ __ ] is boring now, bro.
It died a long time ago. Calling people
an incel that don't suck up to women.
Yeah, it's boring now.
Yeah. Anyone that doesn't suck up to
women is an incel. Yeah. We know, bro.
It's boring now. It's like calling a
woman a [ __ ] It has no substance.
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. You I
mean, you're comparing me to an incel murderer.
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Cuz I
don't suck up to women.
Why is this one gone quiet as well? He
started [ __ ] when I was out drinking.
Why is she gone quiet now? The little [ __ ] [ __ ]
Dude, you're actually insane. Get help.
Coming for you.
I didn't even enjoy myself today as well
cuz of my um what happened and that.
There's no worth a shot about it.
There's no worth a shot about it. It
will work. Oh, I messaged someone yes.
Oh, I actually messaged someone
yesterday, Grezy. Some American. I said,
"Oh, let's go for a steakhouse." Yeah,
let's go for a steak. Again, I was going
to [ __ ] him over. Someone that I
approached like 5 weeks ago. They blocked me.
Like, who do they think they are
thinking that they're better than you?
Who did these dick? And I was going to
[ __ ] her over as well. It's not even
like I liked her. I was like, who can we
find? And they're blocking you like
they're better than you, [ __ ]
And they're blocking you like they're
better than you. Are you [ __ ] mental,
bro? Are you [ __ ] mad, [ __ ] Yeah.
Well, I need to message some people and
then go to bed, I think.
Oh, there was a cat today. He kept
trying to come up.
Yep. The cat was trying to come in the
balcony today when I was at my sister's.
He was trying to copy. He was looking
for a copycat statement. Yeah. I don't
think I videoed it. I said, "Fuck off
you cat." The ginger cat. Yeah. I
[ __ ] hate that cat. copies. [ __ ] off.
You see the towel? Look.
I don't want to feel left out. One second.
[ __ ] [ __ ] Look at the tail. [ __ ] off.
He kept talking about Cheryl Cole. [ __ ] off,
greasy. He kept talking about Cheryl
Cole. The cat thinks I'm gay. [ __ ] off. Shoot.
It's my sister's cat. I hate this cat.
No, I don't. I'm I'm not going to be
bullied into thinking you're way. Look,
it was trying to copy.
It thought he was missing out. I said,
"We're only out here chilling, bro."
Like, you're the cat actually thought he
was missing out.
Um because he doesn't show his losses.
Bit like stop it uh stop and step. Yeah.
He doesn't always win, bro. The guy's an idiot
trying to tell me the high life is over.
I can gamble whenever I want. I can
drink whenever I want. I just don't want
to. [ __ ] idiot.
Again, talking about people that you
don't [ __ ] know, idiot, man.
So yeah, I'll message this uh this uh person tomorrow.
Yeah, that all night mic uh Triple H has
been doing this for years. Like I said,
even when I was back at the old house in
the summer when I used to go for walks,
these people have been repeating for a
very long time now.
But they say everyone else is low IQ.
I won't wake up more positive or wake up depressed.
There's no better days ahead. Not one
single better day. I mean, I wouldn't be
wanting to live off 30 pound a week if
there was better days ahead. I'm I'm I'm
living off 30 pound so I can leave this
country. I mean, I could work and go
faster, but I don't want to work. So,
and like I said, a month and a half I
can go cuz like I said, I've already got
some money saved up. So,
I wouldn't be saving I wouldn't be
living off 30 quid a week, mate. 304 a
week if there was hope here. I'll do
anything to leave now.
Yeah, they've been doing it for seven years.
It's just like if I went out on
Saturday, it would be the same thing again.
It would be the same thing again.
Not interested. Boyfriend numbers that
lead you on. It's never any different.
Never ever any different.
Yeah. He's been doing it for seven years.
Yeah. Definitely seven years.
These people have been doing it for
years, but they say they they say that
other people are low IQ, but then they
just sit and repeat all day.
But don't forget, Grevy, everyone else
is low IQ and these people are smart,
yet they sit and repeat every day.
But yeah, this person, I hope they reply
back tomorrow cuz it's a good age, 26 and 28.
But nah, I'd expect them to probably not
reply or reply once, don't reply or lead
me on. Never going to be any different.
It's never going to be any different.
Every sad life
Yeah, it doesn't matter if she does or
she doesn't. She's not going to meet.
We've seen it all before. We've heard it
We've heard it all before.
What I'm saying?
Reddit told me I'd meet someone. Greasy.
Oh, Reddit's banning me again.
They keep banning me even though I don't
post anything. I just message people and
they keep banning me.
Yeah, right. She might be different.
they keep doing it UK side and I'm not
even posting anything. Why do they need that power?
Power hungry nerds.
I'm not buying a new [ __ ] phone
just so you can [ __ ] know what I mean. [snorts] Just
why do I keep banning it? Is it a power thingy?
Is it a power thing?
Oh, I went on Mom's Net.
Yeah, I went on Mom's Net.
Yeah, but they still have to ban you
manually though, so it's still a power
thing. I've been on Mum's Net. I've not
like I've read stuff they posted. I've
not posted myself.
I didn't post on it, but I know what it
is. I've seen people write about how
much money they've got left over for the
month. Some will say they've got £700
left for the month, etc.
bro. There's no see how you get on. It's
guaranteed. Thailand is guaranteed
you're going to get what you want.
So, it's not a case of maybe you will
get what you want there.
It's not like England where you're never
going to get anything for bad
experiences. It's not It is guaranteed.
It's not a maybe. It is literally
guaranteed to work.
So, it's it's it's always
and know that again, we've all been over this before.
There's women that you don't have to pay
that want to be in relationships.
There's women that want to be in relationships
that that you don't have to pay. So, no. Whatever.
But either way, what you going to do?
Stay here and be depressed all your life?
Sounds like England then, doesn't it?
Yeah, I'm depressed, bro.
Hopefully I die in my sleep today.
We can only pray.
I'm starting on this [ __ ] tomorrow as well.
I'm starting on this [ __ ] tomorrow on
WhatsApp, bro. No, it's not dramatic,
bro. You don't know how pissed off I was
earlier when I woke up, bro.
That's an understatement. You really don't know. So,
you really really don't know, mate.
Yeah. Well, it's not dramatic for me.
It's definitely not dramatic for me. So, yeah.
Not for me, mate. With the experiences I've had,
maybe for you, but it isn't for me. Yeah.
Bro, I went on YouTube once today at the
end of the day.
Same same time, same place. But I went
on YouTube once today at the end of the
day for a maximum of two hours,
which will be 2 hours when I leave.
Yeah. At the end of the day, I went on YouTube.
You probably been on here all day
just like LJ's little fans. What's
What's your point?
What's your point? Okay, so I come on
YouTube once a day for 2 hours. Okay, and
what's your point? Say I done it every
day for two hours at the end of the day.
Okay. What's your point?
Right. What's your point?
What's What's your point? So, yeah,
I tried to go to bed earlier earlier,
but I'm so frustrated. I don't go to bed
until like 600, 7. I can't sleep until
I'm physically exhausted.
Thinking about the dating [ __ ] and the
bad experiences. Enough to put anyone in a depression.
It's enough to put anyone in a [ __ ] depression, bro.
I think I didn't go to sleep today till
7, bro. 7 in the morning.
Anxiety? Nope. Don't have anxiety. Don't
have panic attacks. Nope. Don't suffer from anxiety.
So, nope. Definitely definitely don't
suffer with anxiety. So yeah,
nope. Definitely not anxiety. Don't have So
not faults, bad experiences.
Bad experiences with women. Nothing else.
I think I'll just separate myself from everyone
after um after today. I think
Oh, the gay thing. Oh, boring. We've
heard all this before. Turn gay. Turn
gay. Turn gay. Boring.
Sleeper. That gay thing is so boring.
Do you tell women that moan about men
that they should be lesbian?
No. So don't tell me about turning gay.
Yeah. You don't tell women that
generalize all men to go lesbian. So
don't tell me to go gay. Huh? Come on.
Let's be equal now. Let's not pick sides.
Yeah. Don't pick sides now. So yeah,
you're going on like I've never been
with a woman or had sex. I don't know
why this is turning into I've never had
a woman and had sex.
We're talking about the bad experiences
I'm having and what it's like now. So I
don't know why you're making it seem
like I've never been with a woman and
had sex. I don't know why that's turning
back into that again. I'm unbiased.
So, why does it always go back to being gay?
Why does it always go back to being gay? [ __ ] weird. Yeah.
Yeah. Yeah. Okay. I haven't had sex. Whatever. Anyways,
I think it's because this woman suffer.
Well, you haven't been through what I've
been through and you haven't tried
nowhere near the amount I've tried. So,
why would it affect you?
Yeah, that's a good point. But why would
it affect you?
You haven't tried nowhere near the
amount I've tried. You haven't been
through what I've been through.
So why would it affect you? I don't I
don't get your point.
That doesn't make any sense what you're
saying. Why Why would it affect you when
you don't try?
That doesn't make any sense.
So [ __ ] off.
It does cuz it's [ __ ]
It should affect you cuz it's [ __ ] That's why.
And it's still going on as well. That's
the thing. This problem is still going on.
Yeah. Okay, bro.
Well, it would affect me cuz I've tried
more than 90% of the population. So, why
wouldn't it affect me? It's been going
on for years. So, what am I supposed to
be all right about it?
Am I supposed to go out and keep dealing
with women's bad attitude?
I I don't know what you want.
You know what am I supposed to do?
So if you answer if you can answer a
question then you can maybe help me out
a little bit. Yeah.
What what what do you think we're going
to do? Go out every week and deal with
women's bad attitude and be fine about it.
I don't get your point.
Uh, I mean it's no mystery.
Women are stuck up with unrealistic
standards. I mean, I wouldn't say that's a mystery.
[ __ ] it's no mystery.
It's the West. Women are stuck up.
They've got Tik Tok brains.
Why? And I' and I have done better than
people on here. Why are you talking
about people on here?
Are people on here being seen with women
in bed kissing women? No. But I have.
And why are you talking about people on here?
These people don't leave their house.
Why are you talking about people here?
And it's good women are stuck up. Does
things does these things not register in your brain?
This is exactly why I don't explain my
experiences to Laney because it's one
ear in and out the other. Same old boring conversation.
Very bad for your mental health. So yeah. Yep.
I'll be going bed in a minute.
Well, I'll be on Reddit and [ __ ] I need
to message some people.
Doesn't matter what my experiences were.
You know what they are. I put it up. If
you didn't dismiss people's struggles,
you would know what it is. You'd know
what my experiences were if you kept it.
If you never if you didn't stop
dismissing my struggles,
I wouldn't give a [ __ ] if I died
tomorrow. I've done all of what I wanted
to do. Been on a plane, been abroad,
live my life. I don't need to live, bro.
This life is dead.
You know what? We're in the dating game.
You know it. I know it. So yeah,
I wouldn't give a [ __ ] if I died, bro.
This life is dead anyways.
That's how this country makes you feel, you know.
Yeah, I need to message my friend. I
need to message some people back.
I don't understand how Reddit can tell
you that you're going to meet someone
when every time you go out it would
always be the same
cuz I didn't want to and you're not
worth my time.
Simple. You're not worth my time. And
everyone's biased on here. So
yeah, cuz you're not worth my time.
So yeah, I don't understand how Reddit
can tell you one thing,
but it's always going to be the same old.
Reddit tells you one thing, bro. Yeah. [ __ ] idiot.
I'm going to stay off socials for a while.
Cuz it's funny. Yeah,
I had a really [ __ ] night today, bro.
Even without the wind thing, I didn't
even enjoy it. I can't even say I had a
good night, you know.
Yeah, man. Whatever. Whatever,
bro. You people are not worth meeting on
here. You're [ __ ] weasels. You're not
even worth meeting.
We've seen it all before. What you
people do on here. You're not even worth meeting.
So that's that.
Yeah, cuz you was pissing me off. So yeah, that's So yeah.
Yeah, I am, bro.
I couldn't even afford a train ticket.
Yeah. Okay, bro. Whatever you say.
Are you right? Huh? What?
I mean, I spent over £100 today. So, yeah.
Can't afford. Can't afford. You don't
know how much money I have.
I'm going to make a tea, take some
pills. best with some friends and go to
sleep, I think.
Yeah, it's not going to lead to anything.
I am not showing you anything. I am not
showing you nothing.
Nope. I'm not showing you one pence. How
about that one?
I don't need to prove myself to you. Get a grip.
I just told you I spent over £100 today
and you're asking me to show you £31.
Bro, just stop it. It's embarrassing.
Now, stop creating the same atmosphere. Oh, Franklin,
stop coming on here creating the same atmosphere.
Yeah, I'm a skin virgin. Okay.
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. That's definitely it.
Yeah. calling me a virgin when I prove
I've had sex and this is why people
don't meet you and then you just
wondering why people don't meet you
because you're all biased. Bro, I could
easily come today and smack your face
and give you a couple of uppercuts, but
it's a waste of my time. Doesn't matter
what I've said, it's a waste of my time.
Whether I called you out, whether I
didn't call you out, you're a waste of my time.
You called me a virgin. What the [ __ ]
bro? Even though I proved I had sex.
[ __ ] sake, bro. Stop it now. It's
embarrassing, man. [ __ ] clown.
I could easily go and smack you in your
face. I can meet you tomorrow and beat
and beat the [ __ ] out of you. But what's
the point? You losers are not worth it.
You losers on here are not worth it.
You're really, really not worth it, bro.
None of you are worth it.
You're calling me a skinned virgin. [ __ ] sake. Yeah.
So, yeah. I'm not meeting you. Wait, are
you calling me out?
Wait, so you're calling me out now?
Wait. So you're calling me out now?
So you're calling me out?
So are you calling me out now? Cuz I
told you why I'm not meeting you. You're
calling me out.
Oh my god. You're giving me brain
damage. Stop it.
[ __ ] off, man.
Yeah. And I told you why I'm not meeting you.
You called me a skinned virgin. [ __ ] hell, man. Biased.
Yeah. Yeah. Your your words don't hurt me, bro.
Cuz you're a keyboard warrior, so your
words whatever you say doesn't hurt me.
>> Yeah, man. Whatever.
Your words don't mean nothing.
Your words don't mean nothing. No one
needs to show anything to a [ __ ]
loser like you. You've already been
shown thousands of pounds before. I'm
not showing you nothing. You show me£30.
You come on here and talk and you show me£30
and I'll double it. Come on. Come on.
You come in the hangouts and you show
me. You show me £30 and I will show you 120.
Yeah. Yeah. Skinned virgin again. Okay. Same repeating.
You call people a skinned virgin when
they've shown more money than you have
and they've shown more women than you have.
Have you got autism or something, bro?
Because it's really embarrassing now.
Okay. Well, come in the hangouts and show me£30.
Come in the hangout. Show me £30 and I
will show you.
You know what? You you come in here,
show £30. I'll show you £500.
Can nip to the ATM. I don't have any
cash on me. I can show you £500 if you want.
That's the That's my uh maximum daily withdrawal.
Yeah, I'll show you £500. You show me
30, I'll show you £500. Make you look silly again.
Yeah. You're going to come in and show 30 pound
cuz if you want to prove something to
me, I don't mind proving something to
you. But the thing is with you clowns,
you always think that people need to
prove themselves to you.
You always seem to you you I don't know
why you seem to think people need to
prove themselves to you. This is a bit I
don't understand with you people on here.
You always seem to think people need to
prove themselves to you time and time
and time and time again.
I don't know why you think that people
need to prove themselves to you.
We're not talking about calling people
out. We're talking about you thinking that people
need No, but you're asking people to
show money. We're not talking about
that. You're asking people Why do I need
to show you 30?
Why would I need to show you? Bro,
you've been shown thousands before. And
you run away.
And you run away. You run run run run
Living with mommy. Bro, I at least I've
got a mom that loves me. Unlike you. At
least I don't live in some shitty area
like you. At least I've got a mom that
loves me. Your mom's probably a [ __ ]
prostitute. And that's what kills you.
You don't you ain't got a mommy that
loves you. That's the only reason you're
bitter with somebody living with their mommy.
Bro, your mom's probably selling her ass
for crack on the street every day. Yeah,
my mom hates me. Yeah. Okay, bro. Yeah.
Okay, bro. Where am I now, bro? Where
are you now? Where am I now? And where
are you now, bro? Listen, if you want to
come to London tomorrow, I'll happily
meet you anywhere.
Yeah. So, let's see what you're really
really really really about. Or if you're
the same like these little northern
[ __ ] Where am I now, bro? I'm at my
mom's right now. I'm here for Christmas.
You don't have a mom. Your mom's a prostitute.
Yeah. So, come to London tomorrow then.
If I'm skinny tomorrow, then not a
problem. I'll happily [ __ ] you up in
front of everyone. It's not a problem.
You You can go anywhere you want in
London and what time and I'll be there.
Anytime. And I will be there.
Yeah. Waterloo. Yeah.
Yeah. Waterlue. So, yeah.
Well, your mom's a prostitute. Don't
worry about who I live with. Your mom
hates you. Your mom hates you, you
little mug. And your mom's a little
prostitute. And I'll tell you it
tomorrow to your face, you little mug.
[ __ ] [ __ ] Yeah. I'll meet you in
Wateroo tomorrow at 5:00 p.m.
Yeah. Yeah, your mom's a little
prostitute. Little crackhead.
All cuz your mommy hates you. Don't
worry about who I live with. Worry about
your stinking fat ugly misses.
Yeah, that's who you need to worry about.
You remember Timmy yesterday? Grezy,
go live. Bro, you do a video there. You
do a video there and then I'll go live.
No. Okay, you do. Okay. Yeah. You do a
video when you're on the way and then
I'll go live there. Yeah. Yeah. Do do a
video on the train.
Yeah. Do a video on the train. It should
take you like an hour and then obviously
I'll make my way there.
Yes. So, make a video on the train so I know. Yeah.
I'm going to sub to your channel right now. Actually,
you little [ __ ] You've been trying to
troll me for a while as well, [ __ ]
Yeah. One second. I'm going to sub to
your channel right now, actually. So,
you ain't got no excuses tomorrow.
You ain't going nowhere, mate. And I'm
going to show everyone that as well.
Yeah. Where are you?
So, I am
So, I'm sub to your channel now.
So, you I'm sub to your channel. You can
see I've just subscribed to your
channel. I'd like to see you tomorrow, bro.
Waxies. Why am I going to go wax?
Why do you want me to approach people in
waxies, bro? I don't want to bother people.
All these women have boyfriends,
apparently. Why do you want me to bother
people that are in relationships?
Yeah, I don't meet. Yeah, yeah, yeah. Whatever.
So, what are you lot doing in 2026? Are
you still going to be doing this?
repeating the same old [ __ ] being
keyboard warriors, because to be honest
with you, it is getting quite boring now.
It's actually getting quite boring now.
It's getting quite boring.
Yeah. Do a video when you're on the train.
Do a video when you're on the train. It
doesn't take me an hour to get there.
That's near where I met my mama at
Waterloo. I think I had to get that I
had to get off that station to meet my
mama Grezy Waterloo.
I actually met my mama in Waterloo and
then went to Elephant Castle. So I know
how to get there. Yeah.
Yes. Okay. I'm sub to you.
That's where I met my mama. Pathetic
bro. Don't worry about who I live with.
Worry about you and your ugly fat girlfriend.
Don't worry about who I live with. Your
mom's a little crackhead. Stop changing
the subject. Come, come tomorrow and
I'll be there. Simple. You little farmer boy.
Oh, so so you're not coming now?
Oh, it doesn't matter who I live with.
Your mom's a little crackhead that don't love you
cuz you must be slating Triple H then
cuz he's almost 30 and he lives with his parents.
So you're you're actually insulting
Triple H as well cuz uh Triple H is with
his parents and he's 30 pretty much.
Look at you. So now you're changing the
subject now. Now you're talking about
people living with people. What the
[ __ ] bro? Don't worry about who I live
with. You're going to get smashed
tomorrow if you if you actually come.
You little gay boy.
You little gay boy. Anyways, I'll see you tomorrow.
Yeah, he's almost 30 and he lives with
his parents. So what, bro? Don't worry
about who people live with.
So you're not meeting me tomorrow then?
So you're a [ __ ] house. So you're a [ __ ] house then.
So you're an absolute [ __ ] house then.
You're not coming tomorrow then? Yeah.
Nothing wrong with living with your mom at all.
How did you end up on the floor?
I didn't see you fell.
Step up. Receding. Not receding in the
slightest. Self projection.
Look at you. You know you're not going
to come tomorrow, mate. Everyone's seen
my hairline and I'm not bored like you
ugly [ __ ] Shut the [ __ ] up. Stop
selfjecting. You'll see my hairline
tomorrow just like everyone's going to
see your hairline tomorrow.
So, look at this guy. He's not beating
anyone. Look, I told you. I knew this
guy was a little [ __ ] You know,
before I started arguing this guy, I
knew this guy was a little [ __ ] The
way he was trying to troll as well about
I guess so. It's not I guess so. I know.
So I said that to you multiple times.
It's not Oh, m repeating. Oh, he's
repeating himself. Repeater.
[ __ ] repeating [ __ ] Repeater.
Just repeating little [ __ ] Look.
Repeating. Repeating himself. Repeating.
No new insults. This is what I mean,
bro. It's the same repeating with you
disabled people. It's the same
repeaters. Same episode,
bro. Listen, just come to Waterl
tomorrow at 5:00 PM. Stop being a keyboard warrior.
Oh my [ __ ] god.
Stop the M [ __ ] It's boring. Stop the
boarding [ __ ] It's boring. Think of
some new insults,
bro. Get the peanuts, bro. Listen. What?
How much do you get? £300 a month.
How much do you get? £300 a month. You
don't know how much money I get. You
don't know how much money I have.
Again, self projection. Same atmosphere.
Let's change it in 2026. Come on, M.
Oh [ __ ] man. Stop repeating. Seven years
Bing. Stop repeating.
You know what? I'm I'm getting so I'm
so so so I'm feeling so bad for you that
I might actually start giving you
insults to use on me.
You're supposed to be you're supposed to be intelligent.
You're supposed to be intelligent. So
why do you keep repeating
Lonely Melt? Yeah, we've heard it all
before. Lonely Melt. Yeah, it's
repeating. Anything new? If you tell me
a word, I'll tell you if it's if it's
repeating or not. Lonely melt. That's
repeating. You've been doing it for
seven years now. Try again.
Try again, bro. Come on. I'll give you
some insults on me if you want.
[sighs and gasps]
This is just repeating, bro. Repeating,
repeating, repeating, repeating,
repeating, repeating, repeating. It's
almost 2026. Come on now. You know,
it's just the same people doing the same [ __ ] [clears throat]
Yeah, I knew that ghosting was um dodgy anyways,
even when I wasn't arguing with him.
It's not I guess so. I [ __ ] know. So,
I've lost everything through YouTube.
Uh, I'm not Monty Man. Uh, I'm not Rice.
No, there's no long-term effects. No, I haven't.
Nope. No, I haven't. Uh, you're on the
wrong channel. That's Monty Man.
No, not me.
Definitely definitely haven't lost
everything through YouTube.
Yo, you're on the wrong channel, mate.
You're literally on the wrong channel.
You're on the wrong channel.
They never stopped my subleting and I'm
not getting into this again. They didn't
stop my subleting and I've got plenty of
money anyways without that. Try again.
I'm not getting into this again. So,
you're not meeting me tomorrow then
because now you're just talking a load of rubbish.
They definitely definitely did not stop
my subleting. Absolutely did not.
They absolutely did not stop my tublet
and I've got money and I make money.
Don't worry about that, Farmer Boy. Just
worry about coming to Waterloo tomorrow
at 5:00 p.m. They absolutely did not
stop my subleting because I would be
killing someone if somebody stopped my
income. Trust me, you little clowns
would know if you stopped my income. You
would know, bro. Like even if it wasn't
you, if anyone stopped my income, they'd
be getting killed. And I've said that
multiple times. I'm not I'm not a little
gay boy like you that know where people
live and you won't do anything. I'm not
a gay boy like you. I'm not a gay lord
that know where people live that can't
do anything. I'm not as much as a gay
lord where people's addresses get put
out there. Yes. And look what No, no,
no. Yes. He tried to get my money
stopped. I'm not repeating this again,
bro. I've already been over this a
million times. Yeah. He tried to get my
money stopped. £180. And what did I do,
bro? What did I do when he tried to get £180 stopped?
I put up posters and ruined his [ __ ]
life and he had to go to the police.
What was that over again? What was the
posters over? So, if anyone stopped my
sublet money, I would kill one of these
people. I'd [ __ ] kill him. And I'm
putting and I'm putting out on camera,
bro. Bro, you don't know how much money
I have and you don't know how much money
I get. Worry about meeting me tomorrow.
Don't you? I've got more money than you
will ever have. Do not worry about how
much money I get. I've got more money
than you will ever have. Don't you worry
about that. Just worry about meeting me
tomorrow at 5:00 p.m.
And don't be a [ __ ] house.
Do not be a [ __ ] house. Yeah, I bought a
Marty jeans on tick. Yeah. Okay,
whatever. Meet me tomorrow at 5:00 p.m.
So, you're not meeting me tomorrow then?
because by what you're doing now, you're
just proven to be a little gay boy. So,
you're just proving to be a gay boy,
bro. I I got my money jeans on tick.
Nah, I'm just not skintike you. I've got
more money than you. I know you can't
believe that people have got more money
than you, but I have more money than
you. I don't need to get stuff on tick.
I got more money than you, so I can
easily go out and buy stuff. Yeah. Simple.
So to that's it, bro. Cuz I don't use
colana. I'm not skint like you people. I
can afford 200 pound jeans. I'm not
skint like you people. I've never used
colana in my life. I'm not skint like
you. Never used colana in my life. I'm
not skint like you. I can easily afford
200 pound jeans. You're just jealous cuz
you you don't have designer stuff. It's
your jealousy because you people can
only afford Primark. You hate you can't
afford the money because you're wearing
Primark. That's why you That's why
you're saying people use colana because
you people are in Primark here.
Jealousy. We was talking about you
people earlier, bro. When I was drinking
with my friend. We was talking about this earlier,
bro. Never had to use Colana in my life.
I'm not skint like you people. Me and
you are not the same. Understand? You little [ __ ]
Yeah. Well, I'm saying it's Kana cuz I
say what I want. Yeah. And I'm not skint
like you. I don't wear Primark. So,
yeah. Like I said, Greavves Triple H,
any of you people that want to see
receipts? I'll happily show you them.
Steven Howard, do you want to see
receipts? I'll show you receipts if you
want. All the genuine people that
believe this [ __ ] I will happily
show you my trainer receipts. Happily
show you my gene receipts. Happily show
you money. Not a problem. I just don't
prove myself to fat ugly boy gay boys
that don't go on people's doors. I don't
show gay boys that know where people
live that can't go on their door
like you ghosting you [ __ ] gay boy.
And again, so you're not coming tomorrow
then. So you're not coming tomorrow. So
you So you've just [ __ ] yourself up.
Anyways, Steven Howard, Grezy, any of
you people, I'll happily show you these
receipts. Happily show you them. I'll
tell you where I got him from. I got uh
I got my trainers from Foot Asylum and I
got my jeans from Mainline May. Got both
of the receipts on my email. We're not
skint like you Primark boys. We're not
skint like you. We're not skint like you
people. Me and you are not the same. You
understand? We don't live your [ __ ]
skint life. Get that in your head.
Ghosting. I'm not so much of a [ __ ] gay boy.
I'm not so much as a gay boy that I know
where people live and I can't even come
in my Primark clothes like you. Just
worry about showing up tomorrow at 5:00
p.m. Just just worry about showing up
tomorrow at 5:00 p.m.
Look at him. He's not meeting anyone. Do
what I mean? He's a little gay boy. This
is what I mean with the people in this
community. A [ __ ] gay boy. Look what
I mean. He's not meeting anyone now.
This is what I mean. This is what these
fat ugly people do. This is what we was
talking about earlier. I was talking
about this earlier with my friend. This
is what these fat ugly gay people do on
here cuz they ain't got a life. We were
talking about you earlier, bro.
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Anyways, I'll
see you tomorrow. Anyways, bro. Yeah.
Don't make excuses. Everyone sub to your
channel. You little gay boy. You little
[ __ ] gay boy. Gay lord with no mom.
Yeah. Anyways, you can get a time out
now. I'll see you tomorrow.
See you later, man.
Oh [ __ ] I just blocked him. I need to
unblock him. One sec.
I meant to um time him out, but I
blocked him. I just unblocked him. Yeah.
I'll see you tomorrow anyways, little [ __ ] [ __ ] [ __ ]
This is what I mean with these people.
They're even jealous when people can
afford designer jeans because they
can't. It's madness, isn't it?
You did not stop my You did not stop my
sublet money. I knew exactly what you
was going to say before you even said
it. You little gay boy.
You're a little gay boy. [ __ ]
[ __ ] This is why I don't come on
here, bro. This is why you didn't see me
on here today, bro. I hate these people
on here, bro. I hate them.
Yeah, sure can. One second. [ __ ] [ __ ]
It shows ain't got a life on here.
Like I said,
Like I said, bro,
if you want to see if you want to see my [ __ ]
No, it's not just It's not being wound
up. It's just the same repeating. It's
like watching the same film over and
over and over again. It's not being
wound up. It's just repeating. And it's
been going on for seven years now with
these people. It's not about being wound
up. It's just the same repeating, the same atmosphere.
That's what it is. Bit like what Monty man says.
It's the same self-reflecting fat ugly nerds.
You know what I'm saying, bro? Fat ugly nerds.
So, like I said, Grezy,
I'd love to show you my receipts for
things. Steven Howard, I'd love to show
you my receipts. Triple H, I'd love to
show you my receipts.
And I'll make a point of not proving it
to these people because I don't need to
prove myself to these people. But if
genuine people believe their [ __ ]
I'll happily prove it. I'm not proving them nothing.
They go on about Kana cuz they use Kana
cuz they're skint. Why do you think
they're on here from the time they wake
up to the time they go bed? Cuz they're
skint. Not to be a repeater, but think
about it, bro. Why do you think they're
sat on here all day hating? Cuz they are skint.
That's why Colana comes to mind because
they ain't got no money. They ain't got
no life. They ain't got [ __ ] all.
Don't worry about how much money I have.
Don't worry about how much money I get.
I got more than you. Simple as that.
You definitely definitely did not stop
my sublet money. You definitely did not.
No one did that. You're just saying that
you do that. You're saying that you do
that so you get a reaction. We all know
that if someone stopped my I would they
would be dead. They would be seriously
seriously seriously seriously injured.
You know, look what happened to [ __ ]
non legs with the with the posters. That
was over £180.
That was over £180.
Yeah, £180 when you're getting three
grand a month. It's not the point. I
didn't need £180, but it's that that's
not the point. It's the principle, bro.
You're not going to [ __ ] try and
cause stress in my life trying to get
any bit of money of mine stopped. And
look what happened. That was all over
the um that was all over the the the £180.
It was all over the £180, bro.
It's not the point. And I expect anyone
to be the same as me if they're not if
they're about it. If they're not about it,
you know what I mean? Anyone that tries
stopping my money, bro, you [ __ ] mad.
They'll get they'll [ __ ] they'll pay.
They'll [ __ ] pay, bro. Simple.
Definitely definitely not lost
everything over YouTube. Definitely
definitely not. You got the wrong channel.
But I knew that account was [ __ ]
anyway, Steven Howard. Even when it was
coming on here being normal,
because he was saying stuff like, "I
guess so." No, it's not I guess so. I know so.
No, no, no. I know so. He was trying,
oh, he was saying about how um yeah,
these people do this for reaction. And I
said, "Even when you don't react to
them, they still do it." And he said, "I
guess so." I was like, "No, I know." So,
there's no guessing in it. I know
because I know what these people do. So, yeah.
Just another bomb.
Just another bomb. Just another low life.
It just goes to show that these people
ain't got a life coming on here every
day doing this. It just shows they ain't
got nothing in their lives. So, we'll
just leave him through it anyways.
Yep. I'm Yep. I'm blocked and I'm sub to him.
So, £30. What the [ __ ] bro?
They're just repeating bastards.
I've actually got £1,500
actually to last me a month.
What do you think of that we £1,500 to
last me a month?
Do you think this is that's enough?
Yeah. You'll wait, bro. You'll wait, won't you?
Bit like me. I'll [ __ ] wait. Eh,
what do you think, bro? £1,500 for the month.
Well, I spent 100 today, so Yeah,
you absolute virgin.
Just depends on things that you need to
buy and that is it.
Yeah. Last month was 1,700.
Yeah, it was 1,700, wasn't it?
So, what? Yeah, we'll see if this person
replies back tomorrow.
No, not the same old sad song, Grezy. Come on.
How the [ __ ] do you know?
How do you know about mom's net?
How do you [ __ ] know about that, bro?
What did you get? What did you get
susted? What did you get susted?
What the ghosting out.
What the ghost account?
Yeah, I got a sus from um
about the I guess so. It's not I guess
so. I [ __ ] know. So yeah,
I still need to buy that 250 phone
once it's on offer. Yeah.
Yeah. They're just s people, lad.
They're just s people.
Yeah. The link. Yeah.
just sad people that ain't got a life.
Like you can tell how sad they are. Yeah.
Cuz And you can tell how skinn they are
because they're jealous of Ammani jeans,
bro. Like they're jealous because
someone can afford 200 pound jeans.
Like this is how sad these people really are.
They're sad that they're triggered
because you can afford [ __ ] Ammani jeans.
The [ __ ] scenes on that, bro.
Cuz you can afford a mile jeans.
[ __ ] all because you can afford a
James. It's [ __ ] madness, bro. They're jealous.
Imagine being jealous of Ammani jeans,
bro. That is [ __ ] bad, bad.
>> [clears throat] >> mad.
I told this guy that had done 120 on a
bet. He's like, "You're mad?" I was
like, "I'm mad. Why am I mad?" He says,
"Yeah, [ __ ] 120 on a bet." He said,
"It's mad, Greasy.
Putting 120 on a bet. Yes. >> Yeah.
You want to see them, lad? I needed I
needed them to dry cuz I peed on them a little bit.
Yeah, I pissed on them a little bit. So
yeah, they're just sad bastards. They
ain't got a life. Just leave them to it,
lad. Just sad people.
What makes me laugh is they think they
know people's life. That's so it is
funny, you know. Look at these jeans.
You'll never be able to afford these jeans, lad.
You'll never be able to afford them.
Yeah. They'll never be able to afford
these jeans, lad.
No, just a little bit. Yeah.
Yeah. That's what they're jealous of
because they can't afford 200 pound jeans.
So, of course, they're going to say that
you got it on tick cuz they can't afford them themselves.
jealousy with these people in this community.
190 pounds. That reminds me, I need to
wipe my trainers.
Yeah, I [snorts] need to wipe these
trainers. Oh, they got a bit dirty.
We got some lemon wipes down there.
Where the [ __ ]
need some wipes? Oh, here we are. Here
we are, mate.
Oh, some already opened. Some Oh, they
are, aren't they? But these ones are
like Hold on.
No, they're not.
Yeah, I I I knew that ghost account.
What did you say? Triple H.
You said there's sad people on it, don't
you? You said, didn't it?
You said there sad people in it.
What? You said what you mean? The sad people there.
Some lovely lemon wipes wipes. Trailers.
There people on him.
They're absolute virgins on here if you ask me.
Yeah, I need to wipe these trailers now.
>> Keep them good. You know, these people
on YouTube can never afford these trailers. Really? Yeah,
cuz their skin [ __ ] Yeah,
they can never afford 200 pound jeans.
Say ain't about that life. Triple
saying ain't about that life, lad.
Wipe these nice.
Wipe them lovely and nice.
And then put them let them dry.
Wipe them lovely and dry. Sorry. Wipe
them lovely. Let them dry.
Put him back in the box.
You're an absolute virgin.
How can you say that? You absolute virgin.
Well, I want Timmy to come on here. Do
you like it when Timmy comes on here, Grezy?
Yeah, they're lush these wipes.
Look, man. Whoa.
They look brand new. I like to keep
these good, you know, because
of how much the [ __ ] cost.
Cost a lot of money. Obviously, these
fing skin flints can't afford it.
Skinner than a [ __ ] skin flint.
You're skinting skin flint. Wipe him.
There we go.
Right. Clean them.
Let them dry.
Well, I agree with you. You said if you
have 600 to your name,
it's not skin, is it? away. Uh, Grezy,
you said if you've got uh,
you said if you got 600 to your name,
you're not skinned. Really?
to draw not really.
What about £800?
How about um how about what about
what about 800 gy
Oh, I done that [ __ ]
What about what about that?
Yeah, but you can't just But you can't
just save £10,000.
Yeah, but you can't just save
fucking£10,000 [ __ ] pound, can you?
Yeah. But then you won't be able to go
out drinking and stuff, would you?
So why is £600 why is £600 off the bills
not not that good uh green?
Why is that not good?
Don't you got to spend it or are you
£1,700 last month? I bought jeans and
[ __ ] Bought jeans, trainers. Yeah.
Well, that £900 off the bill's greasy.
I spent £80 today on food. Well, to be
honest, it weren't that bad. £100 20 g
restaurant and drinks.
They weren't even that bad. Uh how much
you should be 120 130. But when you're spending hundreds
when you're spending [ __ ] hundreds of
pounds like [ __ ]
What do you think that? What do you
think about 900 after bills?
See, I don't really get fast money
nowadays cuz I I don't gamble. So, I
don't have chances to really win, you know,
cuz I don't gamble, you see.
So yeah, I get fast money because I
don't want to risk money and then have
that problem to deal with, you know.
What do you think? Like if you had £900
left over for the month, Greezy,
and you had to go drinking,
could you do it?
You could go drinking every day, every
week, every Saturday if you had 900 pound. Yeah.
I reckon you could. What do you think?
900 pound crazy. And you wanted to go
out drinking every Saturday. Could Could
that last you a month, Grezy?
I think so. No.
Yeah. I don't think you'd spend £900 in
a month, would you? Yeah.
The only thing that
the only thing is is when you need to
buy new stuff. But if you don't need to
buy new stuff, then I don't need to buy
new I need to buy a new phone. But
do you think money is everything? Greavesy. Nah.
It's only It's only everything.
It It It's not any It's not everything. If
you uh If you don't have to stress about money,
then No, it isn't.
Not really. No.
That's the only time it's not everything
is when like you don't have to stress.
[ __ ] that, bro. Yeah, he was Yeah. No,
no, no. Yeah, he was okay on a flower.
What the [ __ ]
No, I don't even care really now about
the house when I lost the house at the
at the start. Yeah, cuz obviously, but
now I don't really care,
you know? It's just the money comes more
slower really. I don't really give a
[ __ ] to be honest.
No responsibility. Just not having that
responsibility. Greavesy is so nice. You
don't understand. Just not having that
responsibility of that house anymore is so nice.
You don't understand. You really don't
Like I said, last month I had £1,700.
I don't work. I'll still get money every week.
Yeah. I [ __ ] I'll take it. You know
what I mean?
I don't give a [ __ ] bro. Like, you know
I miss the house as in the house but
really not about the money brojusted anyways. So
the house thing was very very annoying bro.
the house thing.
I'd rather not have it, bro. Like, well,
I'd rather have it for the house and the
people, but the money is not even really
don't really give a [ __ ] bro, about money.
I mean, Rezy,
I really don't give a [ __ ]
Yeah, they were pestering me and you
didn't know when it was ever going to
end and that it was very scary, you
know, but I made the most out of it. I
gambled, drunk, traveled, but
so I don't really care anyways.
You absolute virgin Grezy.
You're absolute virgin.
What do you think of that, Grezy? You absolute virgin.
Do you think Tim is right, Steven
Howard? You can't win big money anymore gambling. Yeah.
Yeah, he's right. You can't.
No, you can't.
You can't, bro. He's right.
You really, really can't, bro. You can
only bet on football and [ __ ] hope you win.
You can't win big anymore.
100% you can't
industry's fittest, man. Yeah.
Greavves is such a little troll, you
know. Such a little troll.
You absolute virgin.
Yeah. Well, let's hope we message this
person tomorrow and they reply. But
what a [ __ ] day I've had.
Yep. I've seen it as well. It's called
Pips Inc. and they've been doing it for years.
Yeah, they've been doing it for [ __ ]
years. [ __ ] years. They've been doing it. Remember
Trip 8 said that he could live off 1,200
pound a month.
Triple said that he could live off
£1,200 a month.
Bless you then. No.
So, what do you say? 10K? I've never had
10 grand in my life. I've never had 10
grand in my life, bro.
The most I had was 7.8.
Yeah, I think I've had 7.8,000.
But I don't have, you know,
I might go out drinking next week. [ __ ] it.
Yeah, I think I've got about 15600 pound
to last me this month.
I've already gone out now. Had my
haircut. So, I can just go out next week.
Yeah, I can just go out next week. I
[ __ ] I probably might go out next week
to be fair, bro.
Thanks a lot for getting me into this [ __ ] again.
Thanks a lot, you absolute virgins.
What about you, Trip Ra? You don't get
your haircut every week, do you? Do you
remember when Bomb tried saying he got
his haircut every week? [ __ ] fantasy.
Got my hair today. Well, someone done it for me. Yeah,
it was hard trying to get that money,
bro. It was hard trying to build myself
up again, but I'd rather it than have
the house, to be honest. The house was annoying.
Yeah, the house was [ __ ] annoying, bro.
That house was really annoying to be fair.
Yeah. So, I'll probably go out tomorrow
uh next week. I won't get my haircut
then the week after. But I'm not going
to get the full service. I'm just going
to get my hair and beard done.
It's winter, is it? Uh yeah.
Yeah, it's win.
Uh, you reckon my hair will still look
good by next week?
You think my hair will still look good
next week? I think so, bro.
Probably should wash it to be fair. Yeah,
I might go for a hair wash in a minute. Triple H.
Yeah, I might go for a hair wash.
So, I'll go for a hair wash.
Is that cute? A hair wash.
Yeah, these [ __ ] have got me too far in
it now, bro.
Seriously, they have Well, hope this guy
shows up tomorrow. I can [ __ ] him up. Yeah, man.
I'm going to go wash my hair. One second.
One second, man.
My lovely hair wash.
Oh gosh. My mommy bought my my mommy
bought me my Ammani jeans.
Yeah, my mommy bought me my Ammani jeans. Captain. Okay. One second.
Yeah, I do sometimes. I was watching his cruise video,
but I don't believe that that the no
money thing. That's [ __ ]
because he cheated.
Yeah, I need to wash my hair. I'm going
for a hair wash, squeezy. One sec.
I'm going for a little hair wash. Oh gosh.
A little hair wash. You are
You absolute virgin. You're absolute
How do you know who is greasy?
Yeah, but the the no money the no money
challenge is [ __ ]
Yeah, but the no money challenge is [ __ ]
That is [ __ ] bro. Do you subscribe?
There's more to it than that.
I normally use Aussie shampoo.
Yeah, I I usually use the Aussie shampoo
usually, but we run out, so I'm using
the other one.
>> [clears throat]
>> Oh, [ __ ]
>> Why does he call you a virgin?
What can we bring up?
>> He's a virgin.
I said to I said to Montage,
"Why does [ __ ] nonsex call me a
virgin?" He says, "Cuz he's a virgin."
Yeah, he is.
He's a [ __ ] big virgin.
>> Yeah, he's a big virgin boy.
Because he's a virgin. Do you remember
that bra? Why does he call people a virgin?
Cuz he's a virgin.
Cuz he's a [ __ ] big virgin.
I want his margin eyebrow. Cuz he's one.
He's a virgin.
He's a big virgin. Never.
You were nowhere near that girl.
You were absolutely nowhere near that girl.
Never [ __ ] up. He's a silver bur.
I had a hair washy.
Do you like it?
Yeah. I need I can't sleep when there.
Did you see that little cat earlier
trying to trying to find a new copycat statement?
Oh [ __ ] Trying to find a new copycat statement.
[ __ ] pathetic, is it? You saw it
though, didn't you? movie
looking for its next looking for its
next victim. The copy.
[snorts] The copy. Oh, it made me laugh.
Yeah. When LT said LJ's kids is one of
his victims, I was dead, bro. They're
one of my victims.
Oh, he's a sick puppy.
O, he said that his kids is one of his victims.
I'm dead. I'm not sure. No one can
actually answer that.
Oh, I [ __ ] hate Christmas, bro. I
[ __ ] hate December. [ __ ] December, bro.
October all the way.
October. October. October. October.
Is that right, Grezy?
October. October. October.
But October is way better than December.
December's [ __ ] wank, bro.
December is wank.
Yeah, it's definitely wank.
December is a wank, bro.
All for nothing.
What do you think, Greaves? Did you say again?
October or December?
I say October. And not not just cuz I'm
born in October, just cuz the weather
and you got Halloween, some nice movies
usually. Not this year. I don't like December.
I don't like December, bro.
I'm just folding up my little tops. My
little All Saints tops.
What was you laughing at, um, Greavesy,
when someone said, "You can't come off
of YouTube. You're going to lose. You're
going to leave Grievy without any
content, poor fucker."
I haven't messaged her yet. I'm going to
message her tomorrow.
He lives like 40 minutes away.
Oh yeah, drop me a message. So,
but yeah, it was really bad today. I
even I even approached a fat one, a
really like fat stinking one just for
the ls. She weren't interested at all. [laughter]
But people on Reddit say you're going to meet someone.
Yeah, poor [ __ ] Yeah. The poor
Yeah. Yeah. That's the one. Yeah. Poor [ __ ]
Yeah. You can't come off here and leave.
Yeah. Poor [ __ ] Yeah. [laughter]
That's the one that's talks about
elephant and castle, isn't it?
Yeah. She was just unenthusiastic, so I
just walked away.
Do you know what I mean by that? Unenthusiastic.
You know what I mean by that, Grezy? Unenthusiastic.
Unenthusiastic basically means
it basically means, you know what it
means? Unenthusiastic. I just walked away.
So whenever being whenever be when they
were acting like [ __ ]
I just Yeah.
What do you think if I go out next Saturday, Grezy?
You reckon I'll meet someone?
Next Saturday, Grezy. If this one don't reply,
Reddit tells me I'll meet someone. So,
no, it's not. Yeah, but Greasy, can you
tell me what your opinion on this is?
What? You think I'm going to meet someone?
What if I go out next Saturday?
The only reason I might go out next
Saturday is because I've already had my
hair done in it. But it's when you've
not had your hair done. Why you going to
go and get your hair done for the sake
of it, bro? Like, depends, isn't it?
Well, you reckon I'll meet someone?
What? Next Saturday? Oh, I might have to try.
I've already had my hair done in it. So,
but I weren't actually going to go out
today. I swear to God I w to go out today, bro. Oh,
so no. I've got boyfriends and stuff.
They're not going to keep pretending
they got boyfriends. Yeah.
Like I said, I'll go out. I'll probably
go out next week and that'll be me. No.
Yeah, but people on Reddit say that I will.
Yeah, but Dusty's just being negative. Poor [ __ ]
Yeah, I approached this woman and then
she invited me and my sister to sit with
him and that. So, I got her number.
I'm a [ __ ] up [ __ ] bro.
My friend said, "You've got some balls
on you." I said, "Yeah, captain." Yeah, but
yeah, but Reddit says that I will find
someone. It just takes time.
That kebab was lovely today. Grezy,
I had a really nice kebab. Oh, this
Yeah, you would have loved it.
Bro, but you should leave him alone.
Leave him alone. Leave him alone.
You should leave Nonss alone. Cut him
some slack, bro.
You know, maybe you just wanted to fit
in with the crowd. You know how hard it
is like being being new in college.
Griezy, you need to cut the guy some slack, lad.
What do you want to do was bloody well
fit in with the crowd.
There you go with your [ __ ] You know
what I mean?
I think you need to really cut the dude some slack.
What do you want to do with bloody off him? You know,
Greasy, you're [ __ ] You ain't You got
something wrong with you. You've
really got something wrong with you, Grezy.
Yeah. Try not to get picked on. Yeah.
You really like you need to give him
some slack. Like cut him some slack. So
what if he wanted to fit in with the crowd? But what?
All he wanted to do was bloody well fit in. You know,
you know, all you wanted to do was
bloody well fit in with the crowd.
You know, it must be tough, you know, being there.
I'm I'm washing my tops.
Yeah. I'm washing my little tops of my
little tops. Is that cute, Grezy?
They said, "Hey, Monty said that these
people go for nonslegs because nonsle go
nons legs goes for me. Nonss goes for
me." No, that's not true. That's not
true at all. Nah, cuz even if he doesn't
go for you, these people will not go for
him. No, I don't agree with that.
No, I don't agree that at all.
>> No, because like I said, even if even if
he stopped going for you, right? Say you
went prison for like a year. Yeah. Say
you went prison for a year. Yeah. You
come out and you went on these you went
on these Virgin Channel.
You went on that Virgin Channel.
No one would say anything. It's not It's
not cuz he goes for me. Monty goes for
Speak of the devil. Monty's live. So
I'll catch you [ __ ] later
and I'm [ __ ] out of here. So
AB, see you tomorrow. Yeah, you need to
cut him some slack. All he wanted to do
was bloody well fit in with the crowd.
But all he wanted to do was bloody well
fit in with the crowd. But I like what
Monty says about these people in this community.
Yeah. So what? Yeah. You need to cut him
some slack. So what if he said about
girl? He didn't want to feel left out.
He didn't want to get picked on. So
what, bro? You don't know what it's like
being that age.
All you want to do was fit in.
There's a lot of there's a lot of bloody
worse things going out there going on in the world.
I never forget that day though, Dusty.
You know, [ __ ] Jack Madness. Jackary
from Scotland was picking on him,
saying, "I don't like I don't like the
way you're dressing. You're gay. You're
gay." And and he was like, "I'm not gay.
I'm not gay. I'm not gay." And they
would constantly keep picking on this dude.
And then one day he was like, I like so
I can't be gay. I like
that's what you were saying, Dusty.
What was you playing? Broulette.
But he got caught in the act, didn't he?
Didn't he? Didn't he, Grezy? He got
caught in the act.
He got caught being a little copycat,
didn't he, Grezy? He got caught being a little copycat.
Then he changed his tone.
Monty was live, now he's not live.
What What's the motion you would put on
roulette now, Dusty?
What's the motion you would put on roulette now? these guys.
Do you think really?
Well, bless you.
So you gamble with £300 a month. Oh, blessed.
Bless you then.
That coke dead.
I like gold.
You like car. I like you.
What's your opinion on Joseph for Dusty
since you're unbiased? H
What's your opinion?
I'm just washing my shorts, my boxes,
and my two tops. H.
Yeah. But would you agree that he he's
he's been biased? Huh?
Would you agree that he's biased?
I don't go really. >> Yeah.
He thinks I can't gamble because I don't
sublet anymore. The guy's a idiot, bro.
Gamble right now if I wanted to.
Could gamble right now if I wanted to, bro. Really could.
I could also work his more money, but try again. everything.
What's all of that going to do?
What's that all going to do, bro?
What's work, exercise, living a healthy
life? What's that going to do? Stuck up
women or stuck up women? See, these
people, right, they spend years and
years and years blaming everyone but
women. People are blaming themselves but
women, but really it's to stuck up women
in your country.
It generally generally is like you could
look smack, you could be fat, you could
be ugly, you could dress good, be good.
Like it doesn't matter what you are.
Women are stuck up [ __ ] So it
doesn't matter what you the [ __ ] are cuz
it ain't you that's the problem. It's them.
I love how they always try to shift it.
And and it's not like they don't know
these things now because of social media.
>> [clears throat]
>> They know that they looked out
cuz of social media.
They know that the women are like this
because like I said, social media.
It's not like they don't know the answer.
Like I said, I might just go out next
week for the lows. Like I said, I
already have my haircut, but then my
hair will be going back by by after
that. So, I won't be out for another six weeks.
What are you doing New Year's Eve, Dusty?
I was really thinking of Nottingham,
bro. I was actually thinking, yeah,
Nottingham's a vibe.
Nottingham's a [ __ ] vibe, bro.
Yeah, I really was thinking that do buy me.
Yeah, Nottingham looks really good, bro.
New Year's Eve. Banging hotel. Plane £150.
Looks uh does look good. But then what's
the point of leaving? Because it's the
same everywhere you go in England.
>> I'll actually walk out.
>> What do you think we should do about New Year's Eve? Seriously,
I can go to Nottingham. Yeah. Train and
back. I could go Nottingham. Yeah. I
could literally go Nottingham. Train and
back. hotel. £150.
That's a [ __ ] bargain, bro. And it's
a good hotel. It's like a It's a really
And it's New Year's Eve as well. That's
cheap. Edinburgh is like £500 a hotel.
You can [ __ ] off, man. Who's going to
really pay £500 for a hotel? That is
ridiculous, bro. I wouldn't even pay 250
for a hotel. Not in England. Not in
England. If I was on vacation in another
country, I would. But my limit is
my limit for hotel probably like 120 maybe.
The only time I ever paid more than that
was leads once. I would never pay more
than that. I would never pay more than
that. I got my travel history and I've
never paid more than that ever in the
years of me traveling. So
I could go Nottingham, bro. I could just
go out next week and then just go out
New Year's Eve.
I mean, that is And if I bring my own
bottle, I could do it all for less than
maybe £200, maybe 180 with food. Not
that I don't have the money to spend,
but it just always is much better when
you don't have to spend as much, no
matter how much money you've got.
And I get money just after again. I get
money straight after again.
Uh so yeah, I might do it. It sounds
like a vibe in it.
But the thing is I have to run it by Greasy first.
Yeah. Hope I do something like that. Okay. [clears throat]
What do you think, Steven Howard?
I think it's I think it's a good shout.
Trains and a hotel 150. And it's a it's
a good hotel as well. It's not like a
shitty hotel. It's a good hotel.
I don't know. It seems that you might
just have a little bit more chance of
finding someone there. I mean, what have
you really got to lose, bro?
I'm too old to go rock city now, bro. I
feel like I'm Bro, I feel like I'm
proper too old to go there now.
I'm too old to go [ __ ] Rock City. They're [ __ ]
I've been rock city like three times.
Do you know what? They never come on the
train, Dusty. You know, ticket
inspectors when you go Nottingham. I
don't think they ever do. You know, I
can't ever recall it going to Cardiff or
going to Nottingham.
Ticket inspectors, they [ __ ] do. In
Houston, they do though. They're [ __ ]
Like when you go Manchester and
Birmingham, they're always there
and King's Cross, but I'm sure they've
never in Cardiff. I don't think so. And
I never have going to Nottingham,
but Manchester, they always do. Oh,
mate. Last time I went to Birmingham
coming back, this ticket inspector was a [ __ ]
I had to get off the train and [ __ ] Yeah,
I get I just I just say that I've got a
rail card. I used to have a rail card. I
just I just I just say I've got a rail card,
but I'd rather just I'd rather just pay
and say I've got a rail card because I
want to actually enjoy the journey.
Yeah. So, you live in London then? Yeah.
So you live in London.
Yeah. But you can't get away with that.
Go Manchester. Yeah. You do that from
Liverpool Street because you live in
London. You wouldn't get away with that
going Manchester though. You wouldn't
get away with it in Manchester
cuz there's barriers there and there's
barriers there. So you're not going to
get away with it.
Yeah. But there's a thing in Houston. If
you're in the toilet, it flashes up and
they'll wait for you to come out. It's
not as easy as that, bro. Not in
Houston. Not in Houston. I don't know
about IPS, but bro, I've been Manchester
loads of times
and it's hard.
Yeah. I don't know. But I'm saying if
you go to Manchester, you're going to
have problems. That's what I'm saying. Yeah.
I would go Edinburgh New Year's Eve, but
I'm not paying £500 for a hotel.
There's no way I'm paying £500 for a [ __ ] hotel.
Yeah, I've been to Brighton loads of
times. So, you live in London then? You
must live in London,
80 miles away from Yeah. So, you
obviously live in London then, you [ __ ]
Yeah. So, you live in London then, don't you?
Yeah. I can go to Nottingham and have a
little New Year's Eve gamble.
I think it's a vibe, bro. I think Notch
is a vibe.
Defo, I reckon it's a vibe, lad.
Yeah, no one cares about that keyboard
warrior, bro. We don't want to know.
Let me know when he's coming to London
and meeting me if he doesn't already
live in London.
I don't know. I don't know, bro. I don't
know. I don't know.
I mean, you can't really argue at that
price, isn't it? £150,
go to a nice Indian restaurant
and but yeah, you can just stay in
London, but you're going to have your
own hotel, aren't you, if you go [ __ ]
And I'll make it as cheap as possible as well
cuz it's funner that way. So 150 bottle
is like uh probably about 170 for everything.
Probably about 170 for everything.
myself to him anymore.
I'm not explaining myself to this [ __ ]
anymore. Ela paid for that. No, she
didn't. Just to get him out the house.
Try again. Now he's living on £30 a week
to save up. Yet he says he's not in
poverty. Work that out. I'm not even
explaining myself, bro. He's not even worth it.
Made that mistake one too many times.
These people are not even worth it.
They're not even worth justifying things
to cuz remember Dusty, they're all biased.
So remember before you think about
jumping on that train or doing a video uh
don't know bro but bro I don't know they
say that I'm receding because they're
they're bull themsel it's just the same
self projecting it's the same repeating
we want to hear something new now
I don't know bro I think I don't know
who it is [ __ ] idiot.
Yeah, but they're not worth it, bro.
They're not even worth responding to these people.
It's like what my friend was saying
earlier. He said they're just jealous of
you. You can go out, you can drink, you
can do what you want. They're sat on
YouTube every day. It's the truth. It
really is. You need to stop replying to
these people. No videos, no nothing.
It's the truth, lad. these people.
Honest to God, it is the truth.
Yeah, I don't care, bro.
Yeah, I don't give a [ __ ]
I don't really give a [ __ ] He's never
going to meet me. He's a keyboard
warrior. I don't care about these low
lives. I'm not responding to them. Simple.
That's the end of that, lad.
That's what happens when you're younger
and better looking than these people.
Doing something right delayed.
That's just what happens when you're
younger and better looking than these
people, is it?
That's That's what it is. They'll never
admit it to themselves, but yeah.
They say they got all this life, all
this money, but they're sat on here
stalking every day. Something smells fishy.
Something's not right there.
I'll let you work that one out anyways.
Let me see if this hotel is still the same price.
I'll play some roulette as well.
Oh, it's even cheaper,
bro. That's even cheaper. I'm going to
have to book a hotel, bro. What?
So, how are these prices? You got Hilton. What?
How are these so cheap on New Year's Eve
and then when you look in Scotland,
they're like500 pound?
That looks sick.
I'm so tempted to book the Hilton one,
but the thing is I'm only staying for
one night. in it,
bro. [snorts] I'm going to have to book
this hotel, lad.
Why are they dirt cheap?
They're [ __ ] good hotels. They're not
even like [ __ ] hotels.
No, that's a bargain, bro.
That is an absolute bargain. Really?
So that's like 120 for the whole thing.
That's like 120 for the whole [ __ ] thing.
That's cheap, bro.
That is, bro. How the [ __ ] is it so
cheap New Year's Eve?
Yeah, I'm just going to travel. Yeah, [ __ ] it. Yeah.
Yeah. Who Who else am I going to go
with, bro? go over there by myself.
This one's even cheaper, but it's two
pound cheaper, but it's not worth it.
That is sick. That's a good hotel as
well. It's not They're not even [ __ ]
hotels. That's the thing.
Yeah, I know. I know. That's what I'm
saying. This is dirt cheap. This is what
I'm trying to say to you. It's even got
it's gone even more downer.
That's what I'm trying to say.
That is mad.
That is really cheap, bro.
That is really cheap. So, you'll
definitely do all of it without with
You'll definitely do all of it under 200 pound.
Definitely under 200 pound. 100%.
That's just too good, bro, to to to say no to.
Especially when I was looking at with
Scotland as well, they even gone down more. Yeah,
I think I'm going to book this, bro.
This hotel. Yeah. Oh, [ __ ]
It is, bro. But I've always wanted to
spend I've always wanted to spend uh
a New Year's Eve out of London. And if I
can do it at a very cheap price, why not?
I would say you'll probably even spend
less than [ __ ]
I reckon you probably spend
less going out of London than in London.
No, I don't need to say for three
months. I could do in about a month and
a half, two months. I've already got some savings,
but um No, not 3 months. 3 months is if
you're like starting from scratch. I
could probably do it in a month and a half, too.
That's without working.
Yeah, but what have you got to lose by
doing this if if this cost less than 150?
That's not even It doesn't even feel
like you're spending anything.
Yeah, I would do this if I could spend
another night, but I'm not There's no
point staying in a
if you The thing is there's no point
staying in a good hotel for one night.
No, they're a thousand.
They're even cheaper if you do it
through um air [ __ ] China.
Air China is it? Some in China. But this
there's no point staying in a good hotel
if you're only staying for one night
though, is there?
Doesn't really make sense. Not for one night.
Two nights. Three nights.
I remember the last time I went
Nottingham. It was [ __ ] good, bro. I
got a [ __ ]
Maybe I'll do this or maybe I'll stay in London.
I went out in Romford today and they
were they were stuck up there as well.
They're stuck up every [ __ ] way. But
this I'm I'm thinking of doing this
because it's just something to do.
This is just something to do.
I could do I could do France, but that's
that's pointless. But that's going to be like500 pound
four or 500 pound. It's not worth it for
one night. Like I said, you might as
well go in March. You can go to Paris
and March two nights for 250. It makes
more sense. just waiting till March. Ah,
yeah. But I'm saying if you wanted to go to France,
you might be able to find a relationship.
The best hotel I ever stayed at was the
one in Newcastle. The first one, the one
I got nicked in. That was a nice hotel,
boy. When I had a date, I had a date. Do
you remember when I had a date? Nice
bath, nice balcony.
That was lush. And then I got nicked. It
took me ages to get that money back as well.
Well, you can't find a [ __ ] relationship here.
Don't snake in you.
I could actually gamble in Nottingham as
well. I could actually play some lush
roulette. But the problem with that is
trying to get your money, isn't it
though, Dusty? It's trying to get your [ __ ] money.
It's trying to get your [ __ ] [ __ ] money.
You're trying to get your [ __ ] money, bro.
Well, how else are you going to get a
sex life here?
How else are you going to get a sex life here? Yeah.
Yeah. All these people like Joe F and
that I'm not reacting to these fat
losses anymore, bro.
Well, how else are you supposed to get a
bloody sex life, Dusty?
Be [ __ ] fair.
Yeah, but I can go to this casino. But
the thing is, Dusty is trying to
it's trying to uh
it's trying to get your money, isn't it, bro?
If you win, it's trying to get your
[ __ ] money, bro. Isn't it?
So, what happen if I win like £700 and I
try to get the £700 out?
It's trying to get your money from these
places, bro. That's the thing. It's all
right in a bookies or a football bet,
but it's trying to get your money's from
these bent places,
these casinos. It's trying to get your
trying to get the money. You know,
I'll do it. I gamble, bro. in this casino
New Year's Eve. But
yeah, but I'm banned from them and they
want this and that and this and that.
They want this and [ __ ] that, you
know. I don't want to give them it.
No, I remember before when I went to
Nottingham like I told you before 150 and
I think I was 150 and 350 out
and they wanted [ __ ] they were trying
to not give that money, bro. And this
was before I was banned. So, have you
got anything with your name on it? I was
like, what? For £350?
No, you [ __ ] can't. No, you [ __ ]
No, you cannot, mate. Trust me. I've
been going to casinos for years, bro.
And I And I know what they're like.
No, you [ __ ] can't. When I went to
When I went to Nottingham with Ant-Man
and I want to No, I think I was 200 in
and I I was I got 350 out. Sorry, I was
150 out. I remember now. Mate, they
weren't having it for toffee. It took
about 5 minutes to get that money.
you know, hipper drone, they're the
same. They don't like paying out. It's
bent as [ __ ]
And I went to one called Horizons as well.
It's called Horizon's Casino. You can't.
>> They uh
But I'll never trust casinos again. They
can they can void a ticket. I remember,
bro, there was a £500 ticket. They
voided it and they never gave it back.
But I got the last laugh out of them
anyways cuz I went next door and won
like £800 today. I got the last laugh
out of the casinos in the end, bro. When
they banned me, I I had the last laugh. Trust me.
I used to rinse them. [ __ ] rinse the
[ __ ] Technically, no, cuz they're
[ __ ] they got millions. But trust me,
bro. Trust me. I got so many stories.
But it doesn't uh in Nottingham, they
were doing anything not to give that 350, bro. Yeah.
It's all bent. It's all corrupt. Have
you noticed they've turn they turn off
the machines by purpose as well?
But yeah, they can void the ticket. They
They can actually void your ticket
and not pay you out. Ever since then, I
was like, "No, that is dodgy, bro." I
mean, the fact that they can do that,
it tells you all you need to know about the industry.
Yeah, it tells you all you need to know
about that industry, bro.
So, yeah, it's not good. Yeah.
What was that? Yeah. So,
yeah. So, yeah, they're dodgy, bro.
Yeah, they're [ __ ] dodgy, dusty.
[ __ ] dodgy, bro. Yep.
I can't believe he was trolling me with
the USA thing.
He was showing me
Yo, a nasty troll. Huh? Yeah.
Greavesy greasy greasy eh
greasy is an absol mate.
This is sad as well.
These people are really obsessed with
me. Shame he can't use clown at the
barbers. Even Laney got sick of him looking.
These people are really, really, really
sad. But like I said, Steven Howard,
they're Christmas projectors.
Yeah, I've never used Cro in my life.
So, yeah, they'll project them. So, like
I said, even when you prove that you've
got more money than these people, they
still talk [ __ ]
So, they think they stop your income
from the subleting, right? So, even when
you prove that you've got more money
than them, they still talk [ __ ]
You got to laugh at it, bro. You really
You really do have to laugh at them. These people.
Yeah, I've never used Colana in my life,
so I wouldn't know. Thank you, Triple H.
I'm not skin like you, so I wouldn't
know about the Colana.
>> Yeah, it just shows like like they're
not even worth reacting to, lad.
these people are very lonely Christmas
I said to them bro multiple times
to show their faces and they won't show their faces.
I said I will show you the receipts if
you show your face and prove that you're
not the one balding.
These people are already bold people
telling me that I'm receding.
Do these people not get bored of self
projecting? I would be so bored if I
were them, bro. If I had to do this [ __ ]
for 7 years.
If I had to keep self-reflecting for
seven years and not have anything new to
say. You would have thought they would get bored.
And it shows goes to show they got no
money either. So everything that they
tried to say about other people, it's about them.
About ugly people obsessed with me.
So I'm just talking about these
self-reflectives on Red Star's channel.
Yeah. Yeah. I can't use Colano at the
barbers cuz I don't need Colano. I'm not
skin like you again. Happy to show you
the receipts when you show your face.
Same offer to you. You show your face
and I'll show you receipts. I'll show
you money. I can't be any I can't be any
further than that.
Look at these [ __ ] nerds that are
obsessed with me lining up to have their
say about Peter Belly.
But don't forget these pe these people
have got good lives, by the way. People,
these people have got good lives and
they've got more money than everyone.
Just just letting just letting you
people know that.
It's like whenever you show that you've
got better than them, they they they
hate. Have you shown that? Have you
known that? Triple H. Oh, the same
account. Who? Apparently I use Kana.
What's it called? Kana.
You're still saying that I use Kana? I
literally told you I'd show the receipts
once you show your face.
Same thing as what I said to that
ghosten. You show me your face. You
prove you're not a M and I'll show you
the receipts. You can't be any fairer than that.
You're saying that I use colana cuz I
can afford something that you can't. How
old are you?
How old are you, bro? Come on. And
you're acting like this.
You these people in their 40s hating on
someone that's younger and better
looking than them for seven years.
They've been doing this for seven years now.
I would love to get my hands on one of
these people, bro. Even at Joseph Farra,
I'd love to just They're just people
that you would just love to smash their
teeth down their throat, but then
they're jealous. So that's why there's
no point in reacting them because they
do this because they're jealous of you.
So when you actually work out why they
do this, then they're not worth reacting.
It's like my friend, it is jealousy with
these people. He said they're jealous of
you. He even said this today and this is
something that you need to seriously
need to understand with these people is
that they're jealous of you. They are
jealous of you. So the more that you
react to these people, Joseph Ferrar,
the fat ugly [ __ ] with a pension and
these [ __ ] [ __ ] the more Do you
know what I'm saying, bro?
That Yeah, bro. But Ronald Pump said
that they were never going to stop, didn't he?
He said you're younger than them, you're
better looking than them, and you got a
better life than them. They said he said
that they were never going to stop.
Yeah, but he said they were never going
to stop. We knew they were never going Yeah.
Jealous, jealous, obsessed, fat, ugly
people. They ain't got a life. They
never They were never going to stop,
bro. You knew they were never going to
stop. You're better looking than them.
It kills them. Just like what Ronald Pump said.
But none of these people can show their
face, can they?
Do you know what? I would go up north to
Newcastle and call that Joseph Ferrar
out and he wouldn't meet me.
The fat tension using [ __ ] would never
meet me. This is what I mean with these
people. They would never ever meet you.
They will never ever meet you. These
virgins, this is what I mean, bro.
They'll never ever ever meet you. You know
that's it. They'll never meet you, man.
I've literally told you that I would
show the receipts once you show your face. Yeah,
you [ __ ] little [ __ ]
You know what I mean? I would love to
get my hands on one of these people,
bro. I hate them so badly, bro. You
really don't understand. I hope this guy
comes to Waterl tomorrow. I really hope
this [ __ ] comes to Waterl tomorrow, bro. Really?
Do you want me to do a video on these
[ __ ] for like two seconds? Triple
on Red Star's channel.
It's the same jokes. You would have
thought these little nerds would have
got bored after seven years. You would
have thought seven and a half years
these these little nerds that don't show
their face cuz they're fat and ugly,
they would have got bored. You would
have thought they would have got bored.
These fat ugly people. I mean, even the
same reaction would get boring.
Even if someone's reacting every day,
you would have thought it would have got boring. H you know
why are they jealous of someone's jeans?
I mean [ __ ] hell.
Why are they so jealous that someone can
afford jeans and their skin? I don't understand, bro.
You know what I mean?
Why are they so jealous that someone can
afford 200 pound jeans?
Sat on YouTube again. No life.
That's the first thing I'll say. Sat on
the internet again. No life, no money,
all the things that they talk about
other people. Am I lying, bro?
Am I lying? Sad people. Do you know
what, bro? Yeah. There's even one thing
you do about these people. You either
ignore these people.
You either You either ignore these
people or you hire a private investigator, bro. You know,
you either hire a private investigator
or you just ignore them. They're like
your two options, bro. And it could be
any one of them. You either ignore them
or you hire a private investigator.
Either way will do the trick. You know,
that's that's the only way you're going
to win with these people, bro. That is
literally the only way you I mean, it's
just easier ignoring, but you can hire a private investigator.
You would have thought these people
would have got bored after seven and a
half years of repeating the same
self-reflecting [ __ ] You see the same
people every day. Same people, same
jokes and they still do it. They're not
bothering anyone. They don't bully
anyone. You would have thought that they
would have got bored by now.
I've never used colon in my life. I'm
not skint like you. And I've said that
multiple multiple times.
They'll be sat alone. The Christmas projectors.
Hey, do you know what, bro? I might do a
video called the Christmas projectors.
Self projecting ugly people with no
family over Christmas.
Would you like that trip to your break?
The Christmas projectors.
No one cares what these fat ugly little
low lives think. They can't show their
face. They're lonely people. Their
opinions don't mean nothing.
I really do hope this guy comes
tomorrow. I really, really do hope this
guy meets me tomorrow, bro. 100%.
So I can bang him one in his mouth,
uppercut, spit in his mouth. Just please
meet me tomorrow so I can bat that face
for all the [ __ ] If I can't get If I
can get one of these people, if I can
get one of these people, bro, I'll be happy.
Just give them one big bang in their
mouth and they'll never forget it. You
know, just one big bang in their mouth.
Like, you don't understand, bro. And
they'll never ever ever come on here
ever again. You know,
stop stalking me, Red Star, you little
weasel. You little bully victim. Go and
suck your boyfriend's dick. Get off of
YouTube. Get some money. Stop being
disabled. Stop repeating, you gay boy.
Stop recording everything, you [ __ ]
gay boy. You [ __ ] dick sucker. I
don't fancy you back, you little [ __ ]
I'm off here, bro, after the new year, bro. 100%.
This guy better better better
meet me tomorrow so I can smash his face
in so I can smash the cunt's face in,
bro. I'm not even joking.
Of course they're virgins.
Of course they're absolute virgins. They
got no life, no family. That's why you
see them on here every day.
No life, no family, no nothing. Of
course they're virgins, bro. What? Why
they Why are they on here on a [ __ ] Saturday?
Why are they on here on a Saturday if
they've got a life? They've got nothing.
Of course they got nothing, bro.
They are virgins.
No money, no life, skin. Yeah, they got nothing.
Nothing at all.
But I'm bored,
bro. Man's nuts. I'm not even bored. If
I'm bored so much, why don't you show us
what a straightforward hairline looks like?
And the thing is, Triple H, they're
never going to make me insecure. They're
never going to stop me showing my face.
They're never going to make me second
guessess my looks. So, I don't know why
they keep doing it. I could I can do
this. I can show my face.
I can show my hair. These people don't
show their faces cuz they're [ __ ] fat and ugly.
Yep. They will be on here Christmas Day. Yeah,
definitely definitely definitely not boredom.
These people need to stop with the
self-reflecting. It's never going to
change the fact that they're all of
these things. They can be on here for
another [ __ ] seven years, bro, and
it's not going to change the fact that
they're all of these things themselves.
What is your obsession with balding when
I'm not even balding?
Like I'm saying you're saying all of
this [ __ ] I'm showing my face. You're
scared to show your face. So you're the
one that looks stupid when you keep
coming on here. Yeah. Doing this. You
don't make anyone insecure.
You know, you don't you don't do
anything. You just embarrass yourselves
coming on here every day repeating.
Repeating the same [ __ ] over and over
and over and over and over again. No
one's bored but you.
No one's balding but Red Star. No, he's
not balding. He's already bored.
He's not balding, bro. He's already
bowled. How long have you been saying
that I'm balding? How long have you been
saying that I'm balding and I've still
got hair and you're already bald? you know. So yeah,
that Joseph Ferrell will never meet
anyone either. He's a coward. He can't
even come on the [ __ ] He can't even
come on the Hangouts and talk to anyone
trying to tell you to join Triple H. And
he can't even talk cuz he's a [ __ ]
He's so disabled. He can't even talk.
That's another thing we've got on this
Joseph Far is that he's so much of a
[ __ ] He can't even talk. How can you
take someone serious that can't even
talk, who's scared to talk? That's embarrassing, bro.
You know, at least with bombing that
they can talk. You're giving it all
this. Yeah. Behind a fake account, but
you can't even talk. You're scared of
your own voice. Let's not talk about
what a man is now. Yeah. [ __ ]
[ __ ] They're [ __ ] [ __ ] on
here. The Christmas self projectors.
That's what they're called, bro. Cuz
they realize they're all going to be
alone Christmas. And I'm not. And I'm
just not. They're going to be alone
Christmas. And I'm not
[ __ ] Colana, bro. What is it with you and Kana?
What the [ __ ] is it with you and Kana?
Why are you jealous of a 200lb jeans?
Definitely definitely definitely not for
you, man. Why are you jealous of 200 pound jeans?
I've never known something so ridiculous
in my life. Why are you jealous of 200 lb jeans?
Human. I'm not fuming. I'm talking the
truth about you people. You people come
on here every day self-reflecting. You
must be fuming.
So I'm not fuming. If I'm fuming, what
are you, bro? Having to [ __ ] sit on
here recording every day doing what you
do for years. What are you then, bro? If
I'm fuming, what am I? If I'm trig if if
I'm triggered, what are you?
Oh, this account says that I use colana
to buy my clothes cuz I got more money
than them. So, even like I said, even
when you prove that you've got more
money than them, they still talk [ __ ]
Even when you prove that you can afford
things that they can't, they still talk [ __ ]
Disabled [ __ ] disabled people on
here, bro. This why I don't come on
here, bro. This is why I didn't come on here today.
I wouldn't have went on here today, bro.
I wouldn't have went on there today if I
didn't go out drinking.
My mom was like, "Oh, can you not go on
YouTube?" I was like, she's kind of got
a point to be honest. All they do is
self-reflect. All they do is repeat. All
they do is wreak jealousy. I mean,
there's no real reason. There's no real
reason to be on here. Same self-reflectors.
self-reflecting bastards that ain't got
a life. Can't show their face cuz
they're ugly. You know, the list goes on
and on and on with these people. These Christmas projectors,
you know, I don't find it funny. Me, if
this guy meets me tomorrow, I'm smashing
his face in. It's not funny, bro. I'll
be up early tomorrow as well. If this
guy meets me tomorrow, I'm smashing his
face in. And you can laugh at that. I
don't find it funny, mate. I don't find
any of these people funny, bro.
If I had any of these people's addresses
like Joseph, I'd be going on the [ __ ]
front door, mate. I don't find it funny.
I don't find anyone on here funny.
I hate them. I hate the atmosphere.
Yeah, man. Trust me. I didn't meet
Smokey. What are you talking about? I
didn't meet Smokey. He knew where I
lived. Shut up now. Stop it. He knows
where I lived and I didn't arrange to meet him.
Stop it. Stop it. You've had my address.
Stop it. You people are not meeting
anyone. You've got my address. You're
not meeting anyone. Reverse that back on to you.
The number one golden ticket is an
address. You've had my address and
you've done nothing.
Stop it. You know, you've had my address
and you've done nothing. That's the most
embarrassing thing because we have said
multiple multiple times if I find one of
these people's addresses, I'm banging on
that front door. I'm banging on that
front door. Like to the point where I
even want to hire a private
investigator, you know where people
live, but you don't do nothing. Stop it
now. Really, really, really stop it. You
know where people live and you don't do
anything but type on YouTube every
single [ __ ] day.
Like I said, if this guy comes out tomorrow,
right, bro? Again, you've had my
address. None of you are about that
life. We've we've already seen you
people. You know my address and I know
that none of you are about that life.
You ain't even come on my [ __ ]
address even when I live by myself. Stop
it. You're embarrassing yourselves.
Anyways, if this guy comes out tomorrow,
Steven Howard, he's getting hurt.
Trust me, bro. You're going to still see
some real boxing [ __ ] tomorrow, bro. If
this guy comes out,
all the [ __ ] these people have done for
years, just one big bang in their mouth,
[ __ ] spit in their face. And I'll
tell you what's funny, bro. I'll show
you what's funny about this community,
bro. Tomorrow when this guy, if this guy
shows up, everyone sub to his channel as
well. Don't let him be a little [ __ ] tomorrow.
Don't let this [ __ ] be a little [ __ ]
gay boy. Little [ __ ] No family. Yeah,
Sharpie. Like I I'll rephrase my bro.
I'm I'm going to admit I'm going to say
it again. You people have had my address
and you ain't done nothing. Take the L.
Stop it. Take the [ __ ] L. You know
how long I was trying to find N legs
address before I done that [ __ ] poster [ __ ]
Stop it. You're proven cowards. You're
When one of you get doxed, I'll be at
your front door. Simple. So that's that.
Christmas projectors. He'll go back to
normal in January.
Steven Howard, have you not noticed this
month has been a prime time for self projectors, lad?
Why do you think they're projecting a
lot and hating a lot lately?
They ain't got no family.
They're going to be lonely Christmas. No
family. Have you not noticed, bro? Like,
it's it's it's worse than usual
considering the community is dead. Yeah.
They're the Christmas projectors.
Um, they come out every They come out in
December every month.
They got nothing. They know they're
going to be lonely Christmas.
Like, [ __ ] money for a second, bro.
Let's just forget money, bro. Yeah,
these people are going to be lonely Christmas.
Lonely. No family. Ah.
No. You're all project. You're all
projecting because you ain't got no
family and you're going to be alone Christmas.
So that's why you're doing this. You do
you, bro. People do it every year. You
do it every year. Constant constant self-reflecting
badly around December cuz you know that
you got no family.
You got no family. You got nothing.
Uh and you're going to be you're going
to spend Christmas alone.
Yeah. I'm skinn. Yeah. Yeah. But
anyways, um yeah, you this is why you do
the self-reflecting defo. If you go on
that Red Star channel, Stephen Howard,
you'll see how many Christmas
self-reflectors are coming out.
You'll see how many of them. There's so many.
Yeah, that skin thing doesn't bother me
though, bro. That's just self-reflecting and repeating.
So, no one cares about that comment. But
yeah, anyways, if you go on Red Star's channel Yeah.
Because the thing is Stephen Albert okay
I'll give you an example here that they
say they say something they say oh you use kana
yeah you sew receipts they will still
talk [ __ ] they don't say you use colana
your clothes are fake like they this is
their this is their life doing this bro
then they've been doing it for years
they used to do it with Monty as well
you wear fake clothes like their whole
life is basically hating on people cuz
their lives [clears throat] are ruined.
That's basically what their whole life
is because their lives are ruined and
they're fat, ugly, nobody, no family.
All they have to do is hate on it every day.
That's literally the only thing that
they have basically. But
sat on YouTube typing shitty little
comments every day.
Typing shitty little comments.
It is funny to be fair. It is funny,
lad. They write shitty little comments,
bro. Triple H again. I will show you my receipts.
Of course they hate me, bro. Yeah, of
course they hate me. I'm younger, better
looking than them. Of course they're
going to hate me. I've got more money
than them. Of course. Of course they
hate me. I'm younger and better looking.
Of course they hate me. That's no
[ __ ] That's no surprise. younger
than them, better looking than them. Of
course they hate me, bro. They don't
[ __ ] love me, do they? It's not that really.
I I think it is that. I really really
really think it is that. Do you want me
to explain? Cuz if you really wasn't
jealous of someone, you wouldn't do what
you're doing every day on YouTube. End
of. I mean, that that is
that doesn't even make sense. If you if
you're not jealous to someone,
then you wouldn't do what you're doing.
I mean, if you really was better than
someone, okay, let's go by your logic
then. Yeah. So, I'm skin and I'm this
and I'm that and I'm all of these
things. So, if you weren't none of these
things, you wouldn't be doing this. You
would be living your life. So, that
doesn't even make sense. So, no, you're
definitely definitely definitely jealous. 100%.
Younger, better looking, more money,
better looks, better life. And you
people are sat on here and have nothing.
And you're fat and ugly. Uh,
you need to get yourselves better. You
need to get off of YouTube and stop
repeating. You've been doing it for
seven years now.
Yeah. I want you to stop repeating on
YouTube every day. It's boring. This is
why the community is so dead.
Get off of YouTube. [ __ ] off. Stop
repeating yourself, you monk, and get a life.
No, no words ever spoken. Isn't that
right, um, Grezy? Not Grevy. Um, Triple H.
So, you're not jealous, but you sit on
YouTube all day doing what you're doing?
I don't know, man. That's a bit weird.
No, you're definitely definitely
definitely definitely definitely
jealous. 100%. You've been at this for
years now. You've been doing it for
years. Definitely definitely. You will
not leave people alone. You will never ever stop.
So, it is obviously jealousy.
Come on, man. It is. It is obviously
jealousy. Everyone can see it. My mom,
my friend today I met, everybody knows
that it is jealousy.
with you people cuz you wouldn't do what
you do if you weren't jealous.
Yeah, my monkey turnouts. Yeah. Okay, whatever.
They need to get off a YouTube trip.
My mom's a [ __ ] Your mom don't even
have a Bro, you don't even have a mom.
Christmas self projector. That's not
nice to call my mom a [ __ ] Christmas
self projector. Another Christmas self
When are you going to get a job and get
a life? You skin bastard.
You remember when Monty man asked these
people that triple. See, I'm on and off
here. I'm on and off here.
My mom hates me. More self projection.
The Christmas projectors are out and about,
people. Self projection. I told you,
bro. I told you. I told you.
I told you about these self projectors around December.
I told you, bro. Cuz they know they're
going to be lonely Christmas. How did I
know these things? I knew, bro. I told
you this and you didn't believe me.
It's cuz they got no family, bro.
Yeah, you are a spaz. Stop calling
yourself a spaz. That's not nice.
Yeah, stop talking about yourself.
It's not nice to talk about yourself like that. [snorts]
Yeah, you can.
Yep. You are a [ __ ] Stop talking
about yourself. Anyway, do you want to join?
I feel sorry for you people, bro. You're
older than me. You're actually older
than me and you're still doing this. What's this?
>> Who the [ __ ] is this, bro? 8K or some
>> Yo, I got a question for you, PJ.
>> This YouTube is mad, is it?
>> I think it's just weird. Yeah,
>> it is mad, isn't it? Yeah.
>> Can I ask you another question? >> Yeah.
>> Do you know when you sit there saying to
people they skint and ain't got a job
and they're constantly watching you on
the internet and that and they stay in
your house constantly?
>> Can I just entertain you on one one
thing? Do you know I could be in I could
be in America right actually got your
channel walking down the road going to
every shop buying stuff. Yeah. and I can
still basically troll you. So it doesn't
mean everyone you speak to in the
internet is actually in your house
actually generally texting you. You do
are aware of that, right?
>> So people that can be on here from the
time they wake up to the time they go to
bed typing away have got a life. I don't think so. >> So
>> I don't think so. It doesn't even make sense.
>> Yeah, it does. So let me ask you a question.
>> Listen, let me tell you something.
Right. You know, the first time I was on
here today was right. I've only been on
YouTube once today, bro. And that was
from 10:00. That was first time of me
being on it, even opening the app.
Yeah. But you're on about people coming
on this app. Yeah. But there's a thing
called notifications. When you go live,
everybody knows that you're going live,
right? So it's like I'm trying to
understand you because I've been
listening to you for a while, right? It
makes it's mad what
>> you're mad in what you're saying because
if they are joining your stream
commenting on what you're comment you
are going live exactly the same time
they viewing you
>> these people it doesn't matter where
they are they ain't got a life that's
that's irrelevant it doesn't matter
where they are America Australia what
these people do every day it proves they
ain't got a life
>> so have you got a life then
>> uh yeah
>> how can you say you got a life but are
broadcasting. But when them viewers view
you, you're saying that they ain't got
your life, but you're the streamer.
>> Cuz I've been out I've been out all day.
>> How do you know them people are not
viewing you been out theirel?
>> Because I guarantee you if I spend all
day on YouTube, I will see the same
people everywhere typing away.
>> No, answer that. Answer that question.
If you've been out today, how do you
know they haven't been out?
>> How do I know they have? Because it's
same people every day.
Yeah, because they you don't get what
I'm trying to say. J, you said you've been out.
>> You've been out today. Yeah. How do you
know them people haven't been out?
>> They could be out.
>> Cuz they don't go out.
>> Because they don't go out.
>> It goes out PJ. They could be out in a
restaurant, right, having a beer and
they're sat there trolling you. How do
you know where they are? They could be
on the It could be anywhere,
>> bro. People that have got a life don't
do what they do. It's It's end of story.
They don't do what they do.
>> So, you are the streamer, correct?
>> Right. Listen, people that have got a
life don't hate from the time they wake
up to the time they go to bed. It's not
possible. These people are supposed to
have jobs. Yeah. Are they supposed to
have jobs? Yeah. A lot of these people.
>> So, how from the time they wake up to
the time they go to bed, it doesn't add
up. Something smells fishy. It's not
right. There's There's something not
right there, bro.
>> You You calling people
>> because some people work at home as
well. Um PJ,
>> so Okay. Okay. So all of these people
work at home.
>> Well, majority of population does now
due to co
>> work at home. Really? [ __ ] really?
>> Yeah. Half of the population work from
home and half [ __ ] go out to work.
>> But they still have breaks, you know, when they're
>> working. They stalk me. Also, they
stalk. You're sat there.
>> You're sat there saying that people are
not in their home.
>> Saturday is Saturday is not a day off.
>> Well, people still work on a Saturday.
How do you get your kebab on Saturday?
>> I just wanted to say that. Yeah,
Saturday is not a day off.
>> Well, exactly. People work Monday to
Sunday, but they still have breaks.
>> So, yeah,
but they ain't got life on here. They've
been on here [ __ ] years. They've been
on here seven years repeating the same
[ __ ] every day. Like,
>> and another thing I want to ask you, PJ,
because you seem very down to earth. You
talk about um people ain't got a
girlfriends. How do you know they not
got a family theirselves?
because I've asked them to prove several
times what they've got and they can't do it.
>> So if somebody's So if I say to you, I
got a Ferrari 911, would you believe I got that?
>> Not unless you proved it. No.
>> So I've got to prove to you I've got
something even though I've got it just
to make you happy.
>> Well, when you're coming on here
constantly hating and trying to talk
about other people. Yeah.
>> Do you not see Okay. Okay. I'll give you
an example, right? Somebody was asking
me to show receipts for my clothes.
Yeah. Even though I don't need to cuz I
paid in full. I said I don't need to
prove myself to you. And I said, if you
show me your face, I will show you the
receipts. And he couldn't do it.
The motto of the story is right. It
doesn't matter where you are around the
world. Anybody can control you. Even
though I could control you in a gym, I
control you in a toilet like Kaye said.
And when you say people ain't got a life
and ain't got a girlfriend and have sex,
you can't that statement's bo bold
because you can't prove that they
haven't had sex.
>> Well, I I can because they can't prove
they have. So until they prove
something, that's the end of that.
>> Have Why would you want to know prove?
>> Yeah. Why do you want to know if
somebody's had a job on coming on here
talking about other people? We're not
talking about who we're just having a discussion.
>> We are listening to you and it's funny
because you was saying um about [ __ ]
and stuff like that like who who in a
right mind will sit there and go PJ mate
honestly I'll give you a link to my
channel and I want you to watch me on
the [ __ ] just to prove that I've had a [ __ ]
>> So you so you think these people So you
think these people here have got a life?
>> Well yeah I think they got a life but
they like trolling you because you're an easy target.
>> No. No, I think they've not got a life.
100%. They stalk me on Reddit. They
stalk me. People that have got a life
that are happy don't do it. You can keep
trying to talk about how they could be
anywhere. People that are happy don't do
this. Look at all of the people in the
world, right, that are working happy
people. They don't do this. And they never stop.
>> So, do you believe I've had a [ __ ] today?
>> I [snorts] don't give a [ __ ] if you have
or you haven't.
>> So, you don't care if I've had a
[ __ ] You care about the people in
your stream comment to you saying,
"Prove that you've had a blowjob."
Why are you talking about a [ __ ]
That doesn't make any sense. [ __ ]
>> Because you just said that you had a
[ __ ] and not ma'am.
>> Like not everybody. So what? Cuz we was talking about
>> we was talking about Nottingham. What's that?
>> Can you prove that?
>> You just said to you care if he's had a
[ __ ] today, but you turn around to
your stream and say, "Oh, I had a
[ __ ] in Nottingham." Who wants to know?
>> I actually have proved I've had a [ __ ] Yeah,
>> I don't really want to know. like you
just said to Rice. So,
>> well, you just said, "Can you prove?" I
said, "Well, yeah, I can."
>> But why would you want to prove yourself
getting a [ __ ] That's just not normal.
>> Well, now you're not making any sense.
Now you're not even making any sense.
>> Well, it does because you said the
stream, I've had a [ __ ] You was
quoting that you had a [ __ ]
>> If these if these if these people put
their cameras on, it would show exactly
why they do what they do every day. And
until they don't until they do do that,
then you know that's that.
>> Yeah. That you you you said to the
stream that you had a [ __ ] and you
were telling the stream, prove to me
that you've had a [ __ ] If you can't,
I don't believe you. But I'm asking you,
did you have a [ __ ] today? And can
you prove that? >> No.
>> So why is it okay for you not to prove
yourself, but you want other people in
the stream to prove yourself?
>> I've already I've already proved myself multiple times.
>> How? But that's your word against it.
>> How how how have I proved myself? Okay.
>> But that's your that's your word.
>> Firstly, money. I've shown more money
than these people. Firstly,
>> the money really matter in 2025.
>> It matters to them clearly.
So now, now you're saying it doesn't
matter. Now I'm telling you things I
proved and now you're saying something else.
>> No, money doesn't really matter
technically. It doesn't make you happy,
does it? I mean, I've I've proved I've
had sex and these people still try to
call me a virgin. So, I mean, don't
>> tell me you're on chatter bait. [laughter]
>> So, you know what I mean? It is what it is.
>> Are you on trib?
>> I don't even know what that is.
>> It's a sex site where you can everybody
can view you having sex. >> No. >> So,
>> so Rice, why didn't you prove that you had sex
that [laughter] you had sex? Why?
>> How have I proved that I've had sex? Uh,
I've been seen in women's beds on YouTube naked.
>> Yeah, but I can lay in bed.
>> Wait, wait.
>> So, you would be So, you would be So,
you're naked next to a woman in a bed.
That doesn't prove that you've had sex. Really?
>> No. Some people don't sleep with one
another in a bed. It depends on the person.
>> I've had women admit to sleeping with
me. I've put a video up of me getting a
[ __ ] That's not proof. No.
>> So, why did you walk down the street a
couple of weeks ago, right? Approach a
woman and say to the woman, "If I give
you £300, will you come and spend a
night with me?" Was you acting at that woman?
>> No, that was months and months ago.
>> Yeah, but was you asking that woman to
be your prostitute for that night?
>> No, I just wanted to see if it would work.
>> So, what would you have done if she said
Yeah. What would you have done to her?
>> I don't know.
So, you would have given her £300 and
you would have stayed in a [ __ ] hotel
and just look at each other.
>> I don't know what I would have done. Why
are you talking about that anyways? Why
does any of that matter? It
>> It doesn't matter. But the the
approaches that you do are quite mad.
>> That was ages ago.
>> Yeah, but your approaches are mad. Come
on, be fair.
>> I think I think it's mad that you used
to watch porn.
>> Well, I think 95% of people watch porn
and I think all your viewers in your
stream watch porn, too.
I don't watch porn.
>> So you're telling me you don't watch porn? >> Nah, >> never.
>> I have, but not now.
>> So what kind of porn did you used to
watch? Cuz I hear you saying yesterday
that you watch old porn like an old lady
>> like porn in the 70s ' 80s interracial.
>> Yeah. So you do watch porn?
>> No, I used to.
So PJ, if he was going down the street now,
>> you used to watch cuz you used to watch
porn from the 70s.
>> No, no, not really. No, I don't watch
that kind of [ __ ] I watch Chatterbait.
Anyway, so if you was walking down the
street now, right, and you saw KK and
she wasn't on the internet, what would
you say to KK if you approached her?
>> I would say that you need to lose some
weight. You're a fat [ __ ]
>> Well, apart from that, and you was
attracted to her, you thought she was gorgeous.
>> I don't know.
>> So K, right? Pretend Kaylee was walking
down the street. You saw her. You was
attracted to her. You wanted her to be
your girlfriend or go out with you. What
would you say to her?
>> Listen. Yeah. I'm I'm hung over and
you're asking stupid questions.
>> Well, it's not. You're doing approaches
online in front of the community.
>> No, it's not stupid.
>> Stupid questions.
>> Well, it's not. Are you afraid that one
day you do approach and it goes wrong
and the boyfriend or the girl, you know,
their brothers might kick your head in?
>> It would never happen.
How can you say it never happened? They
said the Titanic would never sink, but
it happened. I'm not I'm not like I'm
not like you, Rice. I'm not tough like you.
>> Like what? What? What? What? What do you
mean by that? What am I?
>> You lost to Monty. You got your windows
smashed. Like you're just a soft lad.
>> Well, right. It wasn't my fault. And I
didn't lose against [ __ ] actually to be
fair. No one won and no one lost.
>> Yeah, you did. You soft lad.
>> I'm soft. That's why I asked you to come
on that day and you basically backed
out. So you must be soft too, right?
>> No, I'm definitely not. I'm definitely
>> So why didn't So why didn't you turn up?
>> Because I didn't want to. It wasn't It
>> So you asked me You I asked you can you
meet me, but you put put me on a string
thinking you was going to meet me, but you didn't. >> Yeah. >> Why?
>> Because I didn't want to. Why tell us
and send a message and say you was on on
way on on your way?
>> I didn't say I was on my I didn't say I
was on my way.
>> You said you was on your train.
>> No, I didn't. I said I was coming, but I
>> Why would you do that to somebody?
>> It was funny.
>> Oh, it was funny. Okay. It was funny. Do
you know that it is funny? It was,
you know, it doesn't bother me anyway
cuz I had the money. You know, I'm rich
as [ __ ] 13 grand in the bank a lot. Not
like some of these people on the
internet. I don't have to brag like some
people. You know,
>> you don't have 13 grand.
>> I have actually.
>> Uh how do you have 13 grand? That
doesn't even make any sense. You don't even work.
>> It's called uh mind your own business. [clears throat]
>> Yeah, because it doesn't Come on, Rice.
You don't have 13 grand. You don't need
>> Yeah. Yes.
>> Thank you.
What's your beef with anyway? I've done
nothing to you. >> Huh?
>> What is your beef with me? I've never
done anything to you.
>> I don't have rice with you. I don't have
beef with you. You have beef with me.
You was always trying to turn money
against me. So, yeah.
>> Monty, what the [ __ ] Right. That's the
first I've heard. Um, but what happens
between you and Mongol's got completely
nothing to do with me. You both fall out
more times than you turn the TV on and
off. That's nothing to do with me. So,
how can you sit there and say that?
>> Because you used when you was with him,
you used to like like try to turn us
against each other.
>> Yeah. Because I knew what you were doing.
>> Yeah. I wasn't doing anything. You was
the bad one.
>> Me? I was the bad one. So, I sent all
the prostitutes to my own house share. Yeah. [laughter]
>> You remember that?
>> Yeah, I do. And it weren't funny. [laughter]
>> Yeah. But look at the [ __ ] that's
happened to me on there.
PJ, do you know how wrong I was? Even
though Kayie, you do realize, Kayie, you
do realize. Yeah. If I if I didn't get
Monty on here, you you'd still be with
him and you there'd be no rice. There'd
be no him and you know how you should
never know how mad that is. You know how
mad that you would still be with him.
>> Day PJ, you're partially to blame for it
all. Yeah. You cost him his family and
his home and everything. You're the one
who brought us into this mess cuz you
couldn't handle Timmy Eldridge yourself.
Think about it.
>> Timmy Eldridge
part. You missed the part, PJ. When you
brought [ __ ] into it, you missed a
little part of detail. Oh, by the way,
they're into trolling hard as such and
[ __ ] doxing people and whatnot.
>> Yeah, you missed that bit out.
>> Yeah, but the thing is, Kaye, listen.
They done all the stuff to him before
they done it to me. Yes, they did. Yes,
they [ __ ] did. You know them posters
they done to me? They done it to him
first. You do realize that?
>> Then they done it to me.
>> The posters? What? The letters?
>> Yeah. Yeah. The letters to the
neighbors. They done it to him before
they done it to me. They done a lot of
stuff to him.
>> They done What I'm saying is they done a
lot of stuff to him before they done
done it to me.
>> Funny when you dragged him into this
community, right, PJ? Yeah. So many
years ago. Why did they not target him
in his own house and waited for him to
move in in my house? Bit odd, isn't it?
>> I don't know. I don't [ __ ] know.
>> He even done it to me. Petri sent
letters. That's why my windows put
through. False allegations.
>> They done it to me as well.
>> You can't laugh there and say he was funny, right?
>> No, it's not funny.
>> The thing is with PJ, he'll never grow
up. It's like Peter.
>> It's not funny though. Yeah, but no, no,
no. device. Your your [laughter] windows
didn't get put through just cuz just cuz of letters.
>> For what? They're just windows.
>> But PJ, they only put one window
through. That's the point. They didn't do
>> Yeah, but that wasn't just cuz of
letters, though. That wasn't just cuz of
letters, was it?
>> Yeah. But you don't understand life, do
you, PJ? You think what you do is fun.
It's not. It's actually dangerous what you're doing.
>> What do you mean?
>> You're actually a threat to women. I'll
be honest with you.
>> Oh, really? Oh, am I going to go? Am I
Am I a am I serial am I going to go
around killing people?
>> No, you can ask a streamer and a
streamer will agree with with me. You
are a threat to women.
>> Oh, really? So, what am I what am I
going to do?
>> Ask them. You ask the stream. I won't
take no no responsibility for it. You ask them.
>> So, what makes you say So, what do you
what would you think I would do then, Rice?
>> I believe in the future I think you
would actually rape a woman.
>> I would rape a woman? >> Yeah.
And it's not just a woman
>> cuz it's not like my just an opinion.
It's actually other people's opinion too.
>> Bro, I would [ __ ] a woman over so badly
that the civil way. I would do it I
would do it a civil way. I wouldn't
rape. I wouldn't beat I I I just go to a
restaurant, get a 600 bill up and leave
and and leave them with a bill. I I'm
I'm smart. I wouldn't do anything like that.
>> But you know, you think that's funny, don't
>> I don't think what they do is funny. So
explain to me what they do. MPJ,
>> it's none of your business what they do.
>> Well, you're broadcasting about these
women apparently being
>> then you would know that. Then you would
Well, if you watch my videos, then you
would know what they do since I put it
all up, wouldn't you?
>> Have you ever noticed if you go out a
question? Do you like your own mother?
Not in that way, but do you like your
own mother as a woman?
>> I don't really care to be honest.
>> Do you like your sister as she's a
woman? Nothing. I think I think your I
think with family it's biased because
they sort of have to like you because of
your family. Not like that. Not like
have to like you, but I think that's a
bit different than than someone that's
not in your family.
>> So would you treat your mother the way
you treat women off in public?
>> But now you're dismissing all the bad
things that women do. So this is what
the problem is.
>> Okay, let's let's put it a different way
cuz Kay obviously target you through a
different way. What happened if a man
treated your mother exactly the same way
you treated women?
>> Well, it depends what she's done.
>> Well, she doesn't have to do nothing.
She's basically being normal.
>> Well, then the man would be in the wrong.
>> So, what you're doing, going out in
public and doing what you're doing, do
you think that's right or wrong?
>> Right. Because these [clears throat]
women are not normal.
>> So, because So, you think you think
Well, you're Wait a minute. Wait a
minute. Wait a minute. You so you think
by approaching a woman and saying they
got a boyfriend, you were thinking that
they no normal.
>> It's not about Bro, it's not about them
saying they've got a boyfriend though,
is it? Okay, let's go by your logic.
Okay, let's go by your logic. Right.
>> So, if I went out on if I went out on
Saturday, is every single woman going to
say she has a boyfriend or am I going to
get a number or two? Like, what what
what do you think? What do you think's
all going to happen?
>> Well, when I go out and if I could get a
girlfriend, I wouldn't do what you do.
>> It's not one thing. It's not one thing.
I don't think you realize it's not one thing.
>> It's loads of things that they do.
>> Yeah. But
>> so what do they do?
>> Yeah. What do they do so bad?
>> They give attitude. They play mind
games. They lead people on. You've seen
it all. If you watch my videos, you
would have seen it all.
>> So why is it okay for them to do all of
that? But you're not allowed to to do
anything else. Then
>> not every woman is the same brush in the
world. You got it in your
world. They do a lot of the same. and
say the same stuff for people that
aren't the same.
>> But men are just as not as bad as they
are. Men are just as bad.
>> Women can sit there and say men are just as bad.
>> So do you think it's
>> Yeah, but the difference is But you
know, but the difference is is that
women are choosing the men that they
that they go for.
>> Okay. And so do you think it's right
what [ __ ] did with Kaye cheated on her
four times in a relationship?
>> Yeah, but they were both as bad as each other.
>> Michael never cheated. I'll ask you a
question again. Do you think it's right
that Mongol cheated in a relationship
when he was with Kaye?
>> I didn't know he'd done that.
>> He did it four times. Do you think that's right? >> No.
>> Explain to me why you don't think that's right, PJ.
>> Because it's not. >> Why?
>> What do you mean why? Cuz you cheated. >> So,
do you think all women are like that?
I think all women are I think all women
are the same. Not all cheat.
>> So what do you mean all the same? Have
you ever met a woman actually like
>> like all um play mind games, lead people
on stuck up, have the same attitude?
That's what I mean by all the same mannerisms.
>> So have you have you ever gone out into
public into a pub and sat there never
approached anyone and a woman has come
up to you and said, "Oh, hello love. Can
I sit here and have a chat with you? >> Never.
>> Well, I tell you what, take it from me,
right? I don't do what you do, right?
Because women come to me, right? Truth
of the matter. Try this for for a for a
for a a go, right? Go out to a pub, sit
there, go to the pub for a week, maybe a
month, right? And I guarantee you a
woman will approach you, right? You just
got to be yourself. PJ, don't try too
hard because you're trying too hard.
>> Got to approach. You know how many times
a woman's approached me in my life? >> What? >> Twice.
>> Well, she
>> If you stop appro If you stop
approaching, I guarantee you a woman
will approach you.
>> Yeah, right.
>> Well, look at Kaye. She approached me.
>> What I don't understand is how people
can say all women aren't the same, but
they do act and have the same
mannerisms. It's just very strange.
>> Yeah, but your Do you not think it's
very strange? No, I think you're
strange. You're sitting there saying all
women's mannerisms are awful, but your
mannerisms are just as bad. The videos
of you is astonishing. You're going out
walking down the road, right? And you're
asking some random girl, "Oh, if I pay
you 300 quid, would you sleep with me?"
That is not normal. You might just go
and get yourself a [ __ ] escort. It
doesn't matter. Oh, I pay you this much
money. Spend time with me. We all know
you want to get a leg over, [ __ ] sake,
PJ, but that's just not on. That really ain't on.
>> And that's from a woman's view, PJ.
>> I just don't know how you can I don't
know how you can say women are all the
same. I just don't generally don't know
how you can say that.
>> Well, I never approached KK. KK
approached me, but I didn't do anything.
I paid for her to come to me obviously
from Glasgow from any location, but I
didn't try. I didn't have to do anything, PJ.
She fell in love with me the first day
she met me. Do you know the difference
is between me and you? I didn't try. You do.
>> So what
>> the motto of the story is you've had too
many tries in this world and you need to
figure out why you going wrong. Look at
your videos and see what you were doing
wrong in the videos and maybe you will
understand that you will get a
girlfriend if you do the right way.
>> So what about all the messages? What
about all the messages where they led me
on? What about all of the approaches
where they gave attitude? You seem to
dismiss them. See, people like you, you
just you just dismiss people's
struggles. That's why there's no
>> How the [ __ ] did you not say that?
>> I never said that. What I'm trying to
say to you, you don't have to dress
smart to get a woman. You do realize
some women don't want money or don't
want smartness. They just want a normal
guy. If you went out with raggy clothes
on, scrub the air, you'd probably get a girlfriend.
I went out today.
>> Did I? >> Yeah.
>> Yeah. But you trying You're missing the
point. You don't have to wear deer
clothes, dear shoes, you know, cheap you
if you went up with cheap perfume,
graggy clothes. I guarantee you you
could get a girlfriend. You're trying
too hard, PJ.
>> Oh, really? Yeah.
>> I could get you a girlfriend instantly
and ask no lies.
>> Yeah, right.
>> I could just be normal. Be yourself.
Don't try so hard. And Kayie will agree.
>> Yeah. Right.
>> How many times have you said to a woman
you want to come to my barbecue?
>> How many people have you said to women,
"Come to my barbecue?"
>> I don't know.
>> Well, you said it to Katie, right? >> Yeah.
>> You fancied Kaye, didn't you?
>> No. And Katie fancied me.
>> What the [ __ ] PJ, I've never fancied
you. I've met you once. Once. And that
was because of [ __ ]
>> So when [ __ ] left her, you didn't text
her and ask her, "Do you want to come to the barbecue?"
>> What the [ __ ]
>> Yeah. What's wrong with asking someone
to go to a barbecue?
>> Cuz you tried to take
>> Yeah, exactly. [laughter]
>> Was that
>> Yeah, I think I think Kylie fancies me.
>> No, no, no. We not We don't Well,
listen. Listen, if I was a woman and I
seen you doing what you're doing in
public, I wouldn't entertain you one
bit. And I'm not a woman.
>> Kaye likes me. Rice,
>> you do realize what you just said has
just been clipped now. They're going to
put PJ and Kaye. Wow. Thanks a lot.
They're sad people in this community.
>> But you got to understand, PJ, you know,
be normal when you go out. Don't flash
the cash. Don't go out with decent
clothes on. Go out with nice clothes on,
but not dear. You don't have to go out
with a the way that you go out because
sometimes women don't look for that.
>> Yeah. Right.
>> Right. Kayie the people women
just joining in. I'm just
>> I can't believe you got Kayie. I can't
believe Yeah. You got with Rice just to
annoy him, he
>> I didn't get with Rice to annoy [ __ ]
Actually got your fact.
>> Of course you did. Of course. Of course >> No.
>> No. It was called True Love. You don't
know what that is, do PJ?
>> Nah. You done it to annoy money to
>> like [ __ ] got with Natalie to piss me
off and I I ain't bo No. No. You wasn't
arguing. No, no, no. You weren't arguing
with Natalie though. You know, you know
Rice and Bond's enemies. You knew what
you was doing. Come on now.
>> No. Me. No. I appro
>> I wasn't arguing with Natalie. That's
because she's never joined my panel, too.
>> Are you having a baby, Kaye? None of
>> your business if I am or if I ain't.
>> These people keep saying that you're
having a baby.
Yeah. Do you know what you're going to
name the baby? PJ. [laughter]
>> Yeah, right. No, but seriously, are you
are you actually
>> PJ? It's none of your business.
>> So, that's Yes. Then
>> it's nothing to do with anybody.
>> Yeah. So, how do these people know then?
If it's none of their business, how do they know?
Cuz obviously he says on my actual
thing, look, mommy K and daddy arise, you [ __ ] >> Yeah.
>> But PJ, let me ask you a question. How
old are you? 20 something. Can I >> 28?
>> How old are you?
>> I'm Well, I'm old enough to realize
something. Are you ever going to get a girlfriend?
>> Probably not. No. Why does that concern you?
>> Because at the end of the day, yeah.
You're going to be 50, 60 years old
still crying about women.
>> That's my problem then.
>> I find you quite amusing actually
sitting you I've been sat watching you
for about 2 hours PJ listening to you
going on and then you sit there and you
say to your your fellow people in the
chat, stop repeating yourself, but you
have said the same sentences about four
times over each conversation and I'm sat
here pissing myself laughing.
>> Yeah. How many times these people have
been saying skint on here for like seven
years? Well, the whole wow skint, I hate
to tell you that.
>> Has it got anything to do with anybody
if you're skint?
>> No, they're just self projecting
anyways, so I don't care.
>> No, not really. I could say HQ. I'm
skinned, but it doesn't mean I am.
>> Yeah, but these people are skinned. Even
money will tell you that.
>> Yeah, but back again. Can you prove that they skinned? >> Yeah. >> How?
>> Show me money. Anyway, PJ, why you going
on about [ __ ] Thought you fell out of
him. You done a recent video, didn't you?
>> Yeah, because it's the truth. Yeah,
because it's the truth what I said about
Natalie. So what?
>> Why have you fell out again? See what I
mean? Every time I I I [ __ ] talk to
you, you fall out and then next minute you you
>> Because I said that because I said that
Natalie was ugly.
>> You would shag Natalie to be fair.
>> I could I could have bet Natalie when I
could have met Natalie when I was 22.
>> Yeah, but you do love her though. You
would shag that [ __ ]
But if I wanted to, I would have, would I?
>> Yeah. You bend her over and you would.
Honest to God, you would if I think she
I I prefer Kaye to be fair. >> Wow. >> Right.
>> With Kaye Cuz with Kaye with Kaye with
Kaye, we have this lovehate
relationship, so it makes it more like
intense, you know?
>> It's like the chase, you know?
>> PJ, you do realize I'm here, right? >> Yeah.
You're no threat though, Rice. After
seeing your little fight with Monty,
you're no threat, lads.
>> Wow. You've got balls, too, Rob, don't you?
>> Come on, Rice. You know,
>> I'm not being funny. Kayie wouldn't
touch you with a barfall, mate.
>> I mean, if she will touch you, I'm
pretty sure she'll she'll touch Peter belly.
>> She won't touch you at all, mate. Trust me.
>> Well, she touched you, so she must touch
me. Well, she touches me because she's
passionately and love. You [ __ ] idiot.
>> I reckon if I met Kay, if she get with me,
>> she already met you.
>> She already met you when she
>> I know. You know, you know if I came to
Birmingham that day with you, Kayie, I
reckon she'd get she'd jump on me, you know.
>> I was already going out with her, you idiot.
>> Yeah, I know. I know.
>> But PJ, she met you before meeting me,
mate. A long time ago, and she said you
look like a [ __ ] Mong. Yeah, but she
was she had to say that to you though, Rice.
>> No, she she was with uh [ __ ] at the time.
>> Yeah. Yeah, she she had to say that.
>> You really think right you are
attractive, don't you? I'm sorry to bust
your bubble. You're more attractive
right than a [ __ ] you know a stamp
that you know
>> you know you're ugly as [ __ ] mate. >> Right.
>> Come on.
>> Have you seen your own Have you seen
Have you seen your own face? Yeah, I'm
gorgeous, mate. All the women come to
me. I don't have to try.
>> Rice, rice, rice. Stop it.
>> You had to get with you had to get with
a 60-year-old granny.
>> Yeah, but guess what? I'm I'm with a 28-year-old now.
>> So, that is that the only one you had in
your life before Kayie is is a 60-y old granny?
>> Well, yeah.
>> That's all you had in your whole life
except from Kaye? Well, it's more than
you've ever had now.
>> Nah, you're taking a piss.
>> That's my first ever relationship.
That's my first ever relationship. 7
years. It's more than I can say about you.
>> So, that's the only woman you've ever
been with. I mean period. I don't mean
relationship. I mean period.
>> Yeah. I'll I'll date your mom if you
want. No, she's three.
>> So, you've only been with two women.
>> I mean to older women, mate. Did you not
forget that? I mean, there's been into
older women, but then there's 60 year olds.
>> Well, when I'm at though, she wasn't 60,
by the way.
>> So, you've had less women than me then?
>> Well, yeah, I've only had two. Kaye and Marian.
>> Yeah, I've had more than two. You do realize that?
>> So, how long how how long has your
relationship lasted for with these women? And
>> I've had one night stands.
>> Oh, for [ __ ] sake. Yeah, but I've had
seven years relationship. Sex every day.
No problem at all.
>> Right. So, who? Wait, wait. So, how old
are you? 35, 36?
>> No, 38.
>> So, your first relationship was when you
was 30, 29, 30. >> 31.
>> So, you was a virgin up until 31? >> Yes.
>> What the [ __ ] Nah, you're trolling.
>> No, I was 31 years old when I lost my virginity.
>> You was 31 years of age when you lost
your virginity? That is mental, bro. >> What?
I wish I was a [ __ ] virgin again right
>> but to be fair nonslegs is a virgin and
he's he's 30 I think he's 31
>> who the [ __ ] is who the [ __ ] is nonlags
>> you know who that is don't you Kaye the
one on PlayStation
>> yeah long legs
>> yeah [ __ ] Monty introduced me to that >> wow
>> yeah [ __ ] weird
>> shorty shorty long legs loves You done he?
>> Yeah. You see the channel in it. Kaye,
>> would you ever turn gay, PJ?
>> Nah, I can't. But why did you lose Why
did you lose your virginity until 31? I lost my
>> Do you want to know how old I was? But I
do want to know how old I lost mine. Not
an escort without an escort. No. Like,
>> so if if a Wait a minute. So if a gay
>> 23 I was 23.
>> So if a gay guy come up to you here and
basically said, "I love you. I want to
be with you. I got loads of money and I
think you're attractive." Would you ever entertain that?
>> It's already happened. >> Wow.
>> Yeah, it's already happened.
>> I've had on with me.
>> So, why didn't you just turn gay on?
>> Cuz I don't want dick.
>> Well, you don't have to re listen. You
don't have to receive it. You could be the giver. [laughter]
>> You're you're you're a cheeky chap
chappie. You are.
>> Oh, wait. Why didn't you Why wasn't you
able to get with a woman until you were 31?
>> Well, you just said that you lost your
virginity when he was in your 20s. So,
what's the difference?
>> My I lost my virginity when I was 23.
And that's But I got in with an escort
when I was 17, but escorts
because I because I was a I was a gamer,
PJ. I wasn't interested in women.
>> But you never got sexually frustrated. >> No.
>> No, of course you did. Come on.
>> No, of course I didn't. I was into
gaming. I was a broadcaster. I had
155,000 subscribers before coming on to
uh PlayStation. I lost my channel. I was
a streamer. I was a big big streamer.
>> [ __ ] 31. That is crazy, man.
>> Yeah, but I was a streamer, PJ. I was a
YouTuber. I wasn't interested in all
that. My day life was streaming games.
>> I'm just meant when I lost my fragility.
>> Wait, when Okay. Okay. When did you when
did you when did you first kiss a woman then?
>> What? When did you first kiss a woman?
>> Uh, the first time I ever kissed a woman
is when I kissed Marian.
>> [ __ ] hell.
>> You've had it worse than me then. You've
got deal you got dealt a worse um uh
card in life than me.
>> No, not really, PJ. I've actually got a
better card than you cuz I've got a
28-year-old and you're still searching
for that woman that you never get.
>> Yeah, but I've had more women than you have.
>> That is Yeah, but one night stands. Yo,
prostitutes don't count.
>> No, I'm not talking about prostitutes.
I'm talking about normal women.
Prostitutes don't count.
>> They didn't they didn't last that long,
did they? It didn't last 7 years, 2
years, 1 year, one or 6 months. They
lasted one night.
>> Yeah, but it doesn't matter how long
they lasted. It matters that you was 31
when you had your first kiss. I had my
[ __ ] first kiss when I was 20 [ __ ] one.
>> I don't care about that. That doesn't
matter. I don't really think anybody's
bothered about basically when I lost my
virginity. You know what I mean?
Jesus [ __ ] Christ.
>> Does that really Well, that really
bothers you. I lost my virginity when I
was 31 years old.
>> I think it's more sad that you didn't
kiss him until he was 31.
>> Well, because I was a broadcaster and I
had 155,000 subscribers and I was a streamer.
>> Someone to go to a club and kiss someone.
>> I didn't go out, PJ. I was constantly broadcasting.
>> I was a gamer.
>> I was in constantly gaming.
Wow, that is mad.
>> I didn't see the outside like you did.
>> Yeah, but still 31. That is kiss.
>> That is No, no, but okay. What about
when you was at school then?
>> I didn't wasn't at school. I was home taught.
>> No, that is mad.
>> I got seven sitting guills in college,
PJ. More than you have.
>> When did you have your first kiss, Kayla?
>> Said I'm not commenting on my life,
saying about me. She was She was
probably She was probably 15.
>> Oh god.
>> Weren't you Kaye?
>> You are quite funny actually. PJ, to be fair.
>> Kaye likes me.
>> I think you do deep down like me though,
Katie. I actually think you deep down do.
>> I saying like because if you think I
fancy you, that that's just Nah. Nah,
>> I think you do. I'm not even telling
[ __ ] on this one.
You got more open getting a fanny
[ __ ] pocket mate. A pocket fanny and
shagging and shagging KK.
>> So you're trying to tell me Kaye that
rice is [ __ ] better better looking
than me. Are you mad?
>> I'm not getting involved in this conversation.
>> Why didn't you just get a pocket fanny
and just shag that all day PJ? At least
you [ __ ] have quiet in your life, right?
>> Nah. So Kaylee, are you actually coming
to this barbecue then? Huh?
>> EJ, she doesn't want no barbecue cuz
she's enjoying our sausage right now.
>> You You got a little dick.
>> Of course I have. KK can tell you different, mate.
>> Oh my dick.
>> My My dick is that big, PJ. And that
massive. It can't even fit in Kayle's mouth.
>> Yeah, right. Oscar, it
>> is the truth. I can't fit it in my mouth.
>> My My dick is bigger than yours.
I've seen yours PJ and it don't look pleasant. [laughter]
>> Yeah, it's bigger than Ris's.
>> Wait, wait. How did you see PJ's Willie? >> Huh?
>> How did you see PJ's Willie?
>> One time there.
>> Yeah, you saw me get a blow you saw me
get a [ __ ] didn't you?
>> You got a little Tinkerbell. You saw You
saw me get a [ __ ] didn't you? K.
>> Yeah, I did. And that was disgusting.
And you you you was you was fingering
yourself to it, is it?
>> No. No. Oh,
>> rice. Rice videoed himself having a
[ __ ] off his sent it to [ __ ] [ __ ]
went, "What the fuck?" So I went, "What?
What do you mean? What the fuck?" He
said, "Watch this." And I couldn't, you
know what? I didn't even know where to
put me eyes.
>> It was It was um
>> right, you're an absolute virgin. It's
confirmed, isn't it?
>> Wow. PJ, you actually recorded yourself. >> Virgin
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa. How can I be a
virgin when I'm having sex every day
with K P with um KK?
>> No, you're a virgin. You're an absolute
virgin. You're just like
>> a shut up you [ __ ] I'm los What are
you talking about? I'm having sex every day, mate. [laughter]
>> You are a [ __ ] PJ.
>> No, no, no. You love me. Really?
>> Well, yeah. I think you're funny. Yeah.
I won't go far as love you. Yeah. [laughter]
>> You love me, man.
>> I reckon what you should do, PJ, is do
these tours that you do around [ __ ]
London in this uh in them [ __ ] um
restaurants. That's more entertaining
than [ __ ] getting yourself lifted for
baring women. I think so. >> Nah,
>> I like them.
Why do you reckon you could beat me in a
fight? Bryce, do you want to have a
>> You want me to fight you?
>> Yeah, I reckon I could beat you.
>> Why would I want to fight you? You do
realize that day Kayie told me not to
hit him, right?
>> Yeah, but he he he put you on the floor.
>> No, he didn't.
>> Yes, he did.
>> I fell.
>> No, you didn't before you goose. You got hit.
>> EJ, how can I fight you when you don't
even turn up?
Come to London. I'll meet you. You and
Kaylee. And whoever wins gets Kaye. Oh >> wow.
>> Are you willing to to put that to the test, Kaye?
>> PJ, she want to entertain you, mate. Trust me.
>> Kaye can be my new mama, aren't you,
Kaye? You can be my new mama.
>> You know what? I'm old enough to be your
sister, so [ __ ] off.
>> You're old enough to be No. Yeah, but
you can be my mama.
>> Why you got to be your mom? cuz I need a
new bubber over the winter. >> Wow.
>> You know what I'm like though, don't you, Kaye?
>> I need belly needs a new m
>> like is a big word. Um I never said I
liked you. So,
>> you know, I I I think you do like me.
>> Yeah. Don't forget I helped you with the
suitcases that day in London,
>> didn't I?
>> Yeah, you did.
>> Yeah. See, and I think you've got a soft
spot for me because of that. >> Wow.
>> So, you're telling me because somebody
had you with a [ __ ] suitcase or you
had somebody with a suitcase, you think
that they got a soft spot for you? >> Yeah.
>> You're delusional, mate. [laughter] H
>> are you are you like are you like
smoking [ __ ] or are you high or something?
>> Nope. Yeah, I am high. I'm high on life.
>> Have you ever looked back on your
broadcast to listen to the stuff that
you come up with? >> Yep.
>> You're bizarre, mate.
>> O Kaye, I think you're two months older
than me, aren't you?
>> So you could be my new mama.
Cuz you're older than me, aren't you? Huh?
>> When are you going to job anyway, PJ? >> Huh?
>> When are you getting a job?
>> I have a job. [laughter]
>> I have a job. I work for Pizza Hut.
>> You work for Pizza Hut? >> Yeah. >> [ __ ]
>> I do. I'm a delivery driver.
>> Prove it.
>> I'm a delivery driver. I don't need to
prove it. [laughter]
Why do I need to prove it, lad?
>> Because you're telling everybody else to
prove their things, right?
>> Yeah, they don't. So,
>> well, you prove that you're a pizza deliverer. >> Deliveria.
>> Well, yeah. You speak [ __ ] verbal
diarrhea, be fair. [snorts]
>> So, Kayie, when are we um when are we
going on a little day?
>> DJ, stop trolling. Don't you
>> I'm not trolling. And I'm being serious.
I've said this. I always used to say
this to you. >> Stop.
>> She's in a relationship with me. Your mom.
>> Well, we can go. We can all We can go.
We You can come too if you want.
>> I really really don't want to go out
with you, PJ. Because I'm going out with
Kayie. I ain't gay.
>> We can all go out together. We can be in
a freeway relationship if you if you're that jealous.
>> You are [ __ ] sick. You are J.
>> It can be a poly what's it called?
Apollo relationship. I forget the word
for it where three people's in a relationship.
>> You got no hope of that, mate. In a lifetime
>> cuz we know K that rice don't satisfy
you in the bedroom. It's clear to see. >> Wow.
>> You know it's clear to see.
>> You are really full of yourself, aren't you, PJ?
>> No, you just don't do the trick. [laughter]
You just don't do the trick.
What kind of trick is that?
>> Like, you know, you don't hit the G-spot and stuff.
>> Oh, no. What is a G-spot, PJ?
>> I know what it is.
>> Well, explain.
>> I can show Kaye.
>> That's graphic.
>> What do you mean?
>> What is a G-spot?
>> I'll show I'll show Kaye when she meets me.
>> PJ, I've already seen your G-spot and it
ain't pleasant. And it ain't a G.
>> What do you mean?
>> It's an L.
>> Like, do you know a man's got a G-spot
in his ass?
>> You've never seen my ass?
>> No, I said, do you know that the man has
got a G-spot in his ass?
>> Yeah, but Kay's never seen my ass.
>> Well, she's seen your [ __ ] dick and
she wasn't really impressed, mate.
>> It's a lovely pecker.
Yeah, of course. It's that big. Every
woman disappears the next day.
>> Really? Really?
>> How many How many women have you
>> You didn't lose your virginity until you
was 31. So that don't make sense.
>> [ __ ] them women, right? Them women
disappear quicker than the [ __ ]
Titanic sunk, mate.
>> You know,
>> PJ, you've never had a a two-day
relationship. It's one night and that's
it. They [ __ ] off back home with
probably a [ __ ] headache, tell you the truth.
>> Who? What?
>> Every woman you date lasts one day. >> Nope.
>> Not at all. I can't believe you didn't
kiss him until until he was 31. That is tragic.
>> Well, forget about my kissing. Yeah. And
forget about anything. You're never
going to date [ __ ] Kaye. She's never
going to entertain you. I'm in a
relationship. Get over it.
>> Yeah, she's going to say that in front
of you, though, isn't she?
>> Well, PJ, she doesn't even like [ __ ]
see you that way, mate.
>> Yes, she does. [laughter] Yes, she does. KK.
>> Okay. Okay. And let's speed this up,
bud. So, when she left [ __ ] and you
asked her to go to the barbecue when she
was single, why didn't she get to you
when when you was she was single?
Because she wasn't meeting anyone at that time.
>> No, she wasn't meeting you. If she found
you attractive, she would have said, "Yeah, right."
>> But she finds you attractive.
>> Well, yeah, because I'm better looking
than you, mate.
>> You're You're better looking than me. [laughter]
>> Well, yes, PJ. I am better looking than you, mate.
>> Rice is better looking than me, people.
>> Yes, I am, PG.
>> Yeah, really.
>> I know how to treat a woman. You don't.
You're better looking than me.
>> Yes, BJ. You can write it down in the
book if you want to.
>> Yeah, I don't think so.
>> I've seen you, mate. And I'm not being
funny. I'm not going to criticize your
look cuz I don't do that. You ain't no
[ __ ] spring chicken, let me tell you.
>> Do you not Do you even know what that
saying means? You [ __ ] idiot.
>> Well, yeah, I do.
>> That doesn't mean anything to do with
looks, you absolute [ __ ]
>> Well, you look chicken. That's not what
that means. What the [ __ ]
>> Yeah, I know. I'm You know what I mean?
>> You're an absolute Yeah. Do you know
what, Ry? You're a spaz. That You're a [ __ ] spaz.
>> Oh, I've seen his looks. He's no spring.
He's no You don't even know what that saying means,
>> right? You're not good-looking. Okay,
let me put her in.
>> No, no, no. Do you know what that means?
>> But Rice, I'm not the one that kissed
didn't kiss someone until I was 31.
self projecting again.
>> How's that self projecting? What? Why?
What? I said you didn't kiss until you was 31.
>> Well, you're self projecting because you
didn't kiss until you was in your 20ies.
>> I kissed when I was 21.
>> And you're you're actually
soing tragic right now cuz I could just
go in and be like, you know what? But
I'm not. [laughter]
>> A bless you, KK. Oh,
bless you. Bless you. S
>> KK, we should make a uh baby of our own.
>> No, thanks. >> Why?
>> Is it?
>> I'm all right. Thanks.
>> I was actually 21. First kiss at 20. It
wasn't 22. It was 21. And no, it isn't.
That's normal. You have your first kiss at 21.
>> That's not a maz at all. That's actually
completely normal. So if uh if uh [ __ ] said
>> I was kissing birds at I was kissing
birds at 13.
One second. One second. Rice. Whoa.
Whoa. Whoa. Dusty. Your mother doesn't
count. All right. Kissing your mama
don't count. Go on. Rice.
>> If you hear that [ __ ] left fuckingly,
would you be in there? >> No. >> Why?
>> Cuz I've only got eyes for K.
>> Oh. Anyway, stop trolling her.
I'm not trolling. I'm not trolling.
>> Would you shag trolling?
>> Yeah, but would you shag Natalie just to
piss piss [ __ ] thingy off?
>> No, she's [ __ ] She's fat and ugly.
>> Yeah, but forget about that bypass that. >> No,
>> you just shove it in, right? And go, "Oh, yeah.
>> The only thing I'd The only thing Nat
could do is lick my ass."
>> What? Just your ass.
>> Dusty, you didn't kiss any girls at 13.
Your mom don't count.
Uh yeah, she can lick my ass. Yeah,
>> I reckon.
>> Have you ever had your ass licked? Um Rice,
>> I reckon. Right. Yeah, you were licking
my ass right now.
>> No, but has KK ever licked your butt?
>> Well, I'm not talking about my sex life,
unfortunately. Uh in that way, PJ. >> Yeah,
>> that's like me. That's like me saying to
you, did your mom ever get a [ __ ] or
[ __ ] Santa Claus?
That doesn't make any sense whatsoever.
>> Well, you're asking personal
get a blow. Did my mom get a [ __ ] off
Santa Claus? That doesn't even make sense.
>> Well, it's just a figure of speech. You
don't ask people personal questions.
>> This guy is a [ __ ] Hey, this guy's a
[ __ ] man. I said
>> you're calling me a [ __ ] but you
can't spell it.
>> I can't spell it.
>> Go on.
R E T A R D. Try again, [ __ ]
>> Well, that's
>> Can you spell Can you spell captain? >> Yeah.
>> Go on.
>> F U C K.
>> I'm not interested in spelling lessons.
K. Uh uh PJ. But if I didn't come in
here for spelling lessons. If I did, I'd
just basically put [ __ ] you know,
I'll go to school again.
>> So, you can't spell captain? No, I can't
spell nothing, mate. >> Really?
>> Yeah, I'm thick as [ __ ] >> Docs,
>> I've had more sex than you will ever have.
>> Kissing your mom at 13 does not count.
Was kissing birds at 13. Bro, your mom
don't count, bro.
I mean, I had a kiss when I was eight.
It doesn't count.
Actually, my first kiss was actually
when I was eight. That doesn't even
count, bro. Them kisses don't even count.
Them kisses don't even count, bro.
And your mom doesn't count either.
[ __ ] hell, man.
[ __ ] rice is an absolute virgin. Does
he not know what that means? You're not
You're no spring chicken. That means
you're no young person.
Nothing to do with looks. This rice is a
[ __ ] idiot, man. I think he's more
[ __ ] disabled than Monty.
Disabled a Monty man. [ __ ] pack of virgins.
Are you a [ __ ] pack of virgins?
I didn't kick him. He left.
Well, I need to take my wash out and go Betty buys
I think triple H
and go Betty buys. Oh gosh. Oh gosh,
dusty. Oh god. Oh [ __ ]
I'm starting to feel that nasty hangover, man.
I'm starting to feel that hangover. Triple. Yeah, man.
That's nasty, bro. [ __ ]
I want to know you.
Britney didn't want to know him and he
became obsessed. [ __ ] virgin.
Anyways, I'll be in bed all day tomorrow, depressed. Yeah. >> Yeah.
Cuz they're skin.
They call people skinn.
Do you remember? Traf Monty. Why do
these people call me skinned?
Why? Because they're skin.
Do you remember?
Cuz they're skinn. Yeah. Cuz they're skin.
Cuz they're skin. Remember? Why do they
call me skin? Because they're I said,
"Why does Bob call me ugly?" Cuz bomb's ugly.
Do you remember? It was like reverse, isn't it? Oh, [ __ ] Yeah.
[ __ ] burden. Oh.
Oh gosh. Right, I'm gone now. See you later. [snorts]
Oh, I'm mont again. Bro, can you promise
me in 2026 you're going to think of some
new sayings and stop repeating?
It's getting boring now.
It's really getting boring now.
Yeah. Can you stop the repeating? It's
getting boring now.
I'm asking these people on a level trip.
The repeater needs to stop. It's very boring.
They need to stop the repeating.
Stop it. Needs to change in this community. Uh,
can I stop can I stop arranging to meet
people then pulling out? [snorts] Um,
well, I've met I've tried to meet you
people several times before,
but you didn't show up.
Bro, do you actually think anyone's
going to really waste their time meeting
any of you people here?
Like going out of London to do it? You
really think someone's going to leave
London to try to meet any of you people?
Really? [ __ ] off, man?
Yeah. We'll see you tomorrow if he puts
up a video.
Yeah, we've heard it all before. Boston
all talk, Thailand all talk. We've heard
it all before.
Isn't that right, Trip Rates? We've
heard it all before.
Yeah, we've heard it all before.
We've heard it all before. Anyways,
I'm gone. Yeah. See you.