Yeah,
live like I said I'd be.
Let's see if this cunt's actually going
to come today or is he just a lying little weasel?
A lying little [ __ ] mong. There's a
lot of weasels in this community. So, yeah.
Well, I'm going to go live today. But
this [ __ ] said that he he's going to meet me.
Soon as I prove he's full of [ __ ] I'm
gone again [snorts]
cuz this community is only for skin
people that ain't got a life. Little self-reflected.
So, let's see if this [ __ ] actually comes.
Where's my training at? We'll see, won't we?
I'd love to get one of these people
today. I really would love to get one of these people.
I'd love to really hurt him. These
little fat weasels on here. So, I hope
he really does come.
I hate this community. I hate the
atmosphere. I hate the people. Most of
the people, not all of them. So,
hopefully this actually comes today.
It's the same atmosphere.
[ __ ] sake. [ __ ] autistic community.
Don't let us down today. Come on. And
you said you was coming. Christmas projector.
Christmas projector. That's what these
people are called. Greavvesy. Christmas projectors.
You can't let I can't I'm not going to
let you down, Gregy. I can't leave you
with I can't deprive you of content. Oh,
[ __ ] You know I can't deprive you of content.
He ain't going to me. It's bomb behind that account.
He was repeating the same [ __ ]
yesterday. M this month. It's repeating.
We've heard it. We've seen it all
before. Someone that's keep writing like
that ain't going to meet someone.
They're sad sad people on here.
He's not going to meet me. He's not
And then that's it. I'm done on there
until uh for a while. I leave these
little Christmas projectors.
A lot of projector, a lot of
self-reflectors over Christmas.
They call the Christmas projectors grey. [snorts]
You're a virgin.
>> [clears throat] [snorts]
>> I don't know what to eat today, you know. Greasy.
Really don't know what to eat. [snorts]
I don't know. [snorts]
We're going to go for a roast dinner,
but can't be bothered.
I don't know, man. We don't know.
So, I hope you give this [ __ ] [ __ ] if if
they don't post, Grezy. Well, they
won't. If this [ __ ] doesn't post, this
is the bias that's on it. If this [ __ ]
don't post, everyone's going to forget
about it. [snorts]
They're going to forget about it cuz they're biased.
Rice coming in last night. Uh Grey, you
missed it. He's an absolute spazzy is that Rice.
He's he he's actually got no brain cells.
He's He's a bit like the Orington virgin
in many ways.
Do you know Rice had his first kiss at 31? Greasy.
He's only been with a granny and Kaye
and his first kiss was 31. You absolute virgin. No, seriously.
Not even joking, bro.
Jo was projecting again yesterday, but
we're not replying. We're not responding
to these little projecting clowns
anymore. I just want this [ __ ] to meet
today like they said they were going to [ __ ] bro.
Show me self projecting lad. [snorts]
They were saying Monty yesterday.
Boring. We've heard it all before.
Let's think of some new sayings.
Something that's not repeating. Come on.
You're supposed to be intelligent in this community.
Greasy. They're supposed to be
intelligent in this community. Remember?
They're supposed to be intelligent, are they not?
But how can they be intelligent when all
they do is repeat? [snorts]
They said they're intelligent, Greasy. [snorts]
They say that people are low IQ. So why
do they keep repeating? [snorts]
They all like you.
Why haven't we heard from the [ __ ]
You absolute virgin.
Absolute virgin, man. M
yeah when when this when I show this
cloud off I'm off it anyways simple
there's a lot of self in this community [ __ ]
that hair wash was nice This grey hair
wash. I need to go.
That's the thing with rum. It makes you [ __ ] [ __ ]
There's loads of rum, you know.
And man makes me [ __ ] laugh, you
know. He said, "You watch porn from the 70s?"
That is strange. That's what he said.
I was dead. He said, "You watch porn
from the 70s?" That's That is strange.
He thinks it's strange music cuz I
watched Paul for the 70s. That is strange.
He said he knows lots of people that
watch for but not P from the 70s.
I don't know why that stuck with me, bro.
That is strange. >> [laughter]
>> You can't Dusty. You can't beat a good
old bit of vintage P though, can you?
You can't be a
nice bit of vintage B. Come on. >> [laughter]
>> Yeah, I might go and get a rush.
I might I might get a roasted. Might
need to wait for this [ __ ] See if they're coming
or they just another little self-reflect on YouTube.
Probably just I need to I might go get a
roast today actually. You know,
I might really get a roast today. I
haven't had a roast for ages.
Go to my favorite spot. I haven't been
for a very long time. So, you're
probably wondering probably wondering
where I am to be fair.
Okay with you, boss. If I get a rose squeezy.
Okay, boss. If I want to be a little copycat. Oh,
>> I want to be a little copycat today cuz
it seems everyone else can be a copycat.
I'm going to go to this roast place,
bro. They've been mean for a [ __ ]
minute. I text the number, by the way.
They haven't replied back yet, but who knows?
I was happy with one anyways. So, like I
said, I didn't need to get I didn't need
to get loads and loads and loads and
loads and loads of numbers.
I didn't need to get loads and loads and
loads and loads of numbers. Going to be
the same old [ __ ] anyways. So give a
I make my little song I make my little songs easy.
Yeah, I feel hung over today. So, it is
a bit of traveling to get the roast
though. It's a bit long, but worth it.
Hung over today, so why not? So, what is
this little mug doing? Anyways,
is this little self-reflector actually
coming or what?
Oh, I actually went on USA's Instagram
yesterday. Her boobies are looking as
big as ever.
I have to keep tabs on her. Dusty
little bit little bit chubby
but still got healthy boobs, you know,
for the nutrients and stuff, you know.
Anyways, what is this clown doing, bro? Please. Huh?
cuz I don't particularly want to I don't
particularly want to be on there today.
I don't want I don't want to be on here
with the Christmas projectors, you know. >> [snorts]
>> You pair of virgins.
Back up. Pack up. Pack up.
We usually pack virgins.
Pack of virgins. Huh? Huh? What are you
on about? Pack of virgins. Pack of
virgins. Pack of virgins.
Pack of absolute virgins.
Rice and open are a pack of virgins.
Yeah, they're a pack of virgins, Dusty.
They're a [ __ ] pack of pack of
virgins. Pack of virgins, mate.
Uh yeah, we'll see if this number replies back.
Oh [ __ ] I need to message this person,
don't I? That was trying to [ __ ] with me
yesterday. Oh man,
spam that [ __ ] It's 1:00 and I haven't
been on it. [ __ ]
The [ __ ] up. Yeah. So,
but when, like I said earlier, when this
[ __ ] doesn't show up, no one's going to say anything.
That's what I mean. No one's going to
say anything because they're all biased
on here. That's why I don't want any
part of this community.
It's full of nerds, losers,
people that ain't got a life.
But I had to go live today cuz of this
hunt in it. Like I said, [clears throat]
what I [snorts]
What if you didn't want anyone that's
been near a black dick? Cuz some people
are funny like that. Some people
wouldn't go with a woman that that
that's been with a black man. Would you
still be gay?
Some people are like that. I don't know
why, but some people actually are like
that. Don't know why, but you can ask
around. They'll tell you. Would that
still make you gay?
Copycat. You got caught in the act.
We're going to go to one of them events.
I'm saying you're busted. You're under
ar You're under arrest for suspicion of
being a copycat.
You're coming with us.
You're a copycat.
I'm going to put you in handcuffs. You
copycat trying to fit in.
That's fine. That would be hilarious,
isn't it? That' be some great content for Grezy. Copycat. [snorts]
Or maybe I I don't know what to get,
bro. It's long going there, isn't it?
It's so [ __ ] long going there.
It's [ __ ] long, bro.
[ __ ] alone, bro. I like
[ __ ] it. It better not be raining. It
better not be [ __ ] raining next week,
mate. I [ __ ] tell you.
[sighs and snorts]
>> Yeah. I can't have chicken and chips
today. I can't have anything greasy
because of me drinking yesterday. Yeah.
So, I can't have anything greasy.
I I can't go off this YouTube. I'm
supposed to be meeting someone today.
Otherwise, I wouldn't be on here.
I have to come on here today cuz this
continent was meeting me. Otherwise, I
wouldn't be on here. I don't want to be
a part of the Christmas projectors. Triple H.
I don't want to be a part of the Christmas projectors.
Little self-reflecting [ __ ]
I'm going for a roast dinner. Uh, Triple H.
We're going to have some nice roast
pork. I can't wait. It's been so long
since I've gone out for a roast dinner.
[snorts] Oh gosh.
Yeah, he said he's beating me. So,
that's why I'm on here, obviously.
Otherwise, I wouldn't be on here.
You don't need to be on here. You're not
fat and disabled. You don't need to be
on here. It's like what Laney and my
friend said. You're not fat. You're not
disabled. You don't need to be on here, bro.
You can leave the house. You're not
handicapped. The people that come on
here like they're just self-reflecting.
Low low lives. We're mobile people. We
don't need to be on here. Smokey B
disabled. Clint disabled. L disabled.
Trevor Dawson disabled. They're disabled people.
They're disabled people, so
we don't need to be on here. They're
disabled people. I want this guy to meet
today so I can smash him in, bro.
I'm really going to smash this [ __ ] in
today if he thinks he's coming anywhere
near London, mate. Trust me, I've had
enough of these people.
So, whatever happens after today, I'm
done for a little bit anyways.
So that's start [sighs]
just some account.
Yeah. No reply yet.
Same old is it?
I was watching some porn yesterday,
Grezy, some vintage porn, and this guy
was getting a [ __ ] from two women. I
was like, that's mad. You can't even get
a [ __ ] You can't even get a date
nowadays, let alone a [ __ ] from two
women. Jesus Christ.
Imagine that. Jeez.
You'd be lucky if you ever ever have sex
ever again in this country. That's not
an escort. you'd be very very lucky.
Very very lucky. So
that's what I'm saying. You should join
the pool industry. I'll be out next week anyways. So
I'll be out on S. I'll be out next uh
Friday or Saturday. Either one.
Maybe even Thursday maybe because it's
it's new Christmas now. So no no Friday
or Saturday I'll be out again.
And then that's me done till New Year's.
That's that. Yeah.
Same old sad song. Yeah, it would always
be the same here.
I don't mind. I spent £100 yesterday. I
was happy with that. The gambling, the
food, and the drink. So
It's not a problem at all, is it?
[ __ ] I feel [ __ ]
Oh, bro. I feel absolutely [ __ ] man.
I need a nice roast dinner. I'm going to
go for a nice roast dinner. Can this
[ __ ] post something or what, bro?
If he doesn't post something by 3:00, I'm leaving.
So, I'm going to wait and wait and wait
and wait. This should be here giving I'm
going to give him until 3:00. You know,
I can get off of it. I'm just waiting
for this [ __ ]
I'm just waiting for this [ __ ]
Launch legs is so wild.
You're under arrest for suspicion of
being a copycat.
Copycat. I'm going to go to one of these
events and say that you He's a copycat,
everyone. He's a big fat copycat.
He's a big fat copycat, everyone. And
everyone will be looking, won't they? He
got caught out. [ __ ] loser.
Oh mate, I want Timmy on here. I like Timmy time.
Why Triple H? I like Timmy time.
Do you remember Monty man? Triple H.
It's the same people doing the same [ __ ]
Yeah. Why do they call me Skint Monty?
Cuz they're skint. [laughter]
I love that, bro. Cuz these people are skint.
Why do they call me skint Monty? Monty,
why do they call me skin? Cuz they're skin,
bro. That was funny as [ __ ]
Why do they call you Why do they call me
skin? Cuz they're skin.
That's [ __ ] funny, bro.
Why does Why does Bob call me ugly? Cuz
bomb's ugly. It's like just a reverse,
isn't it? Yeah.
Yeah. Done it. Done it proper. I done it dirty, mate.
Yeah. And it was only £180, by the way.
He tried to get stopped. It was when I
was still subletting. It was only like a
little bit of money as well, but I don't
give a [ __ ] It It could be It could
have been £10. You're not going to try
and get any of my money stopped, you
[ __ ] virgin [ __ ]
This is what I was saying to this guy
yesterday. You didn't get any sublet
money stopped. If you got my sublet
money stopped, one of these people would
be getting killed.
So yeah, you didn't get any money
stopped and you don't know how much
money I have. So keep guessing. So yeah,
keep guessing and getting it wrong. Self-reflector madness.
It's your birthday next month. Triple H.
Where the [ __ ] are these [ __ ]
Grezy, where the [ __ ] is this [ __ ]
You're supposed to be coming at 5. We're
waiting. I'm giving you until 3:00 and I'm leaving
to go about my day. I want to see a
community post or a video of you on the
train or some kind of update. You're not
blocked. Everyone knows your channel. to
stop making excuses.
This is what I mean with these little
mongos on this community, bro. It's the
same [ __ ] with them every time. Mongs.
I'm [ __ ] hung over. I want to watch
dinner, but I'll wait. I'll wait until 3:00. Virgin,
but you need to leave [ __ ] Virgin boy
cuz like I said, you don't know what
it's like being new. Being new in
college can be quite scary, you know. It
could be quite scary.
Yeah, it could be quite scary, bro. Timmy. Hey, Timmy. Timmy,
I've been waiting for you. I've been
waiting for you, Timothy Aldridge.
Right. Let me put in cup.
Yeah, he was talking He was talking [ __ ]
about you again yesterday.
Nons was talking [ __ ] about you again
yesterday. Uh Timmy,
he was talking he was saying that you
give um you give alcohol to kids. Greasy.
Yeah, he was live talking about you. He
said that he saw that video of you
giving alcohol to kids. He was calling
you a nons to me. [snorts] Crazy.
Yep. Yeah. He was calling you He's
calling you a N bro to me.
Yeah, he was really going in at you.
I love bacon. I love pickies. I'm going
to go for a roast dinner in a moment.
Well, not a moment. I need to wait until 3.
Same people on YouTube.
It's the same people every day.
Unbound me on your live, John. I saw
your commentary. Right.
I'm baming your live, John. I'm dead,
bro. That is funny.
What did you call him? Triple. You
called him John.
I think he's a [ __ ] pedo.
Why you remember to me this man here?
This man here. Pedo.
Pedo. Do you remember you got called a
pedo? This man here. This man here. Pedo.
Do you remember? Our horable gun.
So what is this [ __ ] Are they meeting or what? Huh?
What is this
other self reflector? I bet he's going
to pawn bomb as well.
>> Yeah. You going to say something? Boring. Bye-bye.
You absolute virgin, man. Same atmosphere. [gasps]
It's just the same people doing the same
[ __ ] Triple H.
Isn't that right? The same people doing
the same [ __ ]
Yo, it's the same atmosphere
only a UK silent.
What? This community might change. Nah,
this community will never change. Repeaters. Nah.
Nah. Never, bro. Never.
No. I don't watch Peter Griffin. That
fat ugly [ __ ]
No, I don't watch that fat ugly [ __ ] Stalker.
I don't want anything to do with these
people on here, bro. I'm only on here
cuz this [ __ ] said he was meeting me
today. So, I'm waiting for him so I can
smash his face in. No,
the community will never change. It's just repeating.
It's just repeat the same repeating people
that ain't got a life. Ain't got that
ain't got a [ __ ] life.
Yeah. When he shows me he's on his way.
Yeah, I'm off here after today. Anyways,
I'm off here after today. I wouldn't
even waste my time on these little repeaters.
I'm giving this cut until free anyways. >> [snorts]
>> One sec. One second. I'll let you in.
One second, lad. Oh no.
[ __ ] off. You're not coming in. Timmy,
do you want to come in or what? Huh? Oh, [snorts]
I don't Nice [ __ ] So yeah,
better make next week count cuz that's
me done until New Year's
and after that I'm leaving. I'm I'm
leaving after New Year's. So you better
make it count. Better make it count, bro.
When's Boxing Day? 26th, is it? You're
drinking on the You're going out the 26th.
Well, yeah, it will never change.
Well, I am leaving. I'm leaving England.
So, I mean, I'm leaving the country.
Boxing day is uh 26th. Why are you
drinking on Boxing Day? I'm drinking
next week and I'm drinking
New Year's Eve. I'm drinking cuz I got
my haircut. I want to get my money's
worth, bro. See, it's all right if
you've had your haircut. This is if
you've already had your haircut,
then you can just go out and drink. I mean,
you know, it's better. You can just go
out and drink, you know. But if you
haven't had your haircut, then who's
going to really want to go get a haircut
and then go out? But if you've already
had your haircut, then
well, you'll be [ __ ] going to Scotland
because the hotels are like £500. So,
good luck with that, lad.
Good luck with that because the hotels
are like £500. So yeah, good luck.
Good luck with that.
Good luck with that one, matey. Cuz
hotel's like £500. I've already looked it up.
It doesn't matter if you're skin. If
anyone that spends £500 on a hotel for
one night is an idiot. I never said you
was skin. I don't care how much money
you've got. Anyone that spends that is
ridiculous. £500 for a night hotel. I
wouldn't I wouldn't pay more than 160
in the UK. One second. can come back to
me. Sorry, man. I was explaining it
doesn't matter if you're skinn or not.
Who the [ __ ] would pay £500 for a [ __ ] hotel
for one night? That is mad, bro. In
England, it's mad. Or you Scotland, it
doesn't matter. It's the same thing.
There's no way. Yeah, I was thinking of
going but there's no way I'm paying £500
for a hotel.
>> No way.
>> Hello PJ. Just just a quick [laughter]
one. Yeah. Why you bo I don't care about
bad at the end of the day. I gave no
alcohol. I did nothing wrong. Surely I
can upload the evidence as said and a
15y old girl was attracted and hopefully
it missed it on on shaggers. even shag,
right? You know, if you're writing to underage girls,
>> I don't know about the Emma Mitchell
thing, but you know more about that than me. >> Yeah.
>> Right. So, I don't really give a [ __ ] if
a nons has called me a nons because he's
a n himself and I've explained this to
you, PJ. Right. Everybody knows he's a
nons, but people on YouTube choose their
victims. PJ, you need to understand
this. Right. If Red Star and all them, I
like Red Star. I'm not going to snag off
Red Star. Now he goes into you, right? But
>> PJ life, he just needs to get alive. That's it.
>> Don't you is my friend. Don't slack off
Red Star. Right. I know you two don't
get on, but I ain't getting involved.
Right. But what I'm saying is your
friend. He's your He's your friend. So
you speak to him off here.
>> He's from Birmingham.
>> He's from Birming Wait, wait, wait. He's from Birmingham.
>> Yes. So why did he come and meet me and
Monty when I was in Birmingham? He does
all of these videos every single day.
cuz he was fishing.
>> Yeah, cuz you are Are you sure he lives in Birmingham?
>> Yes, I know. Cuz I go drinking with him.
>> No, you don't go drinking with him. But
if he lives in Birmingham then, isn't it?
>> Do you really want to know? Do you
really want to know who gets Starbucks?
Do you want to know now? Cuz he doesn't
care. He said I can say it's just text
me. It's money Mike.
>> No, it's not.
>> Yes, it is.
>> No, it's not money.
>> Yes, it is. It is honestly is money. Mike,
>> why does why does his nons keep going at
you though? You haven't even done
anything. He was live talking [ __ ] about you.
>> Because now they're not bigger than
because he's a he's a friend. Understand
this. N go girls go girls go girls go
girls go girls go girls go girls go
girls go girls go girls goes round with
nonsies. Brute king said that he wanted
to rape a 14year-old girl called Dazby's
daughter which we all know happened. Surely
who's decided among a nons nons stick by
nonsis and they call other people
nonsies PJ is to take self-reflection off themselves.
>> Yeah, that's true. Actually,
>> surely I put I think two tons of [ __ ]
out of him. He'll go to the police and
play the victim. Now I don't give a
[ __ ] but I'm I'm not going to beat
Shorty up because when I'm 41, he's like
23. That would make me look like an absolute scumbag.
>> He's actually 30. 31.
>> Oh, if he's 30. If he's 30, that's okay.
I can knock him out then.
>> Yeah. But what if he beats you in a
fight though? But you never know. He
might take you.
>> Oh, come on. Sorry. He [ __ ] cries
when he went to his area and he phoned
the police going, "Oh, I'm the victim."
Oh, this little [ __ ] n [ __ ] square
is [ __ ] doing this to me.
>> Absolute virgin, is it to me? >> Absolutely.
>> Is not a virgin. Look, at the end of the
day, surely has got no evidence of me
giving them kids alcohol because there
was nothing on the video with me giving
them alcohol. So, let don't give a [ __ ]
PJ. There's a difference of you and me.
You care about this [ __ ] I don't I'm
going to the pub in a minute and I'm
getting rat ass pissed and I don't give
a [ __ ] about Shy [ __ ] life. I don't give
a [ __ ] about anything. What's happening
on YouTube today? I don't give a [ __ ]
thing throws his toys out the pan. I
really don't care. PJ. >> Yeah,
>> right. PJ at the end of the end of day.
Surely thinks he's richer than them
[ __ ] Bill Gates. A pathetic fifth
bite of bum with that. He can call me
skint. He doesn't know nothing about me.
>> He is. He is skin himself.
>> So are you. You both live in a [ __ ]
council house and you're both off the
government. So you're both [ __ ] skin yourselves.
>> He's a [ __ ] He's skinned and a
[ __ ] skin flint.
>> I mean PJ, you're not very intelligent
because you know he's you can you can
you can track down his social club and
you can follow him on. You're not very
smart, are you lad? I don't play I don't
play silly games to me.
>> CJ he said about playing silly games
about using your initiative.
>> I went to his area and he didn't come
out three times.
>> Well yeah but PJ I'm not explaining to
YouTube. You're [ __ ] 30 years old.
You should know how this [ __ ] game works. [laughter]
>> Why don't you come down to London and get him?
>> PJ I I guarantee you I could find him at
the social club. I'd walk in your social
club. I whom me like the bastard.
>> You do what?
>> And and I would tell everybody what it
did to Mitchell in that in the social
club. Show the evidence and he'll be
known as a class nons around the area.
Call everybody a nons. So you can
[laughter] call everyone a nons.
You can call anyone a nons on the
internet. All I've got do is go.
PJ send me the link to his channel. Put
it in here now. I'll save the evidence.
So when the priest come, he'll have egg
on his face.
>> He can't [laughter] use his autism as an excuse.
>> He's got he's got two channels though.
>> I don't know cuz I'm not interested in
YouTube. PJ, send me the links. I'll
I'll save all the [ __ ]
>> and the conditions are PJ is if I take
you to his cure after it's
>> okay. Okay.
>> That's that's the deal PJ. That's the
deal PJ. I'll take you to him. You can
bat Sean cuz I ain't touch him. It's
your fight. I ain't going to [ __ ]
upstairs. Once you bat Shan, I'm going
to bat you. Okay.
>> You're going to bat me? >> Yes.
>> Why did you pull your TV?
>> No, I pulled him everything. PJ, you're
a dick on [laughter] PJ.
PJ, I got the edge to go looking for
short channels. All you got to do is put
the link in the chat. both channels and
I'll subscribe to them both and I'll
download everything so when the when he
calls the police because I know how them
all works PJ he can't use the little
baby autism as an excuse
>> Timmy come Timmy come to London today
we'll have a lovely roast dinner together
>> I don't want to come to London today PJ
Sunday and I want to get pissed
>> yeah I want to get pissed with you I was
I was out drinking yesterday
>> so was I and I'm still out drinking now
look PJ I'm with family and that like
>> Timmy I spend £100 yesterday on drink
and uh drink and food.
>> Congratulations, PJ. I spent 140 quid
today. It's not yesterday. It's not a
competition, lad. And I I won all my
money yesterday. I won another 100 quid
yesterday and he spent 40 quid. [ __ ] lost.
>> Oh, bless you. Bless you.
>> And he's standing there with his old
[ __ ] 20 notes [ __ ] tripping over
some nons in London in Albert Square.
>> I got a n
I got a woman.
>> Timmy, I got a woman. Timmy, I got a
woman's number yesterday.
>> Did you?
>> Yeah. You can't do that,
>> PJ. I've had more sex than you've had
[ __ ] crumpets at for breakfast.
>> You've had you Well, yeah, cuz I don't
eat crumpets, you silly goose. >> Listen,
>> what the [ __ ] You've [laughter] had
more sex than I What?
>> Are you Are you gay? Are you Are you
>> [ __ ] bro. Are you Are you [laughter] a
>> You You've had more sex than I've had
crumpets. What the [ __ ]
>> Are you Are you Are you gay or not? Cuz
only gay people call people gooseies.
>> What? Why are you talking about
crumpets? You silly goose.
>> Why you calling me a goose? [ __ ] off. I ain't gay.
>> Anyway, I'm going to p I'm going to get
a p I'm going to get pissed now. Put the
links. I'll go in his social club. by
humiliate the bastard. And he confirmed
the police as much as he [ __ ] wants
cuz it ain't going to look good when the
police investigate his nons behavior on
PlayStation, is it? Oh, I've got a
chism. It's all right for me to bacon.
>> He's an absolute virgin to me. Absolute virgin.
>> Mate, I'm telling you one thing, dog.
Personally won't beat his me. He'll have
egg on his face.
>> Yeah, you
>> I'm not being funny, PJ.
>> I reckon you could take I reckon you
could take non legs.
>> I know. I'm not being funny, PJ. You're
thick. I'm intelligent. There's a difference.
>> Two virgins. Fight it. We're good at it.
>> You don't understand. I will go in his
social club and humiliate him and then
everybody will know the truth. If he
wants to open his mouth on me, he will
[ __ ] have [laughter] egg on his face.
>> Yeah. Yeah.
>> I'm patient.
>> You know what I like? You know what he's
like calling the police about it? Well,
I haven't called the police cuz he's a,
you know, at the end of the day, he's
slandered and he's going and and I'll
say to the police, where's the evidence
of giving the alcohol to the kids? The
police have seen the video. They said
there's nothing being done about it and
he will get arrested for slander. Let
him get on with it. He thinks he's
clever. He's not PJ. Look, don't really
want to go drinking with you cuz you're
just not my cup of tea person. You're a
bit [ __ ] like doxing sensitive and
stuff, right? And you and I don't want
to be around people who take the
fiberactic cable too seriously. If you
didn't do YouTube so much, maybe
there'll be a difference. [laughter]
>> I don't want to be around people who
can't now being suic
Let's let's meet up New Year's Eve.
>> PJ, I'm busy New Year's Eve. Look, PJ, I
would do this for you. I
I will go into your social club for your
PJ. I did I will humiliate but on the
conditions that I can kick the [ __ ] out
of you after
you. You did beat me last time I defeated you.
>> What the [ __ ] are you on about? Are you
really [ __ ] [ __ ]
>> Last time I defeated you.
>> Yeah, you defeated me. Okay, it's your
dickards. You're as bad as [ __ ] good
vibes as you are. You need to go in the
real world and live a live a real life
stop fiberactic cable bollocks it.
>> Okay. [laughter]
Have a nice Sunday that you defeated me.
>> Anyway, PJ, I'm being serious. I will
take you there cuz I'm a lot more
confident and and and ding nons dinged
the little lamb with a lot to learn. All
these people saying because PJ, you've
got to understand this. No one likes Shy
Wrong Legs. They're only being nice to
him because he gets to you. What part of
that boat don't you?
>> No. No. No. No. No.
>> Yes. Yes. Yes.
>> Okay. Answer me this then. Okay. Then
answer me this to me. Okay. Yeah. All right.
>> How comes when Bonnie goes at me, but
when Bonnie goes at me and I go at
Monty, people still go for him? Why is that then?
>> It's because I can explain that cuz
Mongol has [ __ ] rejected his kids. Is
[ __ ] calling Kayie a beast when he's
a booier. He made his [ __ ] own
daughter and then he wasn't trying to
cook her own dinner. He d his daughter
spaghetti and they didn't even have two.
PJ, use your initiative. For [ __ ]
sake, you you are you're not as
intelligent as you are. You say you are
your sons silly.
>> If you call me a goose one more time, I
won't be coming to 55 where you live and
I'll punch you in the face. I'm not gay.
No, no, Timmy.
Timmy, do you remember when you came on
the door and do you remember we had a
fight? Yeah. And then you come knocking
on the door and I didn't answer it. You
come back. I didn't answer it.
>> Yes, PJ. I did. No, P. I really want to
go and enjoy my bed. The neighbor seeing
Timmy Eldridge knocking on my door to
break. The neighbor saw Timmy knocking
on the door. PJ, I really want to get
pissed. Can you Can you just put these
links so subscribe and download the show?
>> One second, Timmy. You know when Timmy,
do you know when you come to on my door
that time? Do you reckon the neighbors saw it?
>> PJ, did the whole neighborhood saw you
go in the mattress? Yes.
>> Everyone looked down the window. [laughter]
>> I can't believe I can't believe that. I
can't believe that you take this
fiberactic cable so excitable.
>> You know what I mean? But Jordy wants to
call me a nons even though I'm not one.
I've got a clean record. I'll just all I
got to do is go around his neighborhood,
show the police station stuff and he
will be a [ __ ] goner. There'll be no peaceful showing
the Tibby magic.
>> Yeah, but PJ, you take me there and
afterwards I'll kick the [ __ ]
>> You absolutely.
>> Anyway, PJ, I'm off to get pissed. Put
them links in the channel.
All right, Captain. You're absolutely
dry that greasy.
Imagine that Grezy looking out the
window and seeing two people from YouTube fighting.
I'll throw you. I'll [ __ ] throw you.
I'll throw you. I'll throw you virgin. [clears throat] You virgin.
Lovely vintage board
in a lovely vintage cord. Right. Sorry, mate.
>> Sorry, M.
I thought anything greasy cuz I went out
drinking yesterday, didn't I? All right, absolutely no.
>> Have you Nobody was hiding under the
table and he was like, "Oh, have you
have you been here long?" He said, "No,
not long. Just a week or so.
He's like hiding under the the um table
and he's like, "Have you been here
long?" No, not long. That's the week or so. Hello. >> Yo,
that to me is wild. Oh, did you reckon
the neighbor saw that time when me and
him was fighting with Tiger? Nah. >> Yeah.
>> What? Because of the noise in it.
>> Um, no. How come I got the minimum?
>> Oh, is that your mama? >> Yeah.
>> Oh, bless Triple H.
>> So, um, did you ask All right, Triple
Yes. Are you going to put these links?
>> Yeah. Yeah, I'll put the link up right
now. One sec.
>> Yeah. Okay. One sec. One sec. Timmy getting sheets.
>> Why do they call you sheets?
because he had a burger on the bed and
>> Yeah, but that was ages ago and they
need to find something new now, is it?
>> It's all I've got on me, lad. Yeah,
listen. So, what happened?
>> So, what's Sean been saying about Tim Eldridge?
>> He said that he's a nons for [ __ ]
[snorts] offering alcohol for kids in the bus.
>> [ __ ] hell. >> Yeah,
we're going at you Timmy really bad. [snorts]
Is that right, Greasy?
>> That Sean?
>> Yeah. Is that right, Grezy?
>> I'm going for a nice roast today, lad. >> Sorry.
>> I'm going for I'm going for a nice roast today, lad.
>> I'm having hot dogs. Me, lad. >> What?
>> I'm having hot dogs. [clears throat]
So yeah, what what onions like with
crispy onions in it?
>> A lovely lad. So what did you say to
that cake PJ? >> Yeah.
>> What did you say to that cake?
>> That she likes me deep down and she she
has a crush on me. [laughter] She wants
Peter Bennett. I think she does like me
deep down Kayie, you know.
>> Yeah, she could be the one for you, lad.
>> I just have this feeling, you know. I
don't know why. I just got this food.
We've got this love hate relationship, you know.
>> Do you know when you asked her to come
farther back for the barbecue, was she
with Monty man then or whe they split up?
>> Split up. [laughter]
>> Yeah, they split up. Yeah.
>> What did she did she reply back or or not? >> No.
>> What did What did you say?
>> He seen me. Listen, you know you know um
Rice, he said that he's seen me. Yeah.
And he's not being funny, but I'm no
spring chicken. That doesn't even make
sense, is it? Nah,
>> I know. I heard that last night. He's a [ __ ]
>> That not a spring chicken means like not
young. That's what it means. He's an idiot, man.
>> Yeah, I agree. Loch Ness Monster, but
she's all right for pay.
>> Yeah, just for [ __ ] and stuff. [laughter]
>> Yeah, that's it.
>> Saying Kay Kay could be my new mama. Truthfree
said he was better looking than you. Oh,
he looks like that. Sid off. Sid off.
[ __ ] eyes. [laughter] >> Yeah,
Tim. Who's more Who's more ugly? Rice or
Timmy? Both in it.
>> Rice. Yeah.
>> Well, is he the ugliest on here?
>> I'd say so. He looks like he's got AIDS. [laughter]
>> I'm going to get me hot dogs now.
>> Oh, bless you then.
>> Bless you. Triple. No, but listen. Hate
chair is is your um would you would you
say Monty man's ugly?
Greavves. I was on USA's Instagram
yesterday. Her boobies are looking as
healthy as ever.
Lots of nutrients.
What do you think of that?
Yeah, I need I definitely need a roach
today. Is this coming coming or not,
bro? [ __ ] sake. I'm giving it till 3
and I'm I'm I'm going out for the day, bro.
Cuz I need to travel there as well. So,
what do you think, Grezy?
Signal Peter Belly's mama. Grezy, do you
remember Sig not Peter Belly's mama?
I said, well, what was she then? Just a
forgettable one night stand. No, not your mama.
Nope. I said she could be mama with that
account. Said nope, not your mama.
There's a lot of history for Peter Belly
in Elephant and Castle. Boozy. A lot a
lot of a lot of history for Peter Belly.
I was watching his vintage porn
yesterday and it was making me jealous.
How does this guy get get two people
give him a [ __ ]
He's lucky. This guy, he had like a
mustache and that
and he was having sex with like seven
different women. How did he manage to do that, Grezy?
I said to this [ __ ] "How are you
telling people to get help? Have you
seen yourself?" She said, "Why are you
still texting me then? To tell you that
you need help? Have you seen yourself?
How are you telling me, bro, to get help
when look at the [ __ ] that you do on
WhatsApp, you [ __ ] [ __ ]
Don't know. How does this guy get these [ __ ]
on his pawn? Mad.
All right. Trip Rage. Do you watch porn?
Do you watch porn from the 70s?
Greasy. You watch porn from the 70s, don't you?
I put the link up. Yeah.
Oh, triple. Do you watch porn from the
70s? That's strange.
You watch P the 70s. That's really strange.
I already linked it to him.
And man said to retra, "You watch porn
from the 70s? That's [ __ ] weird."
Yeah, he said it's weird.
You watch porn from the 70s. That is weird. He said
Yeah, he said that is weird, mate.
I was dead. It's the way he said it though. Goozy,
for [ __ ] sake, I'll link it again.
I just linked it. The absolute virgin.
I just linked you to Skimp Cunt's
channel. The skin [ __ ] [snorts]
Can't believe he's calling me. I can't
believe he's still lying to himself
trying to call me ugly.
Sadness. Really, really sad.
When everyone knows I'm better looking than him.
Insecurity to the max.
autism and insecurity. Still calling me
ugly when I'm better looking than him. I
never had to resort to disabled.
Sad, sad, sad, sad, sad.
Yeah, it'll be the two virgins. It be It
will be the battle of the two virgins.
I think you need to do a video on him. Uh, Timmy,
he was going in hard. He was going in
hard about you yesterday.
on his live stream. I think you need to
do a video about him, mate.
You were saying all sorts about you, but
he deletes his live streams. As you can see,
you were saying mad stuff. I think you
need to do a video to me. Yeah. Virgin Virgin.
Is this coming or what? Nip.
Yeah. Yeah, I went on that USA's
Instagram. The first thing I noticed was
the boobs. G uh Grezy,
that's the first thing I noticed. She
has a little white top on.
And I was thinking, I've seen them
boobies. I've suckled on them boobies
to get my nutrients.
You know, I'll be getting some nutrients
today from the roast dinner. Oh gosh. Yeah. [snorts] Yeah.
There's a lot of self-p projectors on
this community, lad.
There's a lot of self-reflectors,
right? Even you would agree with that,
in it, Grezy. There's a lot of
self-reflectors on this community.
There's a lot of self-reflectors on this community, lad.
I'm going to start getting chains anyways
cuz I I am going for
[groaning and screaming] Uh, just
made myself a cup of K. Didn't even drink it. Oh gosh.
Oh, Mr. B saying again. Come on, Mr. B,
man. It's repeating.
Mr. B's repeating again.
Monty man pulled you up about that the
other day, didn't he? Yeah, that's all
right. But it's just repeating though.
No, I already went nuts last night, bro.
And your mom's I went nuts on your mom. So, uh,
should I have a shower before I go out? Um,
I don't know. I'm trying to think. Oh
no, I'm going out. No, bro. I'm going
out to get a roast dinner. I'm not going
out to drink. I'm not going out to
approach. I'm just going to get some
food. I was out yesterday, Mr. Be. [snorts]
This top smells really nice.
No, I'm going out to get some food. I'm coming back.
Going to roast dinner. I'm [ __ ]
starving, bro. I ain't had a roast
dinner in a [ __ ] long time, bro. Ma,
I don't know whether to have a
shower before going out. I don't think
so cuz it's quite cold, isn't it, mama? You know,
one eyebrow, man. One eyebrow. Does it
look like I've got one eyebrow?
Does it look like I've got one eyebrow,
bro? Bro, really? Stop it now. You're
better than that.
You're better than that. Uh oh gosh.
[snorts] One second.
PJ, you having a you having a fight
today, PJ? Yeah. You having a fight today?
>> Uh, yeah. If this guy meets
>> this YouTube is mad, isn't it?
>> It's really crazy, Rice.
>> It is, isn't it?
>> Is Kaylee there?
>> Yeah. She's uh, you know, drawing a
portrait of you at this moment.
>> Hey, mama. How are you, mama?
>> She's like, "Oh, yeah. PJ, [ __ ] me.
She's my mama.
>> Yeah, this YouTube is mad, isn't it?
>> Kay my mama, is it?
>> Yeah, but it's Yeah, but this YouTube is
mad, isn't it?
>> This is sad. It's just sad people, Rice. Isn't it?
>> So, what's going to happen to say when
you meet up with Big Black Bob?
>> I'm going to smash his [ __ ] in face in.
>> Are you for real? Like, are you going to
broadcast all this [ __ ] Yeah.
>> Yeah. Well, as soon as he says he's on
his way, I'm I'm I'm I'm leaving. I'm
getting ready now.
>> Yeah, but are you going to broadcast it?
>> Yeah, obviously.
>> Are you sure? >> Yeah.
>> So, how was it? So, tell me how it's
going to work out. You're going to meet
that broadcaster who's going to throw
the first bunch. >> Yeah.
>> Wow. You're going to get kicked ass day,
mate. You're going to get whipped, mate.
>> Why is that?
>> I don't know. I think you're just too
confident in what you're saying.
No, I'm just getting ready now.
>> Yeah. So, what [gasps]
>> you look at, you do, don't I?
>> Thank you, man. And I guess I'm not I'm
not I'm not going to get beat like you did.
>> It's YouTube as well, man. >> Yeah.
You lost against Monty.
>> Yeah. You You know, I I really did lose
against him, you know, realistically. Uh
>> Oh, [ __ ] hell. You like a roast in a rice? What
>> do you like a roast dinner?
>> Do I like a roast dinner? >> Yeah.
>> Um I don't give a [ __ ] about a roast
dinner, mate. It doesn't bother me.
>> I'm going for a lovely roast dinner.
>> But I thought you said you're going for a fight.
>> I am. I'm waiting for him. And if he
doesn't if I don't hear from him, I'm
I'm going for a roast dinner. >> Wow.
>> I'm waiting. That's what I'm waiting for
him to to to keep me updated.
>> I'm just here.
>> We're just waiting for the update. We're
all sat there waiting, aren't we?
>> Do you really think he's going to turn up? >> Nah.
>> So, how long how long
>> Well, how long has he been saying he's
going to do this and do that to yesterday? >> Wow.
>> Yeah. Rice,
>> we're waiting.
>> What is that on your picture?
>> Oh, it's a it's a cat. Yesterday, the
balcony. I was sat at the balcony rising
there and there was a cat. He kept like
trying to follow me, trying to copy what
I was doing. It reminded me of Notgs.
>> All right.
>> You know cats copy, don't you? You know
cats copy, Rice.
>> No, that's No cop. No, there's a saying copycat.
>> Yeah, cuz cats copy.
Do you understand?
>> No, no, no, no, no. I think you've got
your wires crossed there, PJ. What do you mean?
>> Do you know when they say copycat? Do
you know what the meaning of that is?
>> What is it?
>> Never mind, PJ. Don't worry about it,
bro. You're good.
>> What is it? What is it? What is it?
>> You're good, mate.
>> No, go on.
>> No, Ju just just Yeah. Okay. Yeah,
you're funny, PJ.
>> No. Okay. Okay. Rice, do you remember
when people used to say Cheryl Cole was
attractive to fit in? That was a
copycat. That was a copycat trend. That
that's that we used to say to copy each other.
>> You understand? Okay. Yo, PJ, I I don't
really give a [ __ ] about Shadow or
[ __ ] Cole, whatever her name is. She
sounds like a What? What the [ __ ] this
conversation got to do with her?
>> Because they're copying.
They copy to fit in with the crowd.
>> So, you believe Wait a minute. So, let
me just analyze your answer. You believe
a cat copies you and that's why they call copycats.
No, no, they're copycats.
>> Yeah, but you just said that it was a
clapped on my balcony. And why they call
copycats is because Yeah, it was it was
looking for its next copycat statement.
They kept following me everywhere.
Greasy looking for its next copycat statement.
>> You are.
>> Anyway, I'm giving I'm giving this [ __ ]
until 3 I'm giving this [ __ ] until 3:30.
If I don't hear anything from 3:30 in
3:30, I'm leaving.
>> 3:30. I'll give it to 2:30. I'll be
extra nice. So you going for lunch then?
>> Yeah, if if I don't hear from him. Yeah.
>> So it's a celebration lunch? >> Yep.
>> Wow. Do you know you well odd you are? Be fair.
>> You're from Cardiff.
>> Do you know if I ever met you in real
life? Yeah. I just run the other way, mate.
>> Yeah, but you're from Cardiff.
>> Yeah. No, I'm from South Wales, bro.
>> Yeah, which is near Cardiff.
>> No, I'm from the valleys.
>> Yeah, I'm from Cardiff.
>> You're from Cardiff? Yeah, originally.
>> Why did you move to Why did you move to London?
>> For a better future.
>> Well, it ain't [ __ ] better by the
looks of it. [laughter]
>> You got Where where did you used to go
for a night out? In Cardiff, in it.
>> I told you I didn't go out because I was
a streamer. Remember the conversation I
said last night?
>> Yeah, but you must have still went out sometimes.
>> No, I didn't go out.
>> Yeah, I can't. Yeah, greasy. By the way,
Rice didn't kiss a woman till he was 31.
I thought he was trolling me. I thought
he was trolling me. I thought he was
actually trolling me.
>> No, I wasn't trolling you, PJ. I've just
>> Oh, yeah. It's a It's a better future.
L11. We can't all be like you
middle-aged fat ugly people sat on
YouTube cuz you got nothing. Yeah, a
better future. Isn't that right, Rice?
>> Yeah, that's right, mate. You got it.
Spot on. You know, PJ's the future of of
all men getting turned down by women.
You you don't think you don't think
getting a first kiss at 31 is is is is
is an that's not an issue. Of course,
it's an issue.
>> It's not what you do when you're
younger. It's do it's what you do when
you get older.
>> Yeah, but how could you not kiss someone
that [ __ ] That's mad.
>> Well, I'm kissing Kaye and making love
to Kaye now. So, my past doesn't bother me. [laughter]
>> You're a little copycat.
>> How am I a copycat? Cuz you've never kissed Kaye.
Kaylee would love to kiss me and stroke
my beard, actually.
>> Wow, you're very deep. I I think is a
word for you. You're [ __ ] sexually uh
frustrated, aren't you, PJ?
>> No, not at all. Of
>> course you are.
>> I don't I don't really have much of a sex drive.
>> You don't have a much of a sex drive.
And you want to entertain Kaye? You're
[ __ ] in our bedroom. Kay
[clears throat] Yeah. Who said I was
having sex with Kaye?
>> Kaye would destroy you in a bedroom apartment.
I I'd use Kayie for vitamins and that's it. >> Wow.
>> Yeah. Nutrients and stuff. She could be
my new mama. [sighs]
>> PJ, have you got a mental mental mind of
a [ __ ] mental man? Yeah. >> N
>> you are. It is something special about
you, aren't it?
>> Nope. Of
>> course it is. Do you not do you not
realize the things that you part with is
a little bit bizarre?
Why? What? Using Kay for my vitamins?
>> Well, no, not that. The things that you
do like. Do you ever question yourself
and say to yourself, do you know what? I
am not normal. >> Nope. >> Never.
>> I can see you now. Right. This is PJ's
day, people. He wakes up. He goes to a
toilet, probably half naked. He comes
out. He looks in the mirror and he
probably goes, "What a gorgeous bastard I am.
I don't actually I'm not actually vain.
I don't care what I look like. I never
say that. But I do I go to the toilet in
a dressing gown. Yeah. My mommy bought
me it my dressing gown.
>> What What's the actual writing on the on
the back? PJ got turned down by every
girl so far. [laughter]
>> But but I I've been with more women than you.
>> I don't give a [ __ ] That doesn't bother me.
>> So that doesn't make any sense. That
doesn't make sense.
>> But it doesn't make me a slag like you
are, is it?
It just makes you an absolute virgin.
>> No, it doesn't. It makes me safer in you
because I don't have sexual transmitted
disease off anybody. You know what I mean?
>> And I heard that you watch porn in the
70s. That is weird, mate.
>> Yo, PJ, have you ever had sexual transmitted disease?
>> Nope. I got tested.
>> Why did you get tested?
>> Uh because somebody said that they got
clidium for me to get tested and it come out nothing.
>> So you slept with a woman. possibility
could have got you chid chlamydia and
you're moaning about me. I've only slept
with [ __ ] two people.
>> I didn't know that. She told me after. I
>> So you were taking a chance on yourself
of sleeping with any person just to say
that you slept with somebody. >> Yeah.
>> So what happens if you sleep with a
woman tomorrow, right? Or the next day
and you caught AIDS. What would you do?
>> I'd cry. Well, why would you cry?
>> I'd cry to my mom to break.
>> Have you Have you ever studied the
actual disease? Actual uh HIV?
>> Can't say. I have rice.
>> Well, you know, you're on about I only
kissed one woman and had sex with two people. Maybe.
>> Why do Why do you lie? Why do you lie
saying that you got 30 grand?
>> Uh why you uh why you ain't got a mind
of your own? Why can't you just say what
you want to say without reading the chat?
There is no chat saying that.
>> Well, well, you know, you're asking me
questions now. Why are why have I got 13
grand? Because I save my money. I don't
go out below on everything. Does that
make sense to you?
>> Okay. So, how long how long did it take
you to save 13 grand?
>> A lot. Long time.
>> Well, like a year.
>> Well, no, roughly a year. No, I get 20
grand a year, mate.
>> Yeah, but you obviously still eating
that in it.
>> Well, in it. No, I save my money. I
don't have to spend it.
>> You work You work out.
>> So, what do you do? You So, you
>> you work at LPJ,
>> but you get takeaways now.
>> No, work it out PJ. I spend £50 a month
on 50 ready meals that last me a month,
right? So, you work that out. I get
around about 1,780.
You times that by 12 months for about I
don't know just work it out six seven
years and you got your sum there and I
get 20 grand a year. So you work that out.
>> So you get about £700 a month.
>> Well yeah more
but you times that you take 50 quid off
that live on that for a full month. Yes.
And then you
>> must be you must be Yeah. Yeah. You
could do it but you must be very bored and depressed.
No, it's called entertaining yourself.
Play games, watch people like you to
pass the time.
>> They would never fancy going out and
having a good piss up.
>> No, no, really. I could do that inside
my house safely.
>> Yeah, but I mean you could you could
pre-drink before you go out. You know,
you don't have to spend loads of money.
You do realize You do realize you could
buy your own, you know how you buy your
own bowl? You could pre-drink and spend
£10 in a pub if you wanted to.
>> So why would I want to spend P10£10 in
in a in a pub while I can go and pay 30
quid? Yeah. for a bottle of rum and sit
in my house and get absolutely pissed
for like two to three days.
>> You can meet some women and meet new people.
>> I don't need to meet a man. I've got Kaye.
>> Yeah, but you before you had Kayie, I mean
>> Oh, yeah. There's a thing called Charter Bait.
>> You're a [ __ ] clown.
>> No. Have you ever been on Chhatter Bay?
You've never been on Charter Bait, have you?
>> No, you asked You asked it yesterday.
No, I haven't. No. No. It's a live
stream of men and women having sex with
each other and you can talk to them live
and you can see everything.
>> Oh, lovely.
>> It's not pre-recorded. It's it's live.
>> You should you should hook up to it
because I guarantee you like you will
see the difference between how the world
works if you watch that.
>> Right. Imagine you have to live off £300
a month because you do it.
>> No, I can live off less now 50 quid a month.
Nah, I just told you I have 50 quid,
right? I have £1,700. Take away 50 quid
for a month, a pound for a ready meal in
Iceland. Tuck them in your [ __ ] uh
what call it freezer and then you wait
till the next month and spend another 50
quid and then ask how you live, PJ.
>> Oh, Ricky. Hello, Ricky Millington. You're right.
>> I went out one second. One second,
Ricky. I want to talk to you. One
second. I have to kick you out for a
second. Uh uh Ricky, I've got a bone to
pick with you.
I'm just about to go out for a ro. Well,
3:30 actually. I'm waiting for this car.
I went out approaching yesterday. Not
bloody interested. Same old [ __ ] I have
a boyfriend. I have a boyfriend. Same
[snorts] old same old bollocks. I went
out local. I got a number. I text the
number. The number's not replied back.
What the [ __ ] is going on here? You told
me I'd meet someone, Ricky.
You told me I'd meet someone. I've got a
bone to pick with you, Ricky.
I've got a bone to pick with you.
Yep. They were given really bad attitude
yesterday. I only stayed local. I'm out
in a bit. Going to get a nice roast dinner.
Yeah, you can come back on now, Rice, if
you want. I just had to say this to
Ricky. I'm getting bloody sick of this.
No one's bloody interested. I went out
in um I didn't go out central London
this time. I went somewhere more local.
Yeah, I went somewhere more local.
Same [ __ ] Same [ __ ]
Someone was even from So, it's
definitely not central London. It's
definitely It definitely is everywhere you go.
Just not just just not interested in it.
Same old [ __ ] in it. Same old. I haven't
had a date since April. It's not looking
good, Ricky. It's not looking good. It
ain't looking good, lad.
Really, really, really ain't looking good, mate.
I did think this person was going to
message back to be fair. I I generally
thought they might have.
They seemed But but then again, I I know
what they're like as well. So,
yeah. What's this [ __ ] say now?
Ricky Millington the the struggle dismisser.
Look at Clint straight away on Monty's.
I just clicked on Monty's. Yeah, look
who's on it straight away. Clint,
but they've got all this money, this
good life. But look who's on straight
away before you could say copycat.
Mad. absolute mad. I'm on here. You know
why I'm on here? Cuz of this [ __ ]
cloud pissing me off yesterday and I'm
waiting for him. You know, yeah, [snorts]
you get £1,700.
I had £1,700 last month, but I bought
some jeans and trainers stuff.
Yeah, I bought some jeans and trainers. So, yeah.
Some jeans and trainers.
So, that's what happened. Oh,
yeah. The boyfriend [ __ ] was giving me a
headache, Ricky. I said to my mom, "Have
you have you left the keys in the boot?"
I was just going to go straight home.
I was like, "Oh, it's giving me a
headache, bro. It's boring."
Yeah. It's not an excuse, though. It's
not an excuse cuz we haven't heard from
him. It's not an excuse. It's not an
excuse. I've showed up many, many, many, many times. You know,
he's got me on this [ __ ] community
again, right, with these Mongs. So I
don't hear no excuses. [ __ ] off. So yeah,
I want to go get a nice roast dinner. Greasy.
Yeah. And I'll be like later and then
I'm done for a little bit like I was the other day.
We're not fat and disabled and ugly like
these people. We don't need to be on here.
It's the truth though, Grey. We don't
need to be on here. We're not fat, ugly,
and disabled like these people.
So, it's like what Laney said.
I want your opinion, Grezy. Right. Why
do these people say about women being
scared and stuff when you approach them?
It's not one thing. I don't know how
many times I said to this I was talking
to this woman on Instagram Grezy and she
was saying yeah she was saying
she was saying right maybe a way to
approach if you ask like that they will
be scared but it's not cutting it bro
because it's what they do via text this
is what I keep trying to say it's not one thing.
It's really really really really really
really not one thing. So it's got
nothing to do with people being scared
or not being scared. It's the [ __ ] that
they do over text which is the main
thing that gets dismissed time and time
and time and time again. [ __ ] boring,
bro. It's depressing arguing it.
I think it's the way you approach women.
Again, I'll repeat myself.
Same old, same old.
Again, I'll repeat myself. Stop
dismissing my struggles.
This is where it becomes unhealthy.
It's not the way you approach women.
Look at the text. Look at them talking
to you on the text, agreeing to meet
you. It's just, do they not have one day
where they just do not make excuses for
these people? Is there a day that goes
past where they just stop making excuses
for women? Grezy,
you know, it's always excuses just for
them having a [ __ ] in between their
legs. This is why I don't bother
anymore, bro. I'm just sick of it, you
know? I'm [ __ ] sick of this [ __ ]
bro. Excuse after excuse after excuse.
Be friends first. So what? You get
friend-zoned. Why would anyone want to
be friends with somebody that they like?
Grezy. What? To get friend-zoned?
What the [ __ ] That's worse.
Anyways, it doesn't matter because you
just dismissed my struggled anyways. So,
there's no point.
Yeah, but that's an old man, right?
Yeah, they defend the women for just
having a [ __ ] in between the legs.
Definitely, bro. It's because they've
got a vagina in between the legs. That's
why they defend them. Yeah.
Why are you telling people to be friends
with women first when you're just going
to get friend-zoned?
No matter what you do, it's not going to
change anything because these women are
the problem. So, it doesn't matter if
you want to be friends first. It doesn't
matter if you grow your beard. It
doesn't matter if you go to the gym.
Whatever you do, it's never going to
change. So stop trying to make it seem
like they if someone is if someone else
is the problem. Right.
If someone if some if if some if someone
else is the problem, it doesn't matter
what you do. It's not going to change them.
I've worked. I've lived by myself. I've
been broke. I've had loads of money.
I've had moderate amounts of money. It
literally doesn't change anything.
cuz you're not going to change people
that are the problem. This is what I'm
saying. They they they go all around for
years and years trying to blame you and
you need to do this and you need to do
that, but the problem is them. So, if
the problem is them, no matter what you
you do, it's not going to change anything.
It's not about being friends first and
approaching differently. You know, they
these people have led people on via
text. They couldn't have been that
scared. That's what I say, Grezy. If
people's really scared, they won't be
leading you on via text. And no matter
what you say in response, they just
dismiss it. So, it's ridiculous. And
they're only doing it cuz they're a
woman, not cuz they're right. That's the
thing. It's because they're a woman.
It's not because they think they're right.
Because if if like I said, if I was
saying it about men,
they would all agree. So, it's not
because I'm even wrong. So, I hate to
say it, people wouldn't be saying I'm
wrong if I was moaning about men. So,
just stop the cat, bro. You know. So, yeah.
Yeah. The problem is them, bro. The
problem is definitely definitely them.
They tell you, have you heard all of
these things before, Grezy? That they
want you to they want a man that lives
by themselves that work. Bro, you could
do all of them things and you'll still
get the same experiences.
[ __ ] I have people make excuses before
that, oh, you live with your mom.
But then when I live by myself for like
four years, what changed? Nothing. So,
they always constantly make excuses for women.
They're just white nighting excuses for
why they're such [ __ ] Oh, you don't
work. You got no money. You live with
your mom. It's the way you're acting.
They have all of these excuses just
because these people have got a vagina
in between the legs.
Go to the gym. I went to the gym,
worked, and lived by myself. So, what
was the excuse that time? I used to go
out approaching all the time. I used to
go out approaching all the time, bro.
Like by the gym. Same old [ __ ] You
can't change people that are the
problem, which is these women. They are
the problem. Doesn't matter what
self-improvement you do, it's not going
to change them. It's not going to change
your experiences. So why do people make
it seem like it will? Yeah.
Anyways, I'll be out on Saturday, so
you'll have some more content on
Saturday, Grezy. And yeah, then we'll do
New Year's Eve
and then Yeah.
And then that's me done
cuz my hair would have grown back by
then. Well, I need to probably get a
haircut again by New Year's Eve. anywhere
cuz I could stay in on Saturday. I could
go out so why not just go out? I've had
my hair done so it's not going to cost
me much money so
I don't care. Can spend £15200. I don't
give a [ __ ] Not that would even come to
that anyways. But yeah,
that's the way I see it.
So when are you when are we going to
meet someone in this country grey that's
not all the same them
on about six approaches yesterday even
my sister was there
seems to be a long playing record now doesn't it
giving me a [ __ ] headache it was
boyfriend boyfriend [ __ ] me. I thought I
was in central London again.
It is mad why they say all of that stuff.
But then they can't find a nice guy.
They can't find a normal person. That's
what that's what these women say, Grezy.
Now, I can tell you that I have not had
anyone approach me yesterday. I
approached loads of people.
So, why do these pe women that moan
about men get sympathy? This is what I don't understand.
They don't um they don't deserve sympathy
cuz think about it, right? I'm moaning.
Okay, let's let's let's use this
analogy. So, I'm moaning and I'm
complaining about women. I approached
six people yesterday. They were all the
same. So, no women approach me. I
approached them. So, why do they moan?
Why do they moan about men? They don't
have no life experience with men.
They have no life. And even if I wasn't
a man, even if I was the third gender,
if there was the third gender, I'd still
say the same thing. It's not because I'm
a man myself. Nothing to do with that. I
just don't understand how they can complain
when they've got all of these options.
No, no, no, no, no. That's not an
excuse, Greasy. They have had a full of
chances to meet people that are decent,
that are normal, that won't use them.
So, it's not about people using them.
It's not about people using them, right?
They they have they have many many
chances for people that want a
relationship. So, so yeah. So, that that
excuse don't even work. That excuse So, because
who said anyone's using them? So, now
you're making stuff up.
So, now you're making stuff up. So, even
when they're shown different, they still
moan about men. This is what I don't
understand. They they generalize all men
and then when they're shown different
men, they're not interested. And then
they continuously complain about men.
Whereas me, I've never been shown a
different woman. I've heard about it,
but I've never been shown it. I've Oh,
trust me, I've heard about it. I've
heard it on Reddit. People saying women
are not all the same. I've been hearing
it for years, mate. And I've never ever
met a woman that weren't the same.
Is is my generaliz is my generalization not woman?
They don't have more experience than me
because they've been in a relationship
with one person. Right? Just because
somebody has been in a relationship with
one person, that does not mean they've
got more life experiences than me.
That does not mean Okay. Okay. Let's use
nods legs, right? So, what has he been
in? Two, three relationships. I have got
way more experiences with women than he
would ever have. A relationship with
individual people is not life experience.
It is not life experience. And that does
not mean that you know more about women
than someone that's been traveling up
and down the country meeting women for
years. That's not an that's not even an experience.
You know, that's an individual person.
A being in a relationship with one
person does not mean you know more about women,
you know. Good good for them.
Good for them, bro. I mean, do they want
a silver, red, or green medal? Good for them.
So, I mean, I was approaching people
yesterday. I weren't looking for sex. I
mean, I weren't looking for sex. I
weren't looking to use people. So, what
you're saying don't make sense. And I'm
sure there's pretty loads of I'm pretty
sure there's other men out there that
want a relationship. I'm pretty sure
there's other men out there that want a
relationship and not just sex. So, think
about it. Right. Okay. Okay. Let me let
me let me let me let me give you this
analogy again. So, they're saying all
men are the same, right? But then
they're rejecting offers that they're
getting. They are rejecting offers that
they're getting where people not even
asking for sex. It doesn't add up. Me,
I've never been shown a different woman
in my life and I probably and I probably
never will be and I probably never will. So
they have got options. So surely if they
have if they've got options then they
should be able to find someone in two
months or one month. Surely with a bit
of effort, with all of the options they
have, I'm sure they can find someone
that um you know isn't trying to use
them. Whereas if if someone hasn't don't
have any options like me, I mean, you be the judge.
Do you know what I'm saying? So, it's
like, like I said to you before, there
even if it's five people,
there's no way a woman could go six,
seven years without finding a man that
doesn't want a relationship. There's no
way. There's no [ __ ] way, bro.
There's no way. Even if 90% of men
wanted sex, right? Say 90% of men wanted
to use them, they would have found that 10%.
Cuz they've got options. So,
so it doesn't make sense. It they they
you approach people, right? And you're
not just using them for sex. You know,
when you're sat there saying about I
didn't use people for sex. I didn't want
I didn't want sex from USA is she wanted
sex for me. Double standards again. So,
when I've met these people, actually, I
haven't just wanted sex
cuz I was prepared to meet them again
and again and again or at least stay in
contact with them. So, what you're
saying doesn't make any sense.
So, what do you think? If someone has
sex with me, I'm just going to leave.
That's basically what they mean. They
basically mean that all men want sex and
then leave. That's not the case. Because
even if I was to have sex, I wouldn't leave. So,
that's it doesn't make no sense when
they're saying they can't find someone.
It doesn't make sense.
And they've got very very minimal
experience with men compared to what
I've got with women. Like I said, if
I've seen women meet hundreds and
hundreds and thousands of men that are
the same, then I'll be like, "Yep,
they're all the same." I'd say, "Yeah."
But you judging people based on three or
four men that you go for, how does that
mean men are all the same? Like, there's
a there's a big difference.
There's a big big difference. Do you not
see the difference in it, Grievously? Do
you not see the difference? You're not
trying to say that I want to use someone
for sex and leave them.
Really? So, I want to use someone for
sex and leave them. I don't think so.
And even if you want sex, you want sex
and a relationship and to continuously
keep meeting that person. So, even if
you're using someone for sex, you're not
leaving them, you're staying with them,
which is basically what people do in a
relationship, don't they? Stay with
them, have sex. So,
yeah. So, what you're saying don't make
sense. I approached people yesterday
normally they didn't even give me the
chance to even get to know me. So what
you're saying don't make sense.
What you're saying does not make sense.
It's not like these women have gone on
the on a date with me and I'll be like,
"Oh, let's [ __ ] Let's [ __ ] Let's let's
fuck." And then they're like, "Oh, uh
well uh do you want to do you not want
to get to know each other?" No, no, no.
Let's [ __ ] Let's [ __ ] Let's [ __ ]
Let's [ __ ] Let's [ __ ] So that's not
what's happening. You go up to someone,
hey, how are you? I've got a boyfriend.
So what they just imag They assumed
automatically you wanted to [ __ ] them
and leave them for just from opening
your mouth. They haven't met you. They
haven't got to know you to know what you want.
So that doesn't make sense.
See, you might think I I think I'm all
I'm right all the time, but I don't
think I'm right all the time. It's ju
it's just this thing I know so much
about cuz I've been doing it for years.
And another thing I'll repeat what I
say. Why is it okay for women to want
sex but not men? That's a bit double
standards, isn't it?
This is what I said to someone on
Instagram yesterday. I said I said,
"Listen, you're saying about me only
wanting sex, right?" Yeah. Which I don't
even want sex anyway. Like just sex like
to leave some. And even if I did,
furthermore, so why is it okay for women
to want hookups?
Why is it okay for women to just want
sex? And there are even if it's 10% of
women, there's still [ __ ] women out
there. So what is it okay for them to
want to pump and dump someone? But
people can't do the same. You see the
double standards with that?
That is double standards because say you
wanted sex, right? You get all these
people that say, "Oh, women are going to
go with somebody that just wants sex."
But no one had a problem with USA is he
wanted wanted me for sex and other
people wanted sex.
Is that not Is that not double
standards? Say I just wanted sex. Right.
Right. Say I just wanted Say I actually
just wanted to have sex and leave
someone every time I go out. Okay. But
there's women that only want sex. So why
why why are you being shamed for it?
Which doesn't even make any sense
because then they're called slags
afterwards. So it doesn't even make that
doesn't make sense, you know? So what
even if you did want someone just for
sex? Not that I [ __ ] do anyways, but
let's just agree with them for a minute.
Say you wanted Okay. So what? Why are
you not allowed? Why are you not allowed
to to find someone for sex?
Why not? They they use people for sex.
USA wanted to [ __ ] me straight away.
Straight away wanted to [ __ ] me straight
away. Why is it okay for her to to want
to [ __ ] straight away then?
And then you realize that it's not you.
It's a gender thing. When you really
realize it's a gender thing and it's
nothing to do with you being right or
wrong, you you you'll realize this. Why
is it okay for other people to want sex?
Why is it okay for fig to want sex?
Why is okay for somebody to give a blow
driven in anyway?
Why is it okay for someone to I had a
one night stand on my birthday. Why is
that okay for them to want to [ __ ] straight away?
It is [ __ ] ridiculous.
But I'll go out next week anyways. Like
I said, I don't mind. I have I've had my
haircut anyway, so I I've got nothing
better to do. It's the times when my
hair is [ __ ] again and I'm like, why am
I going to get my haircut just to go out
and get the same [ __ ] again?
That's when I'm like, nah, nah. I can
just style my hair on Friday and go out.
I'm not going to lose anything. Yeah.
I might not even go out New Year's Eve.
I don't know. But I'm definitely going
out on Friday or Saturday.
Have you noticed the time goes so
quickly? You know when you go out
drinking on Saturday, by the time you
have had a roast easy,
it seems like you're in [ __ ]
Wednesday, [ __ ] Thursday again.
When you had a mad weekend weekend,
you're hung over as [ __ ]
Today I wasn't that bad. I wasn't that
bad today. I'm still hung over, but not
like last time in Liverpool Street. Oh
my god, I thought I was going to die.
Them cocktails. I think it was cuz I was
mixing it. But what did I have
yesterday? Guinness rum. I had some
white rum. White rum. Uh, white rum.
White rum cocktail. That's the thing
with white rum.
That's the thing with white rum, bro. It
makes you so hungry the next day, bro.
Yeah. It makes you so hungry.
the next day like white rub killer bro
killer so I think if you don't mix your
spirits I don't know in in
Liverpool street I was having Guinness cocktails
I was mixing the drinks I can't remember
exactly but I I was [ __ ] the next day
but yeah white run makes you hungry bro [laughter]
hungry as [ __ ] I was hungry at 6:00 in the red. [snorts]
Yeah, man. So, yeah, I think my hair
should still be all right next week. Ty
it up a little bit. Yeah, man.
I had a lot of hair. So anyways, what's
this [ __ ] doing?
I'm [ __ ] hungry.
>> I just put a clean t-shirt on even
though I smell like B a little bit cuz Yeah.
and have a nice roast. Get back, change.
Yeah. If you if you if you say that you
just want a woman for sex,
right, they were like, "Nope, no n
women can see through you.
Women can see through you. Women can see
But then it's okay for a woman to want
to [ __ ] you straight away.
As soon as USA Izzy set eyes on me, I
reckon she would have [ __ ] me that
day, you know. But that's all right. But
if you so much as text someone
to meet them within a week, we're
calling the FBI.
The double standards is insane. And
they're talking about incels.
Yeah, cringe as [ __ ]
There you go. Got my coat on. Yeah, it's
cringe as [ __ ] isn't it? But what I'm
saying, bro, is
you like my little coat? Uh, keeps me warm.
Cost me 90.
What I was saying is though, um,
yeah. Why is it okay for women to want
to [ __ ] you straight away, but if you
want to meet a woman in 5 days, call the FBI?
It's like you're treading on eggshells.
Like, every time you you you you try to
date a woman, you're treading on
eggshells. And people are continuously
looking for things to blame you. Oh, you
done this wrong. Oh, you need to go to
the gym. Oh, you need to work. Oh, you
need to do this. Oh, you They're
constantly looking and picking at things
to blame you. Oh, maybe a woman knows
that you just want her for sex. Even
though women can go around having sex or
wanting sex or not even having sex, just wanting sex.
Why are you not allowed to use women if
they're allowed to use you? Even if it's
10%, even if it's 10% of them, they're
still [ __ ] out there.
Look at that sig, right? That news that
that New Zealander, she went she went,
"Oh, I don't want I don't want um I
don't like people touching me and stuff.
Then she was texting me, "Oh, where are
you gone?" Started kissing me,
[ __ ] everything. We're going back to
my place now, but we're not [ __ ] I
said, "Okay, can we do other stuff
then?" She says, "Yeah, but we're not fucking."
And then she jumped on my dick and
started [ __ ] me.
So, I mean, she didn't just fall on my
[ __ ] dick, did she?
So, it's just it's just mad how they
just mental. It is mental, bro.
I want to do a video on about women
generalizing men because I've never ever
I've never ever done a video on about
how women generalize men and [ __ ] and
it's not right,
[snorts] you know, cuz I'm I guarantee
you one of these women that I've
approached over the years complain about
men. They've got to they've got to
complain about men.
Whereas you're constantly going out
trying to find this different woman that doesn't exist,
you know? So what what's their argument?
You can see that they weren't lying
about you in their messages. Oh, you're
there. You're that. Thanks for coming up
to me. They weren't lying. So they found
they found their match now, haven't
they? They found this this person now.
But then they contradict themselves and
then they go for somebody that's in
prison on death row. There's a woman
dating some guy in death row and she
didn't she wasn't with him before. So, I
think it tells you all you need to know.
I think it tells you all you need to know, lad.
Could you imagine a woman approached us
and showed that they were different? I
don't think we'd be generalizing all
women anymore, would we? But they will
still generalize all men and be adamant
they can't find someone.
Maybe you should stop saying that you
got a boyfriend and you don't. Maybe you
should stop giving people a chance and
then you'd actually find No. And again,
I don't care. The thing is, Greasy, I
generally don't care if these people get
with me or not. I don't care. I'm just
saying it from like their point of view.
Like, it doesn't make sense. And and I
don't care. I don't really care if they
get with me or not. It's just like what
I'm saying. You know what I mean? It's
just it makes it, you know, that
it doesn't make sense why somebody
wouldn't. And I don't care either way,
but you you get me. I'm just I'm seeing
it if I was them like in their shoes, you know?
So that's that. So yeah,
I've even said, you know, that the
options that they have aren't genuine
options. These men's these men are like
simps, white knights, and [ __ ] But
there are someone out there that's got
to be different if they've got options.
Whereas I don't even have options. So
how could I ever find someone different
if I don't have options? Unless I keep
going out and approaching someone. So
they're more likely to meet someone
statistically that's different than I am.
You know what I mean, bro?
So that's that. Yeah.
I don't know. But
what do you mean when it see when it
shows no one will see you? What do you mean?
Yeah, they're cringe words.
So, I could turn around and say to these
women right now,
come and meet me
and I'll show you different, but they
wouldn't meet you. So, they contradict
themselves. So, it's like they just contradict themselves.
And it's not like you're fat. It's not
like you're ugly. Um, this is what makes
the thing makes no sense even more. It's
not like you're blind. So, there is just
no reason for it at all. Really, there
is no reason for it. I wish there was a
I wish you could say you didn't try.
Then I'd have the perfect excuse to keep
blaming myself. Oh [ __ ] you don't try
anything. You sit online every day
winging. Then I could be like, oh yeah,
this is why you don't meet people.
So there is no real excuse for it.
You're not disabled. You're not fat.
You're not ugly. So, there really isn't
an excuse as to this why this happens.
I'd love to say I didn't try.
I met some cab driver yesterday. He was
from up north. He was all right. Vzy cab driver.
Yeah. But I'll never be going out with
people again. [ __ ] that. Bad. Bad. And
I'll be out by myself next week. [ __ ] that, bro. Never again.
Never again. Never again. Never again.
Should be with people. You're trying to
meet [ __ ] baddies, bro.
[snorts] Now you got me [ __ ] saying
that [ __ ] word. What the [ __ ] bro? I
never used that word in my life. Now
you've got me [ __ ] saying it. [ __ ]
heads all over the place. Jesus Christ.
Anyways, ghosting. What are you doing, bro?
It's almost 3:00. What the [ __ ] are you doing?
I've had enough. You got me [ __ ]
saying it now, you [ __ ]
Do you know what I like? I I was playing
pool yesterday, Grezy. I got my ass
whooped. I like a nice game of pool. I
was playing pool whilst drinking rum.
Rame and Paul. Oh gosh.
We Oh gosh.
You know what would be a lovely site?
Yeah. Working hard and then getting paid
at the end of the week, Greezy. And then
going for a nice drink. What do you
think? Working really hard and then at
the end of the week going for a nice
piss up waiting for the money to land.
Is that lush?
Greavesy. Be honest. Is that absolutely
lush? That is absolutely lush.
Isn't it Greavy? Absolutely lush. Yeah.
Waiting for that money to drop.
Especially if it's on a Wednesday. Could
be anything. 100 pound, 150, 100,
whatever it is. 200 300. I remember when
I used to do Uber. Yeah. I used to I I
used to [ __ ] do the Uber. Yeah. And I
used to come back and play Franklin at
the old house waiting for the money to drop
like 160. I think it was like 160.
It was lush. Go to the gym. I used to go
to the gym and that. That's what annoyed
me about the house, man. I had my own
routine, man. [ __ ] had my own
routine, you know? gym, the [ __ ] Uber and that.
Yeah, I had my own routine.
But yeah, [clears throat] it was sick.
Try to have a routine around it.
Everybody's far away from [ __ ] each
other, you know.
Yeah, USA is his boobies are still
looking quite big. Boozy.
They're still looking quite juicy.
If you go on her Instagram,
so Autumn's abandoned me. KK's abandoned
Not good, is it?
See, this woman that I approached
yesterday, she had like a big butt and
big boobs and she was kind of curvy. And
obviously I that those are the kind of
women that I go for, Greasy, cuz
obviously my nutrients and stuff and
obviously if they're going to be a prime
candidate for baby Peter,
they can't be having no boobs because
how are they going to feed the baby?
And in the winter, how am I going to how
am I going to um you know, cuddle up to
someone that's [ __ ] a bone,
you know? That's no good. That That's no
Yeah, that's that's no good, bro. No good.
Cuz then I can't get my vitamins and
stuff. So, it really won't do. It won't
do for me. That's That's not really what
I'm looking for. Like the guy in the
shop said, we've got a Linda Williams.
Absolutely no way.
Um any any particular hair length? Um
anywhere from here to here.
[laughter] That's my favorite sketch.
That really won't do.
Absolutely no way.
We've got a L. We got a Linda Williams.
No, I think he wanted a Linda Williams.
And they had a Lindsay Williams. Did I
mention she should have a glass eye? [laughter]
I was dead, bro. That was one of the funniest ones.
Oh, did I mention she should have a glass eye? [laughter] Yeah.
So, Grevy, if the woman doesn't have
boobies and stuff and she's not curvy, I
like ass, but not as much as boobies.
Yeah, I mean good. There was one woman
before I approached. She said, "Do you
prefer boobs or bum?" I said, "I prefer
boobs." Lucky for you, I've got both.
And I started latching on to her her boobies, Grezy.
Yeah. I started latching on to them. And
she said, "I'm not a cow."
See, I've always been a little booby nibbler, Grezy. haven't I?
One second. My sister's calling me. Hold up.