There you Oh, heat.
questions in London. Just don't
just walk up first. No, no, no. [snorts]
Reddit is a site designed to piss you off.
It's It's designed to get you under your last nerves.
Bit like this country, is it?
>> Yeah. It's a bit like this country, in it.
Yeah. Can't go out and I can't go out
this week to the thing. Is it busy?
Messing these people on Reddit.
No one's replying. Yeah,
just go outside.
You know, another thing, come to think
of it now, a woman's never been told
grievy, to get therapy. Have you noticed
men that struggle are told to get
therapy, but women are never told to get
therapy? Even though some people use
therapists, they never ever get told to
go and get therapy. Have you noticed that? Cuz
when someone says like go, it makes it
sound like it's a you problem because
they're telling you to get help.
Do you know what I'm saying, Grezy? Like
if someone says to you, "Oh, go get
therapy." They're basically telling you
to get help. Whereas if you wanted a
therapist, you would get a therapist.
But why? But it women are the problem. I
don't need help. That's the whole point.
When you're telling someone to get a
therapist, you're you're telling a
person that they need help. People get
therapists because they want they want
to find a uh they want to find um a
therapist. That's telling someone that
they need help. But it's the women that
are the problem. So why would I get a
therapist if women are the problem? You
get therapists if you feel like you need
a therapist. They are the problem. So a
therapist is not going to help you
because women are the problem.
So when someone is saying, "Oh, you need
to go get therapy." They're making it
seem like you are the problem and you're
not. When it's the women,
there are people that use therapists. It
is women that are the problem. You know,
there's loads of people there's loads of
reasons why people use therapy if if
their parents died. I had therapy when
my parent died when I was young because
your your your parent died and obviously
therapy and whatever that wasn't because
of women. You don't need to get therapy
because of women. Women are the problem.
Women are the problem. So when you're
saying get therapy, that's that's
basically taking the blame off women. In
my view, that's that's taking the blame
off women. If you're saying to someone
get therapist, I've had a therapist
before when I was 12, 13, but there was
different reasons. Obviously, you know,
people use therapists, but you don't
that's not going to make women stop being evil, you know.
Well, you would be as well greedy if you
had my experiences. Oh, I got my
WhatsApp back, by the way, and had to
use a different number.
So, this guy in Redden, yeah, he's so
nice, bro. Like, as a friend, I messaged
him. Oh, it's my new number. Said, "Oh,
okay, mate. He just up updated that now.
How's your week going so far? He's
actually a nice guy. This this this guy
I met last month, bro.
Not not in a gay way. Basically, he's
with someone anyway. It's like he's
actually a cool guy. See,
that's why when these women say they
can't find someone, they're full of [ __ ]
You never get this. You see, like I
said, if you speak to a man, there's no
switches. is greasy. They don't switch
the next day.
Yeah. And it will never change. So
that's that. See, when you speak to a a
guy, right, as a friend, Greavves, say
you got a friend, they don't switch.
Have you noticed it's always the same?
You notice it's always the same.
But when you speak to a woman, they switch
the next day.
I messages one saying, "No, you still
full of shit." And they blocked me,
Brit. Uh, they blocked me. Um,
they blocked me, Greasy.
I said, "You still full of shit." That's
all I said. Blocked.
But yeah, your luck's never going to
change. You're best off just staying in
bed, depressed, saving money. Is that right, Grezy?
It will never change. So yeah,
I probably won't even eat today to be
honest. Too depressed, bro. Yeah.
Yeah. I probably won't eat today. Too depressed.
Did you meet Grezy?
I probably won't even eat anything to be honest.
Yeah. Too depressing, bro.
So, I probably won't eat nothing.
In before the your skin comments, it's
so predictable this community. You can
predict exactly what they're going to say.
That's how boring they are, bro.
Yeah. I will just be in bed depressed.
They're not eating nothing.
I don't mind, bro.
It's too depressing, bro. So, yeah.
I'm going to knock him out. Yeah.
Yeah, he did say that. Yeah.
Yeah. I'm back. Yeah.
Just sat in bed. in my dressing gown. Greezy. [snorts]
Yeah, I [ __ ] I [ __ ] I [ __ ] woke up
at 2:00, bro.
Jesus Christ. Still going through this
[ __ ] again. Still going through these
bad experiences again. [ __ ] this.
Absolutely. [ __ ] this, bro. [ __ ] this
life. I'm in. Typical Reddit.
Typical Reddit, bro. Typical Reddit. Hey,
I'm messaging these people on Reddit.
They don't reply. They don't even reply, bro. Yeah.
There's nothing good about it.
The worst thing is the [ __ ] mods.
They're [ __ ] nerds, aren't they?
The mods are nerds.
They sat there all day scrolling on
Reddit, aren't they?
But then they call other people this,
that, and the other.
Yeah, it doesn't really make sense, does it?
Probably another day in this depressing life.
Another day of this depressive [ __ ]
[ __ ] this. But another day of this
[ __ ] boring is it
boring life that no change year in year
out. [ __ ] boring. Bors me. [ __ ]
bores me, bro. Bors the [ __ ] out of me. Yeah.
U you poor [ __ ] Poor [ __ ]
Bless you. Comment of the year is it?
I didn't get snitched up for doing dash.
Bro, you don't know anything. You don't
know what I do. You don't know what
money I have. Just stop it now. You
don't know anything. I've never done
Door Dash in my life.
You know, I don't know what it is with
you people in this community. Like, I
really really don't know. Like, when it
comes to this, I don't know why you're doing this.
I've never done Door Dash in my life.
What the [ __ ] are you talking about?
What are you on about, bro? I can make
money today if I wanted to.
You don't know my life, bro. You don't
know what I have and what money I can
make and what I can do. This is what I mean, bro.
Yes. Yes. Right. I'm not I'm not
explaining myself, bro. Okay, bro. You
stopped my sublet money, you stopped my
Uber money, you stopped everything.
Okay, whatever. I've got no money. Like
until someone agrees with you, bro.
Like, you're not you're never going to
stop, are you? You know, you say you
stop people sublet money when they've
explained something to you multiple
times. They explain something to you
again another multiple times and you
just continuously make up stuff. So,
I've got no money. I've got no money.
You've stopped all of my income. I'm
scared. Happy. You're not going to stop
until someone says that they're down.
the same [ __ ] How many times have I
told you no one on this community has
ever stopped anything of mine? No money,
me doing stuff. I've said this to you
multiple multiple multiple times and
you're still making up stuff. You know,
these people in this community has never
affected my life. I don't know how many.
Look, I've not lost my kids. I'm I'm not
the one who's lost my kids. Yeah. I'm
not the one. You know what I'm saying?
Like Belly and Monty man. They've never
caused me any problems in my life. They
they I remain unbothered.
You know, like that that horse share
that remains unfulfilled. Greavvesy. Yeah.
You know that I'll wait until it's been
made. You know the horse that remains
unfulfilled. I remain unbothered by these people.
I remain unbothered. They never stopped
no money of mine. They never stopped me
doing no Uber. They never stopped me
doing no nothing.
Trust me, they haven't
because I've explained the same thing
over and over and over and over and over
and over again. I've explained the same
thing over and over and over and over
and over again. You know,
you continuously tell people they're
skin even though they tell you that they're not.
Never been skinned in my life, but your
skin self projecting again. It's almost
2026. Let's think of some new words now.
What is it with you people and skin?
You've been saying it for about 8 years
now, bro. Give it a rest. It's boring now.
God, it is so boring. It's almost 2026.
Think of some new Think of some new
self-projected words. [ __ ] hell.
think of some new [ __ ] self-projected
words, bro. It's [ __ ] weird. So,
he was never stopped. Nobody abide.
Never. And I'm not any comment that
keeps talking about it now, I'm just
going to keep I'm just going to b it.
Simple as that. I'm just going to ban it. Simple.
as that. And what is it with you people
and skin as well? What is it? Like I'm
actually asking you. Why do you come on
the internet every day calling people skin?
And you don't even know people. You
don't even know what people have. This
is what makes me laugh. You don't know
what people have and what people don't
have. Yet you continuously come on here
and call people skin. It's laughable.
Really, it's laughable that you're
calling people that you don't know skin.
You don't know what money people have.
That's the main point. And it makes me
laugh. Really really does make me laugh.
You do not know what people what people
have and what people don't have.
Yeah, they can tell that you're a white
knight s and that's why you're a virgin.
Thank you. Thank you for your comment.
Yeah, they can tell you're a white
knight virgin and that's why you're and
that's why they don't want you. Why not? Yep.
I don't care. Anyways, I'm not uh I'm
not I'm not getting into this anymore.
Anyways, these back and forth arguments.
I said this yesterday. I'm not going I'm
not getting into these uh back and forth arguments.
Uh because you people are not worth
sorting out. None of you people are
worth sorting out. That's why none of
you people in this community are worth anything.
Did it affect me? Pretty sure it didn't.
I kept going to casinos winning money.
No, it definitely did affect me.
Yeah, we're wasting energy, bro. Like I
said, in their minds, they think women
can't do no wrong. So, just leave it at
that. I said it yesterday. Will agree to
disagree. I don't know why we keep going
around and around in circles. You can be
shown the world and you'll still defend
women. Okay, whatever. I don't care. I'm
not asked. So why do we keep going back
and forth, back and forth, back and forth?
Anyways, we're moving on now. We're not
talking about these people, bro. Um,
just leave them, Mike. They've got
something wrong with their head. They
want to think women don't do no wrong
and they're not the problem. Let them
think that. Who cares?
Well, I mean that same goes for you now,
doesn't it, player? Cuz you're also
single. So, doesn't the same thing go
for you? Cuz you're also single.
So, I mean, that's self projection,
isn't it? Because you're also single. So,
you're basically taking the piss out
yourself and you're saying that because
you're single, you ain't got no
girlfriend. This is what I used to this
what I had to keep saying to these
people. They talk about people not
having a girlfriend, but they don't have a girlfriend.
It's all self-reflecting with them. You
talk about people, but they ain't got a
girlfriend. They ain't got no money. So,
I don't know why they talk about other people.
Realistically, there's no reason for you
people to be on here. There's a reason
for me to be on here. There's not a
reason for you to be on here.
There's no content on your channel.
So, there's no content on your channel.
Why is there no content on your channel?
Like, there's no content. You don't even
do no videos. You just come on and type
[ __ ] every day. Why is there no content
on your videos? on your channel. Why is
there no videos on your channel?
I think I'm going to go back to bed in a minute, bro.
Oh, here we go.
Yeah, I'm off the bed in a minute, bro.
Yeah, I'm going back to bed in a minute.
Wake up. Have a tea. Go to sleep.
Yeah, that's it. Laney's not here. I
don't know where she is.
Maybe gone around someone's house. I don't know.
But yeah, I'll be in bed soon anyways.
Sleeping again. Oh, I need to get some
batteries for this bastard controller. >> [snorts]
>> So yeah,
that's the good thing about life is you
don't need to do anything else.
But here we go.
We're back on Reddit now, lads. Yeah,
that boyfriend [ __ ] is so annoying. What's that?
I like when I liked when Joe come on
here yesterday, bro. It was quite nice.
But he couldn't answer my question.
There we go.
Yeah, good one, White Knight. No one cares.
Yeah, good for you, bro.
Yeah, good for you. No one cares.
No one cares,
bro. You know that incel word that died
about a year and a half ago. You know,
it got to the point where people was
just calling people if they didn't lick
women's asses. That like that that that
doesn't even mean anything anymore, bro.
When you when you say that to someone
incel, that they just call anyone in in
that don't lick women's asses and speaks
the truth. No one really cares about
that word. It's like calling a woman a
[ __ ] Whatever. No one no one really no
one pays it attention anymore because
they they don't even use it in the right context.
An incel to these people is somebody
that don't lick women's asses and tells
the truth about them. That's what they
think an incel is when it's not an
incel. It's a completely unbiased normal
person speaking the truth. But they call
you an incel. So doesn't really care. Do
I really care? So,
and again, it's a gender thing as well.
So, we don't need to waste our time on
it. It's a gender thing.
If you was a woman moaning about men,
people would would have no problem. So,
I mean, that tells you all you need to
know about wasting your time. So,
yeah, I do feel sorry for pe I do you
know what though? I do feel sorry for
people. Like I actually do feel sorry
for people that are virgins now and
probably now got to the age at 18 19
that must be horrible and they have to
keep trying and getting bad experiences
and they're going to be a virgin. It's
horrible. That must be really really
horrible now nowadays.
Then obviously they're not listened to
as well because they're just going to be
told that they're an incel and women are
the problem and they're going to keep
putting the blame back on to you. That
must be horrible. Must be horrible. Even
worse if you're a virgin.
That must be horrible. Especially now.
Bad. Bad. Bad. Bad. Bad.
Yeah, it must be [ __ ] awful. So yeah. Anyways, Sure. Turn.
Yeah, you said the same self-reflecting
thing yesterday. I don't need benefits.
I've got my own money. You don't know
how much money I have. That's self-p projectioning. >> [snorts]
>> Yeah, I don't need a benefit payment.
I've got plenty of money. Self projecting. Self projection.
Typical self projector.
So basically everything you say is
basically just about yourself.
I can get a lovely Indian right now if I want to.
Why do you think people have to have no
money to be in a bad mood? Can I ask you
that? But why do you seem to think
But why do you seem to think that people
have to um do their balls in to be in a
bad mood? Can I ask you that? Cuz you
used to do it all the time when I used
to come on here, right? I used to come
on here, right,
and I'd get and I'd speak facts and be
like, "Have you done your balls in?" I
was like, "No, I haven't." Like, you
really don't know anything, do you, bro?
You don't need to know anything. I've
got money. That's all you need to know
is I've got money. I can get whatever
food I want. Thank you very much. Stop self-reflecting.
It's just self-reflecting, bro. Every time. So, yeah.
[ __ ] worry about your own [ __ ]
life and how much money you [ __ ] got.
You know what I'm saying, bro? [ __ ] hell.
That's that, bro. There's so many self-reflectors.
So many self-reflectors on this
community, bro. So many self-reflectors
repeating the same [ __ ] for eight years.
Eight years we've heard that now. Skin,
we've been hearing the same thing now,
Monty, for about eight years. Eight
years. I I think it's been seven, eight
They're [ __ ] boring, is it? These
people on here. Boring people. I'm
coming off in a bit anyways. I might be
I won't be live long. Yeah,
won't be live long. I'll be live another
5 minutes and I'm out. I'm gone.
Go for a bit and go back to sleep. [ __ ] this.
[ __ ] this [ __ ] Yeah.
Yeah. And about the benefit payment, that self-reflecting,
I don't need a benefit payment. I've got
plenty of money. You don't know how much I have.
It's really embarrassing. You really
come on here and talk about people that
you don't know.
Coming on here talking about people that
you don't know every day.
It's odd, isn't it? It is odd.
So, yeah, it is odd. >> [snorts]
>> There we go. [ __ ] hell.
No, I went on your channel. I went on
your channel, Monty, and I said and I
said that you're boring.
Are you joining or what?
Yeah, that's self-reflecting. Just Beck
Australia. Yeah, that's self-reflecting.
You're not coming in. You self-reflector.
L the self-reflector is not coming in.
You get banned.
Yeah, that's that's self-reflecting.
You get your you you get a pip and a no.
That's you. That's self-reflecting.
I've got plenty of money. I can go out
whenever I want. Do whatever I want. That's self-reflection.
That's you. You're you get your pit next
week. This is what I'm saying. This is
what I'm saying, bro. Everything is
self-reflection. It's the mirror that
you're looking in. Everything that you
say about other people is just your own
lives. Skin lonely. That's you.
That's you. That's the self-reflector.
How do you know I don't have £4,000 right now?
Exactly. You don't know what people
have. If you don't know what people
don't have self-reflecting
anyways, is anyone coming on? Otherwise,
I'm ending this live stream.
I could have £50,000. How do you know? Again, self-reflecting.
I don't even have 400 quid. [laughter]
Okay, bro. Yeah, I don't have 40 pound. Yeah. Okay.
And how? Okay.
How would you know that?
How How How would you know that I don't have £400?
Okay. I don't have £400. [laughter]
Okay. And how would you know I don't have £400?
How would you know if I have 400 or not?
No, I wouldn't be bragging. No, I
wouldn't be bragging because I don't
need to prove myself to you idiots. I
don't need to prove myself to you fat
ugly people. I've said this multiple
times, but it doesn't sink in your
[ __ ] brain. Some reason.
I don't need to prove myself to you fat
ugly people. I think I've said that multiple times, you know.
Yeah. Okay. Whatever you say, bro.
So, is anyone joining or what? I'm going
just the same repeating
same repeating people.
Is anyone joining or what?
I don't let LJ on. He's a self-reflector
of other people's lives.
Yeah, I'm here. Peter Belly's got more
money than you will ever have,
>> you know.
>> Hello, PJ. Why are you scared of [ __ ]
Are you actually letting me shut the [ __ ] up
your [ __ ] shut up you and I
You're the one who [ __ ]
I would rather be clapping in a [laughter] [ __ ]
crying. I'm crying. Yeah, I'm crying. cry yet. [laughter]
You have to That's how much of a
sleeping father you are. I always see my
mom bastard. Why don't you spend more
[laughter] time with your Why don't YOU
SPEND MORE TIME with your miners? OH,
YOU CAN'T, can you? Cuz you can't even
look after them.
>> Why you don't see your mom, bastard?
>> No. No. Why don't you see your miners?
What have you seen Nathan's mother?
>> How do you know I'm not with my mom?
>> How do you know YouTube if you can't [laughter] I can't
[screaming] plan you [ __ ]
at least I can see my miners. Mongol you
can relax your miners at the weekend. At
least Bang can see his miners. At least
everybody can see their permission officially.
You got your [ __ ] mind is confiscated
as well. Just as badly
no one talks about your [ __ ] [ __ ]
who can't even look after his miners
in the [ __ ] freezer. situation emergency.
>> How can you go into Kylie? How can you
go into Kylie when you're just as bad on
answer that question cuz mus
you can't I know you're notic
yourself out and get your minus back. I
know you're going to YOU'RE GOING TO DO
[ __ ] ALL YOU SO HARD MATE. YOU remember
[ __ ] I mean you chill out. You chill
out, mate. Yeah. Yeah. You've done no
one, [ __ ] You're [ __ ] and I will
[ __ ] flatten you. You've done nothing
wrong. You're a manchild.
>> What do you mean?
>> You are a [ __ ] man.
>> You are. YOU'RE YOU ACT HARD ON SOCIAL.
Meet me today and I guarantee you I'll f
you so hard, [ __ ] You won't get up.
Meet me today. We'll go back to Cano
Park. We'll go back to Can Park [ __ ]
We'll do a one and one, [ __ ] And this
time, [ __ ] [ __ ]
shutting me down.
Are you GOING TO MEET ME TODAY? And I'll
go live with a question. Yes or no?
meeting your mom. No, no, no, no, no,
no. Long go. Don't give her a pigment on
social media and then back out cuz I
want to teach anyway. Are you going to
meet me? Yes or no?
>> Just answer the question.
>> Oh, now you're backing down. Now you're
backing down, little Now you're backing
down. Now you're backing down, you
[ __ ] Where are you [ __ ] [ __ ]
nons? Anyway, go and get your miners
to look after him. [laughter] You
[ __ ] naughty daddy. Nathan [ __ ]
Why don't you Why don't Why don't you
Why don't you Why don't you get off
YouTube and get your miners back instead
of [laughter] your [ __ ] mom doing all
the hard work? You [ __ ] fail. think
you got your [ __ ] kids
from a teenage dating app on his phone
and making use [laughter]
when you got exposed by [laughter]
why you send
That was that everybody knows that was
punt and you [ __ ] with that [ __ ]
>> You were you prick. He's your
evidence. Where's the evidence? Where's
[laughter] the evidence? Where's the
>> Where's the evidence? Where's the
evidence? You want the evidence?
[laughter] So, so, so when you go to a
court of going to say that's the
evidence. You know what m
go and get go and get [ __ ] go and get
[ __ ] Nathan back.
Get rid of him. Get rid of the clapper.
>> Yes. So what do you want?
>> When are you getting off YouTube and
getting a life?
>> When when are you getting off YouTube
and getting a life?
>> I can't be off. I don't really go live
much like I used to. Not like you
bashing over the same women and [ __ ]
>> When do they go live?
>> So why don't you why don't you go live then?
>> Because the gay on your PGA. What's the
point entertaining people who who act
nice on your panel and then slag you off in comments?
>> Well, who's done that? You haven't se
Yeah, but you haven't seen that.
>> A lot more people do this in this
community, man. So what's the [ __ ]
entertaining people and giving people
[ __ ] when you just talk behind your back
and chat [ __ ] You're [ __ ] thick as
[ __ ] either way where PJ I've seen
people I've seen people do it. I have
seen but no one listen the people that
come on my chat none of them do it. I've
seen people do it. I have seen people do
it. Not them though.
>> Not greasy. Not um not not not people
that come on my chat. They don't though.
Must Okay then. I can
>> The people that have the people that
have I've banned them. There has been
people. Yeah. And I banned them. Yes,
they have. Yeah.
>> Okay then. Mr. B is one of them. Okay.
>> I don't go. But the thing is, but I
don't go on Lord Jay's. You don't
understand. I don't go on that channel.
>> You was on his [ __ ] panel a couple of
days ago talking to him.
>> No, I wasn't.
>> Yeah, you were. You was arguing with him
on his panel
>> a couple days ago. No, I [ __ ] wasn't.
>> Yeah, you were. He was on his panel with
him arguing with him on his panel.
>> Maybe maybe weeks ago, Monty. Not a
couple days ago.
>> A couple of days ago.
>> No way. How? I've been live all all day
the past three days. How's How
>> at at night time about 6 7:00 when Lord
J was live. You joined this panel live
room with him.
>> Definitely not.
>> Definitely. Yeah.
>> Definitely definitely defin I don't go
on that [ __ ] channel. He tried these
anyways people. Why you entertaining
people who don't like you anyway? PJ
>> the repeaters in it.
>> I'm asking you a question. Why you
entertaining people who don't
>> really likes me?
>> Yeah. Like I said, there's only probably
a couple of people in this community
who's actually decent, but it doesn't
matter. Does he actually like you?
>> Rice comes on here.
>> Rice is just a little ped. Don't give
too [ __ ] about them either way.
They only on here to use you to get at
me or whatever they do. But it's not
working out anyways for them anyway. So I don't
>> You need to stop saying you need to stop
saying Monty. Yeah. That they don't go
for non legs because non legs goes for
me because if I quit YouTube they won't
go for non legs and you know it. So you
need to stop saying that.
>> Yeah. Only why they won't go for non
legs is because half of these are pedos
just like nons.
>> Only only two people will. Maybe two
people will. Three or three max maybe,
but not the rest of them. >> Uh, you know,
you can't even read it in it. No. All
they want to talk about is a [ __ ]
teen. That's only what I can talk about.
Something what I never went on or
something what I put up on YouTube
myself. That's only what I can talk
about. [ __ ] what I put up on YouTube myself.
So, it's not going to bother me either
way what these little clowns talk about.
You know what I mean?
Not like these little clowns are going
to come on camera now and show their
face. Is it PJ?
>> I know that. I've asked them to multiple times.
>> Yeah. It's because [ __ ] the ugly as
[ __ ] man. That's why. So, they have a
lot of people down and talk about [ __ ]
because they these people are [ __ ] in
life. So, are you going to be on here?
Are you going to be on here in 2026?
>> No, I'm getting off this year. This me
I'm done with YouTube. Literally, this
is the last time anyone's going to hear
from me on this community. E where
>> you've been on seven years?
>> No, I haven't been on here for seven
years actually. PJ
>> six years. Come on.
>> Six years. Yes. Coming up. Six years.
It's been the same [ __ ] in it.
>> Same [ __ ] You're the one who got me
into this shitty community. But I thank
you for one thing and another for other. You're
>> If I didn't If I didn't get you in this
community, you'd still be with Kaye in it. [laughter]
>> No. Won't be with her. What the [ __ ] be with her?
>> Well, you wouldn't.
>> I'm off anyways. I'm off anyways because
this is only who you people talk about
is K and [ __ ] rice. So, I see you
later. Yeah. Only that's all you talk
about in this community. Weird.
>> I'm not talking about rice, [snorts]
>> boy. Listen, Grecy, did you do you hear that? [laughter]
See what I mean?
Did you hear that?
What do you see?
Oh no, man. Anyways, I'm off here. Yeah.
See you um maybe tomorrow or something.
Peace. See you.