[clears throat] Yo, so just wanted to
say to this Smokey Beer,
right, about how I need to unblock you
and T. How about you come to London
tomorrow and you go live and the story?
That's all you're going to get. I I want
to I want to really really Yeah, I want
to I want to test this bullying theory
out. I don't care about your
self-reflecting [ __ ] No woman, no
money. Yeah, that's yourself you're
talking about. But anyways, I want to
test your um I want to test your theory
out. your bullying theory.
You know, I want to test this theory
out, you know. Just come to London
tomorrow and go live, man, and we'll see
who you bully. Simple. We'll see who you
bully, bro. You bully yourself. Like I
said, bro, I'm mentioning you. Just go
live tomorrow in London, anywhere you
want, and I'll be there. See if you can
do it. See if you can do it, bro. See if
you can do it.
See if you can do it.
How's my day been? I woke up at 2 p.m.
My ears are hurting me. I think it's cuz
I haven't ate today, bro.
Yeah, I just argue with some [ __ ] on WhatsApp.
If she go if she gets mad, if she says
anything rude to me, I'll go to where
she works. I know where she works, so I
got no problem with that, bro. But she
hasn't. But I I will literally go to
where she works and shop in front of
everyone everyone. So it's best you
watch what she says, you know.
It's best she watches what she watches
what she says
cuz I will go to where she works cuz I
know where she works. She works in
Stratford. I know where she works. I
have no problem doing that, you know.
But anyway, so this Smokeoky B. Yeah,
back on the point, bro. You know how you
keep saying that you want people to
unblock you and then just go live
tomorrow in London anywhere and I'll be there.
Right. I want to test this bullying
theory and I want it to prove to be
failed. Yeah, just go live anywhere in
London tomorrow. Otherwise, Yeah, that's
that's all I got to say.
Yeah, just go live in London tomorrow.
Yeah, this [ __ ] was like, "Are you 13
years old?" I was like, "No, but you're
clearly 13 years old." [ __ ] leading
people on, so you must be 13 years of age. Yeah,
absolute [ __ ] bro.
They are proper proper [ __ ]
I said you won't say that to my face and
I was waiting for her to like really get
rude. I'll just go to where she works. I
don't I don't care. I know where the [ __ ] works.
I'm not saying, but I do know. [snorts]
I'm message that actually. One sec.
So you want to be a [ __ ] So, I just
said to her, "If I come to your
workplace tomorrow, you're going to say
this stuff to my face.
If I come to your workplace tomorrow,
you're going to say this stuff to my face,
you know, and Smokey B, like I said, go
live anywhere in London tomorrow and
I'll be there within an hour maximum,
lad. So, if you're not willing to do
that, then you can keep continuing being
a keyboard warrior. No one cares.
Unblock you. Unblock you. [ __ ] the
unblocking. [ __ ] YouTube, bro. Just go
live. Just go live anywhere in London.
tomorrow, the next day, the next day.
Bro, just just go live anywhere in London.
Just go live anywhere in London. I want
to test this bullying theory, bro.
You [ __ ] fat mug with chubby fingers.
Got six grand to your name in your 40s.
You pathetic bastard. Yeah, bro. That's
a That's a nasty thing to say. Really
nasty thing to say. You don't bully no
one. You go live in London tomorrow and
you see what will happen to you. Simple. [ __ ] [ __ ]
So yeah, I just said that.
She didn't say anything back. So there we go.
I didn't eat today, bro. I spoke to a
couple of people.
No, I didn't eat. I got put off my food, bro. Oh, damn.
If she doesn't say anything, then
obviously I won't say anything. But I
will just go to her workplace.
If she does if she does start [ __ ] I will Yeah.
Yeah. I'll be in bed all day tomorrow
again. I don't know if I'll be able to
not eat tomorrow. Maybe. Maybe not. I
don't even want to eat, bro. It's that bad.
I think it's worse this year, bro. Cuz I
thought this [ __ ] was going to change,
bro. Like, it's okay when you're 23, 24, 25
or 26, but I thought this [ __ ] was going
to change, bro. I'm 2 [ __ ] eight now,
This should have changed by now.
And we're still having the same problem,
you know? We're still having the same problem, bro.
Yeah. I can't even eat, bro. I'm too
depressed to eat, bro. That is
depressing. That is so depressing, bro.
I ain't got nothing left to prove,
Dusty. I don't need to go out this week.
I've got nothing left to prove.
I have got nothing left to prove, you
know. Nothing left to prove.
Yeah, that's what they do.
Now, I'm not using escorts either. I
don't need to use escorts
cuz I'm not 40. I'm not 50. I'm not
disabled. I'm not ugly. I've not not
tried. No, I won't use escorts, bro. I
just won't I won't have anyone. Simple.
Cuz Dusty, I'm 28 years of age. We're
going into a new year now, bro. Uh we're
going into a new year now. We're having
the same problem.
We're having the same problem. You know,
this should have stopped now. You know,
especially with someone with with the
history that I've got. Nope.
I don't gamble, bro, like that. I don't gamble.
Yeah. I think this is the worst I've
been, bro. And I'm not skinn. I've got money.
Uh nothing to do with not having money.
I've got money.
Um, so yeah, you don't need to be m you
don't need to have money and you know,
you don't need to not have money
for stuff like this to happen.
You know, you don't need to I don't know
why people seem to think that you need
to be skinned or lose money. You don't
need to have any do any of that stuff.
I'm not answering self-reflecting questions.
So, we're not getting into this again.
We're not ask We're not answering self-reflecting questions.
What is that? That must be in Russian or
something. Hold on.
My account's been restricted again. How
has my account been restricted again?
I haven't even sent no dick pictures, no nothing.
What the [ __ ]
This WhatsApp has gotten worse, bro.
This is bad.
What the [ __ ] I didn't even say anything bad.
And then they report you.
What the [ __ ] bro? I didn't even say anything bad.
Is it getting like Reddit now? This
WhatsApp is getting like Reddit, bro.
What the [ __ ] is there like no freedom
of speech? I just said if I come to your
work, are you going to say that to my
face? What the [ __ ] I didn't even say
anything [ __ ] bad. Yeah,
but don't forget I can verify this
number anyway, so it doesn't matter.
Yeah. Telling me to Yeah.
[ __ ] [ __ ] She is. [ __ ] her, bro.
You can't even write in English. And
this is the the attitude we're dealing
with these women.
But people think that women are not all
the same and they're not all bad and
I'm not so sure. I'm not so sure, Dusty. You know.
Yeah. Hopefully this doesn't get banned.
I'll be able to get her back anyways. I'm sure.
Don't give a [ __ ] anyways.
You know, I'm not saying where she
works, but I know where she works.
Bad is it? Bad these women.
I said, "Oh, you still leading people
on." That's what I said to her. I said,
"Are you still leading people on?"
Yeah, WhatsApp's banned with it now.
Yeah, it's bad with banning people. It's
worse than Reddit.
Uh 28 years of age and we're still
dealing with this at 28 years of age.
and we're still dealing with this. At 28
years of age,
December 2025 and we're still dealing with this.
Yeah, I got banned yesterday, bro, for
sending dick pictures and [ __ ] That's
what these [ __ ] do. They give it, but
they can't take it.
They give it, but they can't take it.
These women, that's what they do. They
give it, but they can't take it. Yeah.
If I was younger and I didn't try as
much, whatever, then I'd be like, "Oh,
it's whatever." But I've got no
motivation to do nothing. I give up.
Completely give up.
So, that's me done.
There'll be no going out this week.
I'll be in bed. Yeah. Depressed, I think.
Yeah. I don't know why they do it. Should
be all right though.
Yeah, I'll be I'll be depressed, bro, in bed.
Yeah, I'll be lying in bed depressed.
I don't know about anyone else.
There's absolutely no reason why I don't
have a date this week. There's
absolutely no reason why I'm in this position.
There's literally no reason, Dusty.
There's literally no reason.
I could go out if I wanted to this week,
could go out next week, but I don't want to.
I don't want to,
you know, because there's nothing worth
doing in this country. I'm better where
I am, bro. I'm better better where I am. You know,
if I didn't have bad experiences with
women, then it would have been different
or a little then I'll be okay. Yeah,
you're just feeling sorry for yourself.
But this is very valid. This is very,
very, very valid what I'm feeling, bro.
It really, really is. So, yeah. do. Yeah.
So, I'm basically like that Oreo man,
but he never tried anything. So, and
some people think he's right. I don't
think he's right cuz he never helped
himself. He's 37 and he never done
anything to help himself ever. So, even
though he talks the truth, he is partly
to blame. Whereas me, I've met load and
loads of women. They people have
benefited out for years, traveled up and
down the country. Uh he never done
anything to ever try and help himself.
And he's 37. So think about it. He's 10
years younger than me. So some people
like that, they don't help themselves.
But with me, no one can tell me nothing.
No one can tell me a damn thing, bro. So
that's that's that. Yeah.
28 years of age, bro.
[ __ ] it's bad, bro. It's really bad. You know,
this shouldn't be my life, bro. I'm not
talking about money. I've got money.
It's not about money. But this shouldn't
be my life, bro.
It's okay when you're 24, 25. Like I
said, 25, 26,
you know, but when you're this age, bro,
[ __ ] should be starting to give.
Oh, I do know how women work. Oh, trust
me, I do know how women work. I've been
with several different women. I do know
how women work. I I [ __ ] do. And
they're [ __ ] evil [ __ ] I do know
how they work. They're [ __ ] evil scum.
Um, just like this one I was just speaking to,
Crybaby. I said to her, "Go [ __ ] yourself."
That's what I said to her. [ __ ] old Uh,
do you know what's so mad is that
they've got worse attitude than men.
They've got worse attitude than an
actual man. You know, they're worse than
[ __ ] men, bro. I I swear to God, they
really really are. There's no good women
out there. They're all bad.
Yeah, there's no good women out there.
They're all bad.
They are vermin. I don't know. I don't
care about other people. I'm not
interested in other people. I'm only
interested in myself. Not to sound
selfish. I don't give a [ __ ] Why is
there so many people that got cancer? I
don't care. I only care about myself.
So, I don't compare myself to other
people. I don't give a [ __ ] They're not
going to change my experiences and
they're not going to change my future
experiences. I don't give a [ __ ] about other people. >> [snorts]
>> Um, I'm talking about my own experiences
and everyone's individual. Yeah, they
are vermin. They really, really are. Uh,
this guy that I was speaking to from
Reading, bro, he's a he's a natural cool guy.
He is actually a really, really nice
guy. Like, as a friend and another
friend I spoke to, so they women are
definitely worse than men. Definitely
worse than men in a million way. They
are worse than men. Even if I if there
was a third gender, male, female, and I
was the third gender, I'd still be
saying the same thing. Women are evil,
bro. They really really are evil. Scum
of the earth.
>> So yeah,
they really really are vermin. And when
you give it back to them, well, you know
what happens? So they give it, but they
can't take it.
I put that one in her place. I said,
"Oh, I don't know if you got my message,
but I was just basically saying that uh
you're uh you're uh you're um
you you must be the immature one
ignoring someone and I can send a
picture of my dick because I just did
because I can just have." So, drop the
attitude, you know, Angelina Jolie and
sort yourself out. Sort your attitude So,
I can't even talk. Well, what the [ __ ]
are you going on about?
What the [ __ ] are you going on about?
No, I just don't compare myself to
strangers cuz it's it's a complete waste
of time. I'm thinking about it
logically. Strangers are not going to
change my future experiences. They're
not going to change my past experiences.
and they're not going to change my future experiences.
So, why do I care about other people
that aren't me?
Okay. Okay. What's What's that got to do with anything?
I don't understand what's is that going
to change if I go out on Friday? No. So,
I don't understand why they matter in my life.
Everyone's different. Everyone's got
different experiences. Everyone's got
different luck. Everyone's different in every way.
Yeah. They don't find you attractive
either, bro. They don't find you attractive.
Yeah. I've got nothing to offer. Okay.
Whatever. No one cares about your self-p projecting comments.
Yeah. Yeah. Whatever. No one cares. I
ain't getting into any debates with
anyone. not on Reddit, on here,
because this is a gender thing.
This is a gender thing. This is not a me
thing. This is a gender thing.
So, we've already established that this
is a gender thing.
It's because you're a man, they're
defending women. When you realize it's a
gender thing, when you realize it's a
gender thing, you realize it's a waste
of time arguing back. Cuz
like I said, if you was a man, if you
was a woman moaning about men, no one
would be saying this stuff. So that just
tells you that it's just a waste of
time. So yeah, that's that simple.
So that's that.
Yeah. But do you know what's even worse?
Imagine sticking up for an entire gender
when they don't want you. Imagine doing
anything to stick up women. Stick up for
women and victimize women and they still
don't like people like you. That's the
thing that really doesn't make no sense
is that we've got dudes like you
defending women. Women don't like you.
Women don't want you. But you still
defend them. At least if you're hating
something that's hating you. It makes
sense. You're hating someone that hates
you. You're defending women, but they
don't like you. They don't want you. And
I've probably been with more women than
you. At least if you're hating someone
that hates you, it makes sense. You are
liking something that don't want you.
You're one you're you're to their
defense and they don't like you. They
don't want you. They'll never be your
girlfriend. But you're defending them. I
know. Mine makes sense. Yours don't make
Yeah. You're talking about yourself. No
one cares about you. little Christmas
self projectors. No one cares about you
fat, ugly people trying to put people
down. No one cares. It's coming up to
Christmas. We all know why you people
are doing what you're doing. Christmas
self projectors. No one cares.
So yeah. And if I'm hating someone, bro,
it's making sense. I'm hating someone.
You're liking people that don't want
you. That's that's the mad thing. So yeah,
you're sticking up for women, but they
don't want you. That's that's the bit
that does not make sense. And no, it's
not a competition. It's not I've had
more women than you. I'm using it as an example.
That's the bit that doesn't make any
sense. It This is the bit that doesn't
make any sense. And no, it isn't a competition.
Yeah. You wake up every day smiling.
Yeah. Okay. Of course you do, bro.
Bro, do you not understand Christmas self projectors?
Bro, I'm saying Christmas self
projectors because you come here, come
on here over Christmas every year self
projecting really badly. Really, really
badly. It's nothing like before. >> Yeah.
>> Christmas self projectors. So, what what
I mean by that is over Christmas, you
get loads of people in this community
telling you that you don't have things
that they've never had and will never
have because they're going to be lonely Christmas. So,
restricted [ __ ] account. [cough] [snorts] mad.
>> Yeah, you are on it. But the projection
gets worse over Christmas. The
projection gets worse over Christmas.
Uh, no. Maybe it's not me because then I
look at other guys and then they get the
same thing and it's clearly clearly
clearly women. It's clearly clearly
clearly women because even people that
are uglier than me and better looking
than me get the same [ __ ] No. No. No, I
look at other guys and I think m no,
it's definitely definitely the women.
No, no, no. It's definitely definitely
the women. No, definitely the women. Um
I have done and I was like, let me let
me stumble across some of these guys.
No, it's definitely definitely women.
Definitely definitely women.
And again, you wouldn't be saying it's
me if I was a woman complaining about
men. So, yeah. No, no, no. There's
literally several different videos of
guys approaching women in America,
England, and they get exactly the same
[ __ ] They get exactly the same old
[ __ ] It's definitely definitely
definitely women. Um, especially in
London as well, especially in London. It
used to be this black guy, completely
normal looking. He used to go around
doing the same. I think he still does
it. And it's the same old [ __ ] White,
ugly, better looking. You have a laser
eye. You smile. Yeah, that's self projection.
Yeah. Okay. Why don't Why don't you come
on here? Why don't you come on here and
show your face?
Come on here and let me put a link up.
Let me see your face.
Let's see your face. Let's see your ugly
Let's see your fat ugly face. You sell projector.
Let's see your face.
Let's see your face. Oh. Oh, I'm
blocking you. If you don't come on here
and show your face, I'm blocking you.
Let's see your fat, ugly face. Let's see
your face. You're talking about my
looks. Come on,
bro. Come on and show your face. What
you scared of? If I was coming on
another community calling someone ugly,
I wouldn't be scared. I wouldn't be
scared to show my face,
bro. Come on here and show your face.
And you're gone. Another self-reflector.
This has literally been the past 3 days
with these self projectors on there. You
know, three days. Three days of constant
self projection. The Christmas
projectors are out early.
The Christmas bitter people are out early. Yep.
Anyways, I'm banning these people. I
don't even know why I'm entertaining
them, bro. What the [ __ ] They've been
doing this for like 3 days straight.
Yeah. Uh um these little self-reflectors.
Bro, listen. Yeah, I keep saying this to
you and I really want you to understand.
You are not going to make me feel ugly, bro.
I will show Oh, [ __ ] sake. I
This is the last time I'm saying this. I
will show my face. I'll show my face.
Show my hair. Show my hairline. Here we
go. Look, this is my face.
And I will never be insecure. You can
project for a million years and you're
not going to make me stop showing my
face. You will not show your face. I
will show my face. So, just to let you
know, over the years, you have never
ever ever made me stop showing my face.
You never have and you never will
because everything that you do is just
self projecting. We don't care. We
really, really, really, really don't
give a [ __ ] You won't show your faces
cuz you're ugly.
Simple. We're not going to go round and
round and round in circles. You'd have
no problem showing your face. If I
jumped on a community, right, and there
was people on here like women and stuff
and I'm calling these people ugly, then
I would show my face. I would I wouldn't
be scared to show my face. It doesn't
make sense. My face would get out there
eventually. These people don't want to
show their faces for love nor money
cuz they're ugly. Simple. They are ugly.
That's it. They generally Germany
Germany are [ __ ] ugly.
That's why they don't do it. Smokey B
won't show his face. He's ugly. Joe
You know, it's it's it's it is the
truth, bro. It's weird. Why? It's weird, bro. Especially
when they're trying to hit on women on
the community as well. Why are they not
showing their faces when they're they're complimenting women?
It's weird though. It is strange. It's
weird how they can blame you when you've
put up videos of what women are like.
That tiger tiger guy,
he even agrees with me and we don't like
we don't like each other. We used to
argue all the time and he says, "No,
they led you on. Tiger Tiger
is agrees with me, bro." And he goes on
L J's and he's like, "No, they led you
on straight." So, he must be one of the
only people that are not a white knight
simp. I'm guessing he wasn't born with
the disorder because he's like, "Oh,
yeah. Well, I don't have any advice, but
they led you on." That's what a normal
person would say.
That is what a normal person would say.
A normal person doesn't sit there keep
making excuses for women even when
they're proven wrong.
That's not what a normal person does.
Whatever the [ __ ] normal means. I was
arguing with this woman on Reddit,
Grezy. My [ __ ] my [ __ ] WhatsApp
got banned again.
Should be able to get it back.
I said, "Cry, baby." I said, "Are you
going to say that to my face? Are you
going to say that to my [ __ ] face?"
[ __ ] stupid [ __ ] [ __ ] absolute victim. See?
See what I mean, Grezy?
But women are not all the same. Yeah. Okay.
Do you know what? I have never ever met
a woman that was a good person in my life. Ever.
You know? Oh my god. It's just like this
is like the 30th account you've done today, bro.
This is like the 30th account you have
done and you've been banned and you're
still doing this. [ __ ] hell, man.
Yeah. I don't think I have ever met a normal woman.
Never in my life,
Dusty. Never in my life. I don't think I have.
Never in my life have I.
Well, and family don't count either
because family kind of are obliged to
like you. So, I don't even think your family count.
I don't think I ever have met a woman
that weren't evil. I swear I swear to
God, bro. I'm trying to think of it. I
don't think I can. Mm- In 20
in 2026, people need to really give up
with women. They generally generally
need to give up with women. Seriously.
They really really need to give up with
these [ __ ] women.
Yeah, I won't be entertaining them anymore.
[ __ ] that, bro.
You know, I thought Dusty that, oh yeah,
maybe it's the people I'm meeting, but
no, they are literally all the same. You
will never meet someone that's normal.
You can spend loads of money. You can go
out. You will never ever meet a woman
that's normal. I've realized that at 28
that they are really really really
really all the same. Bro, all you're
going to get is toxic toxicness. That's
all you're going to get.
That is all you're going to get. You know,
I can't believe I did AJ. It's not even
the first time in years.
Yeah, this is the first time I've not
ate in years. Yeah.
No, I think this is I I can't remember
the last time I've gone a day without eating.
Greasy. I can't remember the last time I
went a day without eating. [snorts] Bro, years.
I don't think I ever have. Wait,
no. I'm sure I must have. Maybe five years ago.
That's how you know you're bad, bro.
When you won't even eat. Yeah.
Yeah, to Sony TVs are good, but they're too expensive.
my the fold's having a baby, by the way.
Um, my my phone's pregnant, Greasy. The
baby's due the baby's due in July
because the new Fold's coming out in
July. So, the baby's due in July.
Yeah, the baby's due in July. It's pregnant.
So that's when the new addition to the families. Uh yeah,
I'm only joking. It's just a little
game, bro. But yeah, these women are vile.
These women are vile.
Just message my army friend. Let's see
what he's saying. One second.
>> Hold on.
Leave a message subscriber.
Yeah, I was just talking to a army lad,
a army friend. He said, "Oh, I'm coming
back to London soon. We should go and
send it." I haven't met this guy in ages. Oh, Sony.
No, I think Sony, Panasonic, and
Samsung's the best.
He said, "Yeah, we'll go and send it."
But obviously, I won't be sending it
because obviously I've given up. So,
you didn't know I had mates? Of course,
I've got mates. We're not all like L J
and these little bum chums,
these little sad little followers. We're
not all a Smokey Bee.
They ain't got no mates. That's why they
tell people, "Yeah, we're not all like them.
The best is Sony, Samson, and
Panasonic." I think
they're the best. I think Yeah, Sony. I
think Sony's the best, but
No, I think Sony's the best, but I got
Samsung cuz obviously my phone's Samsung.
Sony's the best, but it's too exp Sony's
too expensive. Sony's, of course, Sony's
the best, bro. They're the ones that
made [ __ ] PlayStation. Yeah. [snorts]
We're just chilling, bro.
I just had an argument with this woman
on [ __ ] WhatsApp, Joseph Fra.
I said, "Are you going to say anything?
This Are you going to say any of this
[ __ ] to my face? I'll come to your
workplace if you want. Then she shut up.
[ __ ] coward. Scumbag.
They can give it, but they can't take it.
They can give but they can't take. Yeah.
[ __ ] same old [ __ ] with them in it. Yep.
But yeah, Smokeoky B, if you ever want
to go live in London, bro, um I'll test
your theory. I'll test your bullion
theory. More than happy to test your
bullying theory, bro.
That must have took you ages to write that paragraph.
That must have took you ages.
Yeah, it's clear that these people in
here ain't got no mates, bro. Like,
Smokey B, no friends. So obvious, bro.
You know, you said that you was never
coming back on my channel. Okay, Joe.
You said that you was never coming back
on my channel after I didn't go to
Thailand, but you're here. You're here
as well. Does everyone remember when Joe
said he wasn't going to come back on my
channel cuz I lied about Thailand, but
here you are. So,
you said you was done ever coming back
on my channel, but you're here. So, same
I can say the same thing to you. I can
say exactly the same thing to you then, can't I?
I can say the same thing to you. You You
promised that you weren't going to come
back on my channel.
It doesn't take a minute. No, it doesn't. These [ __ ]
these [ __ ] women, Joseph. these [ __ ] women.
Yeah. And that tells you that these
people don't affect me. That tells you
that these people on here don't affect me.
They don't bully me. They don't affect my life.
I'm actually starting to feel sick now
cuz I haven't
Yeah, cuz I haven't ate. You know. Yeah.
See, I only come on here to go live
and and vent about women and [ __ ] You
actually come on here cuz you actually
got nothing else in your life and [ __ ]
Yeah. It's bad, isn't it, Dusty? What
would I gain from going out on Saturday?
Joe, you think that I can't afford to go
out? Yeah. You think that I can't afford
to go out, bro? What am I going to gain
by going out on Saturday?
What? More bad experiences.
I I don't Do I don't need to say that. I
told you so. Bro, I don't need to do
anything more. I've done what I've had to do,
so I don't need to do anything. Yeah, basically
I don't need to do anything. I I don't
need to do anything, bro. Cuz I'm not in
the mood to eat.
I'm not in the mood to eat. I don't even
have Coke. I didn't even drink any Coke today.
I never not drink Coke.
Yeah, this [ __ ] ain't [ __ ]
You don't need any more bad experiences.
No, your life is not better than mine,
Joe. I can go out every week. I can go
traveling again. I can do what I want.
Your life isn't better than mine.
If I don't want to go out and do
anything, that's my choice. I choose to
do that. You You need to understand.
Yeah. You need to understand
that is in Russian, is it? One second.
You need to understand that it's my
choice. It's not because I can't.
It's because I don't want to. That's the difference.
So, no, it isn't.
Yeah, go [ __ ] yourself. I said, why
don't you [ __ ] yourself, [ __ ]
So, yeah, if I when I don't want to go
out, it's because I don't want to go
out. So, that's choice.
That's choice. Whereas people in L J's,
they're skinn, they're ugly. They can't
go out and approach. They can't go out
and drink. It's It's a big difference
when it's a choice.
It is, brother. It is. It is. It is. It
is. You will never lead anyone onto your
fa to their face. You will never ever
lead anyone onto their face ever. Never
ever ever will you say anything to anyone's face.
Stupid little [ __ ]
She forgot I knew where she worked in it. So,
I just asked her why why what do you get
out of leading people on? I won't even
being a [ __ ] cuz I got a new WhatsApp in it because
this number, bro, you know, when I got a
new number, I had to delete some
contacts. I had to delete I had to
delete some contacts.
I had to delete some contacts because if
I left them contacts up there, I would
have just end up giving them all [ __ ]
So, I just deleted the contacts. I
All the ones that blocked me before that
come up now, I would have just end up
giving them [ __ ] and getting banned
again. So that's why I just deleted it.
I just delete the contacts. So yeah.
No, it's not about that. It's if I when
I'm staying in this week, that is
choice. Just like now I'm not eating
because of choice. You know, you need to
understand when something's by by
choice, it's a big difference. I I'm not
going to go out this week cuz I don't want to.
I don't need any more bad experiences.
I've proved my point enough times, right?
Make it make sense. Right. And you've
been doing community post about me, so
that must mean I control your life.
You're writing paragraphs about me.
You're talking about me. So that must
mean I control your life. and you're
reacting to me,
right? And you're doing videos to me, so
I must be controlling your life. [laughter]
Same back to you. Then if if if you're
saying right that my title Okay. What
about when you're doing paragraphs when
I'm on your mind 24/7, you don't think
that's me [ __ ] with your head? Like,
okay. Okay. Let me give you an example.
Jamie Thompson, when he's stalking me,
do you not think that's me [ __ ] with
someone's head? If someone has to be
obsessed with me every day, talk about
me, that must mean I'm [ __ ] with your
head. Does that not mean I'm [ __ ]
with your head? If I've got all of these
middle-aged men obsessed with me, then
I'm [ __ ] with your head. Simple.
I am really really [ __ ] with your
head then, aren't I? So
that's that's that. So if you're doing
community post and you're obsessed with
me, I'm also [ __ ] with your head. I'm
psychologically messing with you as well
then. Same back to you. Same back to
So yeah, Jamie Thompson, all of you are
obsessed with me. So that must mean I'm
[ __ ] with your head. I'm [ __ ] with
your life then.
You know, like I said, it takes a lot to
carry on this.
It does make sense. You're making
community posts. Uh, you're making
community posts, right?
So, that must mean I'm controlling you.
If you have to be obsessed with me every
day, that must mean then I'm living in
your head. See, you might seem to think
that I'm [ __ ] with you, but no,
you're [ __ ] with me, but I'm actually
[ __ ] with you. It does make sense.
You're making community posts about me,
videos. You're you're finding ways to
[ __ ] with me. That's me psychologically
[ __ ] with your head when you're
stalking me on these forums. It does
make sense cuz I'm Peter Belly's in the
on the mind 24/7, you know. So yeah. So yeah,
they hate me UK cuz I'm younger and
better looking than them.
I'm younger and better looking than
these people and it kills them.
That's why they do it.
They don't do it for a reaction. They
definitely don't because they're
reacting to me.
And again, for these people to I got
bored of the USA is he [ __ ] after like 2
months. Whereas these people never stop.
They literally never ever ever stop.
So they wake up every day there bitter
doing community posts, but they don't
seem to think that you're messing with
their head. They don't seem to think
that you're messing with their head. Yet
they wake up every day recording, doing
community posts, but you're not [ __ ]
with their heads, apparently. Apparently, bro,
you know, they're not they're not
controlling my emotions. They're fat,
ugly people. They're not controlling my
emotions. I'm controlling them. They're
the ones that keep doing community posts for me.
So, I must be controlling them. If they
have to be obsessed with me every day on
YouTube, is that not you controlling
someone? If you're having somebody stalk
you on different platforms, I won't
leave you alone. That takes effort. That
takes effort. Yeah, they literally
literally, you know, they are literally
I'm approaching average looking. Joe,
you won't show your face. Well, like
I've said to you, Joe, if you show your
faces, it will explain a lot. Right.
Okay. Right. What did Pat Master do for three years?
Does anyone remember what Pat Muster
done for 3 years, four years, however
long it was? What happened when his face
got put out there? It explained a lot.
Bomb. What did Bomb do for years and
when his face got out there? It
explained a lot. Okay, Graycat. What
about Graycat when she's done this [ __ ] for years,
you know? Then what? Then what? You
know, it is a um pattern with you
people. It's a pattern with the what you
do, how you end up looking like, bro.
Like you you do this because you're fat,
ugly losers that have got nothing in your life.
Joseph, you're way below average
looking. Again, I'm younger and better
looking whether I'm ugly or not.
Right. I was alone on YouTube last
Christmas. I wasn't actually alone. I
was with tenants. Right. I was with
tenants. I was actually with people
Christmas. I just wasn't with my mom.
Okay. Fair enough. And I'm telling you
that you are going to be alone this Christmas.
And I'm telling you this year you're
going to be alone. And I'm not going to
be alone. Right.
So yeah. But I'm not going to be alone
this Christmas. You people are going to
be alone this Christmas. Haters, I mean
I mean you haters.
How on earth? Well, if you put your
camera on, I will I will show you. If
you cut your camera on, it will it will
explain a lot of what you do. Same with
Smokeoky B. Same with, you know, all of
these other people. You put your camera
on and it will say a lot. You won't even
need to say. And that is what I am
saying, bro. Joe, Bomb done the same
thing that you're doing for years,
right? Bomb is doing the same thing that
you are doing for years. And he ended up
being fat and ugly. You are no
different. Yeah. He done exactly the
same thing as Pat Muster done for years.
Oh, you don't know what I look like. All
of this [ __ ] And when he got when his
face got out there fat and ugly,
he done the same thing as what you're
doing. Bomb done the same thing as what
you're doing now. So at the end of the
day, it's it is it is you you got to
understand, listen, like I will repeat
myself again. You haven't done this. You
haven't done this over co You haven't
done this over the winter. You haven't
done this over 3 months. You have been
doing this for years. And it takes a lot
of energy to sit and hate every day for
years. So what's going on, bro? What is
going on? Do you think I still [ __ ] with
USA and her family and stuff? No. Do you not understand?
You know, you people have been doing
this for years. Yes. You Red Star,
Smokeoky B, you've been doing it for
years. Yeah. You have been doing this
for years. So you wake up every day
angry [ __ ] with people for years. So
what is going on, bro?
What the [ __ ] is going on?
Well, well, listen, listen, listen.
Well, I can I can say that Joe's fat by
his hands, you know.
No, no, no, no, no. I can do. I can do
because if they wasn't ugly, they'd show
their face. If they weren't ugly, they'd
have no problem showing their face.
Like, okay, I I I'll explain it again.
If I went on a community, right, say I
went on a community right now with with
60 people and they were all arguing with
each other and I said, "This guy's ugly.
That guy's ugly." And they'll be like,
"Well, show your face." Do you think I'd
sit there and be like, "Oh, I don't need
to show my face. Uh, I would just show
my face." You people won't show your
faces cuz you're ugly. It's cuz you are
ugly. And I know it's a hard and it's
hard pill to swallow, but a lot of this
comes from your ugliness. The hating
every day on YouTube, you know, that's
it. You wouldn't want to be anonymous if
if you wasn't ugly. You wouldn't. No one
would. Nobody [ __ ] would. If I went
on a community right now,
they uh docs themselves. No, no, no.
Okay, I'm gonna I'm gonna counteract
that excuse. Um, bomb never got bomb
never got exposed.
So, no, no, no, no, no, no. You don't
show your faces cuz you're ugly. What
was the other excuse? Because you've got
a high IQ, but you repeat yourselves
every day. Oh, that was another thing as
well. Um, people said that they don't
show their faces on here. It's because
they're intelligent yet they repeat
themselves every day for eight years.
So, but they're intelligent, remember?
Okay. Yeah, whatever, bro.
Now, you people don't show your face for
the reasons that we know, but we won't
get into that. It doesn't really matter, does it?
It doesn't really matter though, bro. Does it?
You know, it doesn't really matter, does
it? You know, no.
Yeah. If I get out of bed.
Bro, you're talking about [ __ ]
Christmas dinner right now. I don't even
have a [ __ ] appetite. [ __ ] hell.
You're talking about that, bro.
No, it's nothing to do with YouTube,
bro. It's nothing to do with YouTube.
I've given up on life anyways, bro.
These people are not getting to me.
These people, believe it or not, really
don't get to me. You know,
it's the bad experiences with women
that's [ __ ] [ __ ] with my head.
So, even though it might seem like it's
these people, but it isn't.
So, what if what if my sister does want
me cuz I I talk to my sister and I go
out with my sister. So, that would
that's not going to happen. That
wouldn't happen. I've got two sisters. I
speak to one, I don't talk to the other.
It's not going to happen.
Oh. Oh. What if your mom goes to the
sister? Oh, she she's not going to.
She's not going to. They've got their
own family. That's not going to happen.
And I don't like her. It's not that she
doesn't like me. I don't like her. Um
the few times she's been messaging me,
I've been ignoring her. So, no, I don't like her.
No, not at all. I just It's just a bad
experiences with them.
You look at you look at yourself, bro,
and you think, "You're 28. This should
not be happening. We can't blame lack of
trying. We can't blame being in a
wheelchair. Like I said, it's okay when
you're 24, 25, you know, you're still uh
you know, but at this age, this
shouldn't still be happening. And
there's no excuse why it's happening as
well. Oh, it doesn't matter what
happened. It doesn't matter. But yeah.
Yeah, it doesn't matter. I just don't
like her. Simple. So,
but the other one I do, but uh I just
don't give a [ __ ] Anyways,
uh why shouldn't it be happening?
Because I've tried more than anyone in
the world. Again, you're saying I'm not
a nice person. Again, I repeat myself.
I've put approaching videos up there.
So, keep making up stuff. I don't really
care, bro. You're not getting a reaction
anymore. You've seen my approaching
videos. You've seen my messages. I've
just spoke to a woman right now who's
not a nice person. She's a [ __ ]
That's funny though, isn't it? But you
don't mind these women not being nice
people and being [ __ ]
Again, it's a gender thing.
Oh, did he? Good for him. Yeah. No one
cares what that keyboard warrior says.
That's not even going to get a response. So,
tried more than anyone in the world.
Literally tried more than anyone in the
world. Yeah, literally. Well, 90% 95% of
people in the world.
No, I think tried more than anyone in
the world. No, I think I have. No, no, I
think I have. No, no, I think I definitely have.
No, not traveled, approaching women,
trying with women. And that's how I know
they're all the same.
That's how I know they're all the same.
You see? Yeah.
Yeah. I mean, that's nice. 8.3 billion
people in the world. That's nice. And
all women are the same. So yeah,
whoever the [ __ ] it is, they're a [ __ ] coward.
Whoever they are, they're just a sad old
coward that ain't got no life. So it
don't matter who it is. Some Someone
says it's Pat Mustard. Someone says it's
Bomb. But it doesn't matter. All women
are the same anyways. It doesn't matter
how many billions of people in the world
they are. This one I was just talking to
right now was not nice. Leading people
on, having an attitude,
being a [ __ ]
but they get a free pass. But we weren't
getting to that anyways cuz we know how
the struggle dismisses are. So yeah.
Oh, just some idiot, bro. Just some idiot.
There's a lot of people on this YouTube
lately, isn't there? It's not normally this. Um,
yeah, it is hard to find women because
they're all the same.
Yeah, women defo are all the same, Joe.
They're definitely all the same. I only
went out Saturday cuz I was forced to go
out. I was actually forced to go out.
So, and women was all the same that day
as well. So, yeah.
Yeah. They're defin 100. No. No.
No. They definitely are all the same.
Uh because my my sister's friend come
around and spoke to me the one I was
coming out. So, I couldn't really say no.
yeah. I couldn't um I couldn't really
say no, bro. But now
I won't be going out. [laughter]
I won't be going out next week. I
probably would have been going out New
Year's Eve to be honest.
Yeah, I'm delusional. Well, I mean, I
have met more women than probably most
people in the world. I used to go to
cities every week approaching on the
street. I can't imagine someone that's
met more women than me. I can't I'm sure
there are people out there, but
I just can't I just can't imagine it cuz
most people have got [ __ ] you know.
Nope. But I think you need to grow up
asking that question about being by. No,
you need to grow up with that question.
That's boring now, bro. You need to stop
with that question. It's boring. It's
really, really immature.
No, it's really immature, bro. You need
to stop with them silly questions.
No, I'm not going to go out. I'm just
going to stay in bed, bro.
Why is this not
Let me do this.
Because it's a stupid question. That's why. Um,
but they don't know because they don't
know what they're like. They don't get
their numbers. They don't get to see
their side. So, no, they don't. No, they
don't. They don't meet more women than
me. No way. Cuz they're at work. So,
they're not going to know what women are
actually like. I know what women are
actually like. That's the difference. So,
I mean, what about women that find dicks disgusting?
You call them lesbians slim? What about
women that don't give [ __ ] Are they lesbians?
No. Double standards. I mean, there's
women that say dicks are disgusting. Are
they lesbians? You call them lesbians? I
hope you're calling them lesbians. Nah, caution. Double standards.
Double double standards. That's what you
call double standards right there.
There's plenty of women that say dicks
are gross and no one has a problem with
it. They never call them lesbians.
Definitely double standards. That one
with that one. They're lesbians. Sorry.
They're they're double double standards, you know.
Well, well, yeah. I don't live off much
cuz I don't do anything. Well,
I don't do anything. So, I can live off
about £30 a week. Yeah. I don't do
anything, bro. So,
not £50 a [ __ ] month. I don't I'm a
single person. I don't do anything. I
don't pay anything. I I I don't I don't
do anything. So, I could live off 30 a
week. Yeah. I didn't spend any money
today. How much money did I spend
yesterday? I don't think I spent any
money yesterday either.
I could live off 30 a week. Yeah.
I mean, I don't do anything, so why
wouldn't I be able to? Yeah,
because why? I don't want any more bad
experiences with women. I don't want to
keep going around in circles. I'm 28. I
don't want to keep going around in circles.
I don't want to go around in circles
with these [ __ ] women, you know? I
want to change. So, so yeah. Nah, bro.
I don't need to
£30 a week. Nah, I'm not even hungry, bro.
No, I don't give a [ __ ] about New Year's
Eve. I don't give a [ __ ] about Christmas.
You know, I've got enough numbers on my
phone. There's not no reason why I don't
have a date. There's no reason why I've
not found a woman that's different.
There's no reason for it.
There's literally no reason for it.
>> So, yeah.
Oh [ __ ] bro. What is going on? There's
literally no There's no reason why I
should have to go out drinking again.
There's no reason. There is literally no
reason, Grezy, why I have to even
contemplate going out again.
There is literally no reason.
Nah, thanks. I'm good. I'd rather stay in bed.
I'm all right, bro. I've lived my life.
No, I just want to leave. I think I just
want to leave. That's all I want to do
is just leave.
So, that's that.
Don't forget a couple of years ago I was
younger, so I still was like,
"Yeah, I've tried dating apps." Yeah.
No, I'm definitely like Oreo, man. I'm Yeah.
So, at my age, I should have a sex life.
There's no reason why I shouldn't have a sex life.
There's no reason. There's no There's
literally no reason why I don't have a sex life.
There's no reason. I'm 28, but I've done
a lot in 28 years. Uh 14. I I haven't
done everything, but I've done a lot,
bro. In the past four years, I've done a lot.
Probably more than
how do I explain this? This is hard,
bro. 28, but it's more like I'm [ __ ]
58 with the amount of [ __ ] that I've
done. I've done a lot of stuff, bro, in
28 years. A lot of stuff. So, yeah.
Tells you it's if it didn't get better
now, it's not going to get better ever.
Simple as that.
Why is this Reddit [ __ ] not working, bro?
Nope. Haven't done my balls in.
Nope. Haven't lost any money. Not at all.
You don't need to do your balls in, bro.
To to think like this. I don't know why
you seem to think that you need to do
your balls in to think like this.
And if I done my balls and it wouldn't
have lasted this long.
It last like a day. Bro, I haven't lost
any money. You would know about it. Why
do you keep thinking I've lost money
when I told you I haven't? If I lost
money, I would have told you that I lost money, bro.
Well, going by your community post, Joe.
I don't see what life you could possibly have, man.
When you are on L repeating the same
[ __ ] every day. I mean, I don't know
what life you could have. I don't know
what life you could possibly have, but
it's not a competition, you know?
I just don't understand what life you
could have, Smokey B, when you're on
here doing this every day for years. I
don't know what life you could have, but
it's not a competition anyways, is it?
I don't know what you what life you
could possibly have. So yeah,
it's not entertainment though because
it's just a bunch of repeating bastards
that ain't got a life. It's not entertainment.
But it's not entertainment though, is it? So yeah,
are you scared of the dentist, Joseph Ferrar?
So yeah, there's no reason why I have no
sex life. There's no reason why
basically this is basically this is why
we're why we're where we're at.
There's no reason for this.
Yeah, that's literally what it is. Yeah,
that is literally what it is.
Yeah, literally. Yeah, bang on. You know,
these [ __ ] women. Yeah,
literally, bro. Yeah, literally.
There's no reason that I need to go out
and meet anyone new. There's no reason
for it at all. Like you might think I'm
being awkward. You think I'm You think
I'm being difficult, but I'm not. I'm
really really not. Really? Really? I'm
really I'm not being difficult. I'm being real.
I went out on Saturday. I was forced. Same [ __ ]
So yeah, that's that.
Yeah. And we can't go out dusty because
we don't want any more bad experiences. So,
And that's exactly what you're going to
get. I've got videos, Joe. Yeah. Where I
literally went to man. Oh, [ __ ] me.
There was a time when these people kept
saying, "Keep trying, keep trying, keep
trying." I was like, "I'm [ __ ] sure
you keep trying." went all the way to
Manchester, done a football bet, won the
football bet, seven numbers, nothing.
So, we've done a lot of [ __ ] in our
life, bro. A lot of mad [ __ ] in our life. So, yeah.
No, it does get to me. It does get to
me. I don't want I don't want anything
to do with anyone, bro.
I don't want to go out. I don't want to
do nothing. Simple.
Because I'm scared I would just end up
hurting someone. any more bad
experience, I would just end up hurting someone, bro.
So, there's there's no point me going
out and doing anything.
There's no point in me doing [ __ ] all. So,
yep. I've had bad too many bad
experiences to last me a lifetime.
Okay, I won't do anything at all,
Joseph. Whatever. I stuck it on a
bouncer. You've never done that. I've
stuck it on two guys. You've never done
that. I went to Mark Samson's area,
right? You never done You never done
that. You can't even join a hangout and
talk. Don't tell me what I will do. Your
boyfriend, Lord J, will never do
anything. Your boyfriend Smokey B will
never do anything.
Tell your boyfriend Smokey B to go live
in London tomorrow and see what happens.
Okay. If I won't do anything then. Okay.
Okay. Why don't your boyfriend since
you're scared to go on a panel and talk
to go live in London and and you will
see what I will do and you will see what
I will do and if I don't do anything you
can come back laughing at me you know so yeah
so that's that so Yeah. Oh [ __ ]
Yeah. I'm just going to be Yeah, I'm
just going to be Saturday depressed day
in day out. Yeah,
pretty much. Yeah.
I mean, I woke up at 2:00 p.m. today. Yeah.
Yeah. Okay, bro. Whatever. Yeah. Okay,
Joe. Whatever. I do nothing. Yeah, you
keep telling yourself that.
Whatever, bro. You can't even come on a
panel and talk. Shut up.
I don't think you're in a position to
tell people they won't do anything when
you're scared of your own voice. Just
saying. You're actually scared of your
own voice. Imagine that.
Scared of your own voice. That's mad.
You won't even join a panel and talk.
That is [ __ ] mental. I can understand
not showing your face, but not even talking.
Please, just stop it. Really, really,
really stop it.
You're scared and you're insecure about
the way you sound and you're telling me
I won't do anything. Okay, bro. I won't
Well, you're scared to talk. Well,
you're scared to join a panel and talk.
So, what is it then? You're scared to
join a panel and talk, aren't you? Why
are you scared to talk?
Well, you're scared to join a panel and
talk. So, what is it then?
So, why what is it then? >> [snorts]
>> Oh, so now I'm unbalanced.
Okay. Really? Really? You can't even
join a panel and talk.
You can't even join a panel and talk.
Yeah, that is embarrassing. And you're
trying to tell me I won't do anything.
But yeah, the what you do every day, you
people, you are sad. That's like me
[ __ ] with USA every day. Even now, I
I don't have the time for it. I don't
have the energy for it.
So, yeah. I don't know. And it's weird
because you never met these people, you know.
You know, I don't take YouTube serious.
I just don't like you people and what
you do on here.
So, yeah. I just don't like what you
people do on here.
No, just to be fair, I don't want to go
out, bro, because I don't want any more
bad experiences with women. I don't want
to deal with a white night and then
potentially get into madness. It's just
not worth it. It's just not worth that
energy. It's not worth that negative
There's no point. Nothing good can come
out of it. So,
yeah. There's no there's no reason for
me to go out and do anything. I've done
what I've had to do. That's that. So, yeah. You know, that's
I reckon if I went on another site Yeah.
or community and I had people listen to
me, I think I would just leave this one.
See, I don't use YouTube for the same
reasons that you use YouTube.
Why don't I go out with mates? Not interested.
Yeah, I'm not interested.
No, I can't be bothered. Triple Yeah.
Well, yeah. No one's ever going to
accept your views.
Duh. I mean, Tiger Tiger is the only one
on here that's not biased and says,
"Yeah, women led you on. Women are
wrong." And he goes on Lord Jesus and he
says, "No, they definitely led you on."
And he doesn't like me.
He's a completely unbiased person and he
says, "No, they led you on. They
definitely did." Um, and yeah, people
will never accept your views because they
I don't know. They're brought up
thinking that all women are innocent and
can't do anything wrong. Yeah. No one's
going to accept your views because they
all think women are innocent no matter
what you show them. Duh. It's not just
this community. You can go on Reddit and
they do that.
Yeah. They will always think women are
innocent and don't do no wrong. That's
That's They will always do that. So,
Tiger Tiger is the only one on here that
says, well, Grevy says it as well that like Yeah.
So, but they also dismiss your struggles
as well, Joe. They also dismiss your
struggles. I use YouTube for therapy
sessions. I basically use this for
therapy sessions. Sessions. Sess
Can't even say that right. Yeah.
That's what I use YouTube for. I do.
I do use it for therapy sessions. Why do
you think I don't go on anyone's channel? You know,
why do you think I don't go on anyone's channel? So, yeah. Baby,
did you tell your misses that you're a
non-slaver? Joseph Ferrar.
I remember when Monty man stopped eating
for days when he was in love. Yeah.
Yeah. But you said Yeah. But you even
said that the mods ban people to feel powerful.
You said that it's sad what the mods do.
So what? So now what? You're going back
on what you're saying.
Yeah, you even said that they're sad.
You even said that they're sad. So what?
>> Yeah. Did you not say that the Reddit
moderators are sad?
Yeah, they block people. So what? They
block people to feel powerful.
You said anything that people do to feel
in control was sad.
And they don't get paid, by the way.
Yeah, but you know these Reddit
moderators don't get paid.
I didn't even realize they never got
paid until recently. I always thought
they did. So what? They don't even get paid.
So why would they do it if they don't
even get paid? You know.
Yeah. I hate most I hate most of them.
Not I don't hate everyone on this YouTube.
Yeah, I do hate a lot of these people on here, bro.
Yeah, but I'm not sat banning people
every day. There's a big difference.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no. That's that
that's a bit different. Somebody comment
on YouTube, right, and then being on
Reddit banning people all day. No, no,
no. That's there's a big difference with
that. There's a big difference.
And I got on here [ __ ] from the time
I wake up to the time I go to bed authority.
What? What? Cuz I said I don't like police.
Yeah, I don't like police.
Yeah, I don't like police. Yeah. So, so
what if I don't like police?
I think they play two sides of a coin.
And yeah, I don't like police. So what?
Why don't you get a job? Same question
to you. Why don't you get a job? I don't
need a job. I've got enough money. But
to Same question to you. Why don't you
get a job?
I couldn't get a job, bro. Are you mad?
Are you mad? You're telling me to get a
job? You You think that's really going to work?
No, you can't get a job, bro.
Because one day you'll think of your bad
experiences with women and you're not
going to want to come into get into
work. Trust me, I done it when I used to
work and I couldn't like it put me off
even going to work.
I wouldn't be able to go in one day.
I remember this one time I used to go to
gym and I used to do this u job and I I
was approaching. Yeah. And it put me in
a bad mood. I didn't go to work.
Yeah. It put me in a bad mood. So I
didn't go to work. It pissed me off,
bro. It was like 7:00 in the morning. I
was approaching outside the gym and they
were pissing me off. So I just didn't
go. I just didn't go. I went to the gym
and went back. So yeah.
Yeah. And you have to deal with
[ __ ] at work and stuff. And you
just need to leave this country. Simple.
That's all you do. You just need to leave.
You just need to leave. That's it.
Ant-Man's a legend.
Ant-Man's a [ __ ] legend.
Ant-Man is a legend, man.
To think he was on here doing this and
now look where he is. Antman's a ledge
to be fair.
Yeah, you can say what you want about
him, Greasy. But do you know the thing
is? Yeah. Look at where he was and what
he's done now. No one else has done
that. No one else has done that, bro. So
that you can't even disagree with.
Even LT says that yeah, he's a weirdo.
He's a nons. But look what he done. He
was on here doing all of this madness.
He left. He's done something with his life. Look,
people like Smokey B will never do that.
So, in a way, he is actually kind of
winning over a lot of people on here.
He got off of YouTube. He doesn't come on YouTube.
Now, he's living in a different country.
How mad is that?
That is mad, bro. You know, and he never
come back on here either.
Yep. I won't be eating today. I won't be
Yeah, man is a legend for what he done
to be fair.
Doesn't matter what he is. It doesn't
matter what he is, bro. You know that as
well. He will never ever come back on air.
Do you remember when he was meeting the
trolls for fights, Grezy? And they
didn't show up. and they didn't show up
like that now Den cheese and he still
comes on here you know that now Den
cheese even seven years later he's still doing it
they've been on years these [ __ ] old farts
these old farts have been doing this for is. Yeah,
I I didn't drink. I can't believe I've
not had a Coke today. Jesus Christ. I've
not had a Coke.
You know, I can't live without Coke, Grezy.
Seven years is long. What? To be on air
repeating yourself? Yeah, it [ __ ] is.
Yes, it [ __ ] is to be on here [ __ ] repeating
for seven [ __ ] seven, eight years.
Yeah, it is. Yeah.
No, I haven't been on here over seven
years. No, I haven't.
I come in when I was 22.
No, I haven't. So, yeah.
I don't know. Some people on here has
been Some people's been on here since 2012.
20 [ __ ] 12, actually. What am I talking about?
You're talking about food. Someone's having food.
I can't even stomach the thought of food, bro.
No, it wasn't 2017.
definitely was in 2017.
I knew about Timmy. I've known about
Timmy for 10 years, but I I didn't come
on here until like I was after that. I
knew about Timmy when I was 18. I used
to watch the videos. So, yeah.
It's [snorts] okay though. I'll just wait.
You'll You'll wait until it's been made.
That's okay. I'll just wait. We
wait. Yes. Until it's been made.
That's funny, isn't it? I can't deprive
Greaves of content. The poor [ __ ] Yeah.
No, we're not talking about that,
Greavesy. We're talking about the one
years and years and years ago. Yeah.
Yeah, I did. It was lush. That's the
times I used to go to the gym, isn't it?
No, this was years ago, Greezy. Oh gosh,
non legs come in earlier and I was like,
>> you know what I was doing that greasy
little chubby Copycat.
You little copycat.
I know I should have a sex life, though.
I know I should be in a relationship. I
should have a sex life. There's
absolutely no reason why I'm not. I've
tried a lot. I've tried a lot. I've put
the effort in. It definitely is no life
for no 28-year-old.
It's definitely no life for a 28-year-old.
You can say that again.
Bless you then, Triple.
No. Bless you.
Yeah. It's no life. It's It's no life.
Uh, Joseph Ferrar, it's no life.
I should be having a sex life.
I shouldn't have to be masturbating.
I shouldn't have to be doing any of that
stuff. I should have a booty call that I
could just call up with the amount of
effort that I've put in, the amount of
money I've spent and tried. Yeah. So, yeah. Dude, do
gay man. He's an old gay man. I told him
that I'm not having a sex life again.
Yeah. No, seriously though, you The
thing is, if you go out this week,
you're going to get more bad experiences.
It's not It's not an option. You can't go out.
We've been there, done it, worn a t-shirt.
Been there, done it, worn the t-shirt.
And I wouldn't went out last week even
if I wasn't forced.
So you you're going to get more bad
experiences with women and then the same
thing's going to happen again and again
and again. No, no. There's no there's
nothing different that's going to happen.
And it's just going to escalate and
escalate and escalate and that's all
that ever happens. So yeah,
it's really bad, is it, bro? Oh,
at least I get to save loads of money.
At least I get to save loads of money,
Dusty, by doing this.
Oh, this is lovely. This is lovely.
Have to laugh at it cuz it's so sad.
have any coke.
I don't even have any coke.
Yeah, I don't even have any coke
cuz obviously I wasn't able to go to the shop.
It is for me though. I don't think I've
ever gone one day without eating.
I don't think I've ever gone one day
without eating, bro. Unless I was skinn
like seven years ago. Never. [ __ ]
Moving on. Uh, there is no moving on, bro. Yep. No.
No, no one wants.
No, no, nothing, bro. No, nothing.
I am fully done.
I can do. Sorry, bro. I'm completely done.
>> No, bro. I'm completely done, lad.
I'm completely done.
I can't remember the last time I showered. [snorts]
Quite a while ago.
Nope. I'm not doing no bet.
I'm doing nothing, bro. I've given up my
life. I'm done. Done, bro.
Nope. I'm staying in bed.
I'm staying in bed, lad. Yeah,
I'll be in my little nest
depressed thinking about my bad experiences probably.
I'm surprised I don't go to gambling.
Why? I'm not gambling right now. I could
easily gamble right now if I wanted to.
Yeah, I could easy gamble right now if I
wanted to. 500 versus roulette. Get up
there. But I'm not going to do that, am I?
I just hate women. It's all I think
about every day, bro.
the bad experiences of women and getting
revenge and [ __ ] That's all I think about, bro.
It's really bad.
I don't even think if I won money I'd be
I'd feel better.
I think even if I won money, I still
don't think I'd feel better.
No, I don't I don't even think that I'd
feel better, bro. So yeah, one
Yes, I am innocent.
Dusty, are you scared of the dentists?
Are you scared of the dentist, lad?
Laney scared of the dentist. Few people
I know are scared of the dentist.
I'm not scared of the dentist.
I got a feeling, didn't I, Dusty? Last
month, I got a feeling.
Yeah, I went to the dentist.
listen to some music in a bit.
Yeah, I'm just going to listen to some
music in a bit. Bro,
my hair's going back already. Dusty. Jesus.
Yeah. in a minute.
Yeah, in a minute.
I just message innocent women,
random women, giving them [ __ ] Yeah,
basically. Yeah, relationship stuff. obviously. Yeah,
this Jamie, this Jamie Thompson's
obsessed with me, bro.
I hope you have a nice day. Maybe one
year a job. Either way,
I can leave the country whenever I want.
Michael. Yeah, this is what I mean.
These people in here are just sad people
with no life. This is what I mean, bro.
You can look at the time frame they've
been doing this for as well. They've
been doing it for years.
They have been doing it for absolute years.
Absolute years, Dusty.
Just shows they ain't got a life in it. Yeah.
Yeah, these people have been doing this
for years, bro. You know what the [ __ ]
I've seen these same accounts. Yeah,
but don't forget they're not jealous.
But they're not jealous. Don't forget,
Nah, they're not jealous. They just
spend years stalking and harassing people.
But they're not they're not jealous.
Remember people, they're not jealous.
They just spend all day, every day hating.
But no, they're not. They're not
jealous. No, of course they're not.
They're not jealous. But look, don't
forget they're not jealous.
They're happy people.
Now, am I falling asleep, bro? Am I [ __ ]
falling asleep? I'm awake.
Oh, look at that Jamie Thompson. He's a
fat ugly weirdo, bro. I'm going on some
of his pictures. [ __ ] Yeah,
I don't mind dentists.
I don't mind them. I quite like the dentist.
I had a feeling last month.
Yeah, I had a feeling last month.
I had a nasty toothache. It was [ __ ] stinking.
I can't believe I didn't drink Coke
today. I never go a day without drinking Coke. Joseph for
He has nothing and never will. But these
people have got nothing.
But these people have got nothing.
Because when I don't go out, I don't go
out by choice. This is what I'm trying
to say. I don't go out by choice.
That's that's the difference.
These people have got no choice.
These ugly people ain't got no choice. Yep.
How much how much money is skint to you? Uh
finder, how much money is skint to you?
How much money is skint to you having
money? How much would you cost having in
your bank as skin?
um treating [clears throat] the depression before
before treating um by trying to date
women. And I explained that the
depression is from the bad experiences
with the women. You're depressed because
of your bad experiences with women.
You know what I'm saying? It's because of them.
And if skin is less than 1K. Yeah.
Yeah. I had £1,700 last month. That was
quite good, isn't it?£1,700 last month. I had
No, I was just saying to this guy that I
had £1,700 last month.
Yeah. So, you think so? If you have less
than 1K, your skin,
you agree with that, Grezy? If you have
less than 1K your skin
behind you. You mean a bit? Yeah.
Yeah. I had 1,700 last month.
Everyone, this is Mrs. My struggles.
Yeah, that someone on Reddit said, "You
need to treat depression before trying
to date women." And I said, "No, the
dating women is what's causing me to be
depressed. The bad experiences with them
is what makes me depressed."
No, no, no. The women is what make you depressed.
Do you know what I'm saying? Yeah.
Dusty showers sublet's house, don't you?
Yeah. Dusty sublets.
Why do you sub at your house, Grezy?
Yeah. Was that lush? £1,700, Greavvesy.
Yeah, I had £1,700.
That was lush. Yeah.
Working on yourself won't change your
experiences with women.
[ __ ] give me £1,700 if it's [ __ ] nothing.
Just give me 1,700 if it's [ __ ]
nothing. I'll give you my [ __ ] bank
details right now.
Bro, that's silly to say that £1,700 is
nothing. That is silly.
Come on, bro. We're not millionaires. Of
course, it's something. Don't be silly.
Of course it is.
I don't understand how you can say that
unless you're really, really, really
well off. [snorts]
No, honestly, it is much. Honestly, it
is. It lasted quite a while.
No, no, honestly, it is much. £,700 is.
What can you do with £1,700? Um,
pretty much everything.
Pretty much [ __ ] everything.
You can buy the new flagship phone. You
can go to [ __ ] America. You can go
Nando. You can go out drinking [ __ ]
multiple times a week. What do you mean?
What can you do with £1,700, bro?
pretty much [ __ ] everything.
What the [ __ ]
Seven. You can spend £1,700 in a week.
I don't think I've ever spent £,700 in a
week in my life.
I don't think I've ever spent that in my life.
But yeah, saying what can you do with
17,700 pound doesn't make sense?
What kind of question is that, bro? What
the [ __ ] What can you do with £1,700?
You used to spend £2,000 a week. Nah,
you're talking [ __ ]
Nah, I've not even spent that, mate.
an amount of money that I used to go
through. Well, you used to spend two
2,000 every week.
Nah, bro. That's not even believable.
No, that doesn't even make sense. What?
You spend two grand every week,
but I don't know how you can say, what
can you do with £1,700? You could do a
lot of stuff.
You do not spend two grand every week,
bro. Trust me. This is coming from
someone, bro, that used to go through a
lot of money.
Nah. Two grand every week.
No way, bro.
No way. And how do I know this, bro?
Because I've been sat there with seven
grand next to me and I've never
every week. Really, bro?
That sounds very very hard to believe, bro.
Every week. You might have spent it on
in a day once, but you you didn't spend
it every week.
Yeah, I've lost two grand on roulette,
but not every week. I've I lost two
grand once. Yeah, I lost two grand once.
I lost two grand once. Yeah,
I was online. 1700.
You don't need to know that.
Well, I say I had 1,700. It was more
like 1,900 cuz I got money every week.
So, but I spent a lot on like I spent
that's how I bought the J the jeans and
the vapors. I bought jeans and vapor,
you know. So,
no, I won't be [ __ ]
No, we were just talking about like this
guy said £1,700 isn't much.
It is for a single person with no bills.
What the [ __ ]
The only reason my went mine went is cuz
the [ __ ] what I was what I bought and so yeah.
Well, yes it is 1700. Yeah. 1700 lb is £1,700.
It is something. It's 1,700.
So, I mean, yeah, it is £1,700 is 1,700.
how can you say that it's nothing?
You people must be millionaires because
people in, you know, people don't talk
like that. Normal people don't talk the
way that you're talking.
But it depends. What bills are we
talking about? If you have £1,700, what
bills are you talking about? What? What bills, bro?
What bills are we talking about?
Yeah, it depends how much you have you
have to pay on bills, isn't it? If you
don't have any bills, then Yeah.
Obviously, if you do, then no, it
depends, isn't it?
Depends what bills you have. It depends.
It's not even that. It depends what you
need to buy.
Yeah, but I buy my own food. Yeah, but I
Well, I do have a bill actually. I've
got a phone bill.
You don't need to know that.
I've got I actually do have a bill. I've
got a phone bill. The only reason I
don't I cancel the Xbox subscription is
cuz I'm going to buy the game outright
so I can save money on that as well.
Yeah, I've still got to pay food. I've
still got to pay for my food.
I get money every week anyways on top of
that when I had that 1,700. So, but it
didn't last that long cuz I had to buy
trainers and jeans. So,
yeah, but I've got um
but I strive to buy my own food. Who do
you think pays food for food? You think
I don't buy my own food?
No, I don't have any bills but the phone
bill. Oh, by the way, I can get a phone
contract out if I want to. I can
actually get a phone contract out if I
want to, but
I don't really want to be tied down to a contract. So, Yeah.
Yeah. I bought one on some UGG boots, didn't I?
I get I can actually get a phone
contract. The only time I'd get a phone
contract is when the Fold 8 comes out
and I'll get a yearly I'll get a year
contract. I'll pay £200 a month. I'll
just pay £200 a month and get it paid in a year.
That's the only time I think I'd get a
concert out if it was if it was a yearly
one. I wouldn't get any more than one year.
I think a year is Yeah, I think a year.
Yeah. £200 a month for a year done.
Yeah. So, I might do I don't know.
Yeah, but it's only for a year.
Yeah, but it's only for a year, is it?
It's only for a year. No, I'm not buying
it outright. They're like £1,800. I'm
not paying that for a phone.
I'm not paying £1,800 for a phone, bro.
No, I'm not pay for a phone. Can't
justify it. Back then, now I can't. No,
I'm not I'm not paying 1,800 for a
phone. That's ridiculous.
If it was like a,000 and if it was like
maybe 11,200 and but not not £1,800, bro.
Nah, not £1,800. And the thing is a new
one comes out every year. Nah. No. No. Not £1,800.
Yeah, but you're paying off for it.
£1,800 is not worth it for a phone, bro.
And I've said this no matter what money
I used to have. So, you know,
no, [ __ ] that, bro.
£1,100. Yeah, that's a bit different
than £1,800, though, isn't it? My
phone's a [ __ ] Samsung [ __ ] fold,
but it's blocked. So, I need to get a new one.
But it still works on Wi-Fi and [ __ ]
So, I've not had I've not felt the
reason. I haven't felt the need to yet. So, yeah.
Yeah, that's the thing.
Ant-Man uses an iPhone 12.
Yeah, but it's only for a year. Yes, but
Do you not understand, bro? It's only
for a year.
Why did you get the iPhone 17? Ant-Man
uses the iPhone 12. He said it's good
enough. The iPhone 12.
Yeah, he says the iPhone 12 is good
enough for him.
Yeah, £1,800 is madness.
Really, bro? If I lived on my own, I
doubt I'd be able to even feed myself
every day. Of course, I would be able to
feed myself every day.
What do you mean if it's pennies a
month? What are you talking about?
Yeah, he has the 12 and he says that
there's no point in getting the newer ones.
I think I know people that are using
iPhone 7s. I don't use iPhone so but I
just could never you could I just don't
have iPhones. Simple.
I'd probably just get like a 300 pound Samsung.
I don't like contracts, but that's why
I'm saying it's a year contract. So
after the year, the phone's yours.
Yeah, but you're not going to pay £1,800
for a phone, are you?
Yeah, but you're not going to pay
£1,800. It depends what the phone is,
isn't it? It depends what the phone is.
£1,800. You can't justify that.
So, what are you going to do? Pay £1,800
for a phone? [ __ ] that, bro. I'm not
paying that. 17 £1,800 for a phone.
I would find a way, mate. I would find a
way. I would find a way.
I would find a way. Don't you worry about me.
No. 36, 24, and 12. Nah, they're different ones.
Yeah, but you're getting the minutes
though. No, no, no, no. But you're
getting unlimited everything with the
phone. So, you're paying £600 more.
1 2 3 4 5 Yeah. No. It's about right
because you're you're getting unlimited everything.
No, no, no, no, no. Because you're
getting unlimited everything,
which is Say that's about 30 extra a
month. Yeah. 30 divided by 12. 1 2 3 4 5
6 7 8 9. No, that's about right. Because
it's about £30 a month for everything.
But yeah, don't I would advise do not
get contracts. The only time you should
get a contract is if you want like the
top top top model phone and you don't
want to pay £1,800.
Yeah, obviously if if the phone's like
£1,100 or 1,200 or whatever, yeah, then
obviously buy it outright, but not £1,800.
That is taking a piss. £1,800. That is
I think I'd be feel sick, bro. You know,
I'm not even joking.
Yeah. The bad thing about contracts as
well is it's blocked to one network. The
be if you want the the best thing is
getting the phones from Argos. Argos is
the best. They're the best places to buy phones. Argos.
And I know my mom's got like a
refurbished phone and people buy
refurbished phone, but I don't know, man.
I don't really want used things,
devices. I mean, like a device [snorts]
because you might want to change provider.
You might want to change provider. So,
when I was doing when I was doing this
Uber, yeah, I was with uh who was it
with? Who was I with? I was with three.
And I couldn't get signal. It was so
bad. I lost the bike and I couldn't get
signal. It took me I had to connect to
another rider's phone in order to locate
the bike. And I had to change the SIM to E. You know,
you don't need to worry about what I'm
doing, bro. Don't worry about me. I'm
all good, man.
But no, not if you won't pay it, but you
might want to change. I had to change
the provider to E cuz I couldn't get no
signal. So, I couldn't work. So, I had
to I actually had to change the SIM.
I couldn't locate the bike, bro. I had
to go back for the bike. It was mad.
Yeah, you need to Yeah, is the best but
free. I couldn't get no signal in central London.
I couldn't cope on my own. I've lived by
my I've lived by myself, bro. What are
you talking about? I've lived and I've
worked by myself. What are you talking about?
I can't code by myself. I've lived by
myself and worked by myself.
How How do you work that one out?
How do you work that one out, bro?
That doesn't make any sense. Yeah.
Yes, I was paying bills. I was paying a
broadband bill. I was paying gas,
electric, my phone bill. Yes, I was.
Yes, I was. What the [ __ ] are you
talking about? Yes, I was. And yeah,
I stopped paying the internet bill cuz I
moved. So yeah. So what are you talking about? Yeah.
And if it wasn't the sublet of money, I'
I'd find another way to make money. So what?
Yeah. I don't know what it's like to
live in the in the real world. Okay, bro. Yeah.
Yeah. Even though I live by myself, I've
worked, gone to the gym by myself. Yeah.
Okay, bro. I used to live by myself and
travel all the time, but I don't know
what it's like to live in the real
world. Okay. Even though I worked as well. Okay.
Yeah. Okay, bro. I don't know. No.
No, it's not. It really isn't. I'm really you know
so yeah why are you so obsessed with my
life anyways bro let's talk about your
lives why don't you come on the panel
and start talking about your lives you
seem to be very obsessed with other people's lives
why is that bro like who they live with
what they should be doing. Why Why are
you so obsessed?
Why are you so obsessed with other
people and what they're doing, bro? Can
I ask you that?
Very obsessed with other people's lives.
I'm sure I'm not the only one that's
noticed on here. Madness. [ __ ] madness.
I was in a bedsit before. Never been in
a bedit in my life. [snorts]
Never been in a bed sit in my life.
Shows how much you know.
What's the day tomorrow? Wednesday.
Has anyone got any plans for this week?
Anyone's got any of you got plans.
My condolences. My condolences.
I'll be in bed, matey.
Yeah, I'll be in bed.
I make another cup of con in a minute.
Yeah. You going outside there? Yeah.
That's good, bro.
Me going out getting some [ __ ] No
thanks. I don't want more bad
experiences with women.
No thanks. I've had enough bad
experiences to last me a lifetime, bro.
I'm good. Thank you. But no thanks.
I got nothing left to prove.
You got a date? Good luck. Oh [ __ ]
It's not like me to not have a coke,
bro. I always drink Coke and I haven't
had a Coke today.
That is bad.
No, I'll be I'll be in all week. I'll be
all week depressed.
Am I eating tomorrow? Probably not. No.
Well, duh. That's exactly why I'm not
going out this week. Because of that reason.
Yeah, because of that reason.
No, I think he's been run off of YouTube.
No, I don't need your No, I've got my
own money. I don't need your money. I've
got my own money. I've got I've got
enough money. Put it that way. I've got
enough money to do whatever I want. I
don't need your money.
No, I don't need your money.
Nah, bro. I don't need your money. I've
got my own money.
I just didn't leave the house today again.
No, he's been run off by people on
YouTube. I don't think he's dead, bro.
even though it was all of a sudden. But
yeah, I don't need money. I have my own money, bro.
So maybe this will tell you that you
don't need to be skinned to feel like
this. You don't need to lose money to
feel like this, bro. You could just have
so many bad experiences. Bit like what I had,
you know, dealing with these [ __ ] [ __ ] women.
I never go a day without Coke, bro. I
remember I remember Yeah. years ago.
Yeah. I went three days without Coke and
I started getting headaches when I used
to go to gym. I was like, "Oh,
oh, I can't touch Coke, bro." I started
getting headaches, man.
And I had like a Coke and a packet of
crisps. Yeah, I remember, bro. I was I
can't live without Coke. So yeah,
these women re these women really are
[ __ ] though. They are really [ __ ]
Yeah, I know. I know it would, but I
don't care. Reddit, I just don't give a [ __ ]
Yeah, I know it would, but I just simply don't care.
I used to go gym in the old house. I
used to approach in the old house as
well. I just don't give a [ __ ] you know?
But yeah, it would uh
I could look really good if I went to
the gym and stuff, but I'm not interested.
I'm just interested in staying in bed,
being depressed, to be fair.
Just fed up, you know? So, yeah.
Maybe I should have got a KFC. No, no, no.
That's what happens when you give up
with life, Reddit. That's what happens
when you give That's what happens when
you give up your life. Yeah,
I started it.
But my sleeping pattern ain't that bad.
I wake up at like 2.
Yeah, I wake up at like 2:00 and Yeah.
No, I'm good, bro.
No, I'm all right.
No, I I'll probably drink some Coke
tomorrow. I'll probably drink some Coke
tomorrow, but I don't know if I'll eat tomorrow.
Nope. Even if you paid for it, I still
wouldn't go out cuz it's not about money.
No, I still Oh, that
Nope. He never got my money stopped. No
one's ever got my money stopped on here.
So, no one on here has ever got my money
stopped. So, and it doesn't because I've
got money right now and I can do
whatever I want whenever I want. So, I
still have loads of money and no one on
it got my money stopped. But keep
telling yourself that. If that's what
makes you feel better, bro, you can keep
telling yourself that.
Pretty sure if that happened I'd be
reacting every day going mad saying [ __ ]
where one of you people and I don't
because it's simply not true. You didn't
get any money stopped.
You didn't get any of my money stopped.
And it doesn't matter how much money
I've had in the past. I've always been
like this. So no. No. If I had better
experiences with women, I could have 50
quid to my name and I'd be better.
Nothing to do with money. And none of
these people ever got my money stopped.
So yeah, you keep you keep believing
that anyways. If it makes you feel
better, I'm not going to argue about it, bro.
Trust me, none of you people ever got
any of my money stopped. [snorts] You
tried a couple of times, though.
No, you've definitely definitely never
got any of my money stopped.
You definitely definitely definitely did
not get my money stopped. 100%.
Definitely definitely didn't get my
money stopped. And I've explained this a
million times and I'm not explaining it
again. It's repeating and projecting.
I'm not explaining it again. Like I
said, if you think that, you keep believing it.
Yeah. You keep believing that. If these
people got my money stopped, it wouldn't
have took four years for them to get my
money stopped. That's literally the only
response you're going to get.
So, yeah. Anyways, we're not repeating
this. We've been over this a million
times. Moving on. So, I'm making a cup
of tea in a minute. So, yeah.
[ __ ] hell, bro.
[ __ ] been the lady again. Stupid
game. So, yeah.
Yeah, we're not we're not answering
self-reflectors anymore. So, yeah, that
just makeup stuff. So, yeah.
D. See how calm I am?
See how calm and unbothered I am. Why do
you think that is, bro? Why am I so calm and unbothered?
Because what you're saying about
people's money getting stopped is [ __ ]
That's why we just laugh it off because it's [ __ ]
You didn't get anyone's money stopped. I
told everyone the story and then you
started making up stuff saying that you
got my money stopped. You never got my
You 1 million% never got it stopped. Cuz
if someone on here got my money stopped,
someone would be getting killed. Have
you noticed why I'm so completely calm?
Have you noticed I'm calm and
unbothered? Because no one has ever
stopped my money. So there's nothing to
be mad about.
Nope. They 1 million% never got it
stopped. Nope. That never happened. You
didn't get any of my money stopped.
Nope. 1 million% you never 1 million%
you never. Cuz if you got my money
stopped, it wouldn't have took four
years. Think about it, right? How long
did you know that I was subleting?
You It wouldn't have took four years to
get someone's money stopped. You heard a
story. You heard me tell the story and
you started making up stories that you
got it stopped. That's what you done. We
all know what you done, bro. Yeah. At
the end of the day, Yeah. You never got
anyone's money stopped because it would
not have took you four years to get
someone's money stopped. Yeah. You heard
me tell the story of what happened,
right? And then you made up a story saying
you didn't get anyone's money stopped.
You one million% never, not 100,000. You
never got anyone's money stopped. You
literally didn't get anyone's money stopped.
Trust me. Trust me. You did not get any
of my money stopped. And I'm not talking
about it anymore. It's self-p projecting and repeating.
I know. I said it was £180 that you
tried to get stopped. Yeah.
You didn't stop any of my [ __ ] money
cuz one of you would have been getting
killed if you did. Trust me, you would
have. Trust me, you would have.
Yeah. But you keep saying that you got
it stopped. Yep.
Nope. No, they did not. They did not get
it stopped. The only money they tried
getting stopped was one of my benefits
money. Yeah, trust me. You didn't get
none of my sublet money stopped. I lived
that life for 4 years. Lived the high
life, lived a good life, still got
savings from it. Trust me, it never got
stopped. Trust me, it never got stopped.
People knew I was subleting in the days
when LT was breaking into that house.
Yeah. Everybody knew when LT was
breaking into that house about 3 years,
three and a half years ago. Trust me,
you never got none of that money
stopped. None of it. Not a penny of it.
Trust me, you did not get a penny of it
stopped. Not one person on this community.
Trust me, you did not get a penny of
that money stopped. Not even an ounce of
a penny. Believe you me, you never
because everybody knew about it when LT
when everybody uh when when LT was
breaking in that house, he snitched,
which was 2 and a half, three years ago.
2 and a half, three years ago when you
knew people was making money on that
house. But what it took you four years
to get someone's money stopped, bro,
stop it. Stop it, please. It's
embarrassing now. Gambled, used escorts,
traveled, designer clothes, went out
several times a week. I mean, yeah,
that's what I done. Yeah.
Where does he get? He doesn't have
money. That's his daddy savings.
He doesn't have money. He skid that 30
grand is his daddy savings that he can't
show anymore. He just He doesn't have
any money, bro. He's skinned. Oh, [ __ ]
Yeah, he doesn't have any money. He's skint.
that's his daddy's savings that he can't show anymore.
Yeah, I gambled, designer clothes,
escorts, traveled, hotels,
various different things I done with that money. Yeah. So, [gasps] oh [ __ ]
I know. Winning winning money might
change your mood, but not having money
changes your mood, bro.
Well, it's a better life than what you
was living. I'll tell you that much.
Bro, it was a better life than what you were living.
And no, it really, really isn't about
money. I've got money.
And it doesn't make a difference. You're
still going to feel this way if you had
bad experiences with women. It doesn't
matter how much money you have. It
doesn't matter how much money you have.
Trust me. So yes, yes.
Yeah, but I'm never skin so it doesn't happen.
But I'm never skin so it never happens.
Yeah, that never happens cuz I never
skin. So, but in the past, yeah, like
five years ago. Well, duh.
Oh, here we go. Self-projecting comments again. [snorts]
Yeah, self-projecting comments again.
But yeah, like 5 years ago, bro. Maybe.
Bro, I think even if I won money now, I
still think I'd be like, "Yeah,
yeah, obviously you'll be depressed if
you're skin." Yeah,
of course, bro. If you got like£50 to
your name, obviously.
I'm not having a drink.
I won't be. So, yeah. Yeah.
Yeah. But yeah, if your skin Yeah. It's
depressing, bro. Yeah.
Yeah, I won't be going out, bro, for Yeah.
for for a long time, bro.
No, I didn't eat, bro.
Yeah, it is something when you eat every
day like me. I eat every day. Well,
normally used to eat every day. So, it
kind of is. Yeah.
I don't know.
You say even if I want money, I think
I'd still be depressed.
I generally think even if I want money,
I would still be depressed, bro. Generally would.
Yeah, I generally would, but I think
I would, bro.
Nah, I'm all right, bro.
So, I'm going to go in a minute anyways.
I'm going to make a tea, bro, and then
just watch some [ __ ] and go to sleep, bro.
Go to sleep. I'm my [ __ ] going to go to sleep, bro.
I'm my [ __ ] going to go to sleep. I
won't be asleep until [ __ ] 7 in the morning. >> [snorts]
>> What am I going to do? Nothing. Just
going to make a tea. I know what I'm
going to eat today. I woke up in a foul mood.
No, I woke up in a foul, disgusting mood.
Oh, lady didn't go to bed tonight.
Oh, one second. I'm going to leave the
phone here. I'm going to go downstairs
and make proper [ __ ] Yeah.
Yeah. One second.
Sorry about that. Oh [ __ ] Yeah, man. SP myself. [snorts] Yeah. Meow meow baby.
So many copycats.
My mom heard me earlier when I let the
version in, but I kept saying meow. Meow.
I find shovel car attractive. Greavvesy,
do the honors.
I can't get over I can't get No, I'm not
eating biscuits. I can't get over Monty.
It's the same people and they're here
doing the same [ __ ]
It's the same people and they're doing
the same [ __ ]
It's the same people doing the same [ __ ] Grezy.
Just the same people doing the same [ __ ]
So what did you say about them people
Greasy that was saying Chevco is attractive?
What were they doing Grezy?
What I doing?
What are they doing?
Yeah. Nonsleg said that if I didn't find
her attractive, I'm gay. Finder.
He said, "If I don't find her
attractive, I'm gay."
Sounds like a copycat statement.
Yeah. Copy him. Copying the crowd.
I hate that ugly shovel car, man. He's a copycat.
Why don't you mind your own business?
Why don't you mind your own business and
go on with your life?
Yeah, but nonsleg said that if I don't
find her attractive, I'm gay.
No, that's mad. That is exactly what a
copycat would say.
Yeah, you're a copycat.
Yeah. Anyone that says that they're
copying they're copying the crowd. Yeah.
Have you noticed he stopped saying it now? Huh?
No. [ __ ] Rice.
Yeah, you're a little copycat.
You're a little copycat. Yeah.
Yeah. Self-projecting skin comments
again, lad. It's not going to change the
fact that you're skin. You can say that
I'm a skin. You can say I'm skinn a
million times, bro, but it's not going
to change the fact that you're the one that's skint.
That's not going to change the fact that
you're the skint one.
Yeah, bro. That's not going to change
the fact that you're skin and I'm not. No. Spanklin.
So, what is with these skin comments
anyways? Are we going to change it up in 2026?
I'm going to go on L's on the 1st of
January and hopefully there's different comments.
Triple H. Hopefully, it's different
people, different comments. Yeah.
Why? Why would it never Why would it
never be different people?
It's the same repeating people every day.
I like sh meow meow. Yeah. All right.
Binda. So why did nonsex say if I don't
find shovel car attractive I'm gay?
with no mind of his own. Yeah,
it was a fair with the crowd. It was a fit in.
He wanted to stop getting bullied by
them Scottish lads in college.
Hello. That's what I used to say in it. Yeah.
Oh, he's just a [ __ ] [ __ ] bro.
He's just a [ __ ] I said to that Smoky
B, go live anywhere in London tomorrow
and see what happens.
You know that Joseph Farra is very
obsessed with me as well. Um, Grezy,
have you noticed if you go on Lord J, he
doesn't talk about anyone but me. I've
got a lot of people obsessed with me,
bro, on here.
I got c I got loads of people obsessed
with me, but don't forget they got
better lives than me and they're not jealous.
Remember that people, [snorts]
but they're they're not jealous and
they've got better lives than me. Remember that.
Uh Milton Kings. Yeah, man.
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
Yeah. Really? Yeah.
Hopefully these people stop next year. Uh Grezy No,
he's not bullying me. He's If if these
people were bullying me, I wouldn't be
keep coming back for more. I remain unbothered.
No, you don't bully me.
You bully yourselves.
No, no, no. You definitely bully
yourselves. You need to meet someone in
person to be able to bully someone. You
can't do it behind a keyboard.
Nah, bro. You bully yourselves, but you
just do it on the internet. Don't bully
me, mate. Don't bully me, mate. Nah, you
need to literally meet someone in person
to bully them. You can't bully someone
over a keyboard.
Bro, it doesn't matter about my
hairline. He can't show his face. He
owns me when he shows his face. That's
when you That's when you own Peter Belly.
Yeah, bro. So, he talks about my
hairline, but the guy's bold and he
won't show his face cuz he's ugly. He
will never show his face cuz he knows
he's the ugly one. The ugly one with no
hair. The self projector. The alltime
Yeah. He can't show his face cuz he's ugly.
Yeah. No one cares about that. That's repeating.
Yeah. He shows his face and he's ugly
and I made him go to the police on me
crying to the police. That's not someone
that owns me.
I had him running to the police
screaming he ain't a fighter. That's not
someone that owns me. But again, you
people are nom lovers. So I don't take
it personal. You know, I made him cry to
the police screaming he weren't a
fighter. That's not someone that owns Peter Belly.
screaming down with that police station
that he's not a fighter. I actually made
someone go to the police over me on YouTube
because he couldn't handle me.
No, he didn't bully me. No one's ever
bullied me, bro.
No one's ever bullied me. No, he didn't bully me.
He caught me off guard two years ago.
Get over it.
He will never ever meet me again.
So that's that. [clears throat]
Well, of course, no one's made you say
sorry, bro. You don't leave your house.
You would never meet anyone.
You'd never meet anyone. So, how would
someone make you say sorry? You'd never
meet anyone. You don't leave your house. Uh-huh.
>> Bro, just stop the cat, bro. Listen,
like I said to you yesterday, you knew
where I lived for years and no one once
come on my door. Please stop acting like
your big men on here, bro. Come on, man.
It's getting old.
I've never ever once knew where someone
lived and didn't go on their door. You
knew where I lived for years when it was
with my mom when it was without when it
was without my mom. So, just stop the cap.
You had the golden ticket, bro. You had
the golden nugget and you still done nothing,
you know, cuz you still, you know, and
you still done nothing, bro. Still done nothing. So,
Oh, mate, he's an absolute virgin. cuz I
because he's almost 31
and he still ain't lost his Valentine's card.
He stole He stole that Orington virgin.
I I like to I like to poke it in the
[ __ ] with a stick, you know, mate.
Poke it in the stick. I can't believe
he's [ __ ] still a virgin.
And he still ain't lost his Valentine's
card. He's still a virgin.
Oh, do you like the Incredible Hulk?
Do you like The Incredible Hulk?
Oh, it's already voided. I reckon it's
already voided to be honest, lad. I
think it's already voided
to be fair. Yeah, I think it's already voided.
Yeah, what a loser, man. He actually
went to the police knowing that he would
not not win in the end. Why would you
even do that when you know that you're
not going to win in the end? Just cuz
you got owned on YouTube, [ __ ] loser.
You knew you knew you weren't going to
win in the end, so what was the point of
it? It's just silly.
No, no, no.
Yeah, this poo guy is another one that's obsessed. Jesus Christ.
Wow, these people have got a lot of time
on their hands. Um, Triple H, a whole paragraph again.
This is insane, bro. This is really,
This is crazy.
This is what makes me think that you're
jealous. I I agree with you. Listen to
me. Yeah. Cuz you know, like when I've
said this before and and stuff like, and
you probably think it's a bit weird. I'm
just reading this. But this is why
people think that you're jealous because
of what they actually are doing on here.
The paragraphs, the writing, the time
that they put in this every single day
for years, and they don't seem to ever get bored.
And they don't ever seem to get bored.
It's But they're not jealous. and
they've got a better life than me.
I don't know, Greavvesy, bro. I'm
starting to have second doubts about
these people, bro. Grievy, I'm sorry.
I'm going to have to say your name on
this one, but I'm really having second
doubts cuz I don't understand, right,
how if these people have got all of this money
and stuff, why they on here writing
paragraphs from the time they wake up to
the time they go to bed? That takes a
lot of time, bro. It's a lot of time and
hate and effort for people that they don't know.
I don't know, man. I think it's jealousy, bro.
Sorry to say, bro. I really do think it is.
That is really bad, bro. You know.
Yeah. It's voided anyways. It's voided
Yeah, I think these people are jealous
of me, bro. I think they generally
generally generally generally are
because how much hate they have towards
people that they don't even know and how
much time they do the how much time they
do it every day. It's just repeating.
Look, even Skin M realize he can't look.
It's just people that don't even know you.
Yeah. That's why the police don't do
anything because they know about his channel.
Yeah, because they know about his
channel now. He's [ __ ] He [ __ ] the
whole thing up. The police have seen his
channel. Yeah, he's [ __ ]
Yeah, he's a loser, bro. He's an absolute loser.
So yeah, this is strange to be honest.
So much hate and they say they're not
jealous really, bro.
And they really really say that they're
not jealous and they've got a better
life than me.
I don't think so, Grezy. Bro, I really
really don't. After reading what these
people seeing what these people do, they
clearly have nothing. And you are the M.
Stop talking about yourself.
The only M is you. You rat looking [ __ ]
You rat looking [ __ ] ugly bastard.
The only M is you. You [ __ ] ugly
Go fix your [ __ ] rat face. Look, this
is what I mean. Like, they're coming on
here calling me a m. Yeah, I'm better
looking than them.
I'm better looking than them. And
they're still calling me a m. Jealousy.
This is what I'm saying. It is jealousy
with these people.
The only M is you. You rat looking [ __ ]
with no teeth. You [ __ ] rat looking bastard.
Ugly rat looking [ __ ] with no teeth. You
baldy bastard with your [ __ ] nons [ __ ] dad.
You [ __ ] rat looking baldy [ __ ]
virgin with a disabled girlfriend. Baldy
[ __ ] rat looking [ __ ] That's you. You
[ __ ] bastard. Baldy bastard with no
beard. Baldy rat looking [ __ ] Virgin
from Kent with no beard. You [ __ ] virgin.
You [ __ ] ratfaced looking [ __ ] who I
made go to the police on me because you
couldn't handle me. Yeah, the girls with
their boyfriends. No, they didn't.
That's not what happened. But I went to
your area and I mocked you. I went to
your area and I mocked you and I put up
posters of you.
No, I I went to your area and mocked you
and made you stop leaving your house.
Stopped you going to events.
[laughter] You stopped going to events
because of me. Because of me. I went to
your virgin shitty skin area, let
everyone know about you, put up posters
of you, and I mocked you. I made you go
to the police. Listen. Yeah. When them
people were saying that stuff, I told
them to [ __ ] off back to Newcastle. I
didn't run to the police. I didn't
scream I wasn't a fighter like you. I
didn't keep crying to the police cuz I
got my ass a whooping. So, how can you
compare that situation to your
situation? I told them to [ __ ] off. Ugly
[ __ ] in front of their girlfriend and
they didn't even stand up. You went
running to the police on me. You went to
your virgin area, virgin police station,
virgin life. Yeah, I've got all of these
messages, bro. I've got everything from
the [ __ ] rat virgin.
Yeah, I've got everything from this
little virgin. Anyways, bro.
Bro, the only one I got owned is you.
You [ __ ] skin virgin. Yeah, there you
go. That's already I've got everything
he's done anyways, bro.
>> I got everything the [ __ ] skit virgin
bedsit ridden [ __ ] has done with his fat
ugly girlfriend. [laughter]
[gasps] That's what I'm saying, bro.
One second. Trying to put nudes up again.
You're so much of a virgin that you had
to stop going to events.
Bro, the only one that got owned, bro,
is you. I didn't go running to the
police. I know I told them in front of
their girlfriend to [ __ ] off back to
Newcastle and they didn't even stand up.
You know, if you said that to a guy in
London yet or it could be anyone that's
about something. They're not stay
They're not saying stay and sat down.
I told them to [ __ ] off back to Newcastle.
[laughter] I didn't go running to the
police. The only one that got mocked is
you, you little gay boy.
You little [ __ ] gay virgin with a rat
looking [ __ ] face with your fat ugly girlfriend.
fat disabled girlfriend. [ __ ] off,
Yeah. And I've got them screenshots, by
the way. So, yeah, you shouldn't waste
the police's time, you know? Why would
you even do that, bro? Knowing the [ __ ]
that's going on in the world. People
getting robbed, people's phones getting snatched.
Why would you even do that, bro? Why? Why?
Oh, PJ son, your life is tragic. [laughter]
>> What the [ __ ]
>> He's right.
What the hell?
Did he mute himself? What?
You absolute virgin. You know what,
right? You're going to be that 31y old
virgin in February.
>> Why is your belly button sticking out,
>> bro? My forehead,
>> bro. You went running to the police. You
stopped going to events for 2 weeks.
Stop it. You You stopped going to events
for two weeks. You
happened to me. Especially not in my own area. [snorts]
You literally got bullied in your own
area. You went running to the police
and you're trying to talk about people
that I told about themselves.
>> Trail had you running over fences
because of the pierces he sent out to
your mom's area.
>> No, that definitely definitely that
never that definitely never happened.
>> No, that definitely definitely never happened.
>> No, no, no. You You stopped going to
events because of me though. You went to
the police because of me. I made you
stop going to your events that you enjoy.
>> You went running to the police going to one event.
>> You went running to the police screaming
you're not a fighter. [laughter]
>> I put the date and you got me back.
>> One event have you ever stopped me attending?
>> You You ain't got me back. Yes, I did. I
had you going to the police. Stop going
to your events for 3 weeks.
>> I went to your area.
>> I went to your area and stopped you
going to events for 3 weeks. Stick to the subject.
>> Never. That's delusional. Yes, I did.
Yes, I did. Oh, I'm not a fighter.
>> You speak a fighter because of a [ __ ]
group in pest.
>> I'm not a fighter. I'm not a fighter.
I'm not a do you remember that second
time I went to your virgin area and you
like I'm going to the police? You little
bully victim. Don't come on here with
your fat ugly girlfriend talking like
you didn't get bullied out of your area. [laughter]
>> You remember when I went to your virgin
area? That skin virgin area that you
live in, you skinned [ __ ] >> No.
I Well, kind of my town.
>> I went to that [ __ ] That was No, your
area. No, [laughter] your virgin area.
>> No, it was your virgin area. It was your
virgin area, [laughter]
>> mate. You look like a rat. Look at you.
You look like a rat. You're disabled.
>> You Yeah. At least I've never been with
a disabled girl like you. I've never
been so ugly that I've had to resort to
a disabled. I've never had to resort to
a disabled. But again, I'm not ugly like
you. I'm not ugly like you. So I've
never had to resort to a disabled.
You've never had Sig. You've never had
Morgan. You've never had Britney because
you're too ugly. You're too ugly for them. >> [ __ ]
>> You're too ugly for them kind. They
don't want a rat looking virgin. They
don't [clears throat] want a rat looking virgin.
>> I heard you.
>> Why do you think Britney didn't want
you? They don't like rat looking
virgins. They reject rat looking virgins like you.
>> They don't like rat looking skinned
virgins with no mom. They don't like
skin rat looking virgins with no bub.
You know what I'm saying, bro?
They literally don't
put a [ __ ] nude up,
please. There you go.
>> What the [ __ ]
>> Virgin boy?
What you on about? Virgin boy. >> Yeah.
>> I think he's talking to you.
>> Is that the case?
>> Murder boy. Skin in a bed sitting all
with no bed and no money in it. No life
experience. Had to date disabled girls
cuz he's too ugly to pull anything cuz
he looks like a rat.
>> He's got the face of an ugly rat. come
and slap your ass if you dare.
>> How does it make you feel that you have
to resort to a disabled girl? Woo! Cuz
you're too ugly to get anything.
>> Now look at this. Yeah. Look at this.
>> You get rejected by every
>> You're dating a disabled girl cuz you're
ugly. No woman wants an ugly [ __ ] like
you cuz you look like a rat. They see
your ugly face coming. They think,
"Who's that ugly rat?" Skin on benefits.
You got stoved by his mom and rejected by Britney.
That's what they think, mate. In
>> a more simple way, like a voice changer.
This is getting a bit irritating to
speak like this.
>> You need to get laid. You're going to be
a 31-year-old virgin. You've never had
sex in your life. How does that make you feel?
>> I had it half an hour ago. Actually,
>> your hand does not count. Your hand does
not count. So, anyways, why why do you
say if I don't find Sho attractive, I'm gay?
You didn't want to feel left out, did
you? You wanted to fit in at college, didn't you? >> Yeah.
>> Very attractive.
>> You wanted to You didn't want to You
didn't want to feel left out, did you?
>> Do you remember when we used to meet up?
>> This voice I'm putting on going quite as well.
>> Gay hobo. Do you remember when you used
to say that you wanted to look good?
>> I would be
>> the Cole thing. You didn't want you
didn't want to feel left out.
>> Yeah. Hold on. Let me concentrate on
what this voice I'm trying to do right now.
>> Great local woman.
>> He said that as well cuz he didn't want
he [clears throat] you know why he said
that? Cuz he was getting bullied for
being gay at college and he's like I'm
not gay. I like Shel Cole. I like Shel
>> [ __ ] virgin.
>> [ __ ] virgin with no mind of your own.
>> You [ __ ] skin virgin ain't got no
mind of your own. Virgin. Oh my
>> only only does itself.
>> You had brought her up to me.
>> Yes. I I I I said that people were
copying each other.
>> Yeah. Yeah. Cuz they were copying each other.
>> Can anyone tell me in the comments if
there's a voice changer option on this?
They don't need
>> We hear you. And you sound like an
absolute virgin. An absolute virgin.
>> Virgin boy. Yeah. I'm the biggest
>> Virgin boy getting in his bed with no
bed, no money in it.
>> I did so well last time as well.
>> You like that one, don't you, mate?
>> So, yeah. February, you're going to be
that 31y old virgin. I can't believe you
still ain't got laid. You're still a virgin.
>> Are you going to come to my birthday, Peter?
>> I am going to come. Yeah, I was going to
say, why didn't you lose your
Valentine's card? You skin virgin.
>> It's not strictly for my birthday. It
will be £8 entry. I know that's a bit
bit much for you.
>> No, it's all right. You can afford that.
>> I'm not the one showing daddy savings
and gets run away when I show seven
grand. We're not all skint. We're not
all skin fls like you, mate.
We're not all skint, son.
You copycat virgin. All time virgin.
You're an alltime virgin.
When are you going to lose it? When are
you going to lose it? When are you going
to lose your Valentine's card?
>> When you going to lose it? When are you
>> I don't think you'll ever get laid. I
think you'll die a virgin, mate. I've
said it for years.
I've said it for years. I've been saying
>> Me and my partner live together. Don't you know?
>> No. No. No. Virgin. No. Virgin, mate.
Same [ __ ] bed as me.
>> No. No. No. No. No. Virgin mate. No.
Virgin. Virgin. [ __ ] Virgin, mate.
Backing virgin skip virgin [ __ ] skip
virgin [ __ ] virgin [ __ ] virgin >> really
>> no but yeah you seriously need to get
laid though you don't want to die a
virgin [ __ ] hell you're end up like
[ __ ] Timmy [ __ ] hell
so why have you always been with
disabled women why can't you get
anything normal is it cuz you're too
ugly or is it cuz you you're socially awkward Good.
Come on. Come on. Tell us. Tell us.
>> Show this picture of the blonde girl
pointing and laughing at you.
>> No. No. No. Girl pointed at me, mate. I
told her about herself in front of her
boyfriend and they didn't even stand up.
No, no, no. You got owned by me, though.
You got owned by me.
Why? because he's got a disabled
girlfriend and he's not allowed anywhere
near that disabled girl and there's no
proof and there's no proof that he's had
sex with her.
>> Bro, I told them women about herself in
front of their boyfriends and they
didn't even stand up. You do realize how
stupid you're making yourself look now.
>> You do realize that? You're making
yourself look stupid. They didn't come
to my area and make me go to the police
like I did with you.
>> Okay, but um she said you stuck in hell.
Or was it her boyfriend? They don't
really have them. But her boyfriend told
you your belly button was the
>> and I and I told him that he's a [ __ ]
and [ __ ] back to Newcastle and he
didn't even stand up and I was by myself.
So I'm saying listen Lee, I've put a
porno out there. Go away you little nods
lover. Go away you little nods lover.
There's proof that I've sex with women
throughout the whole video.
>> There's literally proof that I've had
sex. There's no proof that this skint
[ __ ] has ever [ __ ] his disabled
girlfriend who he's not allowed nowhere
near sexually. [ __ ] off you little nons.
Same thing as I said to Joseph.
>> He'd been with his girlfriend for years.
He wouldn't [ __ ] their many times.
>> That sounds like barrist.
>> I don't know class a lot.
>> Yeah. No, no, no, no, no, no. I've Okay,
so if I've Okay, I've proved I've had a
[ __ ] Has he proved he's had a
>> No. He's proved he's shown himself with
a disabled girl. So [ __ ] off, you little non-slaver.
You can hear the bow job.
>> Yeah, it's definitely definitely Brest.
>> It's not Brest. >> Yeah.
>> Do you remember when you got your penis
out to B?
>> I don't. >> Yeah.
>> Do you remember when you got with a Oh,
no. You've never been with a normal girl
cuz you're too ugly. You're too
disabled. You're too much of an ugly
[ __ ] You remember when Britney rejected
your ugly ass? You had nowhere near that, girl.
Nah, the truth, don't know. The truth is
that I've proved I've had sex and he
hasn't. That's the That's the proof. No,
no, no, no, no. The truth is
never proved you've had he's had sex
with that disabled girl. So, no. I've
actually proved I've been in women's
beds and proved I've had sex. You're a
nonslover. Evidence. Don't lie, nons.
And the truth is he's a [ __ ] [ __ ]
with a disabled girl and he's never
proved he's had sex with her.
>> I put a picture of myself up a few days
ago with my girlfriend.
>> Did you prove you [ __ ] her? Did you
>> Did you prove you had sex with her?
>> No. Exactly. Just shut the [ __ ] up then.
>> Anyone could anyone can lie in the bed. Listen, >> virgin.
>> You can't have sex cuz you've got
erectile dysfunction. You've got So your
dick your little dick don't go in. your
little ugly dick don't go in. So even if
you did, even if you eventually was to
get with a normal woman, your your dick
don't work. That's why you remain a
virgin. You could be with anyone. You
could be in bed with anyone.
>> Say the one that needed,
>> but you will remain a virgin. You will
remain a virgin for the rest of your
life. It doesn't matter who you with.
>> It doesn't matter who you with because
disabled women, they don't have need.
You see, they're not they're vulnerable people.
>> They're vulnerable people. That's why
you remain your age.
>> You remained a virgin. You remain a
>> Imagine that poor prostitute has never
>> You remain a virgin. You remain
>> You remain You remain a virgin and
you're going to die a virgin. And you
didn't [ __ ] Aisha. You went nowhere near
that girl. Aisha's a Muslim. You didn't
[ __ ] her. You are a virgin. She's even
confirmed that your little virgin story
are you talking about? Your little
virgin story was made up about you
[ __ ] her. What was it again? Did you
Did you Did you [ __ ] her in a park bench?
>> Did you [ __ ] her in a park bench?
>> What was it? A park bench. Was it?
>> It was a part. You went nowhere near
that girl. You nasty virgin. Everyone
knew the virgin. Even that time.
Remember when them black guys chuck
>> your feature on here, do you know?
>> Do you remember when them black guys
chuck wool on you? They spot the virgin
off. We don't want you in our area. You
[ __ ] skinned virgin. Some skinned
ugly looking [ __ ] with a bad back
[laughter] and a [ __ ] lanky legs
walking around my area being a virgin.
Of course you're going to [ __ ] draw
attention to [ __ ] you know, draw
[ __ ] attention to people, mate.
>> You know what I mean?
And that is it, matey.
Are you [ __ ] going to talk?
You [ __ ] absolute virgin. I say it
better than anyone. Don't mate.
I I say it better than anyone, mate. Don't I?
>> You don't want what?
>> Virgin boy skin in his bed. [ __ ] with no
bed. Nobody in it.
>> Nobody. No money in it.
>> You know what? Yeah, he could he could
get you a little job. Triple H can get
What do you think of that? What do you
>> He get you a little job. What do you
What do you think of that?
>> He get you a little job. You might not
be a virgin anymore, you know. He might
get you a little job.
But yeah, no, seriously, them paragraphs are mad.
And you say that you're not jealous of
people. [ __ ] hell. You got a lot of
time in your hands, man. Tell you that.
You got a lot of time on your hands.
You show them, lads. You show them that
you've got a better life than everyone
by coming on here every day writing
paragraphs. You You show them who's
boss. You show them who's boss.
Why is the Virgin not talking?
Triple H said that if you go to the
Northeast, he'll get you a little job.
He'll get you a little job.
I don't know what you're talking about
in that video. I told them about
themselves and I told the women about
themselves and I told them to [ __ ] off
>> and no and no one stood up once. You
must be comparing it to your situation
where I owned you cuz that definitely
definitely never happened.
>> Autistic community. Autistic community
and you're not able to sleep in the same
bed as another person. You didn't even
specify which sex. [laughter]
>> But you're still a virgin cuz of your
erectile dysfunction. You even made up a
sex story saying that you [ __ ]
yourself [ __ ] flated.
>> You went nowhere near that girl. You
nasty virgin. You went nowhere near that
girl. You nasty virgin.
>> It's embarrassing.
>> Why are you saying that you had sex on a
park bench, you skin virgin? You've
never [ __ ] anything in your life.
[laughter] Do you think any woman would
go near some rat looking virgin [ __ ]
that don't even have a bed? [laughter]
Are you being serious? that anyone would
go near some lanky skinned virgin that
can't even grow a beard with ugly ugly
rat face greasy hair. Anyone would go
near an ugly [ __ ] like you.
>> We live together. We've lived together for
>> a disabled girl. Yes. A disabled girl. Four years.
>> A disabled fat girl. Yes. A disabled
girl that can't live together. >> Yes.
>> Live together for over a year. We share
the same. A disabled girl. It would be plausible.
>> A disabled girl that can't talk
now and again. Yes. A disabled girl cuz
you're too ugly to get anything normal.
That's why you go for the disableds.
You're so much of a virgin. You done it
a couple of times, you know. Yes. You're
with a fat ugly disabled girl.
>> Why did you ask me a question then carry
on speaking over me when I start speaking?
>> Because I asked you a question. Why did
you say Cheryl Cole was attractive to
fit in to fit in with a crowd and you
ain't answer me? In the way that I said
that, but the way you say I said it is
very different to how she went down. You
brought her up to me
>> and then I explained something to you.
>> Yeah. You said if I don't find her
attractive at school, you told me when
you was at school the boys would say
that she was attractive to fit in and
you put this story over to me in some
way. That was something you said to me.
>> Yeah. And you and you said if I didn't
find her attractive, I'm gay, right?
>> Thing up. You made this whole thing up
about some college I attended and said
this and that. It's not true.
>> Wait, so you didn't say that if I didn't
find her attractive, I'm gay. You didn't say that.
>> But she is attractive and I do think you're gay.
>> So if someone doesn't find her
attractive, they're gay.
>> That's not specifically what I said. I said specifically
>> copycat. No mind of your own.
>> No, copycat.
>> The only reason you're trying to The
only reason you're trying to deflect it
now is because you got caught out being a copycat.
>> I don't give a [ __ ] about Cheryl Co. I
don't even know who she is really.
>> Not you. She was saying it to fit in
because you didn't want them Scottish
lads to keep bullying you for your dress
sense at college.
>> Ah, yeah. What were their names again? These Scottish
>> Everyone I've already said their name.
You said bullied in college. Being a virgin
must have said to be a good liar.
>> Being a virgin being a virgin
their names. You had names for them.
>> I've already said their names. You know
their names. Their names again. You know
their names. You're so confident. This is true.
>> Miles and Jack. Miles and Jackie.
>> Oh, it's Miles now. Where
>> Miles and Jackie used to bully the [ __ ] out of
>> Jamie Thompson has this archive channel and he's
>> Okay, good for him. Your little gay was
what? Your little gay boyfriend. You go
on that. You
>> what? Your fat gay boyfriend. The two
[ __ ] that are obsessed with me. What?
The two [ __ ] virgins that are
obsessed with me.
>> Know something.
>> Another one of your fat boyfriends
that's obsessed with me cuz you're ugly.
>> You said originally was not Miles.
>> You You Yes, it was Miles. Yes, it was
>> Oh, Jamie Thompson. Is that your little gay boyfriend?
>> You and Red Star. Your boyfriend? What?
Your boyfriends? Your gay boyfriends. >> Scottish.
>> Your gay boyfriends. Who your gay boyfriends?
>> What? Got your gay boyfriends.
Your little Yeah, your gay boyfriends though.
[ __ ] you. Why are you so obsessed
with Peter Belly, man?
So obsessed with me.
You remember when your mom starved you
and you didn't do a damn thing about it?
You [ __ ] You let a woman starve you.
Let let a woman starve you and you're
coming on acting big. You
>> your mom starved you and put you in
hospital, you little [ __ ]
>> I've lived alone for 11 years. Well,
>> you done?
>> Actually, I got a girlfriend I lived
with. I technically lived alone where I
suppose I was about eight.
>> Yeah, but your mom starved you. She
>> Your mom starved you. Starved you
>> technically. Yeah. It's [ __ ] terrible as well,
>> Cherry. Listen, I went to your area and
The only people that's been bullied is
you. Terry, you let me come to your area
and you didn't show up. That's you, not
me. And same with your boyfriend. Same
like your boyfriend virgin.
>> It's like your boyfriend on. That's what
you both got in common. You let people
come to your area and you don't show up.
You and your boyfriend have got
something in common.
>> In by about next week, my girlfriend's
going to be with her family for
Christmas. I'm going to be around the
Tottenham area. So we could meet if you
like and we could earn the mountain top.
>> So what you Oh, you want to meet me in Tottenham?
What? Me in Tottenham?
>> No, not you. You ugly bald [ __ ]
>> Ugly? Have you seen your [ __ ] ugly
rat face? Have you seen your ugly rat
face? You ugly [ __ ] You got no teeth.
You look like a ratty stinky [ __ ]
>> You're talking about my looks. I've
never once had to go with a disabled
girl. I've never had to once go with a
disabled like you. So look at yourself
in the mirror. Look at that smelly
little rat face. That ugly body. You
skinny armed rat looking [ __ ] with a
disabled girl. Listen. Listen. Listen.
Rat face with the ugly girlfriend. Rat
face with the ugly girlfriend with no
teeth. No teeth. Rat face with the ugly
girlfriend. One second. I have never had
to resort to a disabled.
>> I've never had to resort to a disabled
girl. That says a lot about your looks.
I've been with normal women. [ __ ]
>> I've never resorted to disabled cuz I'm
not a rat m [ __ ] lanky [ __ ] like you.
How is some little [ __ ] [ __ ] in a
council mediter piss rat face ugly no
teeth with a disabled girl talk about me?
>> Not bad you rent it.
>> You [ __ ] rat looking string of piss little virgin.
>> Yeah. Look at all of the women I've been
with and look at the women you've been
with. It says a lot about your looks.
>> That tells you about your looks, not
mine. That tells you about my looks, not yours.
>> A minute or two. Like the 19year-old, right?
>> Mate, the women I've been with have
never been disabled. Yours has cuz you're ugly.
>> You're ugly. That's why you're an ugly girl.
>> And you were shouting at her while she
was on your bed.
>> You [ __ ] ugly rat rodent looking.
Can't grow a beard. Oh, and stop trying
to stop trying to grow a beard. You
can't grow a beard. You don't have it in
you. You ain't got the genetics in a
minute. You can't grow a beard. You
[ __ ] rat looking [ __ ]
>> You [ __ ] rat looking virgin. [ __ ]
off. You and your ugly girlfriend. Go
[ __ ] off. Do yourself a favor and [ __ ]
off the pair of you ugly [ __ ]
Yeah. Do yourself a favor and [ __ ] off.
Oh, we left. [ __ ] rat looking [ __ ]
with a fat ugly girlfriend. Coming to
know for more. As I was saying before
you spoke over me, look at all of the
women you've been with and look at all
of the women I've been with for an ugly
person. And I've never had to resort to
it disabled. No, you didn't get kicked.
No, you [ __ ] didn't. You [ __ ]
virgin. One second. I'll put the link
back up. No.
>> No, you did not get kicked. One second.
>> No, you [ __ ] didn't.
Come back on here, you rat looking
[ __ ] ugly [ __ ]
>> Come on, you ugly [ __ ] Let me have a
whale at the time of you. Come on. Bring
your fat ugly girlfriend. You [ __ ]
fat [ __ ] girlfriend. Come on. I want to
have a laugh at you. You didn't get
kicked. I don't kick people.
Is it true because of what I'm saying
about your rat face? You rat looking
hideous looking [ __ ]
[ __ ] stupid boss, mate.
>> You're going to kick me again, ugly.
>> You didn't get kicked. You [ __ ] virgin.
>> Well, you did. You kicked me.
>> Listen, Terry. Terry, you two do meet
for Please do meet for so I can [ __ ] you
both up. The two virgins that ran away
from me. Please do. Please do. Because
the thing is, Terry, Virgin Boy ran away
from me and you ran away from me. So
yeah, do that.
>> Yeah, Terry, I make you do
you might lose your me.
>> You might lose your me card. You might
lose your Valentine's card. You might
not be a virgin anymore. If you sort
your ugly rat face out, you get plastic
surgery, fix your [ __ ] teeth out, you
lanky stringer piss looking [ __ ] you
might get laid. And I said this to you
when I met you before.
You know, I didn't kick you. I didn't
kick you at all, mate. Yeah. Ugly and
uglier are meeting. The two uglies meeting. [laughter]
Yes, Terry. Listen. I went to your area
and you didn't come out. Take that L.
Listen, bro. [ __ ] all of the taxi [ __ ]
You know where I live. I came to your
area and you didn't come out. End of
story. Just like the Virgin didn't come out.
>> Just like the Virgin didn't come out.
>> It's called the I Hate PJ Club. Exclusive. Midway.
>> Just like the Virgin didn't come out and
I had him run into the police. You're
both alike, so you should both meet up.
>> Yeah. So, you should both meet up. The
two absolute virgin scratchers. [ __ ]
ugly. The two uglies that run away from
PJ. The two ugly club. Ugly and uglier.
>> Hairline. [laughter]
>> Yeah. I don't have a receding hairline.
That's your hairline. That's not mine.
That's you with Red Shaw. That's why you
constantly go on about it every day. The
two uglies. The ugly rat and the ugly
bing with shitty traders. [laughter]
>> The two uglies meeting up. The two
uglies meeting up. [ __ ] hell. When
are you going to sort that [ __ ] face
out? That rat looking [ __ ] No wonder
you've never had a normal girlfriend. No
wonder you're still a virgin.
>> Have you had your face?
>> My ugly face. Big news. >> What?
>> Will you picture up my ugly face? Big news.
>> M. I've already put your ugly face up
and it almost broke my screen. You ugly
[ __ ] I didn't.
>> You [ __ ] ugly [ __ ] I'd rather have a
mate. I don't even have a big nose. Your
whole face is ugly. Your whole face is ugly. [snorts]
>> Ugly face, ugly hair, ugly life, ugly
eyes, ugly girlfriend. Everything about
you is ugly. Nothing's ugly about me.
>> Every woman you've ever encountered in your life,
>> every single woman that's been normal,
>> They've all rejected you. You're not
>> Okay. Okay. Okay. Okay. Let's go over
all of these women. Right.
>> Even ones that I've been with Morgan.
I've been with multiple women that
didn't have special needs. You get with special needers.
>> You get with special needs girls.
>> Creepy in itself.
>> You get with special needs girls. The
only reason that you've only been with
special needs girls. Let's go over all
of what we've been with. You've been
with disabled Sarah, a single mom that
rejected you. Britney rejected you.
Britney rejected you. Britney rejected
you. That 19year-old.
>> Oh [ __ ]
>> The one that we heard talk. >> [ __ ]
>> Mate, is it the one that we heard
>> 19year-old? You said you had to walk her to her.
>> Is that the one that we heard talk? Bro,
you have you have been rejected so
badly. You've had to get with disabled
women cuz no normal women want you.
>> Because no normal woman wants you.
That's why you go for a disabled Sarah.
You can't [ __ ]
>> All of the women that I've met, we've
heard them talk.
>> All of the women [ __ ] in a minute,
[ __ ] All of the women we've met her
talk, we've never heard your ugly
disabled girlfriend talk. She's a [ __ ]
>> Because she's a [ __ ] We've never
heard your girlfriend talk.
>> We've never heard your girlfriend talk
cuz she's a [ __ ] and you can't get a normal woman.
>> Say all this [ __ ] in a minute. You said
you had to walk her to her carer.
>> No, that's not what happened. But we've
never heard your girlfriend talk. We've
never heard your girlfriend talk cuz
she's a [ __ ]
>> Your girlfriend's a [ __ ]
>> Do you know what she looks like? She
looks like a
>> D many times on here actually.
>> Bailey Bailey, mate, you say that I'm
ugly. I've been with normal women. You
never have. Sounds like projection to
me. Sounds like projection to me.
>> Okay. Terry wants to know why didn't you
turn up the last two times you arranged.
>> Uh the same reason why you did not turn
up and he didn't turn up when I went to
both your Virgin areas. Both when I went
to your Virgin areas and you didn't show up.
>> Yeah. When I Yeah. Yeah. Oh, I can
understand why you're bored. Listen,
Terry. I went to your virgin area and
you didn't show up. You [ __ ] ugly
[ __ ] You little [ __ ] I went to your
area and you didn't show up. Just like
this virgin. I went to both your areas
and you [ __ ] didn't show up and you
come back for more. This is what you do
on here, Terry. I went to your area and
you did not come out. Oh, I'm on
probation. I'm on probation. You're a
waste of time. You're a keyboard
warrior. I asked you earlier to come. I
would pay for your Uber to come on this
front door. You're not about it. [ __ ]
boy. Shitty trainer. You're not about
it. Stop it.
>> It's boring out there.
>> 6' free. That's not a [ __ ]
>> Yeah. And you look like a [ __ ] rat.
You lanky string of piss. Aren't you
with an ugly girl?
>> You remember that time on the bridge to work?
>> With an ugly girlfriend. With an ugly
>> I look much shorter than you.
>> You know what I'm saying, bro?
>> Listen, [ __ ] the last two times I went
to your area and you said that you was on probation.
Oh, [ __ ] hell. Do you remember when
your stepdad had you up against the
wall? Slap your face, you little [ __ ]
>> Remember when your dad died?
>> Yeah, [laughter] mate. Your your dad's
going to be dead soon, so no one cares.
Your dad's going to be dead soon. And
guess what? And here's the thing. At
least I'd rather have a dead dad than my
mom abusing me. Your mom hates you. Your
mom starve you. Your mom don't want you.
You don't even see your dad. You don't
even see your dad. Your mom hates you.
And your dad's going to be dead soon
anyways. And I'm going to laugh when
he's dead. I'm going to laugh, mate.
I've even said this as well. We're going
to throw a party raging.
>> We're going to throw a party when your
ugly [ __ ] nod is dead. The pedophile.
Get with your mom when she was 14.
Everyone's going to laugh at the pedos there.
>> Yeah. Yeah. Terry, I owned you in your
area though and you didn't come out.
I've owned both of you. Isn't it funny
that I've gone in both of your areas and
none of you will come out? None of you
will come out.
>> Listen, bro. Your mom hates you. Your
mom starved you. Your mom hates your
gut. She starved you and you done [laughter] nothing.
>> He's still alive though. Jason isn't
>> Yeah, but she doesn't want anything to
do with you.
>> Yeah. And she doesn't want nothing to do
with you. You ugly [ __ ] She starved
you. And your dad's got Parkinson's.
He's disabled. He'll be dead soon. I'd
rather be dead than be a Parkinson's
[ __ ] nons [ __ ] no life [ __ ]
Parkinson's [ __ ] disabled.
Listen, Terry, I went to your dad was an
[ __ ] He used to knock your mom and your sister.
>> No, that never happened. No, that never
happened. No, that never happened. We
know your mom starved you, though. Your
mom definitely starved you. Your mom put
you in hospital. No, I didn't live with
my dad. But my mom didn't starve me. My
mom didn't put me in hospital. My dad
wasn't a nons like yours. I don't look
like a rat. I don't date disabled girls.
I don't live in a bedit. I'm not lanky.
Like you [laughter]
>> your granddad's still alive because you
don't have anything,
>> bro. Your mom starved you.
>> Dark past. None of you speak to him
anymore. probably nons.
>> Bro, your mother starved you. This is
all projection from your childhood. Your
mother starved you. Keep the false
laughing up, bro. Keep the false
laughing. But your mother starved you.
>> Literally has a dark past. And you
>> your mother put you in hospital. Your
mother put you in hospital. This is all
self projection. Listen, your mom
starved you and put you in hospital.
Your mom hates you. Your dad used to
beat your mom about. My dad's never beat
my mom up. I wasn't starved. I wasn't
put in hospital. Maybe your dad did.
>> I wasn't put in hospital like you by
your mom. You [ __ ] virgin.
>> Your dad used to knock your mom and your
>> No, I didn't never tell you that. And if
that happened, I would never tell you
that. Your dad knocked your mom out. No,
your dad knocked your mom out. That's
why your mom dumped him. That's why your
mom dumped him and your mom starved you.
And that's why your dad used to knock
your mom about. That's why your mom
starved you. And your mom don't want
nothing to do with both of you. Your mom
doesn't want anything to do with both of
you because your dad used to beat her
about and used to gamble all of the
money in the house and had debt
collectors. He had debt collectors. He
had debt collectors coming on the door.
Your [ __ ] mom had debt collector and
she didn't want nothing to do with your
dad and your dad used to knock her about
and she starved you. Your mom starved
you because she she saw she saw your dad
in you and that's why she hated you. She
starved you. She left you on the street
at 17 and she put you in hospital. She
starved you and put you in hospital and
that's how you ended up in a in a bedit.
So don't project your [ __ ] your
[ __ ] [ __ ] old [ __ ]
gears to share then. I've been living
here 11 years. Did your
>> Yeah, bro. Your mom starved you. Your
mom put you in hospital. She left you on
the street. Bro, don't project your
shitty childhood onto me. Don't project
your [ __ ] nons [ __ ] onto me.
>> Declare your future. No, don't project
your [ __ ] Nazi dad and your shitty
childhood onto me, bro. Don't project
the fact that your mom starved you and
put you on the street. No, no, that was
definitely definitely you. Definitely
definitely definitely you. I have never been starved.
>> I have never been hit by my stepdad. I
have never been abused. That's
definitely the nods. That's definitely the allin
>> No, no. That's definitely the allin
nods. That's definitely the allin.
>> You You live with your mommy.
>> No, no, no, no. That's definitely not
best. You don't have a mom cuz your mom hates you.
>> I live with my mom, but your mom hates
you. So, you're not going to see her for
Christmas. I do live with my mom
dinner. You bought a [ __ ] curry with you and
>> I live with my mom. Your mom doesn't
love you. You live in a bedsit.
>> Yeah, Terry. Like I said, I owed you in your area.
>> Spending Christmas with my girlfriend.
>> Terry. Terry. I owned you in your area,
[ __ ] [ __ ] was shitty trainers. I
bullied you and I bullied nonsex in the area.
>> I bullied you in your areas though in your life.
>> You grasped yourself up. They putting
all this [ __ ] online and you then then
the trails got you. They grasped you up.
You ain't got you ain't got Albert Square anymore.
>> Uh I've got more money than you and
that's not what happened. Up again.
You got I've got more money than you.
Try again. Seven months or so. I've
literally got more money than you. No
matter what I had, I've got more money
than you. You skid [ __ ] You're the
one showing your daddy savings.
>> You're the one showing your daddy
savings that ain't even yours. You
>> 13. It doesn't
>> You are showing your daddy savings that
you ain't got now.
you ain't got now. You have not got that
money now. You are skintsit.
Yeah. You didn't even go abroad until
you were 30.
>> You didn't go abroad till you was 30 cuz
you were skint. That's when you copied my holiday.
>> That's when you copied my holiday. You
little skin. That's when you copied me.
My Amsterdam trip.
>> So if you go to Black,
>> you [ __ ] virgin. That's mate. Listen,
>> you go to VARIOUS PARTS OF
>> I went to Bro, I went to that means
you're copying me. That doesn't
>> I went to [ __ ] Amsterdam and the next
thing I see is some [ __ ] rat looking
skining [ __ ] in the same place as me.
What did you think it was?
>> An event and I liked it there.
>> No, no, no. The first place the first
place you went was Amsterdam. That was
the first place you went because you're
copying. You're a copycat. Just like the
Chevro call thing. I would say if
somebody is the first place you went to
Amsterdam as the first place that you
went to. That was the first place you went.
>> I I attended an event there and I liked
it. So I went
>> You literally No, no, no, no, no, no, no.
There's over 300 countries. You ended up
in Amsterdam. There's no coincidence.
>> Why aren't you going to them? No. You
[ __ ] copycat copying my holidays with
your fat ugly girlfriend. You fat ugly
you every time. Is that what you're
going to do now? Every time I go
somewhere, bring your fat ugly
girlfriend and ruin it. Your fat ugly
girlfriend with your nons ugly rat face.
>> You've never left the country with a woman.
>> I've left the country more times than
you. I've been to more places than you
and I've got more money than you. I
don't want a disabled girl. I wouldn't
go with your girlfriend if you paid me.
I wouldn't go with your ugly girlfriend
if you paid me. She's ugly and disabled.
I don't want her.
>> I don't want her.
>> I don't want an ugly girlfriend. I can
get something normal. I don't need to
resort to disabled. It's not a badge of
honor. I don't need to resort to special
needs. A disabled girl. I don't need to
do that cuz I'm not autistic like you. I
don't need to do that.
>> Okay. Okay. Yeah. But your brother
>> I don't need to resort to a disabled
girl who looks like a fat the wall. I
don't need to resort to that.
>> I don't need to resort to special needs
girls. I don't need to resort to special
needs because I'm not ugly like you. I'm
not a mon like you. I don't look like a
rat like you. I'm not skint like you. So
I don't need to resort to such things.
Only you would in your world.
>> Only you would in your little virgin
world. In your little virgin world.
>> [ __ ] madness.
>> So anyways, have you got have you got
that have you got that 13 grand now?
>> Jason's dead in his life.
>> Yeah, bro. That doesn't matter. That
wasn't even my full brother. That wasn't
even my full brother. But guess what?
You're not going to see your mommy
Christmas cuz your mama hates you. So
you can keep self-reflecting all you
like. You can keep self-reflecting all
you like. You're not seeing your mommy
Christmas cuz your mommy hates you. [laughter]
>> Your mommy hates you. You can't see your
mommy Christmas cuz see your mommy
starved you. Jesus Christ.
>> Your mommy starved you so you won't be
seeing your How does it feel that your
mom hates you?
>> How does it feel that your mom hates you
and you're going to be lonely Christmas?
How does it feel?
>> He's no [ __ ] brother at all now, is he?
>> Okay, bro. No [laughter] one cares about
half brother. Your mom starved you. Your
your dad used to beat your mom up. No
one cares what you say. All of it is
projection. At the end of the day, you
were starved by your mother. You admit
that you were starved by your mother.
Your mom chucked you out on the street.
So all of the false laughing is, mate,
it's a cover up. It's a cover up, lad.
Your mom starved you and put you out on
the street, you little [ __ ] Her stepdad
used to beat you up.
>> Her stepdad used to beat you up. So all
that false laughing and made up [ __ ] no
one cares, mate. Your stepdad used to
beat you. Your mom starved you. You're
from a broken family. This And you know
this is why you don't gain weight.
>> Your granddad's still alive.
>> Where your mom where your mom used to
starve you. That's why you can't gain
weight. Where your mom used to starve you.
>> If your grand
>> Your mom starved you and you done nothing.
>> Alive. He will be 89.
>> Your mommy starved you and you didn't do
a damn thing about it. You little [ __ ]
Your mom starved you and you done
nothing. You little [ __ ] Your mom
starved you and you done nothing because
you're a little [ __ ] died when you was 12.
>> My dad died, bro. Your mom used to Your
dad beat your mom about. Your mom hates
you and your dad,
>> bro. It doesn't matter about people
dying. People dying. Your dad's going to
be dead soon, bro. Your dad's going to
be dead soon. So what? Why? Why do you
care about people dying? At least my dad
weren't a nons. At least my my daddy
didn't beat my mom about like yours did.
That's why your mom don't want nothing
to do with you. You are your dad.
>> Yeah, that's made up. But you quite
>> That's why your mom don't want nothing
to do with you and your dad. I don't
give a [ __ ] if my dad's dead. Your dad's
going to be dead soon. Your dad's going
>> You said to me big news.
>> Your dad's going to be dead soon. Your
mom used to beat your mom about. That's
why your mom Okay. So why does your mom
not see your dad dead? Okay then. Okay
then. Why does your mom not see your dad?
>> Because they're not together anymore.
>> Because your mom used to your dad used
to beat your bub about. That's why. He
used to be a [ __ ] cokehead.
>> I'll be honest with you. If anything
like that was to have happened, it would
have been the other way around.
>> No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no,
no, no. Your dad used to beat your mom
about your dad used to beat your mom
about. That's why your mom hated you.
>> Your dad, however,
sister's about an aggressive drug addict.
>> My dad wasn't in my life. Okay. Okay.
Let me let me explain this to you. My
dad wasn't in my life. So, how's that possible?
>> Because he died.
>> Yeah. No, no, no. Before he died,
>> he left your life when you was
>> Before he died. Okay. Nothing before he
>> Before he died, he didn't bring me up.
You lived with your mom and your dad and
your dad used to beat your mom about.
>> Your dad used to beat your mom about and
your mom starved you. So all of this
false laughing that you're doing, I
wasn't starved by my mom. I wasn't put
out on the street like you, by your
mother. Your mom used to bully the [ __ ]
out of you
>> when you were 12,
>> bro. Your mom used to your mom used to
bully you. You've even admitted it that
your mom used to bully you. What are you talking about?
>> Booked. She was an aggressive drug.
>> Your mom used to bully you and she
starved you and she split up with your
mother. She split up with your mother.
>> Been hearing about her. Your dad Your
mom split up with your dad for being
abusive. Your dad used to beat her up.
That's what you used to tell me when we
met and that's why you spit up once. But however,
>> yes, you [ __ ] did. How did I know
about your mom starving you? How did I
know about your mom starving you?
>> I've I've said that on here many times.
Yeah, your mom starved you and put you
out on the street, you little [ __ ] And
you done nothing about it.
>> No, that's
>> Listen, you and the virgin will never
make me cry. Terry, listen.
>> Listen, you two bully victims. You two
bully victims will never make me cry.
You two jealous skin virgin bully
victims will never make me cry. I'm the
one that had him going to the police. I
had this [ __ ] going to the police. I had
you running out of your area when I went
to three years.
>> Listen, bro. I went you going to the
police on me. Stop it now. Terry caught
in 3 years.
>> Listen. Yeah. Yeah. I'll see you as well
with your fat ugly girlfriend with your
rat face. It ain't happening, mate. It's not happening.
>> It's not happening.
>> It will be happening. It might
>> It won't happen. You ugly rat face. The
police don't want to know about some
[ __ ] rat virgin looking [ __ ] who got
bullied on YouTube. They're not
interested [clears throat] in you
getting bullied on YouTube, mate.
>> Listen, Terry, I went to you in the
Virgin's area and I made you both run
away from me. Memory again. Memory lane
again. Memory lane. I bullied both of
you in both of your areas. Terry, if you
was a man, you would have come on my
door. You would have come on my door in
Stratford when I went to your area and I
made you hide. I went to your area and I
>> Took the rope and he killed himself. He
literally don't have a brother anymore.
>> Bro, [laughter]
you don't even have any family, bro. You
don't have any family. Your mama hates you. [laughter]
>> I don't care what you say.
>> I don't care what you say, bro. I don't
care what you say. Your mama hates you.
You got no family. You don't even speak
to your sisters. All projection from the starved kid.
>> All reject. All projection from the starvation kid.
>> Not even cat gold. [ __ ]
>> all rejection from the kid that was
starved. The kid that was starved. The
kid that was starved. Guess what, bro?
Listen. I could have 100 people die in
my family. But I was never starved. You
were starved as a kid. A starved child.
The Oliver Twist child.
>> I'm still alive.
>> Oliver Twist. She was She was She was
starved by your mom.
>> Still alive. Oliver Twist. You were
starved by your mother. Oliver Twist.
You were starved by your mother. Shut
up. You were starved by your mother.
>> Oliver Twist. You were starved by your
mom. You were starved by your mother.
Shut up. Oliver Twist. Oliver Twist.
Oliver Twist. Leave me alone.
>> Oliver Twist. Oliver Twist.
>> You She might as well be dead.
>> Oliver Twist. You were starved by your
mother. Calm down. You're having a heart
attack. Shut up. Oliver Twist. Can you
imagine this [ __ ] He was saying to his
mom, "I want some more. I want some
more. Your mom dead.
>> Your mom slapped you and starved you.
Oliver Twist. Oliver Twist. You got
starved by your mother. You got starved
>> 94 years old.
>> You got starved by your mother. Shush.
You little [ __ ] You got starved by a
woman and you done nothing about it. You
little [ __ ] ass virgin. Shut up. Oliver
Twist. That's going to be your new
That's going to be your new name. Oliver
Twist. Mommy, I want some food. I want
some food. Mommy, I want some food. I
want [laughter] some food. Daddy. Daddy.
Mommy. I want some food.
>> And then he
>> Mommy, I want some food.
>> Mommy, I want some food. I'm starving.
I'm starving. I'm starving. Mommy.
Mommy. She said, "Fuck off. You're not
getting no food. You virgin [ __ ]
Chucked you out of the street. Mommy, I
want some food. I want some food.
[ __ ] virgin. Your mom starved you.
Put you in hospital and starved you. You
little [ __ ] [ __ ] starve the [ __ ] out
of you. Yeah, Terry, I owned both of you
in both of your areas, though. I owned
you both in real life. Terry, I went to
your area and I made you [ __ ] yourself.
I went to your area and owned you, [ __ ]
house. Oh, I'm on probation. I'm on
probation. I'm on probation.
I'm on probation. I'm on probation. I'm
on probation, you little [ __ ] house. You
little [ __ ] [ __ ] How do you think LT
knows about what you are now? You
[ __ ] little [ __ ] [ __ ] When you was
trying to [ __ ] email people, oh, I'm
about this. Oh, I'm not the one LT. I'm
not the one LT, you [ __ ] little [ __ ]
house. I went to your little shitty area
in North London. Oh, I'm on probation.
You [ __ ] [ __ ] house. And then you're
coming on here [ __ ] emailing people
like you're some [ __ ] kind of big [ __ ] man.
>> You know what I'm saying? Did he hang himself from?
>> At least you at least you at least you
Yeah. No, you know you know what though?
At least At least you actually at least
you actually left your house unlike
Terry. You know that. Hey, listen.
Nonsense. You know what I will say about
you, right? At least you actually left
your house running around in circles,
running to the police when I pulled up,
when I rocked up cuz you couldn't handle
me. Oh, I'm going to the police. I'm not
a fighter. I'm not a fighter. I'M NOT A
FIGHTER. PLEASE. PLEASE. I'm not a
fighter. [laughter] I'm not a fighter.
>> Do you remember that?
>> Oh, Jason.
>> I heard you going to the police. You
couldn't handle me. I'm too much to handle.
>> Bro, I don't know why you're talking
about my half brother. I met him once. I
don't give a [ __ ]
>> because [laughter] he's your half
>> bro. I don't give a [ __ ] about him. I
met him once. Your mom starved you. Your
mom abused you. This is all self projection.
>> Bro, this is all self-p projection.
You're going to be alone on Christmas.
You're going to have no mother on
Christmas. Your mother hates my dad.
>> I don't give a [ __ ] that. Bro, I don't
give a [ __ ] about a half brother who
I've met once.
>> You don't speak to your sister and you
don't speak to your mother cuz you got
no family. You've got no family. And
guess what? Let me tell you something, right?
>> What's that about? Here's the thing.
Here's the thing. There is some people
for my You know what? Go on. Listen.
>> Can I Yeah, there were some people that
died in my family, but I still have more
family than you. Oliver Twist. I've
still got more family than Oliver Twisting.
>> Mommy hates you. Mommy starved you,
Oliver Twist. I've got family that died.
And I've still got more family than you, Oliver Twist.
You come from a broken family. You come
from a broken family, Oliver Twist. No
sister, no mother. No sister, no mother.
How is it possible? How the [ __ ] is it
possible that I've got people that's
died in my family and I've still got
more family than you, Oliver Twist? That
says something about your Nazi family,
doesn't it? That says something about
your Nazi family that I've still got
more family than you. Yet they two of
them died. But I'm not I've got more
family than the nons and then the
virgin. The one that don't see his mom
because your mom don't want nothing to
do with you.
>> Oliver Twist Oliver Twist.
>> I've got two members of my family that
died and I still got more family than
you. You little Oliver Twist shitty
little virgin who got starved by his mama.
>> Hearing about my mom. My man told me
about her. Lord,
>> your mom doesn't want nothing to do with
you. Your mother starved you and left
you on the street. She left you on the
street and you had to go to the council
to get put in your shitty little bedsit.
>> Not quite. My mom put
>> Yes, it was that actually.
>> You was put in that bedit. That shitty
little virgin bed
>> in that shitty little virgin bedsit
where no action has ever happened.
>> Where no action has ever happened.
>> So here you might learn something here. Big nose.
>> I don't have a big nose, but you've got
a rat face. You look like a rat. Oh, say
>> I don't have a big nose, but you look
like a rat. You look like an ugly rat.
>> Say all that after I'm done speaking or
you won't hear what I'm saying.
>> Okay, rat face.
>> Yeah, I was actually fifth in position
for where I live. By the way, I was
never supposed to get this place.
>> But um see Oh [ __ ] So the person that
lived here before me killed himself.
>> Bobby, I want some more food. I want
some more food. I twist want some more
I want some more food. Mommy, I want
some more food. I want some more food.
>> Shut the [ __ ] up, you skin. No one cares
what you got to say.
>> No one cares. Skin virgin. [ __ ] off and
go get laid. I want some more. Please
sir. Please. I want some more. Mommy.
Mommy. I want some more food. I'm
starving. I'm starving.
>> What I'm saying?
>> I'm starving. Mommy, I want some food.
I'M STARVING. SHUT THE [ __ ] UP.
Leave me alone. Mommy, I want some food.
Shut the [ __ ] up, you [ __ ] little
[ __ ] You got starved. You little
Oliver Twist [ __ ] with no mom. [ __ ]
off. [ __ ] off, you virgin [ __ ] Go get
laid. Go sort your [ __ ] ugly rat face
out. No wonder you can only get disabled women.
>> Sounds like an exorcism is happening. Jesus Christ.
>> I was just talking about your [ __ ]
childhood. You're [ __ ] And and wasn't
your dad 47 when she he met your mom? [ __ ] 12.
>> [ __ ] met your [ __ ] mom at 12.
[ __ ] not. No wonder. No wonder. No
wonder you think it's okay.
>> Believe that.
>> No wonder. No wonder. No wonder you
think getting with a 16y old is all right.
>> Yeah. Yeah. Hold on. So, one second. You
say she was 14, but now she was 12. Mickey.
>> No, I always said she was 12. I always
said she was 12. I always said she was
>> No wonder you think it's okay to get
with [ __ ] 16y olds. No wonder it's
okay to get with 16y olds.
>> Oh, but I don't like teenagers anymore. [ __ ]
>> No, but you did used to say about 16,
but I, you know, I always used
>> I was younger. Yeah.
>> Yeah, but I said 18 and above.
>> That's cuz you like to be strange. I
mean, younger as well.
>> 18 and above.
>> Be different.
>> 18 and 18. Yeah, of course. Of course I
like to be different. I don't copy
people's holidays. I don't say she calls
attractive bitten. Yeah, I don't copy. I
don't copy you. I'm not a copycat.
>> Not one thing I done in Amsterdam was the same.
>> You literally went to Amsterdam because
I went to Amsterdam.
virgin. You [ __ ] ugly skin rat
virgin. Oliver Twist went to Amsterdam
cuz I did.
>> I didn't expect to see some [ __ ] rat
looking ugly [ __ ] copy my holiday.
>> Does that mean [ __ ] ugly skin copying me?
>> No, no, no. It's because it's the first
place that you think of it you've not
been to. You mean if you go to
Blackpool, it means you're copying me.
>> No. Okay. Do you want me to Are you
going to let me answer? Are you going to
>> Random one. So, if you go to real North
Wales, that means you're copying me. Does it?
>> Okay. Do you want me to answer the
Blackpool one? I can answer you. I can
answer you if you want me to. Okay. So,
if I go to Blackpool now,
>> you don't let me answer any.
>> I mean, if I if I if I go to Blackpool
now, I mean, it's one of the only places
I've not been. The first place you went
was Amsterdam because I went. The first
place you went was Amsterdam because
where I went. So, no. If I was to go to
Blackpool tomorrow, that's one of the
only places I've not been to.
>> The first place you went to was
Amsterdam because you're a little
copycat with no you own that. Oh, meow
meow. Copycat. What's the next thing you
got to copy? You little copycat. You
little copycat. YOU LITTLE COPYCAT. It
could have been France. It could have
been Belgium. It could have been
Germany. It could have been [ __ ]
Poland. No. No. It had to be Amsterdam
because I went there. It had to be
[ __ ] Amsterdam because I went there.
You [ __ ] burdened copycat, punk you.
Could have been Paris. No. Could have
been Scotland. Nope. Could have been
Belgium. It had to be Amsterdam. It
couldn't even be Rotterdam, Dusty. It
could No, Rotterdam is not good enough.
It had to be Amsterdam.
It had to be Amsterdam that he went to.
He had It had to be Amsterdam because
you're nothing but a virgin copycat.
You're nothing but a little virgin
copycat. All right, Terry. Listen, lad.
Yeah, honestly. Listen, Terry. You and
the virgin meet and I'll both smash your
[ __ ] faces in. Right. I'll both smash
your faces in. Terry, terrible trainers.
You and your little nons boyfriend meet
up together. Bro, you're not going to
meet anyone. You couldn't even meet LT.
Yeah. Terry, the runaway man. The
runaway man. Do you know what you both
got in common? You're both nons and you
both run away from people. You done the
same thing with LT. You won't meet
anyone, Terry. The little [ __ ] house.
The [ __ ] little [ __ ] house. The size
of you and you're still coming on here
acting like you're big. Have you seen
the size of you? You ain't gone on
anyone's door despite knowing where
people live. Have you seen the [ __ ]
size of you? Coming on here piping up,
you silly [ __ ] [ __ ] off, mate. [ __ ]
off. You're a [ __ ] house. [ __ ] off,
you [ __ ] [ __ ] house. [ __ ] [ __ ]
Anyways, why don't you meet Why don't
you meet up? You and the skin virgin,
bro. Listen, I can [ __ ] Yeah, that's
that's London Turby, bro. I can have
two, three, four family members die. You
I've still got more family than you,
Oliver Twist. I've still got more family
than you will ever Oliver Twist. You
don't see your mother. You don't see
[ __ ] Shut the [ __ ] up, you little
nonslover. We saw me go to Terry's area
and he didn't show up. Listen, no one
cares about you little biased
nonslubbers. End the conversation.
Simple. [ __ ] off. Bias nonsubers. [ __ ]
off. Simple. End the story.
End the story now. We're not getting
into this again. So yeah, if you want to
meet him, I'll meet both of you. [ __ ]
off. Little nons lovers. [ __ ] idiot.
Bye nons lovers. Anyways, I'm banning
these people now. Anyways, oh [ __ ] >> [snorts]
>> Yeah, see you later, [ __ ] This is
what happens every time I come on here,
Jay. Willow lad, I know you're unbiased.
I know you go on laws and stuff, bro.
But this is what happens every time I
come on here. I've got all of these
people that are obsessed with me every
day. But they're not jealous. Remember,
they've got a better life than me.
They've got more money than me. But
yeah. Yeah. But they're not jealous.
Remember that, bro. They just spend all
their life every day doing this. But
they're not jealous. Remember, they're
definitely not jealous.
Just remember that they're not jealous.
Jealous is one thing that they're not these people.
Seems hard to believe, right? But yeah,
sad bastards. I think the amount of
people that's obsessed with Peter Belly
now is insane.
It's worse than Timmy. These people are
obsessed with me worse than they are
with Timmy. with her.
I would say I get it worse. Well, you've
got a funny way of showing you're not
jealous. Coming on here every day,
writing paragraphs, stalking. You've got
a funny way of showing that you're not
jealous, mate. You've got a funny way of
showing that you're not jealous of
someone. That you come on here every day
for years and you will not leave someone
alone. You've got a very, very funny way
of showing you're not jealous. And that
is that is somebody that's completely unbiased.
All I'm saying is you've got a funny way
of showing that you're not jealous of someone
coming on here every day, year on year,
year in, year out, not getting bored. I
don't know, bro. You got a funny way of
showing it, but it don't really bother me anyways.
Cuz I'm thinking in my head now, yeah,
you come across this dude on the
internet that you don't like. or not
that you don't like that that you're
better than so you know that someone's
this to that. So would you get on with
your life because your life is better or
would you spend all day every day not
leaving someone alone?
Think about it. Think about it. You're
better than someone, right? You're not
skinn. You're not ugly. This person is
all of these things that you're saying.
Okay. So for you to sit on here every
day doing what you're doing,
it's only acts of a jealous person. Um,
but I think I'm trying to explain this
to people that are are so disabled that
they don't even understand what I'm
saying. To be honest, my mom knows it.
My mom and everyone else will face
straight jealousy. What these people do
on here every day. It is definitely
jealousy because why people with such
perfect lives would sit on here every
day doing what they do when their lives
are better than yours doesn't add up to anything.
It is definitely definitely jealousy.
Definitely definitely jealousy with
these people. 100%. It's definitely
jealousy with these people, especially
around this time of year. And I'll own
it. And I will [ __ ] own it, bro.
Definitely definitely jealousy for
people to sit there all day recording
someone and stalking someone. It's
definitely definitely jealousy. 100%.
These [ __ ] you can't get rid of
these [ __ ] These harassing obsessed
[ __ ] You can't get rid of them.
You can't [ __ ] get rid of him because
you're self-p projecting and it's
biasness and it's repeating and it's boring.
I definitely I'm not going to be on here
tomorrow. Definitely not going to be on
there tomorrow. 100%. I swear to God in
my mom's life, I'm not going to be on here tomorrow.
Bro, you don't offer to meet anyone. You
know where people live. Stop the cap. If
you was going to meet anyone, you would
have went on someone's door. Stop it.
You're making me lose brain cells.
[ __ ] disabled community, bro. I swear
to God. This is such a disabled
community. I'm losing brain cells again.
Right. I'm definitely not on here tomorrow.
Definitely definitely not on here
tomorrow. The biasness, the jealousy,
the autism. Oh, no. We need at least one
day break from these [ __ ] weirdos on here, bro. >> Yeah.
Oh, you're giving me You're giving me
brain damage again, bro.
You know why you get brain damage? Yeah.
Because they're constantly bringing the
same [ __ ] up because they ain't got
anything else. So when you when you're
arguing with them
Yeah. Yeah. I've already been over the
Terry thing. We're not responding to
that anyways. See, and this is what
makes me think that you're jealous
because of what you do. I'm sitting here
and I'm explaining to you why I think
you're jealous, right? Because of what
you do. Harassing won't leave people
alone, who's probably younger or better
looking than you. It is only acts of
jealous people. And no matter how many
times I explain it, you still don't seem
to understand it. You are jealous. My
mom will say you're jealous of me. Even
other people, you are jealous. No people
with lives come on here doing what you
do every day. End of story. And I'm not
repeating myself anymore. And I won't be
on here tomorrow either. So
autism. Proper proper autism on this
community, bro. Autism.
It's straight autism on this community, bro. Straight.
Jesus Christ. Give it a break, lad. Anyway,
I need to download this thing again.
It's the same [ __ ] with you people every
day, ain't it, lad? I don't know, bro.
Not tomorrow. I need to rest my brain cells.
These people are make giving me brain
damage again, bro.
Well, I'm ignoring this person as well
now. I see what they're trying to do.
It's not going to work.
Yeah, maybe. I don't know, bro. But
definitely not tomorrow cuz I need Yeah,
they've gave me brain damage.
[ __ ] hell. Oh, I need some paracetam more.
Hopefully next year will be different. Fingers crossed.
Fingers crossed it will be different next year.
Yeah, fingers crossed, lad. Yeah,
fingers crossed next year will be
different. They actually give you brain
damage because they're bringing up the
same [ __ ] and you're answering the same
[ __ ] and you're you're actually getting
brain damage because of it. Yeah.
Yeah. They're just low lives on here.
Same people, same atmosphere.
Same PE. It's the same atmosphere.
Yeah. Okay, bro. Whatever you say.
Half one in the morning, bro.
See, I don't think Monty gets the thing
because he doesn't he can't read the
comments, isn't it?
Oh, one second. The Virgin wants to come back in. One sec. Yeah. Hello.
>> You're going to kick me again?
>> Any any any job? Any job, mate? You got
a job? You got a job? You got a job? Yeah,
>> you're going to kick me again.
>> Have you Have you got Have you got a
job? Have you got a job? You got a job?
You got a job? You got a job, mate? You
got a job? No one's kicking you, you
virgin. You're the one that keeps
leaving. No one's kicking you. I didn't
kick you once, you [ __ ] virgin.
Anyways, when are you going to get
yourself a little job? cuz you know
Triple H he he owns a company and he and
he's willing to take you on.
How comes you've never had a little job?
He left again. Look, he keeps leaving
and saying that I'm kicking him when
Triple H swear my mom's life I'm not kicking him.
I just want to know why he's not getting
a little job. Why he's not working. One second.
I don't want to talk to you, Rice. I
want to talk to the virgin.
No, I want to talk to the virgin man. Hello.
>> There's your boy.
>> Yeah, that's a picture of me when I was
15. So what? Yes. What?
That was me when I was 15, by the way.
Why are you putting pictures up with me
at 15? You [ __ ] virgin. I'm not
letting rice on, man.
Use another one.
Virgin boy. Let let there rise up.
Yeah, he's not even talking.
Not even talking, bro. [ __ ] sake.
Oh, I want him on. Hello.
So good has got a little job for you.
Oh, trying to porn bomb me, you sad bastard.
>> You need to get yourself a little job.
Yeah, you're the wildest in life.
Should we put our cameras on and and and
see who's better looking?
>> Do you want to do that? Virgin boy. Mhm. [ __ ] virgin.
You're trying to pawn bomb me. [ __ ] virgin.
[ __ ] virgin trying to pawn bomb me.
What a virgin.
You're mentally obsessed with me, you
[ __ ] virgin. You know, I don't even
care, bro. Even if it gets reported, I
don't give a [ __ ] I don't really care
to be honest. Stop me going live in it.
[ __ ] [ __ ] virgin. Huh?
Freddy's? What the [ __ ] are you talking about? Freddy's
I don't know who that is.
I don't know who the [ __ ] that is, bro.
Anyways, I'm going here.