Yo, so uh I wasn't going to go live
today because some of us have actually
got a life. Um unlike Smokey B, but I
just read your post, but I'm not going
out anyways. Bro, I'll be in all day
Saturday, mate. So, you're more than
welcome to come on my front door and you
see exactly what's going to happen and
we'll get your I quote wife to record
it, bro. Not a problem at all. Um you're
more than welcome to come here on
Saturday. Um just shows you ain't got a
life if you really do. But I love it to
I would love you to though. I would love
you to. Um because I will happily just
slap the [ __ ] out of you in front of
this whole neighborhood. So I'll be in
Saturday anyways. All day. I'll be in
all day Saturday. So no, it's not
welcome back. No, no, no, no, no, no.
Listen, it's not welcome back. I'm
replying to the Smokeoky B because you
don't know saying that he's going to
come on someone's front door. Otherwise,
I wouldn't be on here, right? So yeah,
you're more than welcome to come here
Saturday, mate. You are more than
welcome. and I will slap the [ __ ]
[ __ ] out of you in front of everyone. Do
not let us down because everybody wants
to see this. You posted it now, right?
I'll be in all day Saturday. Um I will
not be going out. So yeah, no excuse.
And we'll see. We'll see who will not be
going back to their area, mate. It will
be you. Yeah, because at the end of the
day, Yeah. I wasn't going to go live.
Yeah, but you know, just to respond to
you, man. I will I will be here all day
Saturday. And I'm also I can't wait as
well because when I shove that camera in
your face and I show everybody what the
likes of you people look like that do
this, I'll be happy. So, you're doing me
a favor, bro. I will be one happy bunny.
Yeah. And that's it. I'll be one happy
bunny because I will show what the likes
of you self-reflected [ __ ] lives
actually look like. So, you're more than
welcome. You can have a cup of tea um
after we're done as well. Yeah, please
do, bro. Please do come on Saturday. And
guess what? When this [ __ ] does not turn
up on Saturday, no one's going to say
anything. Yeah. Listen. Yeah. So, that's
all I'm saying in response. After you
come or you don't come, whatever, I am
doing content on this channel and I'm
disabling the likes and I'm disabling
the comments. Yeah, that's what I'm
going to do. It's what I said yesterday.
I'm going to be going to new places. I'm
going to disable the comments and I'm
going to disable the likes. That's what
I'm going to do. I'm not responding to
any of you self-reflecting people
anymore that ain't got no life, got no
family. Not interested. Right. But since
you said that you're going to come on
people's doors, that's I'm happy about
that. I'll be in all day Saturday, mate.
So I'll be really, really, really,
really happy about that. Yeah. So yeah,
stick to your [ __ ] word. Um I'll be
in all day, so you can come anytime. So
anyways, um yeah, and then after that,
I'll just be I won't even be going live.
I'll just be doing videos, disabling the
likes, disabling the comments. And in
the videos, you're going to see maybe
not one, maybe after three, maybe after
four videos, you know, you're going to
see that you really don't know about
anyone's life. So, you're just going to
sit there and watch and not be able to
comment or like or hate, dislike. That's
what I'm going to do with these little
clowns now. Yeah. After this, this is
what I'm going to do with this little clown.
So, that's that.
Yeah. We're not talking about that.
That's repeating. Anyways, just stick to
your word anyways, bro. that you're
going to come on Saturday.
Yeah, because I'm not entertaining this
self-reflecting [ __ ] anymore.
And let me tell you something, bro. If
you're not fat and ugly, I'll be very,
very, very surprised. I'll be very, very
surprised. Very, very, very, very
surprised if you're not fat and ugly.
So, yeah, just stick to your word, man.
yeah, that's fine. Like you're not going
to you're not going to start coming on
people's doors, bro. This ain't Milton
Kings. Yeah, like I said, I will see you
on Saturday. I will see you on Saturday,
bro. Yeah, you're not going to beat me.
You're a [ __ ] little wimpy [ __ ]
fat, ugly, jealous little loser. Yeah.
So, make sure you you know you actually
do come on Saturday. So, like you said,
you did. Like you said, you're going and
bring your boyfriend with you. Bring
nonsleings with you. I'll slap both of
you up. So, you know, that's it. You know,
and it just shows as well, you know,
when you get your ass whooped on
Saturday as well. It's going to show how
you really ain't got no life. This would
really show you that you really have got
no life. It's a good thing. It is a good
thing. And I want you to come. I want to
whoop your ass and show everyone what
you look like. But it also goes to show
that you do actually have no life
because bro, you said that you got a
wife, you got a job. Yeah. You live out
of London. And you're telling me that
you're going to come on my door. Bro,
try it. Cuz I'm here all day Saturday.
I'm here all day Saturday, mate. I don't
know what my mom's doing, but I'm here
all day Saturday. And trust me, you are
not going on anyone's door and going
back to your area. Yeah. You are not
going back to your door and going on
anyone's area. Going back to your area. Yeah. Simple.
I promise you that. I promise you that.
I I promise you that is not happening. So, yeah.
So, that's that. No, it's not. Welcome
back, Triple H. I only went live because
of this [ __ ] I only went live because
of this Smokey B saying about how he's
going to come on my door on Saturday. I
wasn't going to come back. I wasn't
going to come back. I'm doing videos.
I'm doing videos. If this guy comes on
my door, he's getting his head smashed
in. Simple. If he comes on my door, he's
getting his head smashed in. Trust me,
bro. It's happening. Yeah. So, that's
that's that's what's happening. But
yeah, that's the reason why I've gone
live. Bro, listen. I've already told you
what I want to do. I'm going to be doing
content videos and I'm going to disable
the likes and I'm going to disable the comments.
Yeah, that's what I'm going to do after
I'm finished with this little mug on
Saturday. That's what I'm going to do.
This guy even thinks he's coming on
anyone's door, bro. He's going to see
what's going to happen. Yeah. And it
ain't got to be nice. It ain't going to
be nice. Yeah.
And it also shows he ain't got no life
anyways. It really shows that this guy
really ain't got no life. Just like most
of the people on here.
So that's that's that.
Ow. [ __ ] hell, bro. So yeah, I'll see
you on Saturday anyways, [ __ ] Yeah, man. So, yeah.
Where's Greg? Anyways, I need to tell
him what I [ __ ] I need to tell him
what I ate yesterday, bro. This guy,
he's going to get his ass whipped. He
doesn't understand. He really, really doesn't understand, you know.
But yeah, it really does show you that
you ain't got no life. But I'm glad
you're doing it. Don't think I'm I I
want you to come. I'm not scared. I'm
not scared of anyone on this community,
but it does show you ain't got a life,
you know? It really does show you ain't
got a life. And you're going to get your
ass whipped as well.
So, it's a [ __ ] madness, bro. Yeah.
I'm waiting for [ __ ] Grey to come on
here, then I'll tell him.
He does not understand that this is like
3 years later, bro. 3 years later, you know.
Yeah, I ate yesterday. Yeah, I don't
care what he says. He's a
self-reflector. All I'm interested in is
this Smokeoky B coming on the front door
and then I'm moving on. I'm doing videos
and content. I don't care about any of
these people, bro.
Um, so I don't care what stories they
make up. So yeah, I had a McDonald's
yesterday and I had an Indian today. I
had a McDonald's at 4 in the morning and
I had an Indian today.
No one cares about these self-reflecting
comments. So yeah.
So that's that, bro. I don't care about
these little self-reflectors anymore.
We're going back to the [ __ ] We're
going back to the old Peter Belly days,
the traveling, the hotels. We're going
back to them days, bro. We don't care
about these people, you know?
But I hope this guy really does come on
the door and he actually shows that you
know he he is actually about something
because then because then but then what
when he doesn't come but if he doesn't
come if he doesn't come then everyone's
not going to say anything. So you're
going to see the biasess if he doesn't come
and even if he does come to be honest.
Well, no. I think if when I when I do
the [ __ ] in, everyone will will say
something. But if he doesn't come, like
say he doesn't come, no one's going to
say anything because they're biased. So,
you're going to see that as well.
So, yeah, bro.
But yeah, then I'm done, bro. I don't
care about these little self-reflectors
anymore. Like, I'm not entertaining
them. They're the ones that are
obsessed. They're the ones that are
jealous. So, that's that. I don't need
to respond to them. I don't just give
them any of my time, bro.
You know, so they do what they do every
day. We know why they do what they do.
We don't need to keep going over what they do.
Yeah. Okay. Triple H, whatever. You will
see on Saturday, won't you?
You will see on Saturday, won't you?
Simple. Simple as that. You will see on
Saturday if it if it happens. I was
gone, but apparently just Smokeoky B is
trying to say how he's going to come on
my door on Saturday. So, I'm responding
to him. You're more than welcome to
come. I'm not going out Saturday.
So, if you really want to if you really
want to call my bluff, bro, you're going
to get yourself seriously hurt cuz I'm
going to be here all day Saturday. I
don't know what the [ __ ] my mom's doing.
She might not even be here, but I will I
will be here. And then after I'm done
with you, I'm back to the old I'm back
to the old school videos cuz I'm not
doing this anymore, bro.
I'm not doing this [ __ ] anymore,
you know. I'm not Well, the guy is
saying that he's coming on my door, so
obviously I'm going to be reacting
because he's saying that he's coming on
my door. I don't care about all of the
other things, skin, this. That's just self projecting,
right? That's just self projecting. I
don't give a [ __ ] about any of that
other stuff. I'm back to traveling
videos once I'm done with this guy. I'm
I'm back with um I'm back with content videos. So,
I'm about to I'm I'm still going to be
on here doing videos. I'm just disabling
the likes and the comments,
you know. So, that's that. Oh, I had a
burger yesterday, Greavesy, from
McDonald's at 4 in the morning.
Well, obviously I saw what he wrote in
it because I saw what he wrote. What?
What do you mean? How do I know? Because
I saw what he wrote. I'm [ __ ] sub to
him. What do you mean, how did I see it?
I don't care anyways. If he comes on
Saturday, he's going to know what time
it is. Simple as that. You know, so
anyways, we'll see you on Saturday. Simple.
No, I haven't been on. I saw what he
wrote because I'm subscribed to him. Yeah, simple.
So, anyways, I'll be um I'll be Yeah,
that's it. And then I'm done. No more
live streams. I'm not leaving YouTube.
No, I'm not doing I'm not I'm not
leaving YouTube. I'm not leaving
I'm doing content videos. You know,
I'm doing content videos um from uh next week anyways. So, yeah.
Yeah, I I'm not leaving YouTube, bro.
I'm creating content on this channel.
I'm not leaving YouTube. Greavves, I've
got a nice little video coming up for
you. I can't deprive you of content, you
poor [ __ ] You know, you you you know,
you've been around for a while.
Sorry. No, I will still be on YouTube.
I will still be on YouTube, Dad.
Yeah, he can bring his wife all he
wants. I don't give a [ __ ]
You're going to be seeing some content
and then when you watch these content
videos, you'll maybe think to yourself,
"Oh, [ __ ] I actually don't know what
people have. I actually don't know how
much money people have." That's what
you're going to be saying over time over
about three videos, which is all going
to be put in the space of, you know, a
month, you know. So, you're not you
don't really know what people have, do
you? So, that's what I'm going to do.
I'm not reacting to these clowns anymore
because when they keep doing this, it
shows what their lives are,
you know? It shows what their lives are.
Yeah. So, we'll see if this clown comes
on Saturday and that's it. And if he
does, he's getting he's getting himself hurt. Simple.
You're going to come here and knock some
sense into me. Do you really think
that's happening? My behavior quite
recently has been erratic,
hasn't it, Grezy? That is definitely
definitely definitely definitely not
happening. So, yeah, you can kiss
goodbye to that, but I know exactly what
will be happening to you. So, yeah,
simple as that.
See, I feel better today. Still got the
same amount of money. Yeah, I feel better today.
Don't feel annoyed today like I did.
I've calmed down now. But yep, nothing's
happened. Ain't want money. Ain't got
any more money. Wasn't money. Told you
it's nothing to do with money. Nothing
I don't give a [ __ ] about money.
But yeah, Greg, there's going to be some content anyways.
I took meds.
It's cuz I went out last week,
so I won't be out this week anyway. So,
he can come anytime he wants to. And
I'll be here cuz I'm not going out on
Saturday. And I'm not changing my mind either. So,
don't take meds. Don't need meds. So yeah,
there was this woman on Instagram saying that, "Oh,
oh, sorry, Grezy." She was like, "Oh,
uh, yeah, I've been seeing this guy for
a month and now he's turned out to be a
dickhead." We've heard it all before,
Grezy. We've heard it all before.
We've heard it all before. We've seen it
all before, lad. That's all I said. That's it.
That's all I have to say. We've heard it
all before. We've seen it all before.
Oh, [ __ ] All I had to say.
No, just say a Grizzly. That's it.
And then one commented saying, "Oh, they
don't act like that at the start." Yeah,
of course. Yeah, if that was the case
you would be getting with most men that
are nice to your face, come on, stop it
now. It's not believable. Anyways, um
yeah, that's it. What I have to say really?
Nope. I was all good.
It's Wednesday now and I'll be good on
Saturday if I Well, I'm not going to go
out. So, yeah. Nope. As long as I stay
away from women, I'm fine.
No mood swings, no nothing. Nah.
I had a McDonald's at 4 in the morning.
and greasy. And I went to my little
nesticles. I woke up fine.
I couldn't hold it anymore. I was trying
to stop eating, but I couldn't hold it
anymore. Greavves. I was getting
headaches from the lack of lack of coke.
I generally think if they stopped
Coca-Cola, I don't think I could live
without Coca-Cola, bro. I generally
don't think I could live without it. I
can't, bro. I seriously can't.
Starting getting headaches from the lack
of Coke, bro. I can't live without cola, bro. Nah,
I don't think I I generally don't think I could.
I could probably live without beef or
lamb or I've probably got more chance of
being able to live without meat than
live without coke.
I'm a Coca-Cola head. So,
yeah, it's bad cuz if without meat I
couldn't be vegan. I could be
vegetarian. You just have pizza. Pizza.
Pasta. Yeah, you could be a vegetarian,
but not vegan. Not vegan. Cuz vegan
means you can't even have milk. Don't
know how people are vegan. But
vegetarian isn't that hard. You just
have pizzas with cheese and tomato, pasta,
you know. I could I'd rather have that
than not have Coke.
I can cut down on it. Obviously, you can
cut down. I can cut down on it, but I
don't feel I could completely not have it.
Yeah. So, that's that. So, yeah. No mood swings today.
No, it was fine.
It really does show you that it is
women, doesn't it? Yep.
It really, really does show you that, doesn't it?
Well, we know what we need to do. Still
can't get over it, Joseph. How I've not
found anyone. How I still live a sexless
life. But we I don't think we'll ever
know, do will we? I don't think we will
ever know. It's just one of them things, you know.
You know, it's so bad that you can just
laugh at it. It's just It's so sad that
we can just laugh at it now.
There was this guy on Reddit. He says
he's 35. He's never been on a date. Madness.
I'm joining the porn. I'm signing up for
the porn industry tomorrow. Defo when I
wake up. I'm actually doing it for real this time.
I'm not even joking. I am actually doing
it for real this time. The past few
times I said I'd sign up. I didn't. But
this time I'm definitely definitely
doing it because bro, we can't go around
in [ __ ] circles. This is not good.
What the [ __ ] So, yeah.
So, I'm definitely definitely signing up
tomorrow. I need to watch a film and
then when I wake up, I'll do it cuz this
is it's just not this is not normal.
This is not normal, bro.
I'm all right today and that, but I'm
just it's just it's not normal. It isn't
Oh, I found out that this woman, right,
who I met last Saturday, she's a single mom.
So, think about it, Greavves. Even
people that are single moms now are like this.
I don't care that someone's a single
mom, to be honest.
I think I would still I don't know, but you know. Yeah.
Yeah, my sister found out the scan of
the baby today. It's a girl. Unlucky.
She wanted a boy. So now she will have
two girls. This is how people Joe end up
having [ __ ] seven sisters. I know a
guy that that's got seven sisters cuz
obviously they obviously wanted a girl
and they kept trying and trying and trying. Unlucky.
So you got two girls now. So you you're
[ __ ] now cuz you wanted a boy a boy
and obviously you can't get rid of the baby.
Just some people are prone to having
boys and some people are prone to having girls.
Yeah, it's one of them things, isn't it?
Sad though, is it? That's how people end
up having seven sisters.
Just random though, is it? It's either a
boy or a girl. It's one of one of the two.
Only if I had a child myself or I was in
my 30s. If I had a child myself or if I
was in my 30s. Yeah. But if it was just
sex, I would. If you're talking about
sex, Yeah. If you're talking about a relationship, you know,
I don't want a boy. She wanted a boy.
I I didn't want a boy. She wanted a boy.
She always wanted a boy. She's got a
girl and she's having another one and
it's another girl. My other sister's got
um boys, though.
You got one girl, two boys.
Unlucky. You got two girls. I don't want a boy.
I don't I don't care what the [ __ ] it
is. Um that's what she wanted, you know?
I I think I think it is cool having
children in this day and age.
I was looking on I was on Reddit. Yeah.
And these people saying, "Oh, I've got
300 pound up to live on. I can't even
top up my gas." That is grim. That That
is That is what you call poverty. That
is bad, bro. But that's not even funny.
I don't I just think it's a cruel world
to bring kids up in. Even if you got
money, even if you I just think it's cruel
cuz obviously you you can't get sex,
cost of living, distress society. It's
not why would you bring a child in in this?
But yeah, they wanted they wanted a boy,
so it was a girl. So yeah, sad.
That is definitely what you call
poverty. That is definitely definitely
what you call poverty. Well, let me tell
you something, Joseph. I can go out and
do whatever I want now.
But yeah, I would get with a single mom
if it was just sex, a relationship. Not
unless I was in my 30s or I had a child.
Well, I had a child myself. And I think
that's the right way. I think that's the
right way to be honest.
If you're in your 30s, I think it's
different, you know, than in your 20s as well. Yeah.
But yeah, I can do whatever I want right now.
I can do whatever I want right now. Can
eat whatever food I want right now. So
when you do these little things, Joe, I
just laugh at you cuz you don't know
what I have. You don't know what I can
do. So when you do these posts, I just
laugh at it now because you don't know
how much I have. And I'm going to start
be doing video. I'm going to start doing
videos later as well at late at later
stage. So like I don't really care. You
can say what you want. You can think
what you want. You don't know me. So at
the end of the day, that's that. Sir,
look, how you seem to think having 1,200
lb disposable money is poverty is is mad to me.
That is You don't know what poverty is
if it hit you in the in the face. You
really really don't.
Cuz poverty to me is somebody that has
£50 in their name. Somebody that can't
eat. somebody that can't eat or someone that's struggling.
And if you're not, then you're not
you're not living under poverty.
That's the way I see it.
There's a difference between being comfortable, moderate,
okay, and literally poverty.
How can having say how can having,200
pound of your own money be poverty? That
just does not make sense.
That does not make no sense, bro.
Really? Really? That doesn't make sense.
Well, yeah, that is poverty.
Well, yeah. Well, yeah, of course it is.
What the [ __ ] But having,200 of your
own money is not poverty. That's just like
moderate, is it? It's a moderate amount.
It's a moderate amount of money.
But like I said, when I start traveling again and uh
going to these hotels, you can tell me
who lives under poverty, can't you? When
you see these videos that I'm doing
again, you can you can tell me that I'm
living under poverty, lad.
No, thank you. And I'm nowhere near 30.
And my mom doesn't look after me. I buy
my own food. I pay my own bill. So,
so yeah, when I'm when I'm doing these
videos again, you can try and tell me
that I'm living under poverty, that I'm
living under poverty. And the thing is,
Joseph lives in one of the most cheapest
areas. And this is London. This is this
is London, bro. And he lives up north
and he's trying to say what, £1,200
a month up north is poverty.
Disposable money. That's poverty. No. No
way. No [ __ ] way.
you know, no, no, no, no, no, no, no
way. Even Even in London, you're not
going to starve on that amount of money.
So, I I don't
that just doesn't make sense.
That just doesn't make sense.
And London's the most expensive place, you know.
Well, it's very easy LR11 if someone's
got 1300 disposable money. It's very
easy. Very very very easy.
Yeah, very easy.
No, I I do understand that. No, no, no,
no. I I do understand that. I live in
London. I know exactly how much rent is.
You don't understand that everyone's got
everyone is in different circumstances.
Yeah, I know. You don't understand that
everyone's and Joe doesn't understand
that everyone is in different circumstances.
Hence why you're saying I'm living in
poverty when I'm not okay. Whatever.
You know what I'm saying? It's a
madness. Anyways, we're not talking
about my life anyways. [ __ ] all of this
[ __ ] At the end of the day, £1,300
disposable money is not poverty. I know
it and you know it. So, we're not
talking about this.
[ __ ] hell, bro.
That's the end of that.
No, because I'm not talking about I
don't care about it, bro. I've said what
I'm about to say. We're just going
around and around in circles. It's not
an argument. It's not an argument. I get
money I get and I can live off it. What?
End the story. What What is this whole
thing about? There's no argument to be had,
you know? Just focus on your own life.
Don't worry about what other people get.
What's the argument?
Stop obsessing over other people's lives
and what other people get. Don't worry
about that, bro. Worry about your own
life. you know, like most people do.
It's [ __ ] It's not even an argument.
It's just ridiculous. It's the same
conversation. It's the same argument.
You know, don't worry about what other
people have. Worry about your own life.
Don't worry about me. You know, if I die
tomorrow, it's not going to affect you, is it?
Yeah. Well, good for me, then, isn't it?
That's That's not your concern, is it?
Well, that's not your concern, is it? you know,
don't worry about that, bro. That's my
life, not your life, isn't it?
So, yeah. Don't know how that concerns
you, but okay, whatever. You know,
bro, you need to think about your own life.
Yeah, you need to think about your own
life. Don't worry about me. You don't
need to worry about me. I'm sweet. I can
do what I want when I want. You don't
You don't need to worry about me.
You know, well, I don't have more than
two bills, so I can live off it. Is that
Is that the end of it? Is that the end
of the argument? You know,
you people are seriously obsessed with
other people's lives on here. It's
insane. Really, really, really insane.
You're obsessed with what other people have.
Why do you care? Why do you not worry
about your own life?
Why don't you worry about your own life?
Oh, okay. Again, worry about your own
life. If you worried about your own life
and you stopped obsessing over other
people's lives, you wouldn't find it
embarrassing, would you? Yeah.
Jesus Christ. We're not going to keep
self-reflecting on my life anyways. I'm
done talking about this.
Like this channel is going to be used
for content. Yeah. It's going to be used
Whatever I put up on this channel in the
future, not about my money, not about
what I get when I get it. It's not going
to be about that. You don't need to
worry about that.
[ __ ] It's ridiculous, bro. It's ridiculous. Seriously.
Yeah. Good for you, man. So, yeah.
Can't stop [ __ ] flicking my nails,
bro. It's addicted as [ __ ] Nope.
No more talking about bad experiences.
Yeah, they're like, well, I'll go live
maybe once a month or something, but
yeah, it would just be content videos, I think. Yeah,
there's no point talking about bad
experiences because people just dismiss them. Yeah. Okay.
Whatever. I'm not going to even reply to
that self-reflecting um comment. Yeah.
I'm going to ignore you now. Anyways, on
to your channel. So, yeah. People just
dismiss your struggles and it doesn't
matter. Anyways, so yeah,
that's that is it.
Yeah. Anyways, we're going to not reply
to the self-reflector. Now, there's
another thing that's uh changing uh on
this channel as well is responding to
these absolute idiots.
This is going to stop happening.
Yeah, a lot of uh energy gets burnt. A
lot of time gets burnt on these idiots. Uh anyways, moving on.
And the only reason I mentioned that
Smokey B is cuz uh he said that he's
coming on the door. So all the like nons
all of them people self-reflecting,
they're going to show themselves up.
They're going to when they do this,
they're going to show themselves up for
what they are. So we we'll come back
like every month and and laugh at them
embarrassing themselves whilst we're living life.
So we can go on their channels after
month and laugh at them for embarrassing
themselves on YouTube. Joe F nonsle,
we'll go on it every month. Yeah, we can
all laugh at it together. Yeah.
Yeah, we'll laugh at it together. Simple. So yeah.
Nah, he's not, bro. He's dodgy.
Nah, he's not. He's a He's a One second,
bro. He's a undercover hater.
No, he's an undercover hater, bro. He's
an undercover hater.
That's what he is. He's an undercover hater.
Yeah. Yeah. He's an undercover hater.
Oh, I was watching Timmy earlier, bro.
Yeah, I was watching Timmy earlier. Yeah, man.
This content is going to be lush. It's
going to be [ __ ] lash.
It's going to be better than [ __ ] Joe
F content. It's all gambling's content.
That's all it [ __ ] is is gambling.
Gambling content, bro. Yeah.
Stop asking stupid questions.
Yeah. Stop asking stupid questions, bro.
That's to you, Triple H. No one knows
anything about me, what I have, how much
money I have right now. So, bear in mind
that when these videos come up. So,
that's not possible.
And bear in mind, you're going to get a
lot of these people make up stuff to try
to get people to explain themselves. It ain't happening. Yep. So, yeah. Yeah. Anyways,
yeah, people say a lot of things, Dusty. They're idiots.
They're [ __ ] idiots on here.
Triple H. No one knows how much money I
have, which is another thing you're
going to be you're going to be noticing
with these videos as well.
You're going to I'm going to stay in a
Plaza hotel again, bro. I'll be staying
in a Plaza Hotel,
Lush, with a nice bubble bath.
So, they're going to be on here making
up rumors and I'm just going to be posting videos.
So, and they can't comment and like them.
So, yeah, that's what I'm that's what
I'm going to be doing. Change the
content a little bit.
And we can see who the obsessed ones are
with no life.
Yeah. Every month we'll come back and
see who are the obsessed ones with no life. Yeah.
That's that. We can all look at it together.
No, you can't. I don't want to take away.
Well, the most I have paid was 170.
That's the most I've ever paid. That was in leads.
Trying to think if I paid anymore. No. 170. Yeah,
that was leads. So,
the most I'd spend now.
I don't know. It depends what day it is. Saturday, maybe.
I don't know cuz I always used to go on
a Friday cuz it was cheaper. But yeah, I don't know.
I don't know. Like I feel like if you if
you stay in a good hotel hotel, yeah,
you want to stay for like two days. I
don't feel I don't see the point in
staying one night in like a good hotel.
In a good hotel. I feel like two days
cuz it's always going to be a bit
cheaper in it if you go for two days.
When I was in Manchester for two days.
No, I'm not going back to Leads. I don't like it.
Yeah, two days. But I don't I don't know.
Yeah, I was going to get the Grinch
thing. Um, Grezy,
but yeah, didn't. So
it was in Manchester, Nottingham.
There's been loads of them.
Yeah. Yeah. And they said what the woman
was saying, Greaves, is that, "Oh, then
they're they're always nice to begin
with." But that's not true because if
that was the case, then like I said, I'd
be getting dates all the time. So,
they're making excuses for themselves.
They know the kind of guy that they go for.
So, they're just a they're just lying.
They're just a lying, lad.
They just talk [ __ ]
No, I haven't got the socks yet.
I might get a McDonald's, you know,
because it's not good enough.
Cuz it's not good enough.
I shouldn't be 28 without a sex life.
I shouldn't be, but I am. So that's the
end of that is it? It's not good enough,
bro. Yeah. Okay. I've had six one night
stands. Yeah. Out of how many
approaches, how much money have I spent?
It's not good enough, bro. It's not good enough.
So, I've got a I've got a right to complain.
It's disgusting, bro. It really is vile.
And the [ __ ] that you have to put up
with is vile.
So, and yeah, I shouldn't be 28
having to go out again and try. That's
my whole argument.
Yeah. Yeah. But, but Triple But the the
thing is Triple H is that I've met more
women than you. I've approached more
because I haven't worked. So, what I'm
saying is I shouldn't have to go out
again trying. That's what I'm saying.
You haven't tried nowhere near as much
as I have. and that it's not a
competition. It's facts. It's not about
who's you know what I'm saying.
So there is really no reason for it.
And there's been nothing recently.
There's been nothing since April. So
you've got a you know you've you've
you've got a good right to complain.
Have you been up and down the country
approach approaching thousands of women?
No. So why would it bother you if you
don't have a sex life?
I should have a sex life. There's no
reason why I don't have a sex life.
That there is literally no reason. So,
but there we are. So, that's what it is, isn't it?
You don't understand what I'm trying to
say. I think Gregy understands it. There
is there is no reason for it.
I should have people now. It doesn't
matter what they look like. They could
look like anything.
It could be anyone. Could be anyone. But
you don't even have anyone. Do you not
think that's a bit [ __ ] up?
You should have to try again, bro. You know. Yeah.
Bro, I tried an unhealthy amount of
times. I've tried more than anyone in
the world. It's not even You never
believe me when I say it, but trust me,
it's the truth. I should be getting a
date like twice a month. You should be
getting dates. You should be getting dates regular.
You should be uh
fine dining uh because I didn't. But
there's going to be some good content on
this channel soon. You won't be able to comment.
But yeah, I I should be getting two
dates a month. Yeah.
Yeah. Any anyways, bro, no one cares
about your self-reflecting comments.
Yeah, I do get a pro. Well,
sometimes, but I'm just going to go down
the industry method. I think that's the
best that's the best thing.
Would you would you be a porn star? Yeah.
They think a lot of things, Dusty. They
think a lot of things.
They talk a lot of [ __ ] That's what
they do on here. Um, yeah. Yeah.
But it's not about that. It's about now.
What we What are we going to do now?
You know what are we going to do now,
bro? You know, this is the thing. This
is the thing that you got to think of.
It's not normal, bro. It really isn't normal.
You should be able to go out, right?
Get a number and get a date. Even if the
date doesn't go anywhere, it they're not
always going to go anywhere.
You know, you should be able to just go
out and get some of it for your effort.
Just like if you was to go out and work,
you'd get money. If you was to go out
and work, right, you'd get money. If you
was to go out and do uh sacrifices,
if you was to do sacrifices, you'd get
something out of it. This is this is the
[ __ ] I don't understand, bro.
No, I don't have any plans. Christmas.
Yeah. Again, no one cares about
yourself. reflecting comments.
You can be saying all of that when you
see these videos, can't you?
No one cares about people
that lives are over trying to bring
other people down. No one cares about that.
I was pissed off for my own reasons the
past couple of days. So, yeah.
Yeah. Nothing to do with money, bro.
Nothing to do with money.
But these people will always continue to self-reflect. So,
that's their life, ain't it, man? That's
their life. They'll be doing it for
eight years. Next year is not going to
be any different. So, let them crack on.
[ __ ] eight years next year, you know. Eight years. [ __ ] hell. Hey,
you're going to go on the live stream on
the 1 of January. They're going to be
talking the same [ __ ]
Yeah, I'm not overweight, but okay, whatever.
they're going to be on the 1st of
January repeating the same [ __ ]
Oh, [ __ ] me, bro. That's funny, Grezy.
self-reflecting the same old. They're
going to be doing it the first of January.
Yeah, that's self-reflecting. Peter
Betty is not overweight. Definitely. Definitely not.
So, anyways, like serious, what are you
going to do on the phone? Are you
actually going to get a life
or you just going to keep
self-reflecting like another year in
doing this [ __ ] you know?
You just got to keep doing this
cuz it is quite sad. Oh man.
To be a porn star.
Yeah. To be a porn star.
Same sad people. Same same sad [ __ ]
people as well.
Nah. Monty said that they'll still be
doing it when they're dead.
Nah, Monty said even when they're dead.
Why you asking stupid questions? Imagine that. Triple.
How big is your [ __ ] [ __ ] what a weirdo, man.
That is a weirdo, bro. What the [ __ ]
Why are you asking that question?
But you worry about that.
Yeah, you're weird, bro. Why are you
even the [ __ ] ask something like that?
No, that's my bro.
But yeah, that's that. Anyways, now even
when they're dead, they'll still be doing it.
They'll be doing it in the coffin
repeating. How do they do it? These
people have got to be like robots. So,
what do you think to your brains? You
reckon they wake up at like 7 in the morning?
Because how can they be doing it for
years? like typing the same [ __ ] Are
they even people behind like these accounts? Triple
they can't do you think they
What do you think?
Cuz how do they just It's like you know
when Timmy's live they're there within a
second. Pipple. They're there straight
away. They're there straight away.
Yeah, they are. They ain't got life.
Yeah, they ain't got a life.
Well, listen, Triple. It's the same
people doing the same [ __ ] Do you
remember when Monty man said that? Same
people doing the same [ __ ] Yeah, bro.
No, I wasn't. I'm I wasn't on there today.
I'm talking about other times I've been on there. Dude, dude.
Yeah. Skin. I can't. I just said skin in
it. Yeah. These people repeat themselves every day.
No, not today. But um I have seen it before. Yeah.
That's funny, bro. No.
Nope. I've been sleeping all day. Laney
Laney owns these people. You know that
nonsex? You see how he was making fun
out of dead people uh uh yesterday?
Oh, bro. You know what's so funny, bro?
He's got the biggest mouth for someone
that's such a little [ __ ]
You know that? He's got such a big mouth
for someone that's a little crybaby to
the police. A little [ __ ]
He's got the biggest mouth on here for
someone that's a little [ __ ] in real
life. He's the He's the biggest [ __ ]
house. Yeah. That you'll ever ever come
across in your life. The biggest [ __ ]
house and somebody with the biggest
mouth. You You'll know that as well, bro.
Yeah, but in real life But in real life, lad.
But in real life, you wouldn't even look
at someone funny. [ __ ] virgin.
That nonsleg should come with um
Smokeoky B. I'll [ __ ] them both up. I'll
[ __ ] them both up, bro.
Yeah, I'll [ __ ] them both up, mate. Not a problem.
Yeah, you'll see what happens if he
comes here Saturday, won't you? I will
make an example.
Yeah, he's going to hurt me. That's not
happening, bro. Someone like that can't
hurt me. Yeah. Well, we'll see on
Saturday, won't we? I'll be here all
day. So, definitely won't be hurting me.
Definitely. Definitely. I'm going to
give him a wedgie.
Definitely definitely not going to be
hurting me, mate.
Yeah. Yeah. Well, we'll see, won't we?
This guy really doesn't want to come,
bro. He really doesn't want to come, man.
He really, really doesn't want to come, bro.
He's going to really get embarrassed.
Really, really get embarrassed, bro.
No, no, no. Seriously, bro. He really
doesn't want to.
He might He might want to think twice.
Oh, is it Why is Timmy deleted all these videos again?
But now, you know, hey, Triple H, you
know, if he doesn't show up yet, you
know, no one's going to say anything, is
it? No one's going to say anything.
No one's No one's going to say nothing.
They're just going to all move on.
Nope. My anxiety is not going to be
creeping in. I'm not scared of anybody.
Wasn't scared of the bouncer. Wasn't
scared of them two people. Nope.
Definitely definitely definitely definitely not.
Maybe him, but not me. I ain't got
anxiety. Definitely definitely
definitely not me.
But anyways, when this [ __ ] doesn't show
up, everyone's not going to say
anything. That's how biased they are,
bro. It's not going to happen.
Yeah. Someone is not going to come on my
front door and teach me a lesson. That
is not going to happen. Yeah.
That is not going to happen, bro.
Simple. So, yeah.
Yeah, of course they That's what they
like on here, bro. That's what they like on here.
Anyways, we'll see you on Saturday.
it's not going to happen.
It's not going to [ __ ] happen, bro. So, yeah.
And I know what to I'm going to t I know
what to title the video as well. Yeah.
You know, this is all because these
people have got no family. You do
realize this, Trip Rates? This is all
because these people are jealous that
I've got a family. You do realize that?
This is all jealousy. You know, all of
this is all jealousy. And he's going to
get himself seriously hurt. Seriously,
seriously hurt, bro. Like, mark my
words. He is going to get seriously hurt.
Like, mark my words on my mom's life.
He's going to get himself seriously hurt, bro.
seriously seriously injured. It's not
even a joke.
This is all because these people have
got no family over Christmas. It's
really sad to be honest, bro. You know, so
it's all jealousy with these people, bro. 100%.
Definitely is. And like I said, it's just uh
you know, I hope for I hope for his sake
that he's winding me up, bro. cuz he is
really going to get hurt
and he's and his and his [ __ ] wife is
going to be wanting a divor a divorce after this.
But I'm I'm hoping for his sake that he
is trying [ __ ] cuz he is going to get hurt. Trust me. So Oh [ __ ]
Yeah, of course they will, bro. Of
course they will do that. Of course they
will do that, bro. Joseph does the same
thing though. Triple. He does the same thing.
Joseph does the same thing, bro.
Yeah, Joseph does the same thing, lad. What?
No, I will fight anyone that comes on
this front door.
But yeah, this is all because you've
basically you're better looking and you
got more family than them. It's
pathetic, man. It really really really
really really is pathetic.
I actually feel bad, you know. I
actually really really do feel bad.
But Triple H, Joseph does the same thing.
Joseph does the same thing as what
you're saying. You do realize that he
made excuses for the bouncer.
Uh he made excuses for
uh them two people that was sat down. Um
bro, he's dismissed a lot of stuff.
Yeah. Anyways, we're going to see what
happens on Saturday. Yeah, [ __ ] sake.
this is madness. All cuz you're younger
and better looking than them. Madness.
Really, really sad, you know. Yeah.
We're not talking about that. That's
repeating. I've already explained all of this.
Yeah, I've already explained all of this
LJ thing. We're not explaining it again.
All you need to worry about is what's
going to happen to your boyfriend if he
comes on Saturday.
Anyways, Triple H. Uh, yeah, Joseph does
that [ __ ] He does the same [ __ ]
This is why I started calling him an
lover. He does exactly the same [ __ ] you know.
He does exactly um the same [ __ ]
brother. Trust me, it is not happening. Yeah,
trust me, it is not happening. This guy
is not coming anywhere near this front
door. You're not to worry about that.
Yeah, it is not happening.
Simple. So, anyways,
yeah, Joseph does the same thing. He
does do it, Joseph. So he does does He
does do it. Triple H.
He does do it.
He does it with the bouncer. He done it
with the bouncer thing. Um
he done it with the bouncer thing. He
done it with the two people sat down. Uh
he's dismissed all the times I've gone
to meet people. He does do it, bro. He
does do it. Doesn't he do it? Grievy.
Greavvesy will tell you.
Greavvesy doesn't doesn't Isn't Joseph
biased when it comes to fights and stuff
and stuff? Is Isn't he biased? Isn't he
biased? Is Isn't he biased?
No, he definitely definitely is.
Yeah, you know, he definitely definitely
definitely definitely is.
Um, okay. So,
I'll give you a few examples. When he
straight away to defend nonslegs when I
call him a virgin, but he doesn't say
anything about him calling me a virgin.
When I stuck it on that bouncer and he
was trying to say that the bouncer
couldn't do anything because he was at
work. Yet, we know bouncers beat people
up and start on people all the time. Um
he's not brought up um he's not brought
up the time where I went to Mark
Samson's area and all these other
things, you know. No, he's definitely
definitely definitely biased. He's an undercover hater.
He's just like these people, but he's just undercover.
And I'm not even saying that, bro. To
like Yeah. Defo. Yeah, man. So yeah. So yeah,
anyways, I'm not talking about this
until he actually comes on Saturday.
When he actually comes, you will know
what time it is. We're not talking We're
not even talking about about this. But
yeah, no, he's Yeah, Grezy, he
definitely definitely is biased.
I think he's another one that's secretly
jealous like a lot of these people on here, bro.
No. Yeah, definitely.
Yeah, definitely. Definitely.
He's definitely biased.
The only one that's uh really
not biased is like LT.
He will say it how it is and other people. So yeah. Yeah, bro.
So yeah, bro.
So yeah, he definitely is biased. He Yeah, definitely.
You could literally beat someone in a
fight fair and square, right? And
humiliate them and they would say nothing,
right? That's how biased they are. It's
like LT, right? If LT done what Prime
done, do you know what they would say?
They'd be like, "Yeah, but you didn't
hit them." They're biased, bro. That's
why they're not worth the time. They're
not even worth entertaining, arguing.
They're not worth it, bro. These people,
these fat, ugly losers are not worth it.
Do you get what I'm saying, bro? They're
not worth it.
They're definitely definitely not worth it, bro.
They are definitely biased on it. Definitely biased.
I wouldn't get scared anyways. He
doesn't scare me. No one in this
community scares me.
Yeah. Well, he wouldn't scare me anyways
cuz I'm not scared of anyone. So, yeah,
he is going to get himself really hurt, bro.
he is going to get himself really really hurt.
But I do hope he is widen he's widened
the community up because what's going to
happen is he's going to get himself
seriously embarrassed, seriously hurt
and it's going to show everyone what he
actually really is
in different ways. So I mean there's no
way he's going to win.
Like there is no possible way of him winning.
It will take less of an L if he doesn't
come. He'll take less of an L
cuz he's going to take multiple L's if
he comes. Trust me. And that is a
promise. That is a promise. So yeah.
Oh, that's so funny, bro.
Anyways, we're going to see on Saturday.
We're not going to talk about this until
this [ __ ] actually pulls up because it's
all [ __ ] until he actually pulls up.
We've heard this multiple times. I'm
going to go on your door. I'm going to
go on your door. And plenty of people
haven't. So, we we'll see on Saturday if
this guy actually pulls up. So, yeah,
just multiple people have done this
before, bro. Oh, I'm going to cover your
door. I'm going to cover your door. I'm
going to cover your door. And
you know, a lot of people have said it
and they haven't. So,
but he pulls up. We'll see what happens soon.
Simple as that. So, yeah.
But yeah, people in here definitely they
definitely ain't got no family, bro.
Doing what they're doing over December.
Definitely. Definitely. Definitely.
Yeah. A few people have. Yeah. But most
of the people that said they were didn't.
Well, a few people. Yeah, three people. So, yeah. Yeah, man.
I'm going to make a cup of [ __ ] in a
minute. Is that all right with you, Grezy?
You remember when I went to Nottingham
and I got a [ __ ] Dusty? I was
thinking about that earlier and I can't
even remember what happened.
I don't even think I lasted that long.
We was kissing and I was touching her
and we couldn't [ __ ] because she was on
her period. So, she gave me a [ __ ]
Still got the video, not of the actual
[ __ ] but that was lovely. Lovely
I didn't pay for it. It's somebody that
I met when I was with Ant-Man.
Do you remember that time when I was in
Nottingham and I went home on a Monday?
I was supposed to go back on the sat on
the Sunday. We went Saturday and I come
back on a Monday cuz I stayed another night.
This was ages. This was not last April.
The April before that
was it. I think it was the same month I
met my mama.
Maybe same. Yeah. Same. Yeah. My mama greasy.
That's when I was trying to find a new
mama. Uh, Dusty.
Yeah, I think that's when I met my mama,
Dusty, when I was trying to find a new one.
She's that cute, Dusty.
You used to like the content.
Yeah, she gave me a [ __ ] but I can't
even remember it. back.
I was telling her about USA the whole time, Dusty.
Yeah, I was telling her about USA the whole time.
Come to think of it, I actually [ __ ] a
lot of opportunities up, bro. I actually
[ __ ] a lot of opportunities up
back two years ago. If you actually
think about two years ago, I actually
[ __ ] a lot of [ __ ] up, bro.
Really? I I [ __ ] did, bro.
I'm recording it. Yeah, we'll see if he
Just wait until he comes, bro.
My whole life is a big mess up. Nah, my
life's fine, to be honest. Nah.
It could be worse.
Yeah, I know. I'm I'm doing the content
videos again, Joker. Don't worry. I'll
be doing it again soon. The content videos.
Don't worry, bro. I'll be doing it again soon.
My life's My life's not a [ __ ] at all. So yeah,
I went back to the uni room and she done
my lipstick. Paul,
she done my little lipstick. She done my makeup.
Well, yeah. Well, I was depressed
yesterday. I'm not depressed today.
Also, your life can be fine and you can
still be depressed. You could be a
billionaire and be depressed. I mean
what what what what what relevance that
has there's millions and billionaires
and billionaires that's killed himself
with perfect lives. So you know
yeah she done my makeup.
You could be a billionaire and be
depressed. You could have a perfect life
and kill yourself. Look at all these celebrities. So
yeah, but I bet you my life is better than yours.
I mean, I actually go out. I actually
socialize. You don't.
So I guarantee you, as [ __ ] as my life
is, I guarantee you it's better than
yours, bro. I would even go as far as
saying lany's got a better life than you.
I'd even say Lan's got a better life
than you. Elaine, a 60 [ __ ] sixy old woman.
I'd say Lany's probably get got a better
life than a lot of you people on here.
And that's an old woman. So yeah,
I've got no friends. That's self projecting again.
Uh that's self projecting. What did we
tell you about self-projecting?
So yeah, a 66 year old woman has got a
better life than you. For [ __ ] sake, I
don't even need to talk about myself,
bro. You this Yeah. 66y old woman's got
a better life than you.
Well, if she's got if she's got a a
better sex life than me, then she
definitely has got a better sex life
than you cuz you're still a virgin. So,
bro, if she's got a better sex life than
me, then she's definitely got a better
sex life than you.
No, no, I haven't. No, we're not talking
about that self-p projecting landlord
[ __ ] again. That's self projecting and
you don't know how much money I have.
We're not getting into that again. Moving on.
Right. You said that you wanted a
different episode. So, we're going to
have a different episode and we're going
to we're not going to keep repeating.
So, nothing to do with money. I've got
money. We're not self-reflecting on to me again. So yeah.
So anyways, moving on. So what you were saying was Yeah.
We're not self-reflected onto me, bro.
No, we're not. No, we're not.
Actually, it actually got worse when I
come back to this house. Joker, if you
wanted to know, and that wasn't because
of the money. I just preferred living
there. So, yeah, it was actually because
of that, but not because of the money.
I've still got money. I have money. I've
been having money the past [ __ ]
couple of months.
I just preferred it there. Simple as
that. So what?
My mental health was better when I was
in that house.
Uh 14 Maxwell,
are you new to my channel, lad?
No, it's not cuz it's with my mom. I
just don't like this area.
I used to come here on the weekends to
chill out. I don't I just don't like the
area. Nothing to do with the money.
One second. One second. Uh 14 Maxwell,
uh are you new to the channel, lad?
Cuz I just read your comment, lad. And
you said, "Get out into pubs and bars
and you'll get a girl lying on YouTube.
You'll definitely not find someone."
That's what you just said right
now. You must be new to my channel then.
Uh I've been approaching for about 6 years.
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. I was out last week. I
was out before that. And trust me, going
out definitely definitely you're not
going to meet anyone, which is why I'm
signing up to the porn industry.
I'm I'm signing up to the to the porn
industry tomorrow when I wake up. Bro,
the only thing that's going to happen
when you go out is I'm not interested. I
have a boyfriend. They give you attitude
or they give you their number and they
lead you on.
That's literally all that will ever happen.
So, I mean, a smart person will
literally just [ __ ] do one of these
three things to end it. You know,
there's only one or three things that's
going to end this
this problem that you got. So, that's that.
Like, yeah, I could go out Saturday, but
it would be it would be the same old. So
why why do you think it's going to be
different the next time you I mean
you've got to get someone's number
and you know not have someone lead you on.
It's not going to happen. It's not
happening in this country bro.
It's it's really really not.
So why why if you if you've been
watching me for a while why are you
saying stuff like that?
I don't understand why you're saying
stuff like that. It's never going to change.
And the sooner you accept that, the better.
You know, you the sooner you accept that
and you choose one of these three
options, the better. You know,
if you keep thinking you're going to
meet someone, you're going to be annoyed
forever because you're never going to
meet anyone. You you you having this
hope is going to drive you mad because
there is consequently no hope you know
why are you hating bro porn industry
when you have a small todd suffer from
no that's definitely not me bro why are
you people so like hateful and jealous
over people that you don't know like you
can actually sense the hate in that comment
that is why would you even write
something like that?
I go back to my original statement. I
think a lot of these people on here,
bro, are just fat, ugly people and their
lives are over
and they come on here and try to bring
other people down. I generally think
that is what what it is
generally. I think it is what it is with
these people on here
trying to bring other people down. Why
would you even say something like that, you know?
Jesus Christ. That's very negative,
isn't it? That's very negative, ain't
it, Grezy? She'd be happy for someone,
you know. Jesus Christ.
Oh, by the way, my mom and sister's
going to disown me if I join the porn
industry. But again, I've got to think
of myself. Really, I've got to think of
I can't be thinking about other people.
I need to think what's best for me. You
know what I mean, Grezy?
You know, cuz at that point, there's no
point of having a willie if you can't use it.
There's no point of having a willie if
you can't use it. What's the fun in that?
What is literally the fun in that? Yeah.
Stop with your negative comments
just cuz your life's over, right? You
don't need to try and [ __ ] make it
sound like my life's over.
Do you honestly do you not get bored of
doing this for 8 years just hating on
the internet every day?
Just typing negative, hateful [ __ ] Do
you not get bored of it after 8 years?
You don't get bored of it, man. You
seriously don't get bored of it.
Do these people ever get bored of it?
They don't seem to get bored, do they?
No, they don't.
But no, if you go out, you definitely
definitely won't meet anyone.
It's going to make it worse if you go out. You know,
all that will happen is and then you're
going to get anxiet not anxiety, you're
going to get hangover the next day and
then you're going to feel worse. So, you
basically went out for no reason.
So, all you're going to do is go out for
no reason. That's that.
I am getting bored of it, bro. That's
why I'm not I'm not going to be doing
live streams anymore. I was only on this
one responding to this Smokeoky B. Yeah,
I am. That's why I'm putting content up.
I don't care about these haters, bro.
[ __ ] them. Ah, my armors. Yeah.
Yeah. But it's not just it's not about the well
it's not about the money because I've
got money but I mean technically yeah
you'll lose money you'll lose time
but it's not really about the money bro
that's the what I'm trying to say
how do I explain it like it's
when you say it like that bro it sounds
it makes it sound like someone's got
like300 in their name you
And that's not what it is. It really,
really isn't what it is, bro. I've been
like this. You can ask Antman for the
past year, not wanting to go out, making
excuses not to go out. I've been this
way for I've been right. I've been this
way for like a year, bro. Full on year.
Full on year, lad. Full on year.
But yeah, you will waste money. Yeah,
you will. Um,
you will you will waste money, lad.
There's no point. You might as well just
stack money, bro. Doesn't matter how
much money you get.
It is sad when you say it like that
though, Dusty. Is it? You lose money,
you get It's not even anxiety that that
I get. You just get tiredness. You just
feel like [ __ ] And then it's hard to
sleep as well because you feel like
[ __ ] when I when I get on the rum.
Yeah, it's hard to sleep. I find it hard Um
because I just feel like [ __ ] It's not
even anxiety. So, you'll get you get all
that for no reason. But if you just stay home,
then you just stay home in it or just go
go out do go for a meal or go cinema. It
just it just doesn't make sense.
He said, "Okay, there's no hope here." So,
you're not going to meet anyone import. Yeah,
but it's sad. And you'll deal with
women's attitude as well.
You'll deal with their shitty attitude as well. So,
and that's what you need to do. That's
what you need to put yourself through
to even get a date. Uh, Dusty,
and then you might get into an argument
with someone and it's just it just one
thing leads to another.
Or you can just stay home, greasy, and
watch Mickey Mouse.
No, no approaching videos. I do
approaching videos on my other channel,
but not this channel. No,
I don't know how how people still think
there's hope though, dusty. I don't know
how people still seem to think that
you're going to find someone.
That's the bit I find like proper
strange is they actually still think
that you're going to find someone.
That is funny, bro. They say they say
that, you know, you're still young and that. Nah.
Nah, it would have happened by now.
It would have definitely happened by now.
Nah, he didn't kill himself.
So, you're telling me to go out and approach?
Why am I going to go out and approach?
You just told me to give up, Dusty.
Yeah, but you're going to get more bad experiences.
You're not going to be a woman that's
different. It's not going to happen.
It's not going to happen, bro. So,
I haven't had a date since April. Like I
said, I haven't had a date since April.
So, if I haven't had a
Yeah, they will say try. Yeah, but
it's never going to change if it's not.
Okay, Greavvesy, Dusty, if it's not
changed for years, why is it going to change now?
You know, you're if if it's not going to change now,
no, no, you want to meet someone now,
bro. whilst your sex life is whilst your
sex drive is still semi high. You don't
want to meet someone in your 50s, do
you? And you should have met someone now
already. We haven't stayed in the house
for [ __ ] 5 years, so there's no
reason why we're not through anyone.
I definitely don't want to put myself
through that [ __ ] again.
Definitely not, bro.
It just doesn't It's just not worth it, bro.
But yeah, you should have already met someone.
I should have already met someone anyways.
The people on Reddit say you'll meet someone, Dusty.
No, I don't want to put myself through
it again, bro.
Cuz there is no hope. So why are you
going to go out when there's no hope?
Why are you going to have hope when
there's no hope? It doesn't make sense.
I went out Saturday. I went out last
Saturday. Bro, are you forgetting? It's
not even like they were recent and it
was nothing. Nothing again.
Single mom didn't even reply back.
[ __ ] you know,
but no, I don't want to put myself
through that mental stress again.
I really don't, bro. You know, nah.
What would you do, Dusty?
Listen, listen. And another thing, it
doesn't matter what woman you go for,
they're all stuck up. Whether they're
fat and ugly, whether they're
good-looking, whether they're single
moms, they're all the same. stuck up. I
approached an absolute mter on Saturday.
You can tell she was wearing makeup and
even she weren't interested. She was
given she was just unenthusiastic. I
just walked away. I don't even know why
I done it. But it doesn't matter what
they look like. They're still going to
have the same attitude.
So, you might as well go for uh
you can go for a single mom, they'll
still reject you. You go for fat, ugly
woman, they'll still reject you. It
doesn't matter what woman you go for,
you're always going to meet them and
they're always going to do the same thing.
And all you do is lose hope and become
upset. So there's no point losing more
hope. So yeah.
Yeah. I don't gamble, lad. No. So yeah.
Well, she wasn't a manta monster. She
was maybe like a four. I mean, that's
not a surprise, bro. It doesn't matter
what they look like. They're still going
to reject you. It doesn't matter what
they look like. A 40-year-old woman will reject me.
It doesn't matter. They're a woman and
they're westernized. End of. If they're
westernized, they're westernized. It
doesn't matter what the [ __ ] they look
like. How old the [ __ ] they are, they're
still going to be stuck up [ __ ]
So it doesn't it doesn't matter what
they look like, bro. Does it? They're
here. They're in England. They're
westernized. They're [ __ ] That's
That's that in it. son.
Nah, [ __ ] that, bro.
She's [ __ ] disabled.
That's why he was jealous of all of the
women I got with like USA Izzy and [ __ ]
cuz he could never get anyone like that. Yeah.
But apparently I'm the ugly one. Don't
forget Dusty. I'm the ugly one apparently. Yeah.
Dusty Ant-Man said they're just not
interested in this country.
He's lying in it. Yeah. He said they're
just not interested in this generation.
That's what he said. I'm trying to prove
him wrong. I'm trying to get out there
and like send it and stuff, but they
keep being not interested like he keeps saying.
He said they're just not interested in this country.
But I'm trying to prove him wrong by
like going out and stuff, but I keep
getting shitty results, you know?
What do you do? Hey, Dusty. What do you H,
like I said, I'll go out New Year's Eve
and that's that.
I probably will go out New Year's Eve. Uh
yeah, haircut New Year's Eve, you know.
Got to make some cornflakes in a minute.
Yeah, Gravesy. Yeah, true.
I like Greavves little comments. Poor [ __ ]
Latch on to new boobies. You're so funny, bro.
latching on to new boobies. Grezy,
I might have some digestive biscuits.
Yeah, I might have some digestive biscuits.
Yeah, cup of tea and some digestive biscuits.
I was waiting for it. I was waiting for
it. I was waiting for it. I'm only
joking. I'm having corn flakes.
That's like when [ __ ] the virgin come
in the other day. What was it yesterday?
The skin virgin. I was like, "No."
Mom was like, "I can hear a cat in my house."
Everybody has to say meow when he comes in.
Yeah, you copycat.
You're nothing but a little copycat.
Did you see he tried retracting the
things he was saying? You're nothing but
a little copycat.
He didn't want to feel left out in
college, did he? He didn't want to feel
left out. He likes to follow the crowd in it. Yeah.
Doesn't want to feel left out.
So, was it because you didn't want to
feel left out then?
Is it because you didn't want to feel left out?
You ate all the [ __ ] phone breaks.
You greedy [ __ ]
So I'm angry with them.
Oh, there's a there. I was about to go
mad then. I like corn flakes. [ __ ] greedy [ __ ]
I [ __ ] I buy stuff and then he eats it. Yeah,
[ __ ] lady [ __ ] eat it. Took a bite
and [ __ ] just going to eat it, you know. >> No,
women are [ __ ]
Do you remember? Don't let these [ __ ] women win.
that account's not been on for a while,
has it? Um,
yeah, that account has not been on for a while.
You know that the one I'm talking about,
don't you agree?
Can't deprive can't deprive grooves of
content, poor [ __ ] M
I'm loving this cornflake squeezy, but I
might have to get myself a Donald's
McDonald's as well.
You know what I'm like? Yeah. M mow me.
How are Elevens being a copycat? Triple
H. Your kid is raised by another man. Meow. Meow. Oh yeah,
didn't catch on, did he? Copycat.
He's made a copycat. M m.
Can't be a bowl of cornflake.
M one second. H.
Do you remember that G account that used
to give me an LT grief?
That G account. Stop.
Greasy. The lady said I would meet
someone. Do you remember that comment?
Um, Grevy Laney said we would meet someone
lady said I would beat someone.
I can't. They're so delicious.
I can't stop.
So, do you reckon you're ever going to
use Reddit? Uh, Reddit, Dusty,
you reckon you would ever use Reddit or So,
so what do you think of the mods? Do you
think they're sad? You said they're sad,
don't you? The mods.
The mods are sad, right?
But what do you think about the mods
though? They're sad, isn't it?
They say, right, that people Yeah.
You remember when I went to the
steakhouse with USA Izzy? That steak was delicious. Oh gosh, Grezy.
Ah, I was I was truly fed that day, wasn't I? Gosh,
wasn't I grievy? I was truly fed that day.
Yep. I got fed.
I was pulled off for a week after that. Oh gosh.
>> Oh gosh.
>> Is that cute? Greavves. That little
voice. Greavvesy likes my voices.
probably spreading her legs open today, [ __ ]
Yeah, probably. Well, she's got a
boyfriend, but she's probably still
doing it. Yeah,
it's okay. I'll just wait.
We'll be waiting on Saturday for
Smokeoky B to come on the door. We'll just wait.
Yes, she's a dirty [ __ ] USA. Is he
dirty dirty man? Isn't she greasy?
She's very dirty.
by Joseph Fro says Reddit is sad. He
He said Reddit is sad. Um Dusty cuz the
mods ban people to feel in control.
Joseph Fro hates Reddit. He says
anything like that where people do stuff
that control it is sad.
Nope. They ban you. Even if you don't
post anything, it flags up and they ban you. Nope.
Even if uh
even if you don't you they ban your IP,
which they still have to man manually
ban you. It's definitely a control
thing. It definitely is a control thing.
Yeah, but they're still manually doing it.
They're still manually doing it. Yeah,
they're still manually doing it.
Manually doing it.
They still want me doing it lad basically. Yeah,
when I was gambling.
[ __ ] off joker man.
[ __ ] gambling bro. What the [ __ ] you idiot man?
I'm all right, lad.
I'm all right, matey. I just don't get
my vitamins now. You know,
Joker is I shouldn't have to be have to
go out and try.
That's what I'm pissed off about because
I'm 28, bro. And I shouldn't have to go
out and try, lad. You know,
I should have to go out and have to keep
trying. That's why
you don't understand. 28 is different
from 24, 25. You do realize that
you know the [ __ ] energy for this
[ __ ] nowadays, bro.
You want the link?
One sec. I'm just going back on Reddit. Hold on.
Yeah, they are evil though. Women
definitely are evil, bro.
So what if they they are evil?
Oh, you know that uh woman today
who I was telling you about on the
Instagram when she said, "Oh, the guy
didn't reply back and stuff."
What do you think people said in the comments?
What do you think?
They were all bigging her up saying, "Oh
yeah, uh, it's good that you caught on
early and stuff and r and that was all
because you didn't reply to her message.
There was no there was no excuse to be
made, Reezy. There was no excuse to be
made cuz you you talk about double
standards a lot, don't you, Grezy? M.
Yeah. No excuse was to be made, eh?
You [ __ ] women.
Don't let these [ __ ] women win. I crazy.
But yeah, no one no one was making
excuses for him like they do with women.
Nope. They were all bigging her up
saying that she's going to she just
needs to find the right one and stuff.
But if that was me,
we'd be blamed for everything.
Is that right, Grezy? It's not fair, is it?
But you know,
it's just one of them crazy things,
isn't it, boss?
Oh, I'm going to let you in in a minute. One second.
One second. The Virgin wants to come in.
Greavves, are you going to do the honors
or what? Am I going to do it?
One second. I'll let you in. One second.
Hold on. I'm typing something.
Are you going to do the honors or what?
Yeah, I use mom's net. One second. I'll
let you in.
Yeah, I'll let you in.
>> Are you actually going to let me speak?
You like you like Cheryl Co, don't you?
You like Cheryl Co. You little copy. You
little copycat. You little cuffy cat.
>> Are you going to let me speak?
>> Gay. Gay. I'm gay, aren't I? I'm gay.
Cuz I don't like [ __ ] I'm gay.
Homosexual. But are you going to let me
speak? Big news.
>> Gay. Gay. Gay. You're [ __ ] hobo.
>> Yeah. But do you know what? Can you come
up with some better comebacks and not
the same repeating cuz he's actually getting
>> boring. Let me speak and we want we want
a new we want a new episode. We want a
new episode. Oliver Twist.
>> Well, if you actually let Yeah. If you
actually let me speak, we'll get
somewhere, won't we? Instead of shouting
over me like a Down Syndrome autistic
bastard that keeps getting owned.
>> Yeah, you said you've already said that.
>> Yeah, you said this yesterday. You said
>> Will you actually let me speak?
>> You said this yesterday, Oliver Twist.
We might get some if you let me speak.
>> You said you said that yesterday, Oliver
Twist. Calm down.
>> Let me speak.
>> Calm down, Oliver Twist. It's not my
fault. Your mom starved you. Don't take
out on me.
>> So, anyways, um, you're going to get a little job.
Noises coming through. Sorry. Triple
Triple H got a little job for you.
>> You're very triggered today, aren't you, mate?
>> No, not in the least. Why would I be
triggered? Do you remember when Britney
rejected you? She didn't want to know
what do you
>> I didn't particular
I didn't particularly remember that
because I was [ __ ] like 15 in when I
that's [ __ ] forever ago and you never
>> you was meeting me and you kept talking
about her [ __ ] over and over and over
again. You silly [ __ ]
>> That wasn't nonsense. But
>> he was a [ __ ] she was 12 when you
[ __ ] fat when you was 18.
>> You [ __ ] idiot.
>> People definitely believe you big news.
You said you said big nose yesterday.
Boring now, mate. New boring news. What else makesor?
I'm I'm not I'm not the one that looks
like a rat like you. So I I take I take
the big nose and have the rat face like
you do, mate. I take it.
>> You look like a [ __ ] rat. >> My
>> You look like a [ __ ] rat, son. You ugly.
>> Can you wait until I've said my piece? then
>> your nose is of ginormous proportions.
My nose is normal size.
>> But guess what? I'm still better looking
than you. So, how does that make you
feel? How does it make you feel that
someone with a big nose is better
looking than you?
>> Okay. Not not Okay. Not with a [ __ ]
nose and a hairline like that.
>> Well, okay then. Okay. So, how comes
Okay, then. So, how comes I've had more
women than you and I've never had to
resort to disabled? Answer the question.
>> You believe that for a second? With a
nose like that. I don't believe that statement.
>> One second. One second. One second. If
I'm all of these things, why have I
never had to resort to a disabled like you?
>> That's a It sounds like projection,
isn't it? It sounds like projection.
>> I wouldn't know. I've never actually
been with a disabled person, unlike you.
And they're 19year-old.
>> Your girlfriend's disabled.
>> Uh, your girlfriend's disabled.
>> You're with a disabled girl right now.
>> Oh, okay. If you can provide any
evidence, I will I will accept that that she's disabled.
>> She looks like a dwarf. She can't talk.
disabled. She looks disabled. All of the
women I've been with, how come all of
the women I've been with, we've all
heard them talk.
>> Well, yours can't talk cuz she's in.
Here's the thing.
>> Okay. Yeah. Say that [ __ ] in a minute.
I've never heard one of your girlfriends
speak because you've never had
>> All the women all of the women that I
have been with that were normal and not disabled like
>> uh you have seen me with a woman and I'd
rather have no girlfriend than have a
disabled girlfriend. I think I've done
that. multiple times. I would rather
have no girlfriend than have a disabled
girlfriend. I think I've said that many,
many times. I'd rather be single, mate.
I could drink 30 Guinnesses and I still
wouldn't be with that disabled [ __ ] that
you're not a badge of honor. It's not a
badge of honor. And the fact is
>> and also the amount of times you stalked
me on the internet, you even showed it
and you're not happy with her, but you
just But what it is with you, what it is
with you, you know that you're too ugly
to get better and that's what you hate
because that's why you do all of this
YouTube stalking because you're too ugly
to get anything.
>> Say this [ __ ]
>> That's why you say that's why that's why
you stalk me every day cuz I'm better
looking than you and I say.
>> Okay, but you can say that [ __ ] in a
minute. You don't let me speak. You just
keep going on saying it to you now, you skin [ __ ]
>> Yeah, but wait until I actually said
something first because that's quite
autistic what you're doing right now.
>> You [ __ ] skin [ __ ] Yeah. Hey, money.
>> Oh, there was a stem. Did you hear that?
He went Did you hear that? That was real.
>> He He made He made a steaming noise.
>> Wind back. Wind back. Like 5 seconds. He went steing.
>> How How come you've never had a job?
>> What you doing? Why? Why have you never
had a little job?
>> The job will do you well again. You
would love to know what mine is and where.
>> I I I would love to know where you were,
mate, because how can you be as skinny as you? I
>> I'll give you a clue. >> Okay.
>> It involves photos.
>> Oh, really?
>> Yeah, it does.
>> I I know what it is. I know.
>> It's got It's got the word It's got the
word restoration in it.
>> You're You were called child pulled cuz
you were dogs. I got it. I got it. You
were called child.
>> There's some autistic aggression coming out there.
>> And listen, you need I don't understand
why you keep stalking me. I don't want
nothing to do with you. I don't want to
meet you again. You ugly skinned
bastard. Leave me alone.
>> What the word what the word stalking means.
>> Yeah, it's what you're doing. I don't
want to know you, you ugly c.
>> It's legal definition and it's why I'm
taking you to court in three years.
>> You're not taking anybody to You're not
taking anyone to cult by the time I'm
done with your bank. Anyways,
I don't want nothing to do with you. I
wish I never met you. You big virgin. I
didn't know how much of a virgin you was
before I met you and how skinn you were.
You're [ __ ] embarrassing. You drew
attention to to us in Strapford when
them black guys [ __ ] threw water at
you. Embarrassment. [ __ ] embarrassment.
>> Made up.
>> Nope. Not made up. Definitely not made
up. It happened opposite Burger King.
Black guys threw water at you cuz you
sound so much they [ __ ] >> Huh?
>> Well, here's the thing. in the mail.
>> It was opposite Burger King in Stratford
Mall. Do you not remember?
>> In the mail. There is no Burger King, is there?
>> Uh, yes, there is. Yes, there is.
>> You said that you knew you said that you
knew my area better than than I did, you
[ __ ] virgin. How did you know that
there was a burger there?
>> In the mail?
>> In the mall? Yes.
>> Ah, I wouldn't know.
>> That's where the black guys threw at
you. You [ __ ]
That's totally made up. I would feel
somebody break up. Nothing I say about
you is made up. Not
>> Yeah, it is. It is. I don't
>> Everything I say about you is made up.
>> I don't need to stoop to them lows. I
don't need to make anything up about you.
>> You said that. You said that I put my
finger in my ass.
>> No, I didn't. I actually
You absolute virgin.
>> I actually defended you.
>> Listen, listen, big nose. I actually [ __ ] virgin.
>> Okay. Yeah. Say that [ __ ] in a minute. I
actually defend Yeah. I I defended you a
little bit there because I said you
scratched your lower back.
>> I didn't say put your finger in your ass.
>> Okay. Okay.
>> But maybe Hey, do you remember when I
used to say to you that you should
always be Do you remember when I said to
you you should always be an author?
>> Maybe you just um revealed something there.
>> I I never actually said you stuck your
finger in your derriè.
>> Yes, you did.
The first time I met you, we went to an
Indian restaurant and you shut yourself
the next day.
>> Oh, made up.
>> Nope, not made up.
>> No, but I do remember we went into a
restaurant and we left because I looked
at what I looked at the menu and I was like,
>> "Fuck that for the price of bacon. I'm
not eating in here."
>> No, no, no, no. So, when do you remember
when I used to say that you should be
>> Man, you got some severe [ __ ] autism, lad.
>> But do you remember when I said that you
should be an author?
>> Oh, boy. You remember when I said that
to you? You should be an author.
>> Not particularly. I didn't remember.
>> When you used to make up them sex
stories of Aisha, you absolute virgin.
>> Oh, I I had fallen out.
>> You absolute virgin.
>> Okay. I I Yeah. Okay. I had fallen out
with you at the point I started telling
you about her.
>> You [ __ ] virgin.
>> You should be the times I used to tell you.
>> When's your When's your birthday?
>> Oh, you knew when my birthday is. You're
invited, by the way. You can come. We
we'll give you a good freshing.
>> I'm going to I'm going to get you a
Valentine's card. That's how you ain't
already lost your V card. Persian lo
I lose it every single night if that's possible.
>> Mate, your hand don't count. Your hand
don't count, mate. You still a virgin.
You virgin stories.
>> Okay. Can I just say one thing?
>> You definitely didn't [ __ ] somebody on a
park bench. That is ridiculous. So silly.
>> Well, I did. But can I just say one?
>> No, you definitely definitely didn't.
>> Okay. Well, I did. But can I just say
one? You definitely definitely did it,
>> man. You got bad son. Bad.
>> Okay. So So wouldn't you go to like a
hotel on your gaff or her gaff?
>> Bit extreme, isn't it?
>> Why? Why would you [ __ ] someone on the
park bench, you [ __ ] liar?
>> Are you going to let me speak or you
just going to keep talking talking?
>> I want to know. I want to know.
>> Well, maybe we can get somewhere if you
actually let me speak. autistic.
>> Aren't you diagnosed with autism?
>> Yeah, I am, but I don't have to.
>> Okay. Yeah, so, mate. Sorry. Sorry. So,
>> it's called a spectrum and that's why
you're so different than me.
>> All right, mate. All right. Carry on then. Talk.
>> Yeah. Okay. It's called a spectrum and
that's why you're so different than me.
>> You went nowhere near that, girl.
>> Oh, say that. Say that [ __ ] when we get
to it. Maybe we can get
>> You absolutely nowhere near Aisha. Well,
let's get somewhere first and then start
talking about that.
Can I just say one [ __ ] thing?
>> Yeah, I want you to explain the story.
Everyone wants to hear it.
>> Oh, no. Completely irrelevant to that.
Can I just say one thing?
>> Okay. Have you been reminiscing at all
about your brother Jason hanging from
the ribs spinning like a pendulum, son,
or like something?
>> No one cares about this dead relative
talk, mate. We don't We don't care about
that. You said all that yesterday and
the point is the point is
>> it doesn't it doesn't matter if people
care about it or not. I'm asking you a question.
>> I've still got more I've still got more
family than you. So it doesn't really
matter, does it?
>> I don't see how that's possible. You
said your non
>> your mom I mean your mom you don't see
your mom. Your mom hates you. You
>> that that that [ __ ] would be like a
nightmare if I saw her moving.
>> Your mom your mom disowned you. Your
sister disowned you. I mean doesn't
matter who died in my family. I've still
got more family than you.
>> Okay. Okay. I do wish that were the
case, but it's not.
>> No, that is literally
>> I actually No, what you just described
there is actually a literal nightmare.
That's not the case.
>> Why are you talking about dead
relatives? I've got more family than you.
>> Here's the thing. I bumped into a living
one and it gave me quite a fright. I
didn't like it. It sent the shits up me.
I was on the bus. I I went to the top
floor of the bus and I was like, "Oh no,
she's going to come back."
>> Can I Can I ask Let me ask you this
question. Why didn't you say of this any
of this stuff when I was in your area on
a live stream?
>> I don't remember you ever being in my
area. I remember you coming to my town.
>> I went to Orington, which is your area
close to your barbers and you didn't
come out. Why didn't you come out, big
man? Why didn't you come out? Why didn't
>> Well, there was one time you also went
to Brmley Town Center and I had no
Brmley. I went to You would not come
out, would you? You little You little [ __ ]
>> Why would I? Why? To say what you've got
to say to my face because you do you're
a keyboard warrior. You're a keyboard
>> Okay. Jesus. Yeah. The first time was Brmley, right?
>> Yeah. And you didn't come out there either.
>> And that that was just before lockdown
happened and everybody was fighting each
other in the shops if you remember.
>> You and this little nons will never ever
destroy me. You can't even come out when
I go to your area. Shush. Just like I
went to this virgin's area. See, if you
could say this stuff to my face, then
it'll be like, do you know what I mean?
>> But at the end of the day, you're never
going to say anything to my face. So, it
doesn't really matter what you say. Your
mom hates you. Your mom starved you. You
come from a broken family. No one cares.
>> A little bit a little bit of truth
there. But I
>> Your mom hates you. Your mom starved
you. Your mom doesn't see you. You're
spending Christmas lonely. No one cares
what I'm spending.
>> When you can actually say something to
someone's face, you know?
>> Yeah. You're going to let me finish?
Yeah. I'm actually spending Christmas
with my father unlike you. You're
>> [ __ ] Yeah, I'm spending it with my
mother, the one that hates you. But the
thing is But the thing is your mom your
mom's alive and she hates you.
>> So at least my dad's dead. Your mom's alive.
>> Your mom your mom your mom.
>> Yeah, bro. It doesn't matter. Your mom
hates you and you got bullied by your
stepdad and you got bullied by your stepdad. So
>> I don't have a stepfather. My mom
bullied you and your stepdad bullied you
and your mom hates you.
>> My mom never married.
>> This is you. I understand the
frustration. You're going to be alone
Christmas. Your mom hates you.
>> You could talk about my dead dad, but at
least my dad's not a nons.
>> Yeah, I can.
>> At least At least my dad didn't go to
[ __ ] jail for kitty images.
>> That's more like
>> At least my dad didn't get with my mom
when I was 12 like yours.
>> People definitely believe that big news.
Your you know your dad is not going to
be alive within 5 years. He's going to
be worm food dead. You do realize that
your dad's going to be dead in 5 years.
>> He might die.
>> Your dad's going to be dead soon.
>> He might live to be 84. You don't
>> listen listen. Your dad's going to be
dead soon and we're going to throw a party.
>> Yeah. Okay. In 5 years he will be 84.
It's plausible that he could live. My
girlfriend's grandmother is 87.
>> Bro, when your dad dies, we're going to
have a party. Worm food. Never seen the
old Parkinson's [ __ ] again. Just wait
until your dad dies. Your dad's going to
die soon. Your dad's old.
>> Trust me,
>> bro. Your dad's going to die soon. He's
really going to die and we're going to
make fun of him.
>> You knew he didn't.
>> He won't meet anyone. Nons will never
meet anyone. He's been doing this for years.
>> Who the [ __ ]
>> He's been doing this nonslegs as you cuz you're nons.
This is what I'm saying.
>> He's a coward. He's a big mouth. He's a
big mouth, but he will never beat
anyone. He's a big mouth, but he will
never meet anyone. I've gone to his area
three times and he won't come out. I had him running.
>> I had him run to the police.
>> Says the bully,
>> bro. I had the guy run into the police
three times. He's never going to meet
anyone. He's the same as Terry. >> Say,
>> I have gone to his area three times and
he will never meet anyone. The lucky
will never meet anyone. I had him run
into the police live on camera.
>> Live on camera. I've had him running to
the police. He would never meet anyone.
>> The He's just a nasty. He's just a nasty
little [ __ ] with a [ __ ] up childhood
that got bullied by his mom, bullied by
his stepdad. No one loves him. He's got no money.
>> He's living in a council beds. He's the
definition of a loser.
>> You know what I'm saying?
>> He's not a bedit and it's rented.
>> You live in a [ __ ] shitty bed with no
bed in a [ __ ] mate.
>> You're living in your mom's [ __ ] shoe box.
[ __ ] virgin castle bedit. Shut the [ __ ] up.
>> You're living in a shitty virgin castle
spare room. At least I live in a house,
not a bedsit like you used to. Which is
>> a shitty little bedit.
I'd rather live in a house than a shitty little bedit.
You just keep going.
>> Listen. Listen. I would rather live in a
house than a shitty little bedit that
you live in. You [ __ ]
>> You live in your mom's spare room.
>> I live in a house, not a bedsit. You
live in a shitty bed house.
>> You live in a shitty
rather live than in a shitty cancel bed.
You still live with your mom and
>> shitty castle bedsit. I would rather
live with my mom than live. Bro, you
can't live with your mom cuz your mom hates you.
>> Describe it a nightmare. I don't want to
live with my mom,
>> bro. And I don't want to live in a
[ __ ] shitty castle bed suit with no
bed cuz I'm not skinn like you. You live
in a cent PTSD night.
>> You live in a capsule bed with no bed in
it. Do not tell anyone that they live
with their mom. You live in a bed right now.
owned by the council. That is not an achievement.
>> It's a housing.
>> What's going on, [ __ ] You don't
have a house. You live in a bedsit.
>> [ __ ] me.
>> I live in a flat.
>> Do you know what? Show us your flat and
show us your bed.
>> I'm in bed with my girlfriend right now.
Might trigger you a little bit.
>> Show us your house and show us your bed.
>> It might trigger you a little bit if I
do that. I can't do that.
>> No, no, no. Go on. Because you live in a
catch shitty bed. I'd rather live with
my mom than live in that shitty bed.
that shitty cancel bedsit. Imagine
taking a woman to a shitty [ __ ]
council bedsit with no bed in it.
>> Imagine that. And he's trying to tell
people that they live with their mom
when he's living in a council bedit.
Living in a council bed. Never worked.
>> Girlfriend in bed before.
>> Never worked a day in his life. And he's
talking about people living with his mom
when he's in a council bed.
>> In a shitty council bed out of London.
>> And And you're in your mom's spare room out.
>> Yes. I live in a house. I live in a
house. You don't have a house. Triggered
>> to London, >> mate.
This is a not it. This is a house. This
is a three-bedroom house.
>> You don't live with your You don't live
in your mom's house cuz your mom
disowned you. Your mom disowned you.
They gave you They gave you a council bedsit.
>> I would rather live with my mom than
live in that shitty council bedsit. I'm
not denying it.
I'm not denying that. I don't want to
live in some shitty Kent [ __ ] virgin
beds that you live in. You're [ __ ]
virgin. Part of the reason why you're
still a virgin. You you you live in a shitty shed.
>> I live in a house in Essics.
>> I live in a uh one second. One second.
Where where this is is class as London.
You want to look up?
>> No, like where I live then. Greater London.
>> No, it's not. Kent is not London. No,
>> So the same hold on. So why does the
same virgin area that you live in?
>> Does the same not apply to you then?
>> The [ __ ] virgin area that you live in
has nothing to do with London. That virgin area.
>> The same not apply to you.
>> Victoria. Okay. From you to Okay. From
Victoria to you.
>> I can get to London like an hour quicker
than you can. Nearly.
>> No, you can't. I'm literally one stop
away from London.
>> No, you can't.
>> So am I. I can get a fast train. Half an hour away.
>> Exactly. Yeah, we are one. We are 5 minutes away.
>> I can get a fast train there in
>> No, no, no. And and that and that is
half an hour.
>> You realize the argument you were giving.
>> No, no, no. Bronford is considered
London. No [ __ ] Virgin area was
considered London. The Virgin area that
you live in.
>> So why exactly? So why does Exactly
of London? Kent is not London. Kent is
>> Essex is not London.
>> No, no, no. is not London.
>> Listen, Virgin Romford is classed as London. >> Exactly.
>> So why does Exactly. So explaining this
to you, but you're not letting me talk
>> Virgin. Exactly. So why does the same So
why does the same So why does the same
not apply to you?
>> Because Orington is not London. Bford is
London. And we lived
before that. But you would know that cuz
your mom [ __ ] disowned you. You live.
Listen you [ __ ] virgin [ __ ] Hen is not London.
>> Is not London. Essics is not London.
>> Listen. Romford is classed as London.
>> Virgin. Virgin. Listen. Virgin idiots.
>> Virgin in the bedsit. Listen. Romford is
not Essex. Orton is shitty. Kent.
Virgin. Do you know what?
>> That doesn't make any sense. It's the
same [ __ ] argument. Okay. Let let me look up.
>> That's the exact same argument. You [ __ ] bastard.
>> Let me look it up right now then. Yeah.
Do you want me to look up right now?
>> You want me to look it up again?
>> Yeah. Go on.
>> Okay, I will do you [ __ ] absolute virgin.
>> What? Orington and Brmley? You going to
look that up?
>> Right now. Okay. Yeah.
This says it is in greater London, Kent,
which is not London.
>> Oh, there we go. You lost.
>> We look up Romford. We look up Romford
and it says East London. It says East
London. You [ __ ] absolute virgin.
Well, you're not looking on Google then, are you?
>> You're [ __ ] absolute virgin. You're
telling me, right, you sound like a
Londoner with your shitty virgin accent?
Why do you think that black people bullied you?
>> Why do you think they bullied you? They
saw the virgin. They saw the virgin.
>> Well, big news. I've never seen that.
>> They saw the skint virgin of myof.
That's why they bullied you. We don't
like Kent virgins. London's always had wars. What?
>> They see some [ __ ] some lanky
ratfaced ugly virgin walking and they
throw throw wall at you and you don't
nothing. You little [ __ ] house.
>> That's never happened. That's your
>> little [ __ ] house. Yes, it did. And also
what happened was I went to your area
and I had you run into the police
station and stopped you going to your
vents for 3 weeks. I caused that. I'm
the cause of it.
>> That's more I'm the cause of it. I'm the
cause of it. I took it upon myself to go
to that shitty virgin area. Sorry, a bit
of stingming coming out. shitty virgin area
>> and that's it, you know. That's it. You
stop going to your little events cuz of me.
>> That's cuz of me.
>> You notice Yeah. You notice
>> I had to run into the police cuz I was
too much. I was too much for you. I owed
you badly. You had to go to the police.
>> You go right through and then you don't
let me speak.
>> You see, you notice with me, I just need
to say a little bit, but then you just
make all this [ __ ] up. But everything I
say is quite calm. No, I went I'm making
up that I went live in your area.
>> See, you keep going on again. You don't
let me finish
>> cuz you're an absolute virgin.
Everything you're talking is [ __ ]
>> Clown. You're clown son.
>> Okay. I went to your area and had to go
to the police and
>> Yeah. And and you dream you [ __ ]
[ __ ] You would never say nothing to my
face. You rat looking ugly [ __ ]
>> You rat skin ugly [ __ ] with your booty
dad. You would never say nothing to me. >> [ __ ]
>> You're not going to say nothing. your
ugly n dad who's on his last legs is not
going to say nothingers.
>> I spoke about you. I spoke about your
dad. I went to your area and made you go
to the police.
>> [ __ ] virgin. You will never say
anything to anyone's face. You skin
virgin. Carry on living in your shitty
little beds with your disabled
girlfriend. You ugly [ __ ]
>> Love it.
>> And you have PTSD flashbacks of your
father and your brother dying. Woo! No
was swinging on that thing, son.
>> I mean, I met my I met my half brother
once. I met my half brother once and my
dad never lived with me, but your dad
used to beat your mom about. So, you
probably get flashbacks of that. You
probably get flashbacks of your Oh,
look, he left cuz I own him. Everything
I say about him is the truth. Everything
I say about this [ __ ] nons is the
[ __ ] truth. His dad is a non. He used
to knock his mom out. Why do you think
he's not allowed to see his mother? His
mom's not dead. His mom's been alive for
a very long time. You know, your [ __ ]
dad used to knock your mom about. You
come from a broken family. I don't.
Yeah, my dad died. And what? Your dad's
a [ __ ] nonsense. He's going to be
dead soon. You know, your [ __ ] baldy
[ __ ] [ __ ] Parkinson's dad is going
to be [ __ ] dead soon, [ __ ] [ __ ]
And this is the [ __ ] that he used to do
back in the day, Dusty. But he will
never meet anyone. This virgin will
never ever meet anyone and never say
anything to his face, anyone to anyone's
face. He's just a little keyboard
warrior. Keyboard warrior [ __ ] who got
starved by his mom. He's a nasty little
[ __ ] And this is why I got him on
YouTube. This is why I got this [ __ ]
little rat ugly [ __ ] virgin on YouTube
to start with, bro. People always want
to know why I got him on YouTube, bro.
You know what I'm saying, bro? You know
what I mean? He's a nasty nasty little
virgin. All because his mom starved.
He's a nasty [ __ ] But in real life, he
would never say anything. Just like a
lot of these people on here, they will
never ever say anything. They will never
ever say anything to anyone's face. This
is what I mean, bro. We've all seen me
go to his area and them crying to the
police. But no one will ever say
anything because they're all nons. So,
it is what it is, bro. That's what I'm saying. Simple.
That's that. The [ __ ] didn't get timed
out. The cut didn't get timed out.
Like, bro, you can literally go to the
same area tomorrow and the little [ __ ]
bag won't come out of his shitty bedsit.
His little council bedsit. And he knows
what I'm saying is the truth about where
he lives. That's why he keeps talking
about, "Oh, I live with my mom. I live
with my mom." You live in a [ __ ]
council bedsit. I'd rather live with my
[ __ ] mom in a house, silly little
And to think this has been going on for
years with this virgin Triple H. [ __ ]
years and years and years and years and
years, you know?
Bro, you're boring. [ __ ] off, you little
nons lover. Yeah, you're banned. Go
[ __ ] This is what And this is exactly
what Joseph does as well, bro. This is
what I mean with you, brother. These
people love nons on here. They love
nons. This is what I'm saying. They love [ __ ] nons.
Joseph Ferrar does exactly the same thing.
You know what I'm saying?
You know what? You should come here on
Saturday with [ __ ] Smokeoky B to be
fair. I'm not the [ __ ] out of both of you,
you know. You should come here on
Saturday, bro. Yeah, that's why he left.
[ __ ] bring your [ __ ] ugly baldy
dad. You left, bro. You didn't get
kicked. Bring your baldy dad.
The [ __ ] old nons and your [ __ ]
mom that hate you. Come on, bro. You
should You should come on [ __ ] Yeah,
you should come as well. So why did you
kick me? Did it get too [ __ ] ugly
[ __ ] You left cuz I owned you, bro.
>> Why did you kick me? Is it because I mentioned precious?
>> No one's kicked you, Virgin. It's
because your childhood swinging on that
rope like I'm talking the truth about
your I'm talking the truth about your
childhood. That's why you keep leaving.
You didn't get
>> Jason was swinging on that,
bro. Your dad used to beat your mom
about. Your dad beat your mom up. That's
why your mom hates you. Jason was
swinging on that thing like a [ __ ]
grand. My brother's dead. But guess
what? I've got more family than you. And
my B didn't beat My dad didn't beat my
Bubba about like yours did. You come
from a broken family. No mother. No
sister. Look, he's left again. You come
from a broken family and you can't even
use death as an excuse, bro. You was
bullied by your mom. You was bullied by
your stepdad. I don't give a [ __ ] about
my half brother that I met [ __ ] once,
you know? Or my dad. Your dad's an old
nons that used to knock your mom about.
That's why your mom hates both of you.
Do not find it weird how he's mom and
he's dad. Don't talk cuz he's a all of
this is projection. This is self
And he's going to keep saying that
people's kicked him. No one's kicked the
virgin. Your dad used to knock your mom
about. Used to beat the [ __ ] out of her.
That's why she starved you. That's why
you in a bedsit. Yeah. No one cares
about two dead relatives. Your dad's
going to be dead soon. He can't even
stand up. He's got Parkinson's. He's as
good as [ __ ] dead. You know what I'm
saying? This is what I'm saying, bro.
He's talking about dead relatives, but
he will never say anything to anyone's
face. He goes running to the police.
He's a little [ __ ] outs. He's a little
He's the shittiest [ __ ] you will ever
meet in real life. Absolute virgin. Shy.
Will not even look anyone in the eye. He
will never say anything to anyone's
face. He's just happy to be a little
virgin on a grand a month. Little
keyboard warrior that runs to the police.
This is what they're like on here.
They're very jealous people. Like I
said, I wasn't even going to go live
today, bro. But this Smokeoky Bee tries
to say that he's coming on my dot, bro.
I've already got a plan for this [ __ ]
You do realize that? I've already got a
plan for this [ __ ]
You know, bro, he hasn't tormented me.
This [ __ ] ugly rat [ __ ] I [ __ ]
made him stop going to events cuz of me.
[ __ ] [ __ ] They tormented me. I've
had him go to the police on me. I've had
the [ __ ] run to the police on me cuz he
couldn't handle me. Bro, that's not
someone that's tormented me. You know,
you know, bro, I went and done posters
of him. I had him stop going out of his
house cuz of me. What are you talking
about, bro? What are you talking about?
I literally put up posters and had him
stop going to events cuz of me. I
literally went to the event that he used
to go to and [ __ ] put up posters. I
had him stop going to places because of
me. So don't try and sit there and say
that he's tormented me, bro. The guy's
not going to meet me. Yeah, he's never
going to come out of his virgin shitty
area. The virgin [ __ ] is never going to
meet anyone, you know? Do I need to do
it? Do I need to do it a fourth, fifth,
sixth time, lad? Like, he's going to run
to the police and never meet anyone.
He's a virgin. A dirty little keyboard
warrior virgin who got knocked about by
his dad and his mom hates him. Yeah.
He's never going to meet anyone. And do
you know what I'm going to do now? Yeah.
I'm going to say one more thing when he
comes on. I'm going to say, "Are you
going to say any of this stuff to my
face?" And if he isn't, I'm just going
to not let him in. Simple as that. Same
as Smokeoky B, bro. If he's not going to
meet anyone, then he's not going to have
a voice. If he's going to continue being
a cowardly little virgin, I'm just going
to stop. I'm just going to stop entertaining it.
Right. Bring your [ __ ] ugly dad.
Bring your mom that hates you. Bring
your disabled girlfriend in your shitty
little bedsit. And if he's not going to
meet me, I'm gonna stop entertaining
him. The same as that Smokeoky Bee.
You know, if that Smokey Bee comes, I'm
gonna do the [ __ ] bad, bro. Yeah, I
didn't say this [ __ ] you know,
earlier because these people will not
leave me alone, right? They're [ __ ]
jealous of me. I don't know what it is
over and over and over and over again. I
didn't want to come live today, bro. I
went live cuz this guy said he was
coming on my door. Yeah. Which is why
they want to entertain this. These
people are clearly jealous of something.
They won't leave me alone, right? Which
is why I've said I'm going to put up
content. Disable the likes. Disable the
comments, bro. Because this is what
happens, bro. This is what happens with
these people. They hate that you're
younger and better looking than them.
And they've been doing it for years.
These people have been doing this for [ __ ] years.
You know, they've been doing it for
[ __ ] years, bro.
All cuz you're younger and better
looking than them and you got more money
than them. So, this is what it is with
these people, bro. Seriously. What the [ __ ] man? So yeah, simple. Anyways. Yeah,
I'll do a video to this nonslegs. Yeah.
And I'll say like we'll give him one
more chance, right, to to to to agree to
meeting me. And if he's not going to
meet me, I'm just going to ignore him.
I'm just going to not I'm I'm going to
talk about his childhood. Talk about his
non dad. Horrible ugly little [ __ ]
And if he's not going to meet me, then
he's not coming up. There's no hangouts.
There's no nothing. He's got two
channels to respond on. I will do these
two [ __ ] both in in a week, bro. Yeah.
In less than a week. Yeah. I will do it
both in in a week. And I'm prepared to
say it to your face. Yeah. Seeing that
you've got like such a nasty mouth, I'm
going to give you one more chance, you
rat looking [ __ ] And if you don't, I'm
going to ignore it. Just the same as
Smokey B. Yeah. Simple. And that is that
is that. Yeah.
You little [ __ ] [ __ ] ass little bully
victim. Like you want to talk about
[ __ ] about how people do this. And if
you're just wanting to be a keyboard
warrior like LT is going to tell you,
then bro, we're not interested.
You know, we're not interested.
And the thing is, Dusty, this guy will
never meet anyone. This little shitty
virgin that wears charity shop clothes
will never meet anyone.
This little skint virgin with his
disabled girlfriend will never say
anything to anyone's face. And and and
you know that I've got a mouth, bro.
Yeah, but look, at least I've actually
met people, Dusty. At least I've
actually met people. You've seen me meet
people. Like several people, even though
I didn't know what they look like, bro.
This virgin with the nons dad and the
mom who hates him is never going to meet
anyone. He will never meet anyone. This
virgin never. He will always be a nasty
little keyboard warrior virgin. Still
never meeting anyone. Still running to
the police. You know, Smokey B said that
he's going to come here. He's going to
get his head smashed in. I'm going to
[ __ ] smash his head in, bro. If he
comes on here Saturday, I'm going to
smash the [ __ ] out of him. Yeah. Mark my
words, bro. He is not going back. Yeah.
I'm telling you right now. right here,
right now, bro. I don't care who it is,
he is not going back. Yeah, trust me.
I'm going to do him one so [ __ ] bad,
bro. Because to me, that's catching
somebody that I can't catch because they
won't show me where they are. Anyone
from L channel, anyone from LJ channel,
I don't like them, bro. Yeah. This is
the reason why I went live today. Simple. Yeah.
You know, you talk about dead relatives,
but your virgin ass your n dad is never
going to meet anyone. But people like
these kind of people, Dusty. This is
what I mean, bro. These people like
these kind of people because they love
nonsense on here. They love pedos.
That's why they That's why they go for
this [ __ ] Same with Terry. They'll
never meet you. No matter how many times
you try to meet these people, they will
not meet you, bro. They won't leave you
alone cuz they're jealous of you.
They're at you constantly cuz they're
jealous of you, right? And that's what
they do. And that's why they do this is
cuz they're jealous. They are jealous of
me. That's why they won't leave me
alone. Which is why I'm changing up the
content. Like I told you earlier, bro,
they will never leave you alone. It's
like Ronald Pump. You're younger, you're
better looking, and you got more money.
And it's the truth. It is the truth
because if you think of how many years
these people have done this on here, and
they will not leave me alone, bro. And
it's He's right. You're better looking.
You got more money. And it kills them.
And he was so right. He was so right. He
was ever that was ever behind that
account. It is stinking jealousy for
people to sit on here, bro. Yeah. And
I'm going to And I'm going to mention
this Smokeoky B. I said, "You are
willing. You are going to come here
Saturday and you are not going back. You
are not going back, bro." Yeah. Cuz I'm
I'm going to drag this [ __ ] in this
house, bro. Yeah. I'm going to drag this
fat [ __ ] in this house, bro. Trust me.
Yeah. And I'm going to spit in his face
and I'm going to say, "Fucking get out
of here. Leave me alone, you fat,
jealous cunt." And you're going to see
what's going to happen, bro. Cuz I'm
going to be live on Saturday. I ain't
going nowhere. Yeah, I am not going
nowhere. And I'm going to drag the fat
[ __ ] in the house, bro. Yeah, it's not
even going to be an outside thing. He's
going to be getting dragged in the
house. Trust me, bro. And I will do
whatever I need to do to win. Leave me
alone, you fat, ugly, jealous people.
Simple, bro. Yeah. Simple.
And you know what? Yeah. He's going to
get even more of a [ __ ] beating as
well, bro. When he comes in on Saturday,
he's going to get even more of a
beating, bro. Yeah. I've got a plan for
this [ __ ] bro. Trust me. Trust me.
Trust me. Yeah. Believe you me, bro. Do
not let everyone down, you [ __ ] Yeah.
It's not my fault. I'm not fat and ugly
like you, bro. Yeah,
bro. I don't want to fight everyone on
YouTube. This guy said he's coming on my door.
So, he said that he's coming on my door.
Yeah. So, I'm going to [ __ ] drag him
in the house, bro, and leave his [ __ ]
wife outside. Yeah. And I'm going to
slap him like a little silly [ __ ] that
he is. And the reason I want to meet
this non legs is because he's talking
about dead relatives, but he's never
going to say anything to anyone's face.
Him and his nod's dad and his mom that
hates him that starved him. His mom that
starved him is never going to say
anything to anyone's face. I don't want
to fight anyone really, you know. I
don't want to fight anyone. But these
jealous people will not leave me alone.
So that's what it is.
You know, I said to I said to Smokey Be,
"I'm willing to test your theory. I'm
willing to test your theory about
bullying." He say he was making post
saying that he's bullying people. Yeah.
So I said, "I'm willing to test your
bullying theory like they test the
Samsung phones." Yeah. That's what I
said. These people are so jealous of me.
It is unreal. Like my mama said this
several several times. They're jealous
of you. They're jealous of you. And it
is the truth. They are jealous for
people to do this every [ __ ] day for
years. I won't leave you alone. This
guy, he is getting batted when he comes
here. Mark my words, bro. He is getting
He is getting batted, bro. And I'm not
going to stop. I'm going to spit in his
face. Bro, you don't understand what I'm
going to do, bro. I swear to God on my
dead dad, bro. You're going to see
what's going to happen.
Yeah. I'm going to [ __ ] [ __ ] on him.
I'm going to piss on him, bro.
Everything for being a dirty little
keyboard while we a [ __ ] bro. You're
going to see what happens, bro. You're
going to see what happens.
I'm going to f I'm dragging him in the
house. I'm dragging him in the house, bro.
Trust me. I'm dragging a [ __ ] in the house.
Yeah, he's a [ __ ] another one, bro.
He's another one. Yeah,
he wants he wants to use the word
bullying, Greavesy. Yeah, we're going to
see bullying on Saturday. We're going to
see bullying on Saturday. Yeah. All
because you've got more family than them
and they're jealous of you. Would you
ever thought that people that are older,
right? People that are older would be
doing this, bro.
Like the guy is going to get violated.
Like you don't understand, bro. He is
going He is prepared to get violated
over YouTube. Do not does that not sound
mad to you, bro? Like does that not
sound mad? Yeah. That he is going to be
violated over fiberactive cable and he
doesn't care. Like he doesn't know what
the plan is, bro. He really doesn't know
what the plan is.
Trust me, bro. Trust me.
No, I want to. No, him and him, bro. Him and him.
Same thing with the [ __ ] little
[ __ ] Yeah. Orin na cuz he will never
say anything to anyone's face though.
This is what I'm saying. That they will
never say anything to anyone's face.
Triple. This little naunt with his n dad
and his mom that hates him will never
ever say anything to anyone's face.
Yeah, I copy Timmy saying because it's
the truth, bro. It's the truth.
I will more than happy beat the [ __ ] out
of these two this week. More so near
Christmas where these people have got no
family again. Have you not noticed this,
bro? Please. I want this [ __ ] to not let
me down on Saturday, bro. Please do not
let me let me down. Please let me
uppercut you one in your mouth, bro. and
make your please just let me get more
when I I swear to God, bro, when I get
my hands on one of these people, the
[ __ ] virgin [ __ ] with a mum that
hates him, [ __ ] smoking me, bro. Just
please let me [ __ ] violate you, bro.
Like, I'll I'll drag you in the house.
It's nothing, bro. It's nothing. Bring
whoever you want as well. I don't give a [ __ ]
This is the time of year, bro. All cuz
you got more family and more money than
them. This is why they're doing this,
bro. Listen. If you look at this, bro.
Yeah. Look at this. Yeah, this is all
because you are better looking and
you've got more money than them. Yeah.
And yes, I did tell you to come in the
door cuz I'm going to test your theory,
bro. I'm going to test this bullying
theory and everyone's going to see me
here Saturday as well.
Yeah, you can't because he runs to
police. The [ __ ] [ __ ] The virgin
[ __ ] whose mom hates him keeps running
to the police.
Yeah, I've got tons of evidence on him as well.
Yeah, I've got tons of on ev Do you know
what? Yeah. Here's what I'm going to do,
bro. Here's what Here's what we should
do with this little nons [ __ ] Yeah. Cuz
of Smokeoky B. Yeah. We should give this
[ __ ] one last chance, right, to meet me.
Yeah. One more one last chance to meet me, bro.
And if he doesn't, I'm not letting him
in and I'm going to just keep grassing
on him. Simple as that. If he is not
going to meet me, I'm just going to keep
grassing on him then. Simple as that. If
you don't meet me, right, fair and
square, right? I don't want you to text
me on WhatsApp. Anytime you come in now,
I'm just going to keep calling the
police. Keep calling the police. Calling
the police. Calling the police. Calling
the police. Calling the police. And when
this [ __ ] gets voided again, I'm going
to do posters again. Simple as that. I'm
going to do posters again. Yeah. And
everything. Now, I'm going to record.
So, you either want to do it the normal
way or we'll do it dirty. Simple. Like,
I I don't give a [ __ ] So, you're either
going to meet me, right? If you don't
meet me, I'm going to keep recording
everything and keep grassing because if
you're not going to meet someone, right,
I'm just going to be doing what you're
doing. Simple as that. Yeah. Simple. And
you can say that I'm a grass and be
biased. I don't give a [ __ ] if you do
not meet me. Yeah. I'm going to keep
going to the police. I'm going to break
that order and I'm going to do posters
again. Yeah. Simple. Yeah. Yeah. And as
soon as that gets cancelled, I'm doing
the posters again. So, if you don't meet
me, that's what's going to happen.
You're not going to be coming back on
these hangouts. You're not going to keep
projecting your [ __ ] shitty
childhood. And Smokeoky B doesn't need
to worry about that. You can more than
come on here, bro. Yeah. It doesn't
matter, bro. It doesn't matter. I've got
all of the evidence that he's doing.
I've got everything that this [ __ ] is
doing, harassing people on the internet,
but will not meet anyone. I don't give a
[ __ ] I don't give a [ __ ] bro. I've got
everything this little motherless [ __ ]
has done. So, it's all right, bro. I
don't give a [ __ ] All because he ain't
got no family. Same as Smokeoky B. This
is all cuz you got something they ain't
got. This has been the past two weeks
with these people. Jealous of me. Will
not leave me alone, bro. Yeah. Jealousy.
Jealousy. Jealousy will not leave me
alone for the past two weeks.
You know it has, bro. All cuz his mama
hates him. Yeah. Same with that smoky
be. I want this I want this [ __ ] to come
here. Yeah. Simple. That's all I want is
this this [ __ ] to come here.
Yeah. Simple. And it doesn't matter. I'm
leaving this live stream up as well,
bro. I'm leaving this live stream up. So
that's it. And I'm recording it. Yeah.
All cuz his mom hates him and he's going
to have no family for Christmas. The
same as this Smokeoky B. Yeah. Same as
this Smokey B. All big. Yeah. Behind the
keyboard, bro. They're all big behind
the keyboard. Yeah. That's what they
are. They're all big behind the keyboard.
All cuz you got more family than them.
Have you not seen this? Every day, bro.
Every day with these people will not
leave you the [ __ ] alone. Yeah.
Yeah. Exactly, bro. So that's No, no,
I'm recording all of it, bro. So I'm
going to say you either meet me or
that's that in it. Simple. Simple. Stop
running up your [ __ ] mouth. Yeah, you
[ __ ] stupid [ __ ] Cuz your [ __ ]
mum just like Smokey B. And and stick to
your word. Yeah. Just cuz you got no
family over Christmas. Jealousy. Yeah.
This has been all week, bro. All week
with these people. And that Smokeoky B.
Please let him come here. Please let him
come here and see what happens. Bring
whoever you want, bro. Prime whoever you want.
They hate because you're better looking
than them. It's been the same [ __ ] with
these people for two years, bro. Two
years. It has been the same [ __ ] with
these jealous people on the internet
that will not leave you the [ __ ] alone.
Yeah. Simple, bro. It's the truth, isn't it?
Why are they so jealous of me? What have
I You say that I'm this, that, and the
other. You You're saying that I'm this,
that, and the other, bro. Why are you so
jealous of me? What have I got that you
ain't? Like, you're saying that I'm all
of these things, bro. Whatever. Why are
you so jealous of me? I don't understand
the jealousy. It's been going on for
years and years and years with these
people. years and years and years with
these people, bro.
Why are they so [ __ ] jealous of me?
It's funny I'm asking, but it's
something that I'm asking, bro. I'm
really, really asking. You know,
you know what I'm saying, bro? Simple.
No, bro. I'm going to do I'm just going
to do a little video to this [ __ ] and
if he's not going to beat anyone, just
the same as the smoky beer. Yeah. Simple.
They're trying to ruin people's
Christmas cuz they ain't got no family.
Yeah. If this Smokey Bee comes here, I'm
going to [ __ ] smash the [ __ ] out of
him. Leave me alone, you fat ugly
bastard. Simple, bro. All cuz they're
sat there with no [ __ ] family. Every
Christmas. Every Christmas with these
self projectors. You know, I really hope
this [ __ ] does come on Saturday, bro. I
really don't do hope he comes. And I'm
going to smack him up in front of his
wife, bro. Seriously. Great in the same
atmosphere for years. cuz I hate these
people, bro. I seriously do. Yeah.
But like I said, bro, I'm going to be
saying the maddest [ __ ] bro. I'm going
to be saying the madest [ __ ] back. Yeah.
And if you don't meet me, then that's
it. No more hangouts. Simple.
You know what I'm saying, bro? Yeah.
Bring your wife. Bring your fat ugly
wife, bro. And see what happens to you,
you [ __ ] stupid little [ __ ] Yeah.
I'm going to do a video dedicated to
both of them, bro. Yeah. Yep.
You know, your mom starved you, you
little [ __ ] that had run into the police
several times and that's it, bro. After
that, after that, bro, I just We're not
letting any of these people in because
they're clearly being self reflectors.
So, that's it.
Yeah, I'm getting it Saturday. We'll see
who's getting it Saturday, bro. No one's
getting nothing. No one's getting
nothing with these little
self-reflecting little low lives. Ain't
no one getting nothing, bro. you know, simple.
Yeah, they did do this last time last
year as well.
Yeah, they done this last year as well,
bro. Like, he's going to come on my door
like some [ __ ] fat, ugly, jealous
[ __ ] cuz he's got no family is going to
come on my door, bro. Are you mad? Yeah.
Simple. All because they're jealous of
you. This is insane. The jealousy
towards me for the past two [ __ ] weeks. Madness.
Yeah. They're not going to ruin anyone's
Christmas. Yeah. His mother hates him.
Yeah. His mom used to [ __ ] knock his
And that's it, bro. Same [ __ ] Same [ __ ]
with these people. All cuz they got no
family. Yeah. Everything that they try
to say, bro. And I really do hope this
[ __ ] does come, bro, on Saturday. I
really does hope he does come.
This little self-reflector. I really
hope this [ __ ] does come so I can
[ __ ] smack him on, bro. I really
does. I really do, bro.
Yeah. [ __ ] little self-reflecting
[ __ ] fat. You [ __ ] thinking that
you're going to come on people's door.
Yeah. Thinking that you're going to
start coming on people's door, bro.
Don't forget. Yeah. It's it's it's a no
hold bars. It's a no hold bars. Yes. I
wanted to test your I wanted to test
your bullying theory, bro. Yeah. I
wanted to test your bullying theory.
You're never going to meet anyone. None
of you. Bro, why don't you come
together? Why don't you come together?
Both of you. You and your little
boyfriend. Why don't you come to Why
don't Why don't the two familyless
losers come to together? The two people
with no family. Come on. Come on. You
and the two familyless losers should
come on Saturday together. Simple, bro.
Madness. [ __ ] absolute madness. Insane, bro.
Yeah. Look, now [ __ ] Laney's [ __ ]
woken up as well, bro. What the [ __ ] bro?
Yeah, this this guy is definitely
getting it on Saturday, bro. He's
definitely definitely getting it. and
anyone else you want to bring. You're
more than welcome to. You're more than
Yeah. But it's not funny though, is it
Greasy? Because this is every year with
these self-p projecting people, isn't
it? It's literally every year with these
self-reflecting people that ain't got no
family. Yeah. Do you know what I'm
saying? It's every year with the selfjecting
losers, right? And like I said, if you
don't if you do not come out right, I'm
just going to keep running to the
police. Simple. That's simple as that.
Just like what would you people do every
day because you got no [ __ ] family.
Yeah. Running up your mouth. Just all
you have to do is just keep running to
the police every time he keeps coming
up. Every time he keeps commenting,
you're just going to have to keep going
to the police. Simple triple. If they're
not going to meet you. Yeah. If they're
not going to meet you, like smokey me.
I'm not going to call the police on him.
I promise you I'm not grass. If this
[ __ ] is going to keep on doing his [ __ ]
for another year and he's not going to
meet anyone, then that's exactly what
I'm going to keep doing and I'm going to
keep doing it and doing it and doing it
and doing it and doing it and doing it
and doing it and doing it. Smokey B
don't need to worry about that. You
know, that's nothing to do with him.
But, you know, you got the choice. Meet
someone. Rock up or that's what's going
to be happening. Simple.
Anytime I see your [ __ ] ugly [ __ ]
motherless face on my [ __ ] scream
recorded. Scream recorded. Scream
recorded. That's all that's going to
keep happening, bro. You know, I don't
mind the laughs, bro. And whatever. I
don't mind the laughs and, you know,
whatever. Like, like a bit of banter,
but no, [ __ ] that, bro. You're not going
to run your shitty little virgin [ __ ]
mouth to me, your [ __ ] mom hates you,
and then think you're not going to meet
anyone. Just meet someone. Simple.
You can both message each other. You can
both come here on Saturday. Not a
problem. No one's scared of two
familyless losers, you know. Simple.
Madness. Absolute madness.
[ __ ] the age of these people. Hey,
Mad. How how they can sit there, bro,
every day. Yeah. For years doing this.
Years doing this.
Jealousy. Jealousy. Jealousy. How long
can you be at someone, bro? You understand?
Yeah. They can come all they want and
they're going to see what's going to
happen. They're going to see what's
going to happen.
You know what I mean?
He's talking about how he's going to
[ __ ] stop coming on people's door
with his [ __ ] fat chubby hands. Don't
[ __ ] let us down, bro. You know what I mean?
All cuz someone's got more [ __ ]
family than you, you fat, ugly [ __ ] You
know what I mean, bro?
Every year with these jealous people,
you see every [ __ ] year with these
jealous people, bro.
You know, they definitely aren't coming,
bro. All cuz you're better looking and
got more family than these people. You
know what I'm saying? And and these
people are trying to sit there and say
how they've got lives and they've got a
job and they've got this and they've got
that. What? Cuz you're better looking
and you got more family than these
[ __ ] little geeks.
Simple. What? No one's allowed to have a
family cuz they're fat and ugly and they
got nothing in their lives. you know,
jealous fat little Mongols. And and tell
him to bring his wife up, bro. I I will
slap his wife up as well. You come over,
I'm going to slap your wife up as well,
you [ __ ] silly little [ __ ]
Yeah, that's another thing. You [ __ ]
stupid [ __ ] Bring your wife, I'll slap
her up in front of you, bro. Watch.
Watch what's going to happen on
Saturday. But I'm going to see red with
these people, bro. I'm telling you, I'm
going to see red. Yeah. You don't know
what I'm like, bro. You don't know what
I'm like. Yeah.
Cuz it's true, bro. Your your theory is
going to be tested and failed. Yeah.
Like in these Samson factories. No
family again. Yeah. Just because you
might have a [ __ ] wife, you silly
little [ __ ] sausage fingered [ __ ]
Yeah. Yeah. You sausage fingered little
loner with you little shitty little
£6,000 doesn't mean you've got a family.
Doesn't mean you got a family. Don't let
us all down, bro. Do not let us all down.
[ __ ] stupid little [ __ ] with no
family. jealous fatly [ __ ] with no
That's what it is with these people.
Yeah. This is all because I've got more
family than I'm better looking than
them. You do realize that this is they
have not left me alone for the past two
weeks. Yeah. This fat ugly [ __ ] with
only six grand to his name, bro. Yeah.
Has not left me alone for the past two
weeks. This fat ugly man with shitty
little comments. Yeah. And I will talk
about his [ __ ] wife. And I'll talk
about his [ __ ] wife as well. Yeah.
All cuz someone's got more family than
you. You [ __ ] shitty little loner.
You lonely [ __ ] Yeah. So madness, bro.
Write in your shitty comments, you
little Milton Kees boy. But I'll slap
your [ __ ] wife up in front of you.
I'll slap her up in front of you.
[ __ ] silly little [ __ ] Yeah, stupid
little [ __ ] trying to ruin people's
Christmas cuz you're a fat loner with no
family. We've seen your [ __ ] sausage
fingers, bro. Yeah, we've seen your
[ __ ] sausage fingers. You stupid little [ __ ]
Yeah, [ __ ] little [ __ ] Pair of
[ __ ] [ __ ] bro. Both of them. Yeah, mad.
It's all because It's all because these
people have got no family. They got nothing.
It's all cuz they got no one. This is
what it is with people here, bro. It's
because they're little losers that have got nobody.
It's because they're lonely, ugly people
that have got nothing in their life.
They do this every year. Every year.
Every year. Every year, bro. They do
this. Yeah. Every [ __ ] year. Because
they got no family. They come on here
and self-reflect. Every [ __ ] year, bro. Yeah.
[ __ ] stupid little [ __ ]
trying to say how you're going to come
on people's doors, bro. You're not doing
nothing. You little Milton Kees boy with
your slaggy [ __ ] wife. And I'm
talking about your wife now. Yeah. Yeah.
And guess what? Laney sees all what you
do on here as well.
Fat, ugly, jealous people. She sees
everything that you people do on here,
bro. They She see she sees everything
that you do on here. Yeah. You fat,
ugly, jealous people that won't leave
people alone. She sees everything that
you do on here, bro. So if someone comes
on the door, you know. Yeah, that's that.
She She She knows what you people are
like. Fat, jealous, will not leave
people alone. They They know what you
you [ __ ] are like, bro. Yeah, they know
what you [ __ ] are like. Yeah. Simple,
bro. It's mad. You ain't coming on
anyone's door. You're not bullying no
one. You [ __ ] chubby sausage sausage
fingers with a fat ugly wife. And I am
mouthing off to you now. I am mouthing
off to you now because I'm expecting you
on Saturday, bro. Yeah.
These jealous people will not leave me
alone. It's exactly what that Ronald
Pump said. You know,
stop your [ __ ] talking, you [ __ ]
silly coward. You're not going to be
knocking no sense into no [ __ ] Silly [ __ ]
Simple, bro. All cuz they got no family.
They do this every year. Do you know
what? I'm going to do a video on this,
bro. I'm actually going to do a video on
this. I'm really going to do a video on
this. This is every year with these
people that ain't got no family.
Everyone sees the trend with these
people now, bro. Everybody sees the
trend with these people. Yeah.
It's cuz they got no family.
They done this in Albert. They done this
in Albert Square as well, bro.
Yeah. And trust me, let me tell you
something as well. If you do come on
Saturday, it ain't going to be a fight.
Uh, it's not going to be a fight, okay?
It ain't going to be a fight. Trust me,
it's not going to be no fight. It's not
going to be no you teach someone lesson,
you [ __ ] low life.
You're just going to take multiple L's.
So, you're you're best off just not even
wasting your time. Sort yourself, your
fat, ugly self out. Stop coming on here
self-reflecting every [ __ ] day, you know? Simple.
It's not going to be a fight. Yeah, it's
All because you got no family. You mto
of a man. You like your wife is a mto of
a woman. All cuz the two mters have got
no family. Every time this year every
time you [ __ ] m of a man. I'm going
to say it to your face as well on
Saturday, bro. I'm going to say it to
your [ __ ] face. Yeah. I don't know
where you're from or where you live,
bro. Yeah. But that's not what happens. Yeah. Simple as that.
Yeah. And that's all I'm going to say,
bro. That's all I'm going to say. Now,
the [ __ ] ain't getting a link. You want
to You want to say something, you can
say it to my face now. I didn't mind the
odd banter. Yeah. You're not coming up
now, bro. You're not coming up now. You
come and say something to my face. And
this is going to be a video as well. You
bring your little boyfriend as well on
Saturday. I I'll let I'll have two of
you on me, bro. I'm that confident.
Yeah. I'll have two on you. Yeah. So,
you want to say something, you can come
on Saturday with your boyfriend. You
like to [ __ ] reply to people's
comments over and over and over and over
again. Yeah. You want to reply to each
other's comments. So, why don't you both
come out? Why don't you both come on
Saturday? Why don't you both come and
I'll do the both of you come soon. Simple. Yeah.
You was doing this last summer as well,
bro. Not as much, but I remember you
doing this last summer as well. Yeah. I
remember you doing this last summer. Not
not as much, but you was doing you was
doing it uh you was doing it last summer
as well. So, you've been doing this for
a very long time, you little [ __ ] house,
despite knowing where people live. Yeah,
but two of you little [ __ ] houses are
never going to meet anyone. Bring your
boyfriend. Bring your boyfriend.
Maybe it was this summer. I think it was
this summer. Yeah. Either way, just
bring your boyfriend. I'll have no
problem doing doing you both, bro. Yeah.
You got a lot of energy behind the
keyboard. You got a lot of [ __ ] [ __ ]
to say behind the keyboard, bro. a lot
of [ __ ] to say.
Madness, bro. I can't even believe this
is this is this is even a thing, bro.
All cuz they got no family. This is a
madness. This is literally a [ __ ]
madness. All cuz they have got no family.
This is, by the way, I'm I'm just going
to keep adding it up like over and over
and over and over and over and over and
over and over and over and over and over
again. And I also want to point out how
sad you're actually going to look if you
actually do come on Saturday as well.
You're going to look sad and you're
going to take multiple L's. But again,
people that have got no family would
really have nothing to lose. You know
what I'm saying? So they don't mind
showing themselves up, you know, acting
like you're going to come start coming
on people's doors like who do you think
you are, bro? Yeah. Yeah. Two weeks with
this three days. This has been going on
for two weeks with these people.
So you got anything to say, you can come
with your boyfriend smoky bit. You know
that's that that's another thing. Until
then, bro, you're not coming up on the hangouts
having you projecting your [ __ ]
little lonely life when your mother
hates you. [ __ ] that, bro. You you and
him can come together. Simple.
Cuz you ain't got no [ __ ] [ __ ]
mother. You ain't got no dad. Yeah. You
ain't got no [ __ ] nothing. Sat on
here talking [ __ ] after [ __ ] after [ __ ]
You know what I mean?
Madness, bro. Mad.
These people really are mad, bro.
Seriously, they are. You actually have
to think like what the [ __ ] is going on.
You cheeky bastard [ __ ] talking about
how you're going to come on people's
doors. You know that thing with L J, right? Yeah.
You know that thing with LJ? Yeah. That
was like years ago, bro. And even then,
that weren't even that bad. So, you
think someone's going to lose to a clown
like you? Seriously, bro. Yeah, we've
all seen your hands.
And make sure next year you don't let
the same thing repeat, bro. Make sure
next year you don't let the same thing
repeat where you're coming on here
December cuz you got no family. Cuz your
family don't like you. Yeah. You're the
one coming on here saying about how
you're bullying people. Yeah. Every
single day. So, I said, "If you're going
to bully me, come and bully me to my
face." Yeah. That's that that's what it
is. But you won't do that
[ __ ] idiots, bro. Do you know what? I
think it's best just staying off in this
this [ __ ] until the first of January.
You know, I generally generally
generally think it is like after
Saturday. I don't know if you agree on
that or but yeah,
I'll challenge both of you little
[ __ ] Yeah, I ain't scared of none of
you, bro. None of you. None of you. None
of you. So that's that, bro.
Probably it's best to be honest after
Saturday. Let all the projectors calm
down again. This has been non-stop for
two weeks, bro. Non-stop for two weeks.
Seriously, it has. This has been
non-stop with these people cuz they
ain't got no got no family, bro. Yeah.
And they're depressed as well, bro. And
that's the thing. They're [ __ ]
depressed as well. You're not going to
[ __ ] start putting someone in their
place. I don't know who you [ __ ]
think you are. Yeah.
who you think you're talking to, bro.
And when you do come on Saturday, it's
also going to prove how much of a low
life you are as well, and you really
don't have anything, you know? So, it
will show you up even more. So, I love
it, bro. I will love it. I will really,
really, really love it. You could have
easily said that you're going to come to
London and you'll go live. No, you don't
want to do that. You want to try to look
good for YouTube. What are you, bro?
What are you? Yeah, you're saying about
how you're older than people, bro. What
are you really? Really? Cuz trust me,
all of the L's I've took before, I'm not
going to [ __ ] take an L against you
or no [ __ ] stinky little virgin,
right, that lives in Kent. I ain't
taking no [ __ ] Yeah,
I am not taking no L's against [ __ ]
you know, any of you [ __ ] So, make
your make sure you come with your little
boyfriend as well because, bro, it's not
even going to be a twoon-one.
Yeah, a baseball bat. Yeah, bro. I don't
know about a baseball bat, but all I'm
saying I am not take I am not losing to
this [ __ ] Trust me. You know,
so just put your money where your mouth
is and don't [ __ ] it like the last
person did. Yeah.
Do you know what it is mad how how
someone Yeah. is willing to like travel
to someone just cuz they got no family,
bro? Like, do you do you not think that
is like madness
that they're actually willing to do this
all because they've got no family over
Christmas? You know,
cuz if you wasn't doing what you was
doing in the first place, you wouldn't
have been called out in the first place.
Do you understand? So, you clearly ain't
got no life despite what you're telling
people on the internet.
You know what I'm saying? You clearly
clearly don't. How old am I? 28.
28. Am I 28?
Yeah, I'm 28. And you said that you're
older than me. So you're 33, 34, right? You know,
and that's what it is. And you're and
you're and you're still doing this [ __ ]
and you're going to be embarrassed.
They have nothing. They literally have
got nothing in their life. That's why
they do this. They really don't not have
no family or these people on here, bro.
Trust me, they really don't.
Yeah. And the other thing, so like we
got people going to people's doors even
though they're going to lose all cuz
they've got no family. Think about it,
bro. Just think about these people and
they're saying that they're [ __ ]
older than people. Yeah. Madness, bro. Absolute madness.
Absolute madness. Ronald Pump was right.
These jealous people will never leave
you alone. I should have come off it
years ago, bro. I should have literally
come off of it years ago.
So I tell you what, bro. You bring your
wife and you also bring that little [ __ ]
with you as well and I'll [ __ ] knock
the [ __ ] up all three of you out. Yeah.
Simple, bro. You need to get some help.
Get some help, bro. You generally
generally need it. It's not normal.
Yeah. So, what are you 33, 34? You're
typing all day on YouTube. You ain't got
jack [ __ ] Yeah. And I'm going to show
you on Saturday that you ain't got no
jack [ __ ] You [ __ ] loser. How many
times have you keep going on at me and
Timmy, me and Timmy, me and Timmy. You
ain't got no life, bro. You're prolific.
Yeah, just like this Red Star. You're
prolific. We know the people that have
got [ __ ] in life, but it ain't you.
Yeah, it ain't you,
you know? All cuz someone's better
looking and got more family than you.
[ __ ] what a loser, mate. Look at You
know what I mean? Like, it's this is
insane, bro. Insane, you know?
So yeah, just bring your little
boyfriend as well,
you know. I'll take you both on the same
time or oneonone since you clearly have
these foul [ __ ] a foul [ __ ] mouth,
you know? Madness. It is [ __ ] insane, bro.
Why should people have to [ __ ] ruin
their Christmas? Cuz you've got to no
family. Yeah. You know what I'm saying?
Because nobody wants you. Yeah. It
doesn't matter if you got a wife or not.
You ain't got no family. Clear. You
ain't got no mom. You ain't got no
[ __ ] dad. Yeah, it it's the truth,
bro. It is the truth.
You know what I'm saying? You [ __ ]
fat handed little [ __ ] idiot. Yeah,
I'll teach them a good old lesson, bro.
A good old lesson. Good oldfashioned lesson, bro.
A good oldfashioned hiding. Yeah, that's
what they need. a good oldfashioned hide
and they'll learn to stop coming on here
[ __ ] annoying people.
Yeah. And this other [ __ ] if he doesn't
come right, then I am going to be
recording everything that he does.
Everything that he does. I'm going to
keep ignoring him and I'm just going to
keep running to the police. Simple.
That's it. Or maybe I might even run to
the police to be honest. I'll probably
just ignore it to be honest with you. Uh
because everything he does will just be getting ignored.
It's becoming worse and worse and worse
now, bro. This is becoming worse and
worse and worse. Do you understand?
This is normally like, okay, it's the
odd wind up now. This is getting really
really really very very nasty now.
And we are the 11th of December. So, we're two
we're two weeks away from Christmas.
No, it's not going to end well for him.
It's not going to end well for him.
Definitely not going to end well for
him. So this has actually become really
really nasty now. All because they have
got no family.
All because they have got no [ __ ]
family over Christmas. This is what this
is. All cuz they're ugly fat people that
ain't got no family, bro. Swear to God.
You know, it's sad. All because you got
you're better looking than you got more
family than them. It's bad, bro. these
fat, ugly, jealous people.
Yeah, it's sad. It's really, really sad,
bro. You know, it's actually bad and sad.
It is actually getting more prolific.
And they're not going to ruin my
Christmas. Yeah. All this [ __ ] has got
to do is put right his money where his
mouth is and do what he says he's going
to do. Simple.
They're like the Grinch, bro. They're
trying to ruin Christmas because they've
got nothing. Yeah. They do this
everywhere. Any every you know all the
time. Oh, you got no money, your skin,
all the things that they are, bro. But
the thing is, yeah, is that they are
literally like the Grinch of Christmas,
bro. Like, they actually just want to
ruin people's Christmas cuz they've got
no one. This what really tells you, bro.
I'm right about these people. January,
February, March, April, whatever month
they're doing it, bro. This This month
tells you what these people are like.
For real, bro. For real. really really
nasty nasty spiteful people.
So, at the end of the day, like, yeah,
just bring your boyfriend with you. Just
bring your boyfriend with you. [ __ ]
Prime. [ __ ] the other woman. [ __ ] the
bouncer. I want you two [ __ ] Yeah, you
Simple. I want you and your [ __ ] boyfriend.
Yeah, because this is an LT now. You
can't try and blame LT and ret t Today
we don't want to hear none of that [ __ ] now. Yeah.
[ __ ] stalkers. [ __ ] fat, ugly,
prolific people. They ain't got no life.
See, see that? How hard can it be? This
guy's a normal guy, bro. Yeah, this guy
is a normal guy, bro. Yeah, he come on
my door before. How hard can it be? Must
be 42, 45. I forget the guy's name. This
is what you call a normal guy, bro. On
the community. Yeah, I don't know how
old he is.
Um, his name is Simon. He must be in his
40s now. Yeah. This is what you call a
normal guy with kids. He doesn't bother
anyone. Even though he goes on holidays,
he doesn't come on air. He doesn't bother anyone.
Yeah. Just a normal guy that stays out
of everything. Do you understand?
Yeah. This Smokeoky B, bro, and this
[ __ ] non legs, the two with no
family. Yeah. Have been absolutely prolific
for the past two weeks. Yeah. because
they have got no family. They have got
no life. Yeah, that's it.
Uh he come on my door to give me a coke
and a football bet cuz he was around my
area in it. So he just wanted to see how
I was doing and that. Yeah. Did like the
likes of this person Smokey B. Yeah.
Ain't got no family, ain't got no looks,
ain't got no life. Yeah. He might have a shitty 6,000
in his 40s, mate, but you know, at the
end of the day, bro, what does a guy
really deeply have? Nothing. Yeah. And
you're going to see that on Saturday.
Yeah. If he if he grows a pair of balls,
you know, simple.
Yeah. He gave me a Coke and a football
bet cuz he knew I liked Coke.
Yeah. I stopped talking to him, but he's
that's what you call a normal person.
He's older than me. So, we don't pick
people out of a [ __ ] box, bro. And
start saying, "Oh, yeah, everyone's
jealous of me." Nah, no. We don't We
don't think we're anything. You know
what I mean, bro?
Yeah, he's a cool guy, bro. Yeah, he
come on my door years ago, bro. He's all
right. And this is just someone that's
just normal. Um, he lost a parent, you
know, was just talking about stuff.
These guys are not normal. They do not
have anything in their life to be doing
this. This nodlex, this smoky bee, they
don't have anything in their lives.
Yeah. It's like you can tell with these
people like who's actually got a life
and who ain't got a life. Yeah.
It's bad. It's actually like It's bad.
Like it's bad enough, right, that they
actually come on here every day trying to like
make people feel the way that they feel,
but then they're actually trying to ruin
people's Christmas. Now,
what the [ __ ] They're trying to ruin
people's Christmas now. You can you can
make this [ __ ] up,
but they do it they do it in January as
well. They do it December. January.
Definitely. Definitely. Definitely. They
definitely do it these two months as
well. But not obviously December is the
worst. And then Yeah.
They just want to ruin people because
they're ruined. They're ruined. They're
ruined goods. They're damaged goods.
You know what I'm saying? And it ain't
going to happen, bro. It is not going to happen.
You know, and the Smokeoky B ain't going
to be happening anymore when he comes
here on Saturday. He won't even He won't
even exist anymore, bro. On here. So,
so that's it.
So, yeah, it does go to show it. It does
go to show it, bro. Yeah. Christmas for
one for you people. You've made that
clear. Yeah. Christmas for one for you
people. Yeah, definitely. Definitely,
mate. You've more than proved that you
people are going to be alone on
Christmas. You people have more than
proved that. I'll be doing this video in
a bit. Anyways, so and I'm going to tell
him basically who to bring. And if he
doesn't, so yeah, Christmas for one is
definitely definitely you people. You've
proved that over the past two weeks with
what you have [ __ ] done. Yeah. With
what you have done.
What is it with you people, bro? What is
it? What is it? What is it? Yeah, you're
supposed you're supposed to be older
than people. Yeah, you're supposed to be
older than people, right?
And you're still doing this year in year
out. Year in year out, year in year out.
Bro, listen. Whatever your issues are in
your life, right? Being bullied,
having no money, whatever the [ __ ] it
is, it's not anyone else's problem. It's
not anyone else's fault. Yeah. You could
have [ __ ] done something eight years
ago instead of being on here whilst you
were still semi young, but you didn't.
You chose to stay on here. Keep calling
people what you are. That's your own
fault that you've got no family over
Christmas. Don't let Don't [ __ ] take
that out on me, bro.
You know, do not take that out on me. Do
not take that out on me, bro.
You know, because you're ugly or you're
skinned or you're this or you're that or
whatever the [ __ ] it is you are. That
ain't my problem, bro. Don't
self-reflect your [ __ ] on me and try to
tell me you're going to come on my door,
bro. Cuz that just ain't happening. That
Simple. That just ain't happening. So,
you really really have got no life.
Simple. You really have got no life,
bro. Look at the [ __ ] I've had with
women and stuff. Yeah. The past [ __ ]
god knows how many years. Do you see me
coming on the internet saying
you're this, you're that,
you're this, you're that, you're this.
Yeah, I'm I'm leaving next year, bro.
I'm definitely definitely leaving it.
Well, it's either I'm leaving or I'm
just not going live anymore. And I'm
just doing content video. Yeah.
Or I'm just doing content video. One of
the two, bro.
It's either content video or I'm
leaving. And I'm not going to lie. So,
it's one of It's one of the two, bro.
cuz this is [ __ ] weird, bro. Very weird.
So, I might just do videos and whatever.
But yeah, I explained all of this on a
video anyways, bro. But whatever your
problem is, bro. Yeah. Like, you had
your life to change it, bro. You
shouldn't be trying to ruin other
people's Christmas because your family
hate you, you know? That's that's
nothing to do with me, bro.
So, it's either that it's going to be
content or I'm either just going to [ __ ]
it all off cuz this is [ __ ] up, bro.
Yeah, really, really, really [ __ ] up.
I can understand the whole wind up thing
and trying to take the piss and but no,
no, no. You're talking about dead
relatives cuz your mama hates you. So,
why don't you [ __ ] join this [ __ ] on
Saturday and see what happens? I promise
you if you beat me, I won't say it's a
2v one, bro. Yeah. You wanted to piss
people off. Now you've pissed me off. Yeah. Simple.
Just traveling. Yeah.
Just traveling videos. Just whatever
whatever comes to mind, bro. Like just
just saving the likes and comments,
which is what I was going to do cuz
there's no point with these people.
They're just jealous. They think they
know people's life. They don't know
people's life. Yeah.
No, they can't a getting a link. You
want a link, bro? I'll tell you a link.
Come here on Saturday with your boyfriend.
Yeah. Come here on Saturday with your
boyfriend and see if you're going to say
any of that vow [ __ ] to my face. Yeah.
That's your link, [ __ ] It's only a
couple of days. It's only a couple of
days away. Yeah. So, bro, let's see how
wicked your mouth is. Yeah. That's an
old school saying when you when you're
in front of someone. Simple as that.
Little keyboard warrior.
Madness, bro. Madness.
But yeah, there'll be content. Yeah,
bro. There'll be content.
There'll be content. Just all different
things. But yeah, you want to say
something, bro? You You come on
Saturday, bro. I'm making it even easier
for you. I'm making it easier for you. Yeah.
This is seriously pathetic, bro. You
people really need to grow up.
Really, really need to grow up. Mad.
>> Yeah. Yeah. You keep saying that, bro.
That ain't happening.
Yeah, that ain't happening, bro. Yeah,
that's not happening. You're all little
keyboard worries and you're not going to
ruin anyone's Christmas.
You little Christmas [ __ ] projectors. Yeah.
Just cuz you people are fat and ugly and
you ain't got no [ __ ] family, bro. Do
not take out on us just cuz your family
hates you. Yeah. Not even saying stuff
to wind people up. Like you're not going
to slap no one, bro. You come on this
door and I'm telling you, you're not
going back. Believe you me, you ain't
going. You are not going back. Trust me.
Yeah. Simple, bro.
And that's a good thing as well, bro,
because you're not going to try and get
the police involved, bro. I'll [ __ ] you
up real life, bro. Yeah. And you're not
going you're not going to call the police. Yeah.
Oh, police. I went on someone's door
because I got no family and I want to
try and ruin other people's. Do you know
what I'm saying?
Yeah, brother. You're going to be
Listen, listen, listen. I don't need to
say anything. Yeah, I don't need to say
anything. you people what you've done in
the past two since this month of
December what you people have done you
have proved what you are bro you have
proved what you're about yeah talk about
whatever you want listen
bro you people have proved what your
Christmas is going to be you've more
than proved it
yeah you have more than proved it more
than proved what you're about yeah
then they can run to the police oh
please I went on someone's door because
I got no family for and they slap me up
or they done much worse. I don't know
what I'm going to do yet. All I know is
someone ain't coming to my door, mate.
That's all I know. No matter what it takes.
So, what I'm saying, bro,
this guy's done this to LT as well
before without um without bringing this
uh guy up before. He's he's done this to
a couple of people. This little
self-reflector. He's done this to a
couple of people.
He has done it to a couple of people,
bro. He's definitely done it to a couple
of people. this smoky BS. Yeah. Yeah.
It's all good, bro. All good.
Yeah, they can try to come, bro. They
can try to come.
Yeah, they can try it. They can try it,
bro. And they'll see what happens.
No one's coming on this door. No one's Yeah,
it's definitely not happening.
But I should It is my fault. I should
have left. I should have left ages ago.
The these people's jealousy will never
stop. It is, you know, I'm not perfect
as well, bro. To be fair,
it's like I've said to you many, many
times before. I'll say it once, I'll say it again.
When you're not fat and ugly like these
people, they pick problems with people,
right? This is one of the main reasons
why even though Joseph R seems cool and
whatever, right? You got to understand
that he's biased in many ways. Do you
understand, bro? He's biased in many ways.
So they pick basically they pick
problems with people that are like
younger and better looking and just
[ __ ] you know? They can they could they
could, you know, they can talk about
people's lives and whatever, bro, but
look at their lives.
You know what I'm saying, bro? Yeah.
They find problems with people that are
better looking and younger than them,
bro. They're prolific. Very, very
Nah, I'm not leaving, bro. I'm just
going to do content videos because these
self-reflectors are not just they're
just not worth responding to.
Trust me, ain't no one coming on this door,
bro. Do you know this is an area, bro?
So, what do they actually think is going
to happen? This is an actual area.
Like, what do you actually think is
going to happen?
like you know what I'm saying?
So yeah, and back to that Joseph Ferrar.
Yeah, that Joseph Ferrar is um he's he's
he's another one of them as well basically.
Feel sorry for Laney to be honest. I
actually feel sorry for Laney.
Sad, bro, isn't it?
Yeah, that ain't happening.
No, that is not happening.
Yeah, you got white. So that must mean
that must mean that must mean that
you've got to be in your 30s and you're
and you're doing this just because
someone's going to have a better
Christmas than you, bro. Listen, you
you're not a newcomer, bro. Yeah,
you're not a newcomer, bro. You know
what I'm saying? Like, you've been doing
this for years. It's bad. It's so sad.
You know, I don't know why they can't
just leave people to have a Christmas
all cuz they their lives are over. Their
lives are ruined. It doesn't mean they
have to try to ruin other people's lives
just cuz their lives are ruined.
They're definitely jealous of me. I've
been saying it all all along. It's
jealousy. I've been saying they will do
anything to make people feel like these
fat ugly losers. It is jealousy, bro. Of
course, it's jealousy. And that Joseph
Farrar does it as well.
Look at the pattern. Look at the
December pattern, bro. They've been
doing this. Yeah.
It's madness. It's absolutely madness.
All cuz people have got family in there.
Fat, lonely people. This is where all of
this comes from, bro. All of this comes
trying to ruin people's Christmas cuz
they're loners. Who's passed their
[ __ ] sale by date, bro? Not much
older than me, but got a wife. So,
you're older than 30. So, that must mean
Sad, bro. It's actually sad.
Definitely definitely losers. But like I
said, bring your boyfriend as well.
Bring your boyfriend as well.
Bring your [ __ ] boyfriend. And I And
I didn't even say I didn't even
necessarily call this [ __ ] out to my
door. I just said, "Show me your
I basically said, "Show me your um I
want to test out this theory.
cuz it's the truth. You're saying that
you're bullying people. You're coming on
writing pavagraph saying that you're
bullying people. Yeah. So I said I'll
test out your theory. It's the truth.
So really these people have actually started it.
So but you know they're narcissistic and
they can't they won't admit that. So
that's absolutely fine bro.
You would have thought really bro if
these people had family
they would actually be doing like
Christmas shopping. they'd actually be
doing stuff instead of like coming here
and taking a big fat L that they're
never going to forget for the rest of
their life. Like, think about this
logically now, bro. This is how you're
going to catch these clowns out. This is
how you're really, really going to catch
these clowns out. Yeah,
it's madness. It is actually a [ __ ] madness, bro. You know,
jealous people on this community. It's madness.
So yeah, I'll be doing I'll be doing
that video anyways, lad. And I'm going
to tell him to bring that foul mouth
[ __ ] with him as well. You both got a
big [ __ ] mouth. Yeah, you both got a
big mouth, you and the [ __ ] virgin.
And what is it going to be, bro? Is it
going to be another year of this [ __ ] H
is it going to be another year of this
[ __ ] with you jealous people? Or are you
going to do something different on the
1st of January?
Mad. What is it? Is it going to be
another year of this [ __ ] H
madness. Yeah. Another year this [ __ ] [ __ ] clown.
>> Yeah, [ __ ] absolute clowns.
So, we got someone we got someone saying
in a comment on someone's door. Then we
got another person self-reflecting their mummy issues.
No one's bringing any [ __ ] You people
will not leave me alone. You have not
left me alone for the past two weeks.
Yeah. You jealous people have not left
me alone for the past [ __ ] two weeks.
So, I said if you're going to bully
someone, come and bully me to my face.
Yeah. That's what I said. Yeah. Cuz
you jealous people with no family will
not to leave people the [ __ ] alone. You
know, weak in week
with you [ __ ] jealous people cuz you
ain't got no [ __ ] family. You know,
everyone has seen this now for the past
two [ __ ] weeks, you know?
[ __ ] go and [ __ ] you know what I
mean, bro? Like, go and get a life. Get
a [ __ ] life, bro.
I didn't already. No, I haven't already
had her moved again. You're
narcissistic. You're narcissistic. Yeah.
Stop trying to ruin people's Christmas
because you because you ain't got no
family for Christmas. Yeah. Simple,
simple, simple. And I also gave you an
alternative. I said you can go live in
London. I said go live in London. Didn't
I didn't I say go live in London? So,
you could have easily went live in
London, but again, you want to be a
jealous [ __ ] and you think you're going
to come on someone's door. Typical [ __ ]
with you people that's got no family.
Same [ __ ] every year. It never changes.
Just like the same projection [ __ ] never
changes with you people every [ __ ]
year. Same old self project projection
cuz your lives are over. So, do you
think like Yeah, bro. If you people had
family, you wouldn't be doing this [ __ ]
You would not be doing it. You'd pack it
in. You pack this [ __ ] in, but you can't
pack it in. You know, you can't You
literally can't pack it in. You're prolific. Yeah.
Simple. And And especially now, bro. You
know what I'm saying? Especially Especially now.
That's what it is. Why do you think no
one's going for Monty, bro?
Why do you think no one is going for Monty? Hm.
Why do you think no one's going for
Monty? Because the guy's got no family.
You don't understand? Yeah. They call
the guy [ __ ] nons and he's this and
all that. Why do you think people are
not [ __ ] with him? Because he's got
no family just like these people. These
people are these people get on with
people that are the same as them. Fat
old ugly losers. Shitty people. They get
on with each other. And anyone that's
better than them, they hate on. Yeah.
We've seen it with these people now for
[ __ ] years, years and years and years
and years and years. It's no one
different and it's nothing different,
you know. Simple as that.
So that's that.
So yeah, bro. Simple.
You just don't like anyone that's
younger and better looking than you with
family. Just admit it. You don't. This
is what it is, bro. You This is what it
is with you people on here. This is what
it is with you people. You don't like
someone younger and better looking than
you. This disad lives are over. Yeah.
And it is the truth. Yeah. I I also told
him to go live in London. I said go
around London and go live. And if that's
too much for for me, you can come on my
dot. Yeah. Yeah. I gave you two options.
Yeah. Okay. I gave you two options.
Okay. But trust me, bro. You come here,
you will get seriously hurt. And I'm And
I'm not even joking. You will definitely
definitely seriously get hurt. And I'm
not even joking. You will really get
hurt. Trust me. So, it's up to you. I
don't really care to be honest. You got
two options. I gave you two options.
It's slow skin off my nose.
But just admit why you do the [ __ ] that
you're doing now, bro.
No, I talk about kids. Nons talks about
kids. There's loads of people on here
that's talked about kids. This is your
excuse. You are jealous. You are jealous
of me. Come on now. It's nothing to do
with what people have said about kids.
You are jealous of the younger and
better looking. You know, if you if you
literally don't admit this to yourself,
you're never going to move on. You're
going to keep coming on here ruining
people's Christmases. Like, for [ __ ]
sake, bro. By spoke about kids, nods
legs is a nod. You are jealous. It's It
doesn't take Einstein to work out. Yeah,
you are jealous. Leave kids out of it.
Stop bringing up kids. It's nothing to
do with kids. You are jealous. There's
loads of people on here that spoke about
[ __ ] kids and people are actual
nonses. Nons is a nons. Monty man said
stuff about kids. I don't think he's a
nons, but he said stuff about kids.
Yeah. There's a million other people in
here that's done this. Yeah. So, at the
end of the day, you you you people are
jealous. You are definitely jealous,
you know. Yeah. But listen, you're
saying that I've got nothing. But what
do you people have coming on here every
day doing this [ __ ] What do you people
have coming on here doing this [ __ ]
every day? You know, you have got
nothing cuz you wouldn't be on here. And
I'm not going to keep repeating myself.
And after this video, I'm done with this
[ __ ] Done with this [ __ ]
You It's not about kids. It's because
someone's younger and better looking
than you. It's not because someone said
stuff about kids. Shut the [ __ ] up. You
people have been doing this [ __ ] on here
for years. Years and years and years.
You people have been doing this [ __ ] on
here. Yeah. For years and years and
years. You will not leave people alone
because you're jealous. It's the same
thing as what Ronald Pump said. It is
because you are jealous and you use this
kid thing as an excuse. Listen or 11.
Yeah. If anyone heard someone say stuff about kids,
they just forget about it or oh
whatever. These people don't because
this is the excuse that they use because
of their jealousy. This is how they try
to justify in their heads that their own
jealousy. Oh, you said stuff about kids
in retaliation because they use it
because it's part of their narcissism to
keep being jealous of you. So, they say,
"Oh, yeah, you said stuff about kids."
They don't like cuz you're younger and
better looking. This is what This is
what it is, bro. I'm telling you. It's
nothing to do with what people have said
or what people have done. They don't
like cuz you're younger and better
looking. So they turn their nose up.
It's nothing about kids. Leave kids out
of it. [ __ ] off about kids. It's boring
now. And it doesn't wash in the washing
machine. Yeah. It's boring, lad. Yeah. Simple.
Nothing to do with kids. Cuz how did
this whole thing Okay. How did this
whole thing on the internet start?
Right. Right. How did this whole thing
on the internet start?
No. No. No. No. No. How did this whole
thing on the internet start, bro? cuz it
wasn't about kids. Yeah. Was not about
kids. So you just don't like it cuz
someone's younger and better looking. I
think it started with the women [ __ ]
Never started with kids. Like and it's
as simple as that. It is. It is.
So I would have just said stuff for no
reason. I come on here. I used to go to
the gym. Women was pissing me off. I
said stuff about women. Um,
and yeah, that I didn't say anything
about people's kids until 3 years ago.
So, what what have you been doing for
seven years? What have you been doing
for 7 years? You people do this because
you're jealous. Simple. Yeah. If I heard
someone say stuff about kids on the
internet, I think, okay, that's a bit
weird. And then eventually I'd move on,
which is what most people do. You're
using that as an excuse. Yeah. We all
know who the real nons are on this
community. Yeah, the actual nons. We
know who the pedophiles are on this
community. Simple as that. And when we
don't and when we come off of YouTube,
you don't go for actual pedophiles.
You go by people based on what they are.
That's what it is. You go on people
based on what they are. That's what it is. Yeah.
So, stop using kids as you people have
been doing this for years and years and
years and years and years.
Yeah. A nons legs is also a nons as
well. An actual pedophile. No one no one says anything.
So yeah, trust me. I don't believe I'm
anything. I don't believe I'm
good-looking. I don't believe I just
know that you're jealous. That's all I
know. That's all I know for a fact. I
know that for a fact, bro.
100%. Cuz even if you come off of here,
they'll like they will still not go for
like other people like non-sligs and and
you'll know that they they're pedos
themselves. How can they sit there and
say that they don't like things that you
said when they're pedos themselves?
Simple as that. They're actual
pedophiles themselves. Because if they
wasn't, bro, then
this is what I was saying as well.
And that's it, bro. Like, yeah. So,
after this Saturday thing is out as well.
And this nodlex has been saying sick
[ __ ] for years, bro. Sick sick sick
stick [ __ ] for years, bro. And this is
what I'm trying to say to you, bro.
Like, he's he's never going to meet anyone.
Never. Just like, yeah, he's And he's
got a worse mouth than me, bro. And I've
had a bad mouth. But at least with me,
I've actually met people. See, the thing
is with me, right? Listen, listen,
listen. We can go on about Primal we
want. We can go on about LT all we want.
But here's the thing, bro. Here's the
thing. I've actually met people. I've
actually took some W's. So, you know,
okay, I might have took some L's,
whatever. But bro, I've shown to be more
of a man than that [ __ ] ever has been
and ever will be. And my mouth is
nowhere near as as bad as that ugly
[ __ ] you know? Trust me. Trust me.
I've I mean, I've gone to meet people,
you know. I've stuck on people. I've put
myself at risk. So, I mean, I've had my
fair share of of conflicts and put
myself at risk. Doesn't matter how many
hours I took, I still met people. This
[ __ ] whoever he goes on about, will
never [ __ ] meet anyone ever. year in
year out he will never meet anyone the
[ __ ] clown. Yeah.
So I really do hope if this guy comes on
Saturday he brings him along with him
cuz you're all as bad as each other.
You're all as bad as each other. You
know simple as that. Yeah.
But why are you not going to meet me
now? Cuz I'm a grown. But you know the
reason why this [ __ ] won't meet me LR11. Yeah.
Do you know why this [ __ ] won't meet me,
bro? Cuz I'm not a 17 18year-old kid.
I'm a grown ass man. Yeah. You know when
we talk about people picking their
targets? Yeah. Picking their targets.
Yeah. Do you remember how we we talk
about people picking their targets, bro?
This little [ __ ] And I'm going to say
this on the video as well, bro. When I
do this to Smoky Beers that, bro, he
would have no problem meeting you if he
was 18, 19. He'd have no problem. But
because he knows he's a little [ __ ]
house and he would never say anything to
a grown man's face. This why he would
never meet you. He will never ever ever
meet anyone and you know and even when
people try to meet the country he runs
to the police.
Oh then you're going to talk about me.
But the thing is I can tell you a
million times where I've mouth talked to
people. A million times where I've met
people. That's the that's the
difference. That's the difference. I I
have actually met people
and you are definitely self projecting
when you're talking about a woman
telling me to [ __ ] off. We've all seen
the video. And guess what, bro? In none
of them videos did anyone have me
running to the police screaming I wasn't
a fighter. You know in recent times
ain't not one person in these recent conflicts
made me run to the police in my area
saying I weren't a fighter. That's you.
That ain't me. That's you. Yeah. So I'm
going to add that bit in as well. You
seem to be getting se severe memory
loss. Memory loss. Yeah.
from whatever condition you you you know
you suffer with you know
and that's that and it's not even like I
was a fighter or I was bigger or anything
but no I was just saying that Triple H
that throughout the whole years on
YouTube yeah people can sit there and
try and say that I've not met people and
so I've took L's and whatever but bro at
least I've met people at least I've
tried to meet people unlike this little
[ __ ] virgin with the [ __ ] rat
looking face. Never meet anyone
even when they're taller than them and
they like you. I'm not a fighter but I I
don't know how to fight like not like a
professional fighter. But the thing is
the thing is bro this guy will never meet anyone
ever. You know you you see the amount of
people I've met. I've took L's and I've
took W's and I've turned up to places
where people ain't turned up
and they're still giving this [ __ ]
nons a platform. Yeah. And they and they
and they say that they don't like nonses.
Well, listen, why don't you go give nons
legs a hiden? He spoke about kids
multiple times saying that he would get
with a 15y old, but you wouldn't do
that, would you? Cuz you're biased.
Because you're [ __ ] biased. He he
spoke about getting with kids multiple
times. His dad's a nons. his dad. He
literally said that he he how old the
mom was with the dad. I mean, you're
Bro, you're saying that you don't like
nonses? Well, can you go for everyone
then? Everyone that you think is a nons,
you should go for all of them then,
shouldn't you? Yeah.
Cuz go my man, bro. What the [ __ ] You
know, bro, he has said that he would get
with a 15year-old. Yeah. He said that
his dad, listen, listen. His dad, right,
was with his mom when she was 12 years
old. Yeah, he is a [ __ ] pedo. He's a
wronging and he's a pedo. And what he
done, what he does on here is [ __ ]
But you give him a platform.
Yeah. Simple. It doesn't matter about a
court case. He's already [ __ ] that up.
He's already [ __ ] that court case up.
But like I said, I'll invite him on
Saturday, bro. I don't give a [ __ ] I'll
invite him on Saturday just to invite
him. If you've got anything vile to
repeat to my face, you [ __ ] [ __ ]
Then you're more than welcome to to to
to go my guy, bro. Bro, show proof.
Listen, bro, you've been shown proof
that he's a nons. Yeah, but two jealous
minds think alike, which is why you
don't go for him. Yeah, you don't go for
him cuz you're probably a n like him.
You've seen all the proof that he's a
nons. You've seen all the proof that
he's a nons. But again, two jealous
people, two nonses think alike. So,
you're never going to go for him, you
know? Probably cuz he's not good-looking
like me. Maybe because he can't he's not
been with normal women. Maybe because he
ain't got as much money as me. Who knows
how your mind thinks, bro? Come on now.
You don't know who he is. Okay,
whatever, bro. I mean, we all we all
know. We all know, bro, who this [ __ ] is. Yeah.
And that's the thing, though. Do you
know what I'm saying, though? Do you
know what I'm saying?
Do you know what I'm saying? Triple H.
Like the thing is, yeah, is that this
[ __ ] will never meet anyone. He'll talk
about dead relatives, but he will never
ever meet anyone. Just like that, Terry
will never meet anyone despite saying
that he will. You know, this is the same
thing with these people. You would have
thought now they would have got bored of
it coming into a new year. You know what
I mean? Like the windup chip was funny,
bro. The windup chick was really really
funny at first, but it's like nah. It
just it gets to the point where it's
just like bitter, bro. You know what I mean,
bro? And then you want to talk about my
encounters. I never run away once from
any of them three people. I didn't go
running to the police screaming I
weren't a fighter like you did, you little [ __ ]
Yeah. So, don't tell me about some
[ __ ] girl and some man that stood the
[ __ ] down when I was telling them about
themsel. Don't worry about that woman on
the train either.
who I answered back to that had a not
don't you worry about them people cuz I
didn't run out of my area saying to the
police that I wasn't a fighter.
Yeah. That I wasn't a fighter. I was I
that was not me. That was you. Doesn't
matter who won. Doesn't matter who lost.
Doesn't matter. That was not me. That
was you. Yeah.
So, she knows what this little obsessed
little virgin's like.
But I'm taking this Ronald Pump's
advice, bro. I'm just going to put
content on here if I don't leave now. I
think this is getting
She didn't own me. I told her that she
was an ugly crackhead.
I mean, I told her she was an ugly
crackhead. I told her about herself
back. Okay, whatever. That What did you
want me to say, bro? I was half asleep
and I told her that she's an ugly
crackhead and look in the mirror. You're
boring. Okay, whatever, bro. I didn't
run to the police screaming I wasn't a fighter. So,
so that's it, bro. What did you want me
to say, bro? What did you want me to
say? I was half a [ __ ] sleep. I
already said the same thing three times. Yeah.
But that's that.
And that is it, bro. I'm done with these
jealous people, bro. 100%. After this
Saturday, I'm definitely definitely done
with him, bro. Yeah. 100%, bro. So, like
I said, you're going to see content
videos and that's it. Yeah,
bro. Listen. But the thing is, I opened
my mouth back. Ella, I opened my mouth Yeah. One second. chicken, please.
I'm doing something. So, yeah, that's
basically that, bro.
This community is seriously seriously
[ __ ] up, bro.
Yeah, she Yeah, he did. She did start
it. But listen, bro, it doesn't matter.
I didn't keep my mouth shut. I didn't go
running to the police. He did. This This
was not me. Yeah. And then Yeah. And
what, bro? I went to this guy's area
three times and he didn't come out.
You're biased. You're jealous. We don't
care. Simple, bro. Yeah. I've stood up
to people. I've run up my mouth to
people. I backed up the [ __ ] I have
said. Yeah. Multiple times. Even if I
took L's. I didn't go I'm not on the
internet every day making videos of
people then running to the police when
somebody comes to my area. That ain't
me, bro. And guess what? If that was me,
guess what? I'd still be taking some W's.
You know you you're weird on here, bro. [ __ ] weird.
really really sad, you know. So, yeah.
Yeah. He said, "Oh, don't talk to a
woman." I said, "I'll talk to her how I
want." She started it. Yeah, I did say that. Huh?
But the thing is, I didn't go running to
the police station when somebody come to my area.
I didn't go running to the police when
somebody come to my area three times
despite having a YouTube channel on
someone, did I? So, I mean, either way,
bro, the fact that you've not took any
that is in embarrassing, bro.
See, with this LT thing, right? Yeah. If
I was on if I was on this guy's case
every day. Yeah. This is how I always
compare it to. Yeah. He leaves me alone.
I leave him alone. I'm not deliberately
trying to annoy him. If I was to do a
channel on this guy, bro, for 2 years,
I'd meet him. Anyone that was younger
than me, anyone that was older, bigger,
whatever the [ __ ] they look like, bro, I
literally Yeah, I would literally, Bro,
your empty threats don't bother no one.
Yeah, your empty threats don't bother no
one. So, don't even try it with me. Um,
and I'd done this for like two, three
years, bro. I would meet the [ __ ] I
would 100% meet him and I wouldn't care.
And this is the point I'm trying to make
is that how can people be like this for
years and still be a little [ __ ] year in
year out, year in, year out. None of you
are going to hurt me. None of you scare
me. Yeah, we all know what you are doing
on here now.
Simple as that.
You know what I mean? You need to get a
life and [ __ ] leave people alone.
Like that's what you seriously seriously
seriously seriously seriously really
need to do. You know, I come on my
channel, I create my own content, you're
coming on here, you won't leave people
alone. We get it. Yeah. It's boring now.
Very, very, very boring.
Yeah. Okay. Whatever, bro. Yeah. Yeah.
Whatever you say. Whatever. Whatever. Yeah. Whatever.
Simple. Yeah. Okay. Whatever. Mate, I
have met people and they I've stood my
ground multiple times,
whether it was a draw or whether I won.
Yeah. You need to you need to take a
closer look to your boyfriend that's not
met anyone despite somebody going to his
area three times. So, shut up. Shut up.
Yeah. I've stood my ground multiple
times, unlike your little jealous
boyfriend who's got no mother over Christmas.
So, you know what I mean? So, yeah.
You know what I mean?
[ __ ] him putting windows in. My man's
been doing this for four years now on
YouTube and he still will not meet
anyone. And he still will not meet anybody.
Yeah. Still will not meet nobody.
What the [ __ ]
But like I said, we're wasting our time,
bro. We know why these people do this.
We know that they're jealous. So, we
need to stop giving these people air
time and stick to like what we
originally said that we was going to do. Simple.
Yeah, these people are definitely
stalkers on here, bro. Definitely
definitely stalkers on here. Yeah,
it's weird. It is weird. Very weird.
Yeah. Okay, bro. Okay, whatever.
Yeah, whatever. And don't try and tell
me that I'm in it too deep and I'm going
to get hurt. Not one of you muppets are
ever going to hurt me, bro. Well, you
know why you're doing this. It's cuz you
got no family over Christmas. You've
been doing this for 2 weeks now. Laney
has said it. I have said it. Yeah, it's
boring now. Stop it. Your New Year's
resolution is to get off YouTube, get a
life, and stop harassing people. And if
you are going to stay on here, you
should you might want to actually post
your own [ __ ] content up. Yeah.
Yeah. They can come all they want. I'm
not scared. They can come all they want
and they'll see what's and they're going
to see what's going to happen to them as
well. Yeah. They will see what will
happen to them. So that's that.
Yeah. They they're more than welcome to
come and they're going to see what's
going to happen to them. All because
they've got no family over Christmas.
How mad is that? All because these
jealous people have got no family over
Christmas. They can come all they want
and they're going to see what's going to
happen to them. All cuz these people
have got no family over Christmas.
Sad, sad, jealous people with no family.
It's [ __ ] It's embarrassing, bro.
So yeah, two people are not coming. I remain unbothered.
So yeah, I want to do this video in a
bit anyways cuz I need to go to sleep, lad.
Whatever they are, they are the [ __ ]
Grinch or whoever the [ __ ] they are, bro.
Like I said, you either stay on this
community, bro, or you just do videos
and you just disable everything.
You go live like once a month or
whatever. Like, yeah.
Yeah. Okay. Whatever, bro. Whatever.
Whatever. This guy, I should have
listened to this Ronald Pump, you know,
like ages ago, bro, in the summer.
You're better looking. You got a better
life. You got more money and it kills
them. Get off of YouTube and live your
life. He ain't wrong, bro. He ain't
wrong. He ain't [ __ ] wrong. That's
why we love That's why we love [ __ ]
McDonald's so [ __ ] much, to be honest
with you. He is so right. He is so so so
so right. And to be the fact of the
matter is is that, you know, you could
still be on here for 10 years and these
people would still be doing this. They
would literally still be doing this
[ __ ] He was actually very, very right
about what he said. It is the truth. It
really, really, really, really is the truth.
It is sad. It really, really, really,
really, really is sad cuz that USA easy
thing, I gave up after a while. This was
someone I met.
This was someone I, you know, I liked
that I actually met in person. May might
I might have met them once, but, you
know, I still like them. You know, at
the end of the day, it's like you you
people don't know me. You understand,
bro? You don't know me. You've never met
me. And you know the fact that you
you're doing this for years and years
and years and years to people on the
internet that you don't know, bro. I
guess the thing is it only says
something about your life, bro. It
really says something about your life.
It really, really does, bro. Strangers
you've never met. And what are you
really doing here, bro? You know, I
[ __ ] with them for a while and I just
got bored of it. You do this constantly.
You never get bored. You never leave
people alone. You never ever stop. You
know, I can I I can name loads of you
people on here.
You live to [ __ ] with people. That's
literally your life. You live to harass
and [ __ ] with people that you don't
know, that you've never met every day.
Not for two months, not for 3 months.
You do it constantly. You don't stop.
Yeah. Because do you not understand?
Like there's been people on it, bro.
They stopped in the end. You people
don't stop. You literally will never
ever stop. As long as I'm alive, you
will never stop.
No, I don't do the same.
Uh, women. Okay. Firstly, firstly,
firstly, firstly, firstly, one second.
Well, the kid thing you got a point
with. The women have done stuff to me.
Women have led me on. Women have [ __ ]
me over. So if I want to retaliate to
women being [ __ ] and being [ __ ]
that's my choice. They're not innocent.
They're not children. They know what
they've done. They can defend. They can
defend themselves very verbally. So if I
want to have a go at a woman, I will do
what I want. You don't tell me what I
do, what I don't do. If I if a woman
wants to be a [ __ ] to me, I'll be a [ __ ]
to her back. It works both ways. You
know, the biasist doesn't doesn't wash
with me. So I'm not going to accept. I
don't listen listen listen listen listen
let me understand this right these these
kids are innocent right women I don't
share the same views as you do that's my
choice if I don't want to lick women's
asses and I don't always want to think
they're in the right I will say that I
don't agree I don't agree them I don't
agree with them I can't stand them
that's my experiences they're my views
simple just like I said to the guy on
the train and then he he He got his head
crushed in the door. Everyone, I am not
a white knight. I am not a s. So if I want to,
you know, if I want to
have my views and they're right and
they're rightfully views, I can have
them. That's none of your business.
You know, that's and that is the point
because these women are not innocent. So
they've been [ __ ] So everything I've
done is in retaliation. But with the
women thing, you got no you got no
argument. The only argument that you've
got is the kid [ __ ] But then again, you
don't mind nonsense. You don't mind
So, and I actually said I was going to
die and dash someone. Yeah. Okay. I was
going to go to a meal with someone and
not pay. Okay. What about all the [ __ ]
they've done over the years? The making
up stories, the [ __ ] Everyone has
seen it. And what? So, what if I wanted
to die and then someone?
That's That's my choice. That's my
See what I'm saying?
Well, no, cuz I wouldn't actually attack
somebody. I would just [ __ ] them over. I
would just [ __ ] them over legally. And I
think that is that is justified.
That is justified.
So, yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. But women
have done stuff to me, so I can do stuff
back to them. That's my argument.
They've done stuff to me. I'll do stuff
back to them.
Simple. That's that's that's fair game,
bro. I don't give a [ __ ] if it's illegal.
They've been [ __ ] to me. They've done
stuff to me, so [ __ ] them. So,
yeah, the community ruined. No, not
really. No, no,
no. But the community didn't ruin the
Izzy thing, bro. I just stopped talking
to her cuz Yeah. I mean, it didn't help, but
I mean, I could have still met if I
wanted to. The thing is the long story. So, yeah.
Yeah. So, it's So, it's okay for women
to lead people on. So, it's okay for
women to lead you on and be a [ __ ]
towards you. Is that all right? Is that
Is that okay? No, it isn't. Do you think
that maybe people are just sick of their [ __ ] So
if if men have been [ __ ] you over
for majority of your life, yes, it is. Yes.
Yes. If you've been [ __ ] over the way
that I've been [ __ ] over and you've
had bad experiences like I have, yeah, I
would say it's fair game
if you wanted to [ __ ] somebody over the
legal way. Yeah. Yeah. Definitely.
Definitely. Definitely. Definitely 100%.
Man or woman, whoever's done it to you.
Yeah. Yeah. Whoever Whoever
if this has been going on, if you have
met people the way that I've met people
and you have had people [ __ ] you over
and lead you on, get them back legally. Yeah.
100%, bro. What the [ __ ]
Why? Why not, you know? So, yeah. One sec.
Right. But I've just answered your
question and you've just ignored it.
Right. I've just answered your question
and you've just ignored it.
I've literally told you that women have
led me on and [ __ ] me over and you
just completely ignored it. So, I don't
know what was the whole point of you
asking if you were just going to ignore
what anyone else said. Bit rude, isn't it?
We know why you people give people [ __ ]
on here. We know why you people do what you do.
No one else needs to say anything about
it. But there was no point asking me
something if you didn't like the answer. So
yeah, I'm blaming women. Yeah. Yeah.
Yeah. And it's warranted. Yeah, I am
blaming women. Yeah. Yeah.
I mean, okay. Okay. Let's put it this
way, right? Yeah. Right. Okay. Let's put
it this way. If I went around [ __ ]
with people on purpose, leading people
on, playing games, leading people on,
playing games, you'd have a problem with
me. No. So, why have you got not why do
you not why do you not get my words out?
Why do you not have a problem with what
they're doing? If I was to go out now,
no beating up, no smashing, no nothing,
and I went around doing what they do,
you'd have a problem with it. Would you
not have a problem with it? So, why have
you got no problem with them doing it?
Answer it. Go on. If I went out every week
looking for people to lead on and be
immature, no violence, no just what they
do, you'd have a problem with it. So why
have you got no problem with them doing
it and then say that oh we're playing
with women? You've got clearly got no
problem with them doing it. You've been
shown evidence, multiple evidence of
what they've done. You just dismissed it. So
I mean I don't I don't understand. I
mean, if I if I literally see out people
to dine and dash, if I see out a people
that I dine and dashed, it would be
equivalent to what they're doing, pretty
much. So, why have you got no problem
with them doing it? I don't understand.
Yeah, but we're not talking about people
being ignored. No, no, no, no. Now
you're twisting things now, aren't you?
We're not talking about people ignoring.
Why are you talking about people that
are ignoring? We are talking about these
people that have got bad attitude, that
lead people on, that play games with
people, right? If I went around doing
that to every single person I come
across, you'd have a problem. So why
have you got no problem with them doing
it? We're not talking about being
ignored. We're not talking about what
they do so many different things. So why
have you So okay, so what do you expect
people to do? Just be like, "Oh, yeah,
that's fine. That's okay." Well, and
just accept that these women are playing
games and being [ __ ] No, bro. No
person is going to accept that.
Because people just leave. Why do you
think people go to Thailand? You know,
this ant man has not dealt with [ __ ]
5% of what I've dealt with and he left, you know.
>> So why why do you have no problem with
them doing that?
Why? What you're saying does not make
sense. What you're saying does not make
sense, bro. What you're saying does not
make sense. You have seen evidence of
them leading me on and playing games. Yeah. So
why have you got no problem with them doing that?
Why have you got no problem with them
leading people on and giving false hope?
You'd have a problem with me doing it.
I'd be hated on it if I done what they
done. So do you not understand that?
It's just what the [ __ ] bro?
So yeah, I definitely do blame them. I
definitely definitely do. Well, I'm not
going to blame myself, am I? Why would I
blame myself when the problem is them?
And [ __ ] the women [ __ ] anyways, bro.
It's this is a waste of conversation.
It's a waste of time because you can't
answer my question. So
if I went around doing what they done,
you'd have you'd have a problem with it.
But you got no problem with what these
women are doing.
And all the things that I've done is completely justified.
It's completely completely completely justified.
And I'm going to call this nonsense out
because he's more than happy to host
fights because he's put this smoky beef.
You know what? LG is going to click on
this video and he's going to think,
"What a load of old [ __ ] The same thing
is going on again, bro. The same thing
is going on and on and on again.
He He is literally going to be like,
"What the [ __ ] This is the same [ __ ] again."
Cuz it really is the same [ __ ] again
with the same people. So yeah,
but it does make sense. It does make
Women are [ __ ] Women are [ __ ]
End the story.
You know that's that's that's that. Bro,
they're not innocent. I've shown what
they've done. You shouldn't really have
a problem with that. I don't know why
you got a problem with that.
You have given these women the benefit
of the doubt to prove that they're not
all the same and they haven't. So, I
don't know why you have got a problem
with my with that. Just doesn't make sense,
bro. I'm not answering that question.
It's It's silly.
Yeah. You don't you're never going to
learn. You're never going to listen. So,
it doesn't matter.
I don't understand why you are pissed
off because I've had bad experiences and
I've gave these women the [ __ ] that they
gave me back. I don't understand how
that would concern you.
So, it's just like you constantly make
excuses. You're an idiot. Who's really
going to sit there and keep taking their [ __ ]
Who's really really going to do that? I
don't deal with them because of this reason anymore.
No, no, no, no. But men aren't all the
same. We're not talking about men. We're
talking about women all being the same.
No, men are not all the same. But women
are all the same. There you go. I
answered your question.
So what? Simple as that.
Dirty little V [ __ ]
[ __ ] proper trying to host fights and
[ __ ] Yeah, he's actually I don't even
know how you do that. I don't have the
option to do that. Trying to host the fights.
Yeah, you know what I'm trying to say.
Mad, bro. Absolute madness.
Uh, I'm not having this conversation
again, bro. I ain't having this boring
conversation again. Change the record. It's boring.
It's really, really, really, really boring.
Okay. All women are perfect. Is that
what you want to hear? What is the point
of this conversation?
I don't see what the point of this
conversation is. I don't care what you
say. I have proven that they're all the
same multiple times. End of. I've got my
opinion and it's not for you to change
it. It's for them to change it and they
can't. So, I don't give a [ __ ] I don't
want you to tell me anything. I've gave
them chances to prove me wrong and they
haven't. So, I don't care what you say.
I have gone up and down the country
proving that these women are all the
same. I don't care what you've got to
say. Whatever you say is not my life
experiences. I don't give a [ __ ] Simple.
Don't say anything. I want to be shown
different. I don't care what you say. I
want to be shown different. But these
women are all the same. So if I want to
dine and dash someone, I will die and d someone.
Completely [ __ ] legal. [ __ ] madness. Absolute madness.
You people in here are [ __ ] idiots, man.
No. No. But but I've been with women.
So, does that not tell you that I'm I'm
biased? Okay. Okay. Okay. So, if I've
been with women, would that not favor my
argument more then? Would it would it
not would it not favor my argument more
if I've been with women which I have
been with multiple multiple women.
Wouldn't that put my argue wouldn't that
put me being unbiased more in my favor?
Because Yeah. Because I'm telling the
truth. I'm not saying something that I
don't believe. They are all the same.
They lead people on. They're stuck up.
Why would I lie about that? I've been
with women. I've had sex with people
that weren't escorts. Why would I lie
when I've been with women? It doesn't
make any sense. I'm not going to defend
them when they don't need to be
defended. Doesn't matter how many women
I've been with. I I just I've woken up
and I've smelt the copy. Yeah, I know
what they're like.
So, and it is the same for most men.
It's the same for most men.
Okay, whatever. We're not having this
conversation again, bro. It's boring.
Yeah. They don't like you either. They
don't like you either and they don't
like most men. So again, I'm not having
this conversation with you. And yes, I'm
ending it now and I'm terminating it
because it's the same conversation.
We're having the same conversation every
day. Okay? Other men don't struggle.
Women are perfect. Is that what you want
to hear? Like will you you're not going
to stop until someone agrees with you.
You won't stop until someone agrees with
you. So like I don't understand what the
point is. You're right. Women are all
perfect. They go for every man in the
world but me and I'm a virgin. Happy
cuz we'll be here until [ __ ] midnight
until you stop. Bro, women are perfect.
I've never been with a woman. Every man
gets a woman but me. Happy.
I don't I don't understand you, bro. Is
that Are you happy now? You know,
are you happy now?
You didn't answer the question. I'm
literally agreeing with you. I'm a
virgin. Never been with a woman, never
kissed a woman. I'm a 28-year-old
virgin. I don't know anything. You know
more than me. Everyone gets women but
me. Every single man in the world does
not struggle with women but me.
Is that what you want to hear? Like
ridiculous, bro. Come on now. [ __ ] insane.
You know, if I want to have an opinion
on women, I would have any opinion that
I [ __ ] want on women. That's on me,
bro. You don't you don't tell me what to think.
Just like I don't tell you what to
think. You don't tell me nothing. So
yeah, you've been with your woman for 12
years. Okay, good. Good for you, bro.
I've never been with a woman. I'm a
virgin. What does being with a woman
feels like feel like?
See, the thing is, right, have you ever
met an incel that's actually been with a woman?
No, I don't think No, I mean like in
their in their whole life. Like, have
you ever met some an I don't think
there's an incel that's ever been with a woman.
So, that completely sucks your whole
argument up to begin with. I'm trying to
think the guy in Plymouth, no. Elliot
Rogers, no. These are all people that's
actually never been with women.
So that's why they're they're told
they're these things.
So the fact that I've been with women
would completely tell you that I'm not
an insult and I'm a completely unbiased
person. And that's the thing. People are
allowed to be unbiased, which is which
is what I am. So
you can't even say that I'm a virgin or
I've never been with a woman. You can't
even say that. So what I'm saying must
be what I'm thinking.
This is just silly. This whole argument,
bro. Just this whole argument is so silly.
So so silly.
I just When are you just going to
[ __ ] [ __ ] off, bro? And just leave
people alone, people in this community.
Seriously, when are you just going to
just stop your [ __ ]
Is it still plugged on this little cunt's channel?
[ __ ] idiot. Yeah, I've never been.
We've heard all of this self-p projection before.
We've heard all of this self projection [ __ ] before.
Right. Give it a break now.
Okay. It's the other channel. So, you're
trying to host fights again. Yeah.
Right. Yeah. So, you've posted this,
right, for this guy. Right.
Oh, almost subbed to him on my [ __ ]
main channel, bro. I'm going to be doing
a video in a bit anyway. Strip H. Don't worry, bro.
I don't want you to agree with me. I've
agreed with you, bro. I'm 28. I'm a
virgin. I've never been with a woman.
Every man in the world gets women, but
me. Yeah. 50% of men are single. But
yeah. No, I've literally agreed with you.
Yeah. I've literally agreed with you.
I'm a virgin. I've never been with a
woman. You clearly know me better than I know myself.
Yeah. Yeah. And look, Trip H, he's
plugged this up right on his channel
when we all know the little Bro, I'm
going to rip into these two on this video, bro.
I'm going to rip into them. Like, don't
don't don't put up. Yeah. Don't put up.
Yeah. Yeah. You can see why I can't get
women even though I've showed
screenshots and approaches. Why do you
come on? Why do you come on if you're
just going to dismiss everything that
you're shown? You're saying about people
agreeing with you, right? Bro, you can't
lose a debate. Like, you can't lose a
debate, bro. Even when you're showing
black and white evidence, you still talk
[ __ ] So, why are you coming on here for
a debate? You've been shown what they're
like. You have literally been shown what
they're like, and you're still coming on
here talking [ __ ] So, how are you ever
going to admit you're wrong if you can't
even be you can't even admit to what you're shown?
You know how silly that is?
You've literally been shown what they have done,
right? And you're still coming on here.
I don't understand. You're an idiot.
You have seen You have You have been
shown what they have done.
You have show You have been shown what
they have done. Stop dismissing it.
Because you like to come on here and
say, "Oh, people don't uh you know, you
have been shown women have an attitude."
You have been shown women leading people
on, right? Let's let's talk about what
you have been shown. Stop saying about
this, that, kids. [ __ ] all that. Let's
talk about what you have been shown.
Yeah. And don't sit there and say, "Oh,
they don't like you." [ __ ] all that.
Let's talk about what they have done.
Yeah. Yeah. and stop dismissing it,
right? Just like Tiger Tiger, don't
dismiss it. Stop dismissing the [ __ ]
that you're shown.
Yeah. For once in your life, this 10
minutes of your life, bro. Yeah. We're
not talking about being blanked. We're
not talking about being blanked. Again,
stick stick to what you've been shown.
Stick to stick to what you have been shown.
Yeah. And being ignored is very very
annoying. Um anyways, but we're not
talking about that. We're talking about
all of the stuff that they have done.
Stop dismissing it. You're saying that I
always think that I'm right. Stop dismissing it.
No, it's not that they didn't reply.
It's that they've led me on multiple
multiple times. Yeah, they've led me on
multiple multiple multiple times. If I
went around leading people on, you would
have a problem with it. Stop being sexist.
Simple. Stop being sexist.
And if I go out 10 15 times and I'm
getting [ __ ] from women and I want to
react, I will react. You don't tell me
what I what I can and can't do. Yeah.
You need to understand this. If I if I
go out 25 times, right? One week. Okay.
Two week. And then we get to the 25
fifth week and I'm sick of their [ __ ] I
will tell them about themselves. I will
do what I want. Yeah. Simple. You don't
tell me what I'm what I can do and what
I can't do.
If they want to be a [ __ ] for 25 weeks,
I will be a [ __ ] for one of the weeks.
Yeah. I don't care about normal men have
not been through what I've been through.
I don't care about normal men. I don't
compare myself to other people. Simple.
even talk about normal men. I'm talking
about me and what I've experienced. I
don't care about other people.
You are not It's not for you to tell me
how to react. Yeah. It's not for you to
tell me how to react. Don't worry about
me. I'm not your son, bro. I don't know
if you've got kids. I'm not your son.
You don't tell me how I react.
Normal people don't lead people on, but
you've got no problem with women leading
people on. So, I'll do what I want. Simple.
Normal people don't lead people on and
give people false hope.
But you're not going to tell them off
for that, are you? So, that's that is it. Simple.
The [ __ ] is toxic. First of all, it's
toxic. Yeah, it is toxic. They do what
they do on purpose. They lead people on
purpose. Why can't I retaliate to them?
Why can they do what they do?
Yeah. Any any thoughts on the women
leading me on? You've kept ignoring
that. This is the fifth time I'm
bringing it up. I mean, the fifth time
I'm bringing this up about the women
leading me on and you keep dismissing
it. So, you got something to hide, don't
you? Really? You know,
right? I'm telling you about women
playing games and leading me on, but you
keep you keep it doesn't suit your
agenda, so you keep changing the subject
because you know what I'm saying is the
truth. So, you keep making stuff up.
You're here. You want the debate, right?
I'm here. No one's getting blocked. I'm
showing people women have led me on.
Women have played games. Women have had
attitude problems. Yeah. Everything I
have said back, I'll say what I want.
Simple. That's that. So, if I want to
retaliate to them, I'll retaliate to them.
So, it's okay for them to be verbing and
lead people on and [ __ ] do madness.
[ __ ] off, bro. [ __ ] off.
Right. We're not talking about that.
Yeah. Yeah. Again, stick to the subject.
Sixth time. We're not talking about
that. We are talking about people that
are leading people on. We are not
talking about that. Why are you talking
about one conversation?
You keep you keep dismissing it again.
You're saying I I I I block people and I
ban people. I haven't banned you. You
are dismissing what I'm showing you,
what I have said.
So [ __ ] it doesn't make sense. I
don't need to explain it. The messages
explain it. I don't need to explain.
You've seen the messages. Stick to the
subject. I don't need to explain it. The
messages explain it. Right. The the the
messages show more than enough of what
they've done. Everyone has seen their messages.
So, I don't need to explain something.
You've already been shown. You did it if
you wasn't so ignorant and dismissed
people's struggles, right? You you would
know that, bro. You've already seen
them. Yeah. So, like I said, if I went
around leading women on on purpose,
would you have a problem with that? I'm
asking you a question. If I went if I
went out every other day approaching
people just to [ __ ] with them and lead
them on, would you have a problem with
it? So, why do you not have a problem
with them doing it? Answer the question.
Come on. You say you're saying that
you're beating me and whatever. Answer
the question. Why is it not okay for me
to be this and be that, but it's okay
for them to play mind games and lead
people on? I'm asking you a question.
Why is it okay for one and not the
other? You know, come on, answer the question.
You can't answer it because you know I'm
right. Exactly. You know I'm right, bro.
I mean, I'm almost 30. Guess what, bro?
These people in their 40s and they're
still leading men on. So,
you can't you can't even answer the
question, bro. You know, you know.
Oh, so it is okay then. Oh, oh, so, so I
can go out tomorrow, right, and get
people's numbers and lead people on and
dine and nast people and [ __ ] them over.
Yeah. So, that is okay. So, I can do
that. Oh, so it is okay then. I thought
you said it wasn't okay.
So, is it okay?
You you're going to realize that this is
all a gender thing in the end. You know,
it's going to come to a point, right,
where you realize
that this is going to come to an end and
you're going to have to admit that it is
a gender thing. It is really a gender
So, is it okay?
Oh, right. Did you Did you lead them on, though?
But did did you lead them on? Did Did
you say that you was going to meet them
and not meet them?
It's not about blanking. It's what they
do. They literally do it on purpose.
They leave people on purpose. They don't
sit there and say on the first message,
they're not looking to meet anyone.
They're never ever honest. But I don't
know why they moan and complain about
men when they literally have chances to
meet people and they're not interested.
I don't know why they moan and complain
about men. But seriously, seriously,
seriously, don't. Strange. There was
this woman on Instagram today. She's
like, "Oh, I've been dating this guy for
a month." And yeah, he stopped replying.
And I was like, "Stay old. We've heard
it all before." But you don't actually
want a normal nice person. Um, so I
mean, what can you really moan about?
It's the men that you're going for.
They know the men that they're going
for, bro. Trust me, they they definitely
know the men that they're going for. So
yeah, everyone turned out to be the same.
I mean, you don't want a normal nice
person. So why are you moaning? I don't
see the the the point in them moaning when
you come across someone that's normal
and decent, you're not going to be
interested. So why do you moan about
men? I just don't understand.
No, no, no. There's there's no way.
There's no way, Ryan, because there's no
way because I have had women, right?
There's no way because I have had women
message me before saying, "Oh, you're
nice. You're this, you're that, and
whatever." Um, but some reason they're
not interested. So, if they really went
for people that they thought was nice,
bro, you'd be getting dates all the
time. You know, it's they know what
these men are like. They know that
they're [ __ ] They don't know that
they abuse them, but they know that
they're [ __ ] There's no way.
There's no way they want a normal nice
person. And the sooner that they admit
that it's there's nothing wrong. You
like what you like, bro. I'm not here to
tell you who you like or what you what
you don't like. But don't say that you
want a normal person when you're writing
on your messages said person that you
want, but you're making every single
excuse not to even go on a [ __ ] date
with them. It's [ __ ] ridiculous. Stop
moaning. I don't care. I don't really
give a [ __ ] if and and I'm saying it
from their point of view. I generally
don't care, you know.
I generally generally generally
generally generally don't care. But you
can't really moan and win when you've got plenty.
You you have got people that are
different that will meet you and you're
not interested. So just stop winging.
Stop moaning. Know what you got to moan
about to be honest.
Cuz there's no co coincidence that these
women keep going for the same guys.
There's no coincidence. There was no
coincidence that they keep going for the
same man, the same men. There's no
coincidence, bro, that all of these
people put a face on and they end up
with some [ __ ] There's no way.
They're obviously choosing them, bro.
They're obviously [ __ ] choosing them
cuz it's obvious. It is obvious that
they moan and winge about and complain
about men. I don't get it.
Because the thing is is like I've said
before, if they've got 500 options,
right? They've got 500 options.
Out of them 500 people, I'm sure there's
five people that are normal. If a man
doesn't have any options, how is he ever
going to find anyone?
That's the way I see it. So, I just I
don't I don't get them. I really really So
it doesn't it really really doesn't make sense.
It really doesn't. I don't care who they
go with. I don't really give a [ __ ]
Like stop motioning.
I can use myself in that example.
So yeah, it's like if I went out right
now and I started speaking to someone,
they would say straight away not
interested. I have a boyfriend.
So then at the end of the day, they
really really can't winge. They can't moan.
It's like me, right? It's like me,
right? Say, say if an average person
come up to me, right? Okay, let's put it
this way. Say I had I had an option with
an average person, right? I can't dump
the person and then start moaning about women.
I can't do that and then stop moaning
and winging about women because it
doesn't make any sense. It doesn't
matter who the person is. They seem to
go for the same guy, reject all the
normal people and then moan about men.
How does it work? You know,
that's that, bro. And again, I don't
give a [ __ ] if they go with me or not.
It's great. I don't care, bro. But yeah,
you're saying that someone's diss thanks
for coming up to me. No, no, no, no, no.
So why wouldn't you give that person a chance?
just it actually blows my mind. So yeah.
So yeah, bro.
Why are we on this subject again, bro?
Why are we on this subject again?
Why the [ __ ] are we on this subject again?
cuz I'm probably the most down to earth
person I'll ever meet. And again, I'm
not trying to say they should get with
me. I don't care. But I'm just using as
an example. I don't care
because because they moan that they
can't find someone.
They moan that they can't find someone.
So it just to me it doesn't make any
sense why you wouldn't cuz I assume that
most people are looking for someone
eventually know that they're looking for
someone. So I just don't understand why
they wouldn't give it a go, you know,
to be honest or even at a later time. It
just to me it just doesn't make any
sense. They say they can't find anyone.
If I found a woman that was different, I
would never slag off a woman. Like that
is actually that. But I've always been
shown the same. One way or another, one
it's either they pretend they've got
boyfriends or they say they're not
interested or they give you their number
and lead you on or they get with you and
you hook up with them and then they
ghost you and do madness and leave
there. There's several different things
that they do, bro. There's several
several several different things. And I
generally don't think there are good
good women out there.
I generally don't. So that's that. I'm
sure I'll go out again at some stage.
No, no, no. Let me Well, let me let me
tell you something. I went out on
Saturday and there's no way four of them
women have boyfriends. There's no way.
There's no way, bro. There's no way.
Nah, there's no way. I would honestly
say that women that say they've got boyfriends,
they're lying. Three times the only
three out of 10 have boyfriends. It's
[ __ ] There's so many single people
out there. There's so many single people
out there. Trust me, there's so so many
single people out there. Okay, think
about think about it this way. Okay.
Okay. Put it this way, right?
Think of how many guys out there that
are single, but yet all of these women
claim they've got boyfriends. Let's say
half the Okay, let's say half the pl
half the population is single, right?
Let's say half the population single. 40
50%. Yeah, what it says on Google. So,
how is it that all of these women seem
to have boyfriends?
Because it's [ __ ] It is [ __ ]
Yeah, there are some people that have
boyfriends. Yeah, there are some people
that have girlfriends, but majority of
the ones that are saying they've got
boyfriends, they are full of [ __ ]
definitely full of [ __ ] It depends on
the context. It depends on the context
and how they say it and it just depends.
It depends on But most of them are full
of [ __ ] 100%.
I would say three, four.
Yeah. And that goes to my thing again.
Stop moaning and complaining that you
can't find a man, but then when you're
given the opportunity, you're not
interested. Stop moaning and stop
winging because it's mocking the people
that actually can't find someone.
So don't moan and winge about men then.
Simple. Stop complaining you can't find
someone. Simple. I don't care, lad.
Uh yeah, Triple H, obviously. But why
are they not interested? Because they
moan they can't find someone. Triple H.
They they moan that they can't find someone.
But then when someone normal is coming
up to them, they're not interested. So
why the [ __ ] are they not interested?
Not that I care. And why do you keep
moaning about men? Simple. So
just doesn't really make a lot of sense,
does it? Triple, you know. So,
but I gave up to get away from this
[ __ ] So I don't know why we're still
talking about it, bro.
We gave up to get away from this [ __ ]
So, I don't know why we're still harping
on about it. I don't know what we have
different views. We're never going to
agree. So, what's the point? Simple,
mate. A lot of bro all of the women that
I have approached in years
some of them have definitely moaned
definitely moaned about men
obviously they've moaned about men
but there's loads of women that moan about men
yeah but there's no reason because I'm
decent looking triple eight so that
doesn't even wash it anymore
it's not about copper te's cuz there's
nothing wrong with the way that I look
so it goes back to them having
unrealistic standards cuz there's
something wrong with the way that I look.
And that goes back to unrealistic
standards. Yeah, every woman is in the
same bucket. They definitely are all the
same. Bro, listen. You're not going to
change my views.
So, I don't know why you're trying. I've
met more women than you. I know what
they're like. So, just let people have
their own opinion. They are in the Listen, listen.
When you're typing this [ __ ] just
remember that I've traveled all over the
country meeting thousands of women. Just
just keep reminding yourself every 10,
15 minutes that before you're writing
this [ __ ] you need to understand that I
have met a lot a lot a lot a lot a lot a
lot of women, right?
You know what I'm saying? So,
so you know what I'm saying?
Okay. Well, maybe there is people that
don't find you attractive. Okay,
maybe some people like black people,
some people like ginger people, some
people like blue eyes. Yeah, I mean that
is that is understandable. No, but then
at the same time, you should have met
someone by now.
Do you understand?
Okay. Okay. Yeah, trip that that is
true. They might like black, mixed race,
blue eyes, g whatever it is. They could
very well have a specific type. There
could be somebody with tattoos that like
men with tattoos and they might have
specific types. Still quite shallow that they would
exclude anyone but that type. That is
still shallow. But yeah, there is there
is there is people. However, you should
still be getting dates.
You should still be not having these problems.
You know, that's what I'm saying. So you
even though you might not be people's
type, you should have been someone's
type by now. So that's it. You're not
ugly. There's nothing wrong with the way
that you look. Your face is symmetrical. So,
so it's just it doesn't it doesn't make
sense, bro. But no, you're not going to
be everyone's type.
But you should be someone's, especially
every time you go out. Yeah,
exactly. And there's some women that I
do find attractive.
So, that's what that's the whole point
I'm trying to make.
You haven't had more success than me.
I've been with plenty plenty of women.
So, you haven't had more success than
me, bro. I've had plenty of women,
but yeah, some people I don't find attractive. Yeah.
But I will find someone that I do find attractive.
So, the only thing could be is they
they've just got unrealistic standards
and they're stuck up. That's the only
thing it can be.
Cuz you're not ugly. See, the thing is,
Triple H, you're not ugly. By you, I
mean me. So there is when I was saying
this [ __ ] earlier, bro, not earlier, two
days ago, [ __ ] earlier. You're not
ugly. You're not bored. You're not
disabled. You're not good-looking but
haven't tried. There's no reason for it.
This is the whole point is there's no
reason for it. If you was good-looking
and never tried, there'd be a reason. If
you was in a wheelchair, there'd be a
reason. If you had no [ __ ] arms and
legs, there'd be a reason. There is no
reason for it.
And as much as the trolls want to sit
here and try and say that you're ugly
when me and you both know I'm not
[ __ ] ugly. I just look [ __ ]
normal. There's no reason for it, there
really is no reason for it to be ongoing.
And that's and that's
and that really really is it. Doesn't
matter how like how you put it, bro. You
know what I mean?
So that's that. Yeah.
No, they are average. They are average,
bro. All the people I go for are
average. There's no eights and nines in
this country, bro. They're all like
average, below average.
They all They've all got unrealistic standards.
They've all got unrealist.
Maybe because I don't look fully white.
I think that's a problem as well cuz I
don't look fully white, which is also a
race thing as well. I don't look fully
white as well. So that could even also
be an issue as well. So
I have tried average people, bro.
They're all they're just the same. Just
they do the same [ __ ]
I have a boyfriend. Same old [ __ ] I
don't even think a lot of these people
look at you before saying it. Uh,
doesn't matter anyways, bro.
Yeah. Okay, bro. I mean, stats, the
statistics don't lie. I mean, I've got
friends that are single. I see men
approach women all the time. And let me
tell you, more people are not getting
women than getting women.
So there more men are not getting women
than are getting women. The ones that
are single 100%.
Yeah. And I know that. And again, I
don't care anyways. Why does it matter?
Why are we why are we talking about other men?
It's always other people in it cuz you
think you think that's the only way you
can win the argument. So anyway, there's
no there's no reason for it anyways.
You're not ugly. You're not disabled.
You're not in a wheelchair. So, there's
no reason for it. Simple.
There's no reason for it at all. So, yeah.
H for [ __ ] sake. I hate talking about
this. This is depressing, bro. Why are
we talking about this anyways? This is depressing.
I didn't come live talking about this
earlier, bro. I said one thing about the
Instagram. This is depressing, bro. Why
are we even on the same subject?
Simple. I ain't going out this week. I'm
not going out for a long time. So that's
that's that, bro. We don't even need to
talk about this anymore.
When I go out again, it will be the same
old [ __ ] So what? Why are we even
talking about this? Huh?
It's the same subject. It's the same
thing every time, bro. Yeah.
Yeah. Okay. You've had more women than
me, bro. Whatever. I don't even know why
we're on this subject. I woke up today
[ __ ] feeling normal for once and
we're talking about the same subject.
It's actually depressing, you know?
Why are you even talking about this?
What's the relevance? I could go out
tomorrow. What's day tomorrow? Thursday.
Today is Thursday. It will be the same
old. Does it really matter? Really, you know,
the only thing I will find strange is that you know
what I find strangers. Honestly though,
the last thing I'll say about this is that you're right. Huh.
talking to someone. Why? Yeah, talking
Yeah, I will. I will, man.
They're really weird, bro. No, no, no.
They're very These people are moving
really weird, Mom.
Around this time of year, they're moving
very, very weird.
>> No, no, no. Yeah, I know why. You know
why as well. It's actually creepy.
Like, everyone is actually saying the same thing.
It's really weird.
No, no, definitely not. See, even even
Laneia has said exactly the same thing.
Um, no, what I was saying is just to end
this, right? The thing that I find
strange is the fact that
you don't think anyone can have um a
different opinion without being an incel.
Like you seem to think anyone that just
[ __ ] thinks that women are [ __ ]
or like virgins that's never been with a
woman rather than people that have just literally
Yeah. My mom woke up because of this
stupid [ __ ] shouting over [ __ ] hangups. Yeah.
It's not going to happen again today anyways.
I don't even want to be on it, bro, for
the sake of Elaine. She doesn't even
[ __ ] like me being on here, bro. I
feel very well. I feel really, really bad, bro.
It's that time of year. That time of
year again with these people.
Poor Laney. E.
Poor poor poor poor Laney. Huh?
What are you up to today? Oh,
you're going to get in the neck in it.
But what can you do? You know, it's it
was going to be one or the other, isn't it? >> Yeah.
You stop this [ __ ] bro. Honestly, I
don't know why you don't think anyone can
have a different opinion without being
labeled as something. I just I just
don't understand how you don't think that, bro.
But yeah, not everyone's going to find
you attractive, but you you should have
people that find you attractive. There's
nothing wrong with the way that you look. So
even if it's 1 in 20, one in 30,
cuz that just tells you that they've got
unrealistic expectations because there's
no reason why they wouldn't find [ __ ]
whatever. Anyways, I don't care.
[ __ ] them, bro.
Do a video on this [ __ ] bro.
I I'm not going to lie, bro. Seriously.
Yeah. 11th today, ain't it? It's
Christmas soon. Triple H.
The projectors are here.
This community is never alive, bro.
Never alive like it is.
Never alive like it is, bro.
No one really ever comes in only because it's December.
Yeah, I think they're mad that I'm going
to have Christmas dinner this year.
They're very mad I'm going to be having
lovely Christmas dinner this year,
Triple H. cuz I was live last Christmas
and these uh I was live and people was
also on the live
and don't forget that was only one year
for me. So that one year showed that
these people don't have Christmas.
No, no, no. Not like this. Not like
this. No, no. You don't get [ __ ] You do
not get [ __ ] like this when it ain't Christmas, bro.
You got people talking about dead
relatives. [ __ ] you got mad people
writing paragraphs. No, no, no. Not like
this. Not like this, bro. This is It's
actually gotten worse. And also with the
people that have made accounts, I've had
to block their accounts.
It's definitely 20 times worse over
Christmas. It's cuz they want to ruin
people's Christmas. It's simple as that.
Like how they want to ruin people's
life. They want to ruin people's
Christmas. It's obvious what you're doing.
They're not going to take a day off
Christmas. They'll be on here Christmas.
I was live Christmas. They were also on here.
Nor is going to say
no. Not by non legs. Not by nle.
Maybe people that don't come on here are
not buying nons.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no,
no. This is It's definitely worse, bro.
So, yeah, but people will pretend
they're not in on a Christmas triple
like like LJ will pretend that he's not
on it Christmas, but he will be on here.
He will definitely be on here. They'll
say that they won't be on here, but they
will be on here.
They want to say that they're going to
try and act like they've got lives, you
see. So, they're going to be like, "Oh,
I'm not on here Christmas. I'm not going
to be on here Christmas." But we all
know they're going to be on here Christmas.
They definitely definitely will be on
your Christmas and you'll see that if
anyone goes live,
bro. I wouldn't even do it anyways. He's
a little grass. He's a snitch.
He's a snitch. And another thing is you
think him doing that um bell thing is
him winning. It's just [ __ ] [ __ ] And
everyone knows deep down that he's a
[ __ ] So I mean even if that I probably
still wouldn't do it anyways. He's a
grass. But I'll give him the invitation
to come here Saturday with his boyfriend
um since he wanted to host this fight.
So he's more than happy to come um you
know and that's that's a perfect way of
of seeing it. But bro, that bell thing
is [ __ ] [ __ ]
It's [ __ ] [ __ ] And then and anyone
will tell you that anyone that comes on
the internet like some kind of bad man
and then has to run to the police, it
shows that they're just a [ __ ] [ __ ]
And it ain't winning anything. It ain't
winning anything. It's being a coward.
It's being a [ __ ]
And I bring all of this up on this video
as well when I invite him with the smoky
bee. Since you're trying to egg stuff on,
you little [ __ ] You know,
they will be on here Christmas Day. They
will definitely be on here Christmas Day.
They will definitely be on here Christmas Day. So, yeah.
But yeah, you've got the um you've got
the invitation since you want to plug
people's [ __ ] and try to [ __ ] stir. Uh
yeah, I'll bring it all up in a video,
bro. I'll bring it all up. Trust me.
Why are you showing Smokey B [ __ ] Come
with him, bro. Come with him.
And I'll deal with both of you. Not a problem.
Cuz we all start. We all We all know Red
Star is never going to meet anyone
because I was on here last Christmas and
they were on here.
I was live last Christmas and people was
on it. Definitely was on here. So,
they're all going to be on here, bro.
They're just going to say they're not on here.
If anyone goes live Christmas, Yeah.
like say Lisa goes live Christmas. L is
going to be like, "Oh yeah, you went
live Christmas." But he's going to be on
here Christmas. He will actually be on
He actually will.
>> Yeah. So,
can't believe you're saying all of that
vile [ __ ] when you're the one that went
running to the police. That is madness,
bro. That is
That is [ __ ] up. Very, very [ __ ] up, bro.
That is really bad, bro.
But no, even if it's void, I don't think
I would do anything anyways.
Unless they actually come here because
yeah, you know they're a grass. You know
that they're a little snitch
and you know that even if you went there
the [ __ ] is never going to come out cuz
he's a coward.
So the biggest coward going little [ __ ]
He's been doing this for like seven
years now. This virgin come to think no
hold am I? Yeah, he's been he's also
been doing this for seven years on the internet
because of the whole Izzy thing. Yeah,
he's also been doing this for years.
I remember I think I've been to his area
about five times, you know, bro. Three
in that area and two in the other which
are like 10 minutes away from each other, you know.
Bro, listen, there is no bell cuz I've
got plenty of evidence on this little
[ __ ] and what he's done. So, I've got
plenty of evidence of what he's done.
The police have seen his channel. So, yeah.
So, yeah. And he's been doing this for
seven years now. This loser Triple H.
He's been doing it, he's also been doing
it for seven years, the loser. And I've
been to this cunt's area five times.
Five [ __ ] times. Three in one and two
in the other.
And it's been for seven years now. when
I was 21. This this [ __ ] virgin has
been doing this.
So yeah. And bro, just easily Yeah. Just
come with Smokey B, bro.
Yeah. He's not getting no one done,
mate. I've got plenty of evidence of this [ __ ]
So I've got plenty of evidence on this
[ __ ] He ain't getting anyone done,
mate. The only one that's going to be
getting done is himself.
So yeah. What a loser he is. And I'm
going to talk about how much of a loser
he is as well in my video before I get
onto that smoky bee.
Your life being obsessed every day for
seven years. Yeah, you you did you did
not you did not cut contact with
someone. Yeah, you [ __ ] stupid little skint virgin.
You didn't cut contact with someone.
Seven years you've been doing this. And
I'm sure I've been to that area four or five times.
[ __ ] never come out once. [ __ ] never
Not even once, Dusty. Not even once.
Yeah, bro. I I Yeah. Okay. You keep
telling yourself that, bro. I've got
evidence of what he's done. The police
have seen everything he has done. So,
yeah. Good luck with that, bro. Yeah.
Good luck with that. He's not going to
win, brother. Let me tell you something.
Yeah. Someone that's been nicked
multiple times. He is not going to win
in the end. All of this [ __ ] right, is
temporary. Temporarily. He is never ever
ever ever ever
going to win in the end. Never.
Yeah. Trust me on that one. Yeah. And
you can you can you can you can talk to
your MS who's a solicitor, right? And
and and she will she will tell you that
you're not going to win in the end.
Whether it's one year, two years, three
years, you're not ever going to win in the end.
And you're just going to be like the boy
who cried wolf. Trust me, you won't.
So, it's all for nothing really. You're
just wasting everyone's time. It's just
you've decided to come on YouTube being
a loser. You got owned.
No, no, no. It will. It definitely
definitely definitely definitely
definitely definitely will. 100%. It
definitely definitely definitely will.
So, I mean, it ain't even going to go to
court anyways, but it definitely
definitely definitely will. So, you've
wasted everyone's time all cuz you're a
loser on YouTube that's obsessed when
there's people that are literally
getting their phone snatched, getting
killed. [ __ ] domestic violence is
going on. Imagine that. Yeah. Triple.
There's people in the world. Yeah.
That's getting their bike stolen,
getting stabbed up there. There's
serious crime in the world. And then
you've got some little virgin loser. You
ain't got no life outside of YouTube
having to ring them up. And he's never
ever going to win in the end. Never.
He's never going to win in the end. Trust me,
never ever ever going to win in the end.
The only reason this has happened,
listen, listen, right? The only reason
this has happened is because he went
crying to the police a million times,
crying and crying and crying, and he did
not show them the stuff that he's been
doing. That's the only reason is cuz
he's a grass and I'm not. That's the
only reason. He kept crying, crying,
crying, crying, crying. No, they won't.
No, they won't. No, they won't. Because
he that that has already been that has
already been voided.
So that's already been voided.
>> So yeah, that's already been voided. So
trust me, man. I know more than you,
man. Trust me, that's already been voided.
Trust me, man. That has already been
voided, man. And when it goes to court
in 3 years, man, you're going to see, man. Yeah.
Simple. Yeah, that live stream. Yeah.
It's I'm going to Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
Yeah. I'm going to keep this live stream
up as well.
[ __ ] this little virgin [ __ ] up.
Oh, bro, listen. We're not getting into
this again, bro. Listen. Go back to your
boyfriend's channel and go lick his ass.
Yeah, he is not going to win. I know
more than you about this. Stop coming on
my channel. [ __ ] off. Yeah, simple.
Yeah, he ain't going to win, man. I know
more than you, man. I've got [ __ ] 200
pages of [ __ ] that he's done, man. Yeah.
You understand me, bro? Simple.
You're breaking your own restrictions.
How are you going to win in court? How
are you going to win in court, bro, when
there's evidence of you harassing
people, doing people? How how are you
going to win that, bro? Yeah. If your if
your solicitor if your miss is is an
actual solicitor, you tell her, "How are
you going to talk your way out of
antagonizing someone every day for
years?" And they're not going to look at
that. And they're not going to look at
that. So, you've got all of this. Yeah.
you. So, you've got all of this evidence
of someone harassing you every day and
the court's going to be like, "Nope,
nope, nope." And what what and just send
you in jail. You're a [ __ ] bro. You
don't know how the law works? You
obviously do not know how the law works.
And the fact that it's been reported
multiple times and then it's going to be
like, "Yeah, yeah, you're going prison."
Yeah. Really, bro? You really think
that's going to happen? Yeah. You're an
absolute idiot, mate. You're an absolute
idiot. I do understand how it works,
mate. I've been nicked multiple multiple
times. Yeah, multiple multiple times.
Yeah. Okay, bro. You don't understand
how it works. You're a [ __ ] idiot. Go
back to your boyfriend's channel. Go
and [ __ ] his dick some more. You don't
know how it works.
Well, there's none now, but it was not
to contact him, but obviously he's he's
been contacting me. So, I've got
everything, bro. I've literally got everything.
And anyways, why are we talking about
that? That's in three and a half years.
It's not even going to go to court. But
in terms of the conditions, bro, he's
already broke the conditions
by contacting me. So, he's already broke
themself. So, it's void.
So, that's that.
So, anyways, that's that. [ __ ] hell.
I could be [ __ ] dead in three and a
half years. Why are we even talking about that?
So yeah, and the only reason Triple H
that it's this is because he kept
running crying to them cuz he's a loser.
He kept coming on YouTube starting [ __ ]
starting [ __ ] and then go running and
crying to the police. That's the only
reason why this has happened. By the
way, that's not winning. An unbiased
person would know that it's not winning.
But these jealous people always side
with dancers cuz they're dancers themselves.
Bro, he has no conditions because he
went crying to the police and I didn't
snitch once. No, no, no. Listen to me,
[ __ ] Listen to me, [ __ ] Right.
Listen to me, you [ __ ] [ __ ] Cuz
you don't understand how this works. If
me and Triple H was arguing right now,
right? Say me and Triple H was going
back and forth, back and forth, back and
forth, and he was and I was worse than
him, and I continuously grasped on him,
and he didn't grasp on me. What do you
think's going to happen, you [ __ ]
What do you think's going to happen? You
absolute [ __ ] He's going to get
nicked and I'm going to have conditions
on him. You [ __ ] [ __ ] The only
reason he's got conditions is cuz he
kept crying to the police over and over
and over again. Yes. Because he kept
crying to the police.
Yes. Yes, bro. He kept running and
crying to the police, harassing the
police. Yeah. That's not winning. Do you understand
that is not cuz he kept crying to the
police over and over and over again
[ __ ] and I didn't grass once because
he's a little grass
again not winning. I don't know how many
times someone's had to say this to you
but again because you love nons on here
cuz your nons your [ __ ] self you know
you're you are just going to you know
just make stuff up bro that's what you do.
running to the police and crying is not
winning. And the people that sit there
and say that are people that you just
know they're just idiots,
you know, idiots. And yes, it is a joke.
Loads of things go to crown court now
straight away instead of magistrates.
Again, that's not winning. That's being
a loser. And again, you people here like
pedophiles. The thing is, Triple H, with
these people on this community, they're like pedophiles.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no. A lot of
things go to Crown Court now. No, no,
Triple H, a lot of things go straight to
Crown Court now. Um, a lot of stuff
does, you know.
You know what I'm saying? So, but again,
because these people like actual pedophiles,
um, they are just always going to say
that he's one. That's part of their
jealousy as well. Two minds think alike.
You know what I mean?
You know what I'm saying?
So yeah, you you kept running to the
police continuously crying. Uh that's
why they done something about it and
you've got conditions. Again, not
winning. We know that you love
pedophiles on here, you know. Yeah, bro.
No, you're not scaring me. It's not
going to court. So again, that's not
winning. That's not winning. That's
being a loser. That means you got owned
on YouTube that you had to go run into
the police. That's not winning. That is
literally not winning. Maybe in your
little mind it's winning, but it's not winning.
So, and I don't want anything to do with
a loser. I don't even want to mention
the [ __ ] loser. So, in a way, they
done me a favor.
So, but again, because you love
pedophiles, you know.
So, yeah, you love pedophiles on here.
You say that you've got a problem with
what people say about [ __ ] kids.
Yeah. Well, you definitely not scare me
because it ain't going to court. So yeah.
So yeah, and because you kept running to
the police, crying to the police, that's
why they done something. They done it
two times. He done it two times. Triple
H. Yeah. The first thing with the money.
The first thing with the money in the
post is then he went crying to them
again. He literally has been harassing
the police cuz he's a loser. So that's
why they've not seen that everything
that he's done yet. But they're aware of
what he does now because of my
solicitor. That's probably why every
time he tries to call the police, they
just tell him to [ __ ] off because they
all know about his channel now. He's a
loser, bro. He's a proper proper proper
proper loser. So, as you can see, these
people have been doing this for years
and years and years and years and years
and years. They've been doing this, bro. So, yeah.
And the sad thing is it's all jealousy.
That's the bad thing about it, bro. This
is, you know, Yeah.
No, that thing got dismissed. The poster
That's something completely different.
What he does, what this little weirdo
does, right, is is he goes to people on
YouTube. He's a proper proper loser. He
goes people on YouTube and then when
they react to him, he goes to the
police. He's a loser. It doesn't matter
what I went. It doesn't matter what I
went, but that's not over the poster, you know.
Yeah, simple. And we're not talking
about this little rat, bro. I'm going to
do a video in a bit. Anyways, I'm not
talking about this little rat loser
anymore, bro. It just pisses me off. I
hate keyboard warriors, bro. Little
[ __ ] keyboard warriors. I hate
keyboard warriors, bro. So, like, I
don't even want to talk about this rat
anymore. But anyways,
you people just don't know when to leave
people alone, do you? Jealous.
Up, down, up, down.
Yeah, bro. We're not talk I'm not
talking about this anymore anyways. Just
keyboard warrior [ __ ]
You're not going to jail over that. Grow
up. And I'm not talking about this
anymore, bro. Stop bringing up [ __ ]
stupid [ __ ] You know what I mean?
Talking about this little keyboard
warrior. This little jealous little
lowife keyboard warrior. You know
what I mean?
[ __ ] me, bro.
It's not even winning. It's just
cowardly. It's It honestly is cowardly.
And you're never going to win in the
end. So, what was even the point of just
wasting everyone's time? Does that not
show you in itself that that is obsession? Yeah.
Simple. And we're not talking about
these little clowns anymore. I'm not
talking about him, bro. Bro, I don't
care. I'm not talking about this
anymore. This little clown.
So, stop bringing it up, bro. I would
talking about this anymore, bro. I
really don't give a [ __ ] So, yeah.
been keeping this live stream up as well
along with all the other evidence that
I've got on you. So, yeah.
So, yeah, bro.
Some madness, bro. Madness.
And I think if this [ __ ] does not come with him,
I want everyone to stop bringing this
coward up on my channel. Simple as that,
bro. This little coward, motherless
loser up on my channel.
You know, and I and I hope you really do
do it, bro.
You know what I mean? People
just be getting timeouts from uh from
the future, bro. You know what I mean? That's it.
I'm not playing. I've got all the
evidence. I've got all the evidence. So,
I'm not playing into anyone's hand
hands. And I've got the crime reference
number. And I'm not talking about this
no more. Stop bringing the [ __ ] up, bro.
I don't like keyboard warriors. So, stop
bringing it up to me, bro. I don't want
to talk about it no more.
So, we're not talking about this same
argument with this loser. I haven't come
on here to talk about this. I'm going to
do a video. I want this [ __ ] to come
with Smokey B and see what the cunt's
really about. You want to host fights.
You want to antagonize people. We'll
bring up some of your L's and that's it,
bro. I'm not saying anything more. Yeah.
I don't even have to be wasting my time
doing this one more time.
Oh, bro. I don't care. Stop bringing it
up. I don't care. [ __ ] drop it now,
bro. Cuz I'm just going to start timing
you out. Drop it. Read the room. Stop
it, bro. Yeah.
Jesus Christ. I'm not talking about this
no more. I'm going to do what I said I'm
going to do, bro. Yeah. And that's it.
Simple. You don't need to know what I'm
going to do. You people need to [ __ ]
just grow up and get a [ __ ] life.
You've been doing this for seven, eight
[ __ ] years now. Seven, eight years now, bro. Yeah. Simple.
I've got all of the [ __ ] that you've
done to me. Simple. I'm not talking
anymore about this. I'm blocking, bro. I
don't want to talk about this. Stop
bringing it up. You do the same [ __ ] on
Monty's channel. Stop bringing these
little clowns up.
Simple. I don't give a [ __ ] Bring up
one more time. I'm blocking you. It's
annoying, bro. Same [ __ ] same
atmosphere. And I'm going to explain
this as well on this video as well. I'm
going to explain this as well on this
[ __ ] video, bro.
You know, simple.
So, you got to do this anyways. Anyways,
moving on now. Yeah. So, what what
what's your New Year's resolutions? Are
you just going to keep coming on YouTube
every day harassing people?
Like, I'm asking you, what are you what
are you doing, bro?
Are you still going to keep coming on
here harassing people? Cuz I've already
told you what I'm doing, bro. I'm I'm
telling you what I'm doing. I'm posting
content now. I don't care about you little clowns. So So yeah,
going back to this thing. Yeah. Like
what are you doing? Are you going to
keep coming on here harassing people?
I'm just I'm just curious, bro. Like,
you don't even need to know. I'm just curious.
I just want to know like what cuz I told
you what I'm doing. You see,
I don't know what it is with these
people. Triple H. It's [ __ ] eight
years, bro. Eight [ __ ] years.
Like I told you with that USA Izzy
thing, I gave up after a while, bro. And
this was someone I met.
I gave up after a while. I just couldn't.
But I don't think they they have the
intelligence to understand how bad
they're actually doing this, bro.
Like, it's bad, bro. It's really shitty,
man. What they're doing on here.
It's been going on for years, bro. It
really, really, really has.
Just the same people doing the same
[ __ ] you know? over and over and over
again. But it's my fault. I shouldn't
have let the little nons on to be honest
with you. But I thought it would just
been funny because I was asking you why
you copy my holiday. But bro, listen.
Like now if this [ __ ] is not going to
come with this smokeoky bee then, bro,
just just drop me out, mate. It's
getting boring now. 7 years you've been
doing this now. You ain't got no [ __ ]
life. You've been doing this for seven
years. And anyone that brings it up, I'm
just going to ignore them. I ain't even
going to block them. Simple as that.
It's very very obsess obsessive. It's
obsessive. Even with the police, it's very obsessive.
Every day they they wake up thinking,
"Who can we [ __ ] with today?"
They get out of bed. Yeah. They're like,
"Hm, who can we [ __ ] with today?" That's
literally these people here, bro.
That's what they do. They're like, "Oh,
who can we [ __ ] with today? Let's [ __ ]
with this [ __ ] Let's [ __ ] with that
That's literally what they do, bro.
We've seen what they do on here.
It's mad. So yeah, hopefully he can come
with Smokey Be. That would be that would be ace.
And that's another thing with this
little coward. He's such a little [ __ ]
house that everything that he tries to
do is he tries to he tries to stir [ __ ]
That's another thing. He tries to host
fights like which is what uh LJ used to
do as well. He used to host. He tried to
host fights but would never ever
actually want to get involved himself.
They're little [ __ ] I can safely say I
can confirm, bro. Honestly,
he's probably the biggest coward on this community.
Probably. Yeah, man. With that Trevor
Dawson, I'd say no. He's definitely the
definitely the worst.
You know what I mean?
These jealous people will never leave me
alone, bro. It's mad,
bro. If he comes on my Bro, if he comes
on the door, he comes on the door.
Simple as that.
What do you mean? They're coming on your door.
So, I mean, they're coming on your door.
They won't leave you alone. They've been
doing this for years and years and
years. They will not leave you alone.
Yeah. So, okay. What?
So that's that.
Yeah. Anyways, I'll be done after this. So yeah,
[ __ ] madness with these jealous
people on here, bro. Jesus worst. You
Yeah. Yeah, it's fine. >> Yeah. Madness. Absolute madness.
No, no, no, no, no. I'm not going to
ignore them, bro, because they've been
pissing me off, bro. No. I'm not going
to ignore I'm doing this video and then
I'm going to ignore it. Yeah. I'm going
to set this record straight once and for
all. And all of these [ __ ] that are
going to try coming on, they're not
coming on here anymore, bro. They're not
coming on my live stream cuz I've had
enough of it, bro. I've had a [ __ ]
enough of it. Yeah, this has been two
weeks with these little [ __ ] on
here. Two weeks. We've had to see their [ __ ] Yeah,
we've had to see their [ __ ] bro. We've
So, that's that, bro.
Coming on here, bro. [ __ ] No, I'll
set it straight once and for all, bro.
That's it. And then I'm done. [ __ ] idiots.
[ __ ] idiots, bro.
So now you have now you know the story
how this [ __ ] actually got on this YouTube.
Now you know how this little [ __ ]
actually got on YouTube.
Bro, I've got him harassing me. I don't
give a [ __ ] I'm willing to take that
risk. I've got the [ __ ] harassing me.
I'm willing to take that ris risk. So
I've got no problem. So
yeah. Yeah. I don't really give a [ __ ]
No, I've got proof of this little [ __ ]
harassing me. So I'm willing to take
that risk risk cuz this has got to stop,
bro. This has seriously seriously got to
stop. So like I said, remember Triple H,
they're never going to win in the end
with the law. So do what you want. You
already tried that two weeks ago. I
don't give a [ __ ]
Simple. There we go. I'm screenshotting
that now. This little [ __ ] right? And
I'm leaving this live stream up. Don't
worry, I'll be doing a video of you in a
bit, mate. And you're not going to have
me I I only want your response on your channel.
Yeah. On your channel. I only want your
response on your channel. Right. [ __ ]
hosting fights with Smokey B and all of
that. Don't worry, you'll get your video
in a bit, bro. You're not coming on. [ __ ] off.
There we go. More evidence for me now.
You want to play this game, bro? We'll
play this game. It's not a problem.
All cuz your mom starved you and don't
love you. Probably similar to Smokey
Bee's uh Smokeoky Bee's situation, but it's okay.
There we go.
I've got a lot of your comments as well
recently, so that's not a problem. Yeah.
Right. This little harasser. One second.
You will never stop. They will never
leave you alone. One second.
>> Yeah, there we go. Got that lovely
evidence for me. Thank you. That's even
more evidence for me. Thank you, matey.
Listen, you can say whatever you want
because I'm going to do a video of you
in a bit. I'm going to do a video of you
in a bit and I'm going to talk about
your L's and how much of a coward you
are and how you're not going to come
here with Smokey B yet you're more than
happy to host fights. It's all right, bro.
I don't give a [ __ ] I'm willing to take
that risk. I don't care. I'm willing to
take that risk. I don't care. I've got
plenty of evidence. I'm comfortable,
bro. I'm very, very, very, very
comfortable. I don't give a [ __ ]
Literally, I don't care. Like, I don't
care. I've got plenty of evidence. He
will not leave me alone. This stalker,
I'm willing to take that risk 100%.
That's how confident I am. Yeah.
Simple, lad. Simple.
That's fine. I've got all my evidence
and that's fine. And I will keep
reporting and reporting and reporting.
If the police come here, this [ __ ] will
not leave me alone. Not a problem. Not a
problem at all. But we're going to talk
about how all of the L's that you've
took, right? and you're going to be
invited with him. If you've got anything
to say, you can come and say it to my
face. Simple. Stop typing. Stop doing
fights when you've run away multiple
times to the police when people have
come to your area. I'm going to make you
look silly in this video and that's all
I'm going to say. And I'm going to go on
your channel and I'm going to want a response.
I've got plenty of evidence that is him.
I've got him talking about me with his
face. I've got the lot, mate. I've got
everything. I have literally got the
lot. I've got 200 pages and screenshots
and videos, mate. So, again, I've got
enough evidence. I don't give a [ __ ] Simple.
That is completely fine.
That's why. Look at this little projector.
This is definitely because his mom
starved him. Bro, the Christmas
projector's out. The Christmas projector is out.
Yes, the Christmas projector is out. All
because his mom starved him. It's the
It's a trend of Bro, listen. Triple H. I
don't care. I've told you I don't care.
Listen to me. I don't care. Listen, I've
got plenty of evidence.
Yeah, I've got plenty of evidence. I
don't care. Listen to me. I don't care.
I'm going to do one video. Yeah. And
that's it. You've run away when people
have come to your area. Stop trying to
[ __ ] stir people's fights when we've all
seen it multiple times. [ __ ] That's it,
bro. I've got plenty of evidence. I'm
comfortable. Trust me, I'm comfortable.
Yeah, I've got proof. I have got proof.
It's him. I've got videos. I understand
more than you. Drop it now. Yeah. Drop it.
You know, I've got plenty of plenty of
evidence. I'm more than comfortable.
Drop it now. Right. We're not talking
about this no more. You're going to get
a video in a bit. And that's it. Simple.
I've got plenty. I'm comfortable with my
evidence. And that's it. Simple. Of this
motherless loser, this motherless [ __ ]
And that's that. Simple. You don't need
to worry about it, bro.
Simple. Of this motherless loser.
Yeah. And that's that. Right. We're not
talking about this anymore. Anyways,
I've all screenshotted this [ __ ] anyway,
so it's all good, bro. Not a problem.
I've got loads and loads and loads of
videos with his face. I've got everything. Yeah,
bro. I know more than you will ever
know. Yeah, mate. Listen. Right. Bring
it up one more time and I'm blocking
you. You bring it up one more time and
I'm blocking you, bro. Yeah.
You bring it up one more time and I'm
[ __ ] blocking you. Simple. Yeah, you
got the chance. Simple. Bring it up one
more time and I'm blocking you. Simple.
you will ever know. Yeah. Bring it up
one more time without blocking you.
Simple. You got your warning. Yeah. You
like to keep bringing these people up
time and time again, bro. Yeah. Simple.
Yeah. I'm not talking about this no
more, bro. Leave it. Don't worry about
me, bro. Move on. Let's move on.
move on from this anyways, bro. Let's
Let's not bring it up anymore. Don't worry.
Don't worry, bro.
No, no. I need to do a video to this
Smokeoky B anyways, bro. I need to do a
video to the Smokeoky B. So, yeah. Don't
worry, bro. It's not a problem.
Right. There we go. More evidence.
Lovely. Keep the evidence coming. Keep
The motherless loser. Keep the evidence
coming, motherless loser. Give it all to
me. Bring the evidence to me,
you [ __ ] with no mother. Keep the
evidence coming cuz you ain't got no
money. Keep it coming. Keep it coming.
That's all I'm saying. Keep it coming,
motherless loser. Keep it coming.
Keep it coming. Come to papa. Give all
the evidence to me, bro. Come on.
Right. Keep it coming. Keep it coming.
Keep it coming. Keep it coming. Thank
you. Keep it coming. Thank you.
[ __ ] loser. Loser with no mother. I'm
going to do a video on this [ __ ] as
well. This loser with no mother. It's
cuz he kept [ __ ] talking over people.
This is all because I've got a mother
and I've got family unlike him. This is
all cuz he's jealous cuz I've got a mom.
It's the same with Smokeoky B, bro.
It's It's the same as Smokeoky B Joker.
This is all because my mom didn't starve
me. All cuz I weren't rejected by my
mother. You do realize that this is all
because, right, my mom didn't starve me
and leave me on the street like this
[ __ ] And I'm going to bring up all of
your L's when you ran away when you ran
away to the police. When people come to your area,
when people went to your area, you kept
running to the police, yet you keep
trying to host fights between me and
people. Really, bro? Really? Come on now. It's embarrassing.
You need to [ __ ] get off of YouTube
and [ __ ] get laid and lose your
[ __ ] Valentine's card, you [ __ ]
virgin. This is what I said to you earlier.
Get off of YouTube and go get laid and
get a life. I've been saying this for [ __ ] years. Yeah. Proper. Yeah.
Yeah. Anyways, I'm going to do a video.
well, we're not talking about this
anymore. Anyways, we're going to do a
video to this Smokeoky B in a bit. Talk
about your L's when people came to your
area and you when people came to your
area and you didn't come out. We'll talk
about some of your L's. We We will
actually edit things and talk about the
time that you didn't come out when you
was begging LT to do stuff. We'll talk
about some of your L's just just to set
the record straight.
Yeah. We'll set the record straight of
all the times you didn't come out and
you didn't so much as say anything to anyone. Yeah.
You know what I mean? You know what I'm saying, bro?
And that is literally going to be it,
bro. That is literally going to be it.
He doesn't have a life. He does, bro.
Listen, Joker. The Virgin don't have a life.
The Virgin does not have a life,
mate. I've tried to get away from this
[ __ ] virgin for years, Joker. He
won't leave me alone. The skinned
version won't leave me alone. I' I've
been trying for years and years and
years with this skint virgin, but he
won't leave me alone. He will This has
been going on for seven years with this virgin.
Through this motherless skint virgin for
8 years, I swear to God. Eight [ __ ]
years this skint little shitty virgin
has been at me with his shitty little
virgin face, bro. For eight years. Eight [ __ ] years.
Leave me alone, you [ __ ] virgin. Like
I said, I'm going to give you the chance
to come out with your boyfriend on on on
Saturday and that's it.
And if you're not going to do that,
virgin, you're not getting a platform
anymore. I was nice enough to give you a
platform, you motherless loser. But then
you became bitter again. And we don't
like that kind of talk on this channel.
You know what I mean?
[ __ ] virgin. Yep. There we go. Keep
the evidence coming. You're only [ __ ]
yourself up. you all you're doing is
[ __ ] yourself up.
All you're really really doing is
[ __ ] yourself up. So just just carry
on and carry on and carry on and carry
on and carry on. Yeah.
Yeah, I will be doing after this video,
bro. Don't worry. But that means don't
bring this virgin up anymore, bro. Yeah.
Do not bring it up. Do not bring it up,
bro. I want to do this video to this
[ __ ] Smokey Be the cheeky little
Yeah, you got me on this [ __ ] again when
I didn't even want to come on here
today. The [ __ ] got me back on it, bro.
These people, bro, they really get you
deep in this [ __ ] bro. I swear to God.
So yeah, what are we on, bro? Uh 8%.
Bro, do you know what I'm really
thinking of doing? Yeah. Um
I don't know how many people I can trust
with the channel.
I was thinking of just sending people
over to my new channel, like people that
I could trust in that. I don't know, bro.
I don't know, man. I don't know what I'm
doing with this channel. I'm trying to think virgin.
No, don't talk about my [ __ ] L, bro.
You [ __ ] didn't even come out your
area when people went to meet you, you
shitty little [ __ ]
You shitty little [ __ ]
Even when even when there were [ __ ]
drawers, you absolute coward.
I'm surprised even other people still
give this kind of platform. You know,
[ __ ] the lengths these people go to.
Joker, bro, is is insane, lad. Is insane.
Madness. Absolute madness.
[ __ ] madness with these people, bro.
I think I'm just going to end up getting
off here and living my life, bro. To be
honest, before long. Serious.
I've got a whole another channel. I've
got a whole another channel, bro. I've
bro. I think I'm just going to just go
on that channel, you know, man,
and I'll come live on here once in a
while. I'll post videos on here once in
a while, but that's it, bro. This is
weird. This is [ __ ] weird. It's
giving me the ebiejeebies.
No, I've got a separate channel, bro.
I've got loads of videos on my separate
channel. They can't find me. They'll
never find me.
Yeah. Anyways, no one anyways, bro.
Nah, these people in this community
definitely don't have a life, bro. They
definitely definitely don't have a life.
Most people on here don't have a life,
bro. Just like that Smokey B.
Listen, the thing is, Triple, don't ever
mention a guy's name again after this
video. Yeah. Don't ever mention this
guy's name again. Please
do not mention this guy's name again to
me. Don't do it to me because he ain't
never ever coming up. If he does not
come with Smokey Be on Saturday, this
little virgin is is never ever getting a
platform again on my life. I'm never
mentioning this coming again. Yeah,
simple, bro. I'll put them both in their
place and that's it. And I don't want
nothing now, bro, until then. Simple.
Yeah. And I will not even mention the
[ __ ] No more silly quot. No more nothing.
No more nothing, bro. Nothing. No funny
quotes. If this country ain't going to
back up these foul mouth. Yeah. Then that's it.
This is Yeah, that's it, bro. They're
not They don't They don't They ain't
deserve the platform.
We'll talk about some of your L's. We'll
talk about some of your L's you seem to
be projecting about. Yeah.
Yeah. That's it, bro. Exactly. Yeah,
we're not even going to bring it up.
We're not even going to do, like I said,
I'm not going to be going live much
anyways. I'll just be doing videos. So,
there's no way they can do anything.
You would have thought, bro, they would
have just got a [ __ ] life by now. Madness.
So, yeah, that's that. Yeah,
I've had to block about 30 different
accounts. You know that yesterday I had
to yesterday I had to block about 30
accounts from these self projectors. 30
of the same people. Now again, bro, we
know that they self project usually.
Yeah. Yeah. You know what I'm saying, bro?
You know what I'm saying? Like we know
that these people are self projectors
but not on this level. It's like they're
being the Grinch, bro.
I'm going to talk about your L's when I
come to your area two times and you
didn't show up. Would start talking
about your L's. Not a woman on a train
where I actually defended myself and
told her that she looked like an ugly
crackhead. Uh that was not me running to
the police. So yeah.
Anyways, we'll talk about some of your
L's when people went to your area and
you didn't show up, but you're on here
trying to host fights. Um, which is
something that LJ J used to do. Uh, LJ J
used to try to host fights,
but uh, LJ used to try to host fights,
but I mean LJ actually met people. When
people come to your area, you don't even
show up. So, uh, yeah, that is just
self-p projection in many, many
different ways. And we'll also bring up
your childhood as well.
Yeah, that's definitely projection when
you're talking about L's because
everyone knows that I went to your area
four times and you didn't even come out,
let alone say anything. You didn't even
say anything. You didn't even come out.
So, yeah, you might want to want to
practice your own nails. We'll talk
about your dad knocking your mom about,
how your mom starved you,
how you was put into care at a young
age. He was literally put into care at a
very young age because of it.
which is what I was trying to hold out
and saying, but you drove me to it. You
was actually put into a care at a very
young age because of it. You know,
[ __ ] was put into care and he
was talking about me.
He was put into care at a very young age
because of it.
Yeah. Put into care. That's mad, bro. Cuz
your mother couldn't handle your erratic behavior.
You little [ __ ]
Yep. Know a lot about you.
I know a lot about you.
And we're talking about going to talk
about your childhood. You reflect a lot
on dead relatives today.
But guess what? My all bro more family
members could die. But guess what? I've
got more family than you will ever have.
And you're going to be Christmas with no
mommy. Not me. Yeah.
Yeah. I've got mommy for Christmas. You
ain't got mommy.
You know what I'm saying? You ain't got
mommy for Christmas.
Yeah. Well, I mean, my dad died. Okay.
Yeah. But your mom hates you. I mean,
there's no excuse. your your mom's, you
know, you're talking about a dad that I
don't care about. All you do keep doing
is talking about my dad that never even
lived with me, you know?
So what, bro? I don't give a [ __ ] I've
still got more family than you. And my
mom don't hate me. So,
and you still ain't grown a pair of
balls to say anything to anyone's face.
Once a virgin, always a virgin.
You know what I mean? Yeah.
So nothing changed there in 8 years.
Your mom starved you. Shut the [ __ ] up,
you little [ __ ] Yeah.
I don't know why he's making fun out of
dead relatives when his dad is literally
going to be dead in like 5 years and
he's making fun out of dead relatives. You know,
your dad is going to be dead in like a
couple of years and you're making fun
out of dead relatives. Strange, isn't it?
When your dad's going to be dead in like
5 years, your dad is literally going to
be dead when you're still alive. Like,
it's only a matter of a time when you're
talking about people's dead relatives
when your mom hates you and she's not
even dead. Madness. But like I said, you
can come with Smoky B anyways on
Saturday and you can come and say to my
face. You can say all of this vile nasty
[ __ ] to my face. This time hopefully you
actually come out
because the last [ __ ] four times I
went to that virgin area, you didn't
come out. But you're one to talk about
people taking L's when you literally
don't even come out.
You literally did not come out.
You literally didn't come out your
virgin area, which is why you're so
mistaken with these [ __ ] L's.
You I went to your area. You didn't come
out. Whereas these train station videos,
I told a woman she's an ugly crackhead.
You didn't come out.
So even if I didn't win, it would have
been a draw. You didn't come out of your area.
You didn't come out,
which is which is which is [ __ ] less
than people [ __ ] saying [ __ ]
No, no, no, no. It's nothing to do with
that, Joker. Even if you don't come on
here, they still won't go for him.
Trust me, bro. There's a lot of jealous
people on this community. There's a lot
of jealous people on this community,
bro. Trust me. It's not about that. They
do like him, bro. Even when you're not
on here, they will never go for him.
They love nons on here, bro. Trust me,
they're nonsers. They're nonsers
themselves. Believe you me, bro.
So, yeah. But like, I'm not I'm not
continuing this back and forth [ __ ]
bro. If this [ __ ] ain't going to come
If this [ __ ] ain't going to come with
his boyfriend Smokeoky Bee, then bro, I
ain't interested. Simple. Yeah.
Simple. And that's that. So why are you
putting the man [ __ ] up when you're
never ever going to come and meet anyone? You know,
you [ __ ] obsessed little virgin
went to your area. You didn't even come
out. Who you talking about elves? How
the [ __ ] are you talking about L's, bro?
What the [ __ ] How can this [ __ ] talk
about L's when this virgin took the
biggest L's ever? He's literally let
someone come to his area three times and
he didn't come out.
I literally went to the virgin area
three times and he did not come out.
What the [ __ ] Yeah,
madness, bro. And you're talking about a
[ __ ] woman on the train. What the
bro? What the hell are you talking
about? You didn't even come the [ __ ] out
and even raise your voice at all. You
didn't even come out and raise your
voice. You didn't even come out and say
anything, you absolute [ __ ] clown.
You know, the real is if I'm running
away the way you run away three times,
you [ __ ] idiot. you know.
Yeah. You've got no desire to meet him,
but yet you just want to be on YouTube
obsessed every day. So, you don't want
to meet anyone, but you want to be on
YouTube obsessed every day for seven years,
right? Yeah. Make that make sense.
Yeah. You got no desire to meet because
you're a [ __ ] and then you want to talk
about people taking [ __ ] L's.
Yeah. You got no desire to meet someone,
but you're more than happy to be a
virgin on YouTube for 8 years, you
virgin. And on my videos, you're not
going to be able to talk over me.
You absolute virgin. You've got a whole
YouTube channel dedicated to me. You
absolute virgin. All anyone has to do. I
do not have a channel dedicated to some
little ratfaced virgin. You're the one
that's got a channel dedicated to me. I
do not have a channel dedicated to some
virgin like you. You have got the
channel dedicated to me. I think that
pretty much sums up the person who's obsessed.
The one that sums up the ones who's
obsessed is you and your virgin channel.
I do not have a channel on some ugly rat
looking Kent virgin.
You know, I don't have a channel
dedicated to some virgin. You have got a
channel dedicated to me and all your
channel is is dedicated to [ __ ] me.
So, shut the [ __ ] up. Obsessed is you.
You are literally obsessed. And you're
the biggest incel ever. You've never
been with a You've never been with a
normal girl. You are the incel. So, you
might want to show people yourself
because you're the biggest incel going.
I've had more women than you, more girls
than you, never had to resort to
disabled. So, you might want to show
people yourself cuz you are the incel,
which is another thing we're going to
talk about. Only an incel would target
disabled women because they can't get
anything normal. Only an incel would do
that. Only an you're so much of an incel
that you had to start targeting disabled
women. Yeah. Show them yourself. Show
them yourself, you incel. That's another
thing I'm going to start calling you.
The biggest Orington virgin incel.
That's what you are. Yeah,
bro. Just show them yourself. The
biggest incel. The incel that had to
start targeting disabled.
The incel that couldn't get normal
things. So, we had to start targeting disabled women.
You need to show them yourself. The
alltime incel. That's you. I've never
resorted to disabled. All of the women
that I've hooked up with have never been disabled.
You should show them yourself. The
biggest incel, the alltime incel.
That's you. The alltime incel. And
you're also a [ __ ] You know what I'm
saying, bro? You start targeting
disabled cuz you can't get anything
normal. That's more of what an incel
will do. You know, I [ __ ] I literally
I literally talk about my experiences.
Yeah. I've had more women than you ever
have. The only incel is yourself.
Incel. That's another word that you like
to use. That's yourself. An incel. A
virgin. Everything that you say is self
projecting. You're the biggest incel.
You knew that the normal women didn't
want you, so you started targeting
disabled. Yeah. You are the incel.
You literally are the biggest incel. Yeah.
That's a fact.
the incel. An incel can't be I can't be
an incel if I've had more women than
you. How how can an incel have been with
more women than you and they've never
once been disabled?
No. No. The incel is you just like ugly
is you. I think you're getting yourself
definitely definitely mis mistaken here,
bro. I think you're getting yourself
definitely definitely mistaken. You are
the one that gets with disabled and
you've had less women than me. I think
you're the incel and I also think you
are the ug and I actually think you are
the ugly one as well.
So, you're actually getting yourself
seriously mixed up. You're getting
yourself mixed up with me. Definitely.
Definitely. You're the incel. Definitely
definitely you're the ugly one. No. No. 100%.
No, that is definitely you. Ugly incel.
No, no, that's definitely you. And you
can keep coming on here repeating for
seven years and it's not going to change
the fact that uh you know it's that that
is that is literally about you. That's
your life. So yeah,
doesn't change the fact that you're all
one of these things. You literally can
you literally can say that I'm ugly and
an insult all you want, but all you're
doing is talking about yourself,
putting yourself down for another 8 years.
Nah, not at all, Joker. Even if you come
off of it, they still won't go for him.
No, no, no. That's what everyone used to
think. But even when you come off, how
could this little virgin call anyone an
incel? He must be getting himself confused.
No. No, no, no. He's definitely
definitely the incel. How can someone be
an incel if they've technically been
with more women than that person? You do
realize most incelss have not had sex.
They've not been with women. An incel
that has had more women than you.
That literally does not make any sense.
Cuz if we see all of these incelss, you
love that word cuz that's what you are
yourself. Because that's why you started
targeting disabled and you started
targeting vulnerable people because you
are the alltime [ __ ] incel. Incelss.
Incel people don't even [ __ ] ain't
even had sex.
You [ __ ] absolute idiot. You are the [ __ ] incel.
Anyways, I hope you join your boyfriend
on Saturday as well since you like to uh
promote his [ __ ] if that's the word. you know.
Oh, well, you just not and you're just
going to do this [ __ ] again for another eight years. [ __ ] loser.
[ __ ] loser. Virgin.
Yeah, you're an incel yourself. You
might want to put yourself on your
channel, bro. You're the biggest incel
going around stalking women, asking them
about their sex life, all cuz you're
still a virgin. will bring up all of the
people that you stalked. All the women
that I've been with that you stalked.
No, that's that's definitely you. That's
the incel. Definitely definitely you.
Let's let's click the eye on the
information. Everything is about you.
All the L's are about you yourself.
Cuz let's put it right. If someone's
owned me in an argument,
what does that make you? If you ain't
even come out when someone's gone to
your area, what would that literally
make you? If someone's come to your area
Yeah. and and you ain't come out four
times, you little [ __ ] You know, you
you you little [ __ ] boy. I mean, what
what type of L's, bro?
Does does that mean you've took? Just
just just just think about it. What what
L's have you actually what L's have you
took? Many many different L's, you know?
Even that L J thing, bro. Yeah. At least
I actually opened the door. I was
chucking it to him. You know, this [ __ ]
didn't come out once.
Did not come out of that virgin area
once. That skint virgin area once.
So, anyways, make sure you come with
your boyfriend on Saturday as well.
Yeah, bro. I'm just going to do a video
on this Smokey B and this [ __ ] and then
I'm done with them, bro. Anyways. Yeah.
buy a pair of balls and start actually
[ __ ] saying [ __ ] to people's faces
and then that's it, bro. Yeah.
[ __ ] freak. Absolute freak.
[ __ ] weirdo on here, bro. Freaky
jealous weirdos. That's what they are. [ __ ] off.
I feel sorry for Paul Laney, to be
honest with you, man.
Bless her little heart. All cuz these
people got no family. [ __ ] got
nothing in their life.
It's sad, Joker. Really is sad, lad. It
is bad. It is bad. These people are bad, bro. Seriously. Yeah.
make a tea soon. And yeah,
then I can actually say this Smokeoky B
has actually started it this time, bro.
He actually has started it this time,
bro. Yeah. So, there's not even no case
of, "Oh, you're bringing trouble. I've
been live the past two weeks. You little
weirdos have not left me the [ __ ]
alone." Yeah. You know what I'm saying, Joker?
I've been live, bro, two weeks,
maybe a week and a half, and they have
not left me the [ __ ] alone, bro, for the
past two weeks. Yeah.
I'm not even I'm not even joking.
And that's another thing. Why are you
even talking about people's mothers? Cuz
you ain't got a mom. You know, it makes
it more and more now with these people.
Bro, they they this another thing I'm
going to mention in my video as well.
They have got no problem with
pedophiles. Yeah. These people on this
community have got no problem with nons.
Yeah. They've got no problem with pedos
and they've got and that Smokeoky B
actually started it bro. So there's not
even no You trouble. This guy has been
[ __ ] begging it, bro, for like two
weeks. Yeah. And then he's trying to
insult people's mother. He's trying to
insult people's mothers now. Oh, bro.
It's so obvious you ain't got a mother.
Both motherless. You know that's You
know what? That actually should be
titled the two motherless losers.
Yeah, that's that.
And they ain't got a life. That's
another thing, bro. They ain't got a
life. All they do is just harass people
that's got family and they ain't got family.
Every day. Every day. Every day.
Every day. Do not stop every day. Yeah. [ __ ] madness.
Don't try and call me a [ __ ] incel,
you little [ __ ]
You're the one stalking women, asking
them about their sex life when you're
supposed to be in a relationship, you
[ __ ] weirdo trying to say that
people's obsessed with you. You're the
one that's got a channel dedicated
an active channel dedicated to me, you
little [ __ ] Yeah. So, yeah.
I don't know what's going to be worse if
this guy doesn't show up or if he does
show up. I don't I don't know which worse.
Cuz if he doesn't,
well, he's going to look like an idiot.
If he does, it's going to show he's got
no life. He's got nothing going for
himself. and he's going to get beaten
up. So, I mean, I really really don't
know what's even worse to be honest.
See, when how hard can it be come on the
door, right? Here's the thing. When this
guy come the door, he was watching uh
West Ham. I think it was a West Ham
supporter. So, he's around the area.
It was one of No, no, no. I think it was
at O2. No, no, sorry. He was watching
some I'm sure it was football he was
watching it basically. He was around my
area. So he thought he'd pop on the door,
right? So everyone is going to know what
this Smokey be really really is about
now, bro. Yeah.
That's madness, bro. And then you're
insulting people's [ __ ] mothers that
you don't even [ __ ] know.
Weirdo, bro. Weirdo. Yeah.
I think Timmy needs to get off this [ __ ]
as well over Christmas to be fair with
you, bro. I generally think he needs to
get off of here.
Uh, we're just chatting.
So, this guy's older than me. Yeah, he's
actually he's going to travel to my door
and beat me up in front of my mom. That
is not happening. So yeah, you can kiss
goodbye to the idea.
Yeah, he's he's he's talking about an incel
and he's the one that's more of an incel than anyone.
Stalking innocent women that you don't
know, asking them about their sex life,
all acts of an incel, bro. Not me. I
ain't an incel.
How can I be an incel if I've had sex
multiple times? That doesn't make sense.
[ __ ] idiot, bro.
But yeah, it is harassment.
You just need to get off this community,
bro. You just need to get off this
community. That's it.
Or like I said, do the videos where you
disable the comments
because it's actually getting creepy
now, bro. It is actually getting creepy.
Greavves doesn't have a mom or dad.
Greavvesy doesn't have a mom or dad. You
don't see him doing this. Could you
imagine you made fun out of Greavvesy's
dead parents? Why would somebody even
Why would someone even make fun out of dead people
when you're not ever? It's just like I
can understand if you're about it, bro.
I can understand if you're about it. Yeah,
but like you're you're you're talking
about dead people and you're not about
that life. We've all seen you multiple
times, but the people in this community
are non-slers, so they will never ever
say anything about it. It's [ __ ] wild, bro. It's wild.
That is crazy, bro. So, the jealousy and
harassment is actually getting worse
now, you know? [ __ ] leave me alone,
you [ __ ] weirdos.
Who do you think gets harassed more, me
or Timmy? I think me. You know, I don't
think it's nowhere.
I think it's I think I get worse than Timmy.
I think I get worse than Timmy to be fair.
That's another one. You're you're try
You're big enough to try to bully a
disabled person, but bro, you're not
going to bully me, bro. You're not going
to come on my door in front of my mom.
That is not happening.
That's another thing. This guy goes for
Timmy as well. You go for a disabled
person, but you ain't going for me, bro. Simple.
This is another thing. I mean, yeah,
there is people that go for Timmy, but I
don't think there's as many people as me.
To be fair,
I don't think so, bro. I think people go
for me more than Timmy,
which is strange because they go for Timmy, right?
But there's an actual nons and no one.
See what I mean? It's weird.
No, I think they go for me. They go for TE.
I think so. Yeah, cuz I have multiple accounts.
Multiple multiple multiple counts. Yeah. Simple.
Someone's going to end up dead by the
end of this year, bro. Oh [ __ ]
It's not even funny. It's mad.
Don't even do a community post. Come
with your boyfriend on Saturday. Don't
even do any response. You're talking
about dead family. You've got a lot of
energy behind the keyboard. So, simple
as that, bro. You know,
stop promoting. Stop [ __ ] stirring, little wanker.
A fresh start after this. Yeah. Done, bro. [ __ ]
Don't even try to call me an insult,
bro. Don't even try to call me an insult.
[ __ ] sad people when lives are over. Yeah,
that's that is it.
This is what I understand.
You're fast enough to talk about
people's L's, but we'll talk about some
of the L's that you took.
What is with these people here, bro?
What is wrong with these people?
Yeah, I'm going to do a video in a bit
anyways, lad. Be back later as well. You
got sleep, man. [ __ ] cowards.
He's a just sad sad sad bastards, bro.
Really really sad people in here.
You got to laugh at these people, bro.
I don't know why they don't stop these
people. Triple H lad.
Would these people ever stop Trip Rates?
It's [ __ ] weird.
No, they haven't affected me at all. I
was affected the past two days because
of women. It weren't these people.
No, definitely definitely not. And this
will be the last I'm saying about it,
bro. They really haven't affected me.
Yeah. No, they definitely definitely
haven't affected me, bro.
It's just a cowardness. But the thing
is, bro, I'm still here. The past few
days was women. It weren't these people, bro.
That's why I was kind of vulnerable cuz
of the women [ __ ] It weren't these people, lad. Yeah.
Anyways, I'm going I'm going to do this
video anyways. Yeah. But
and then yeah, I'll be back whenever,
bro. Probably not today, tomorrow. So, yeah.
All right, see you later. Yeah, we'll do
this video. Peace, bro.
5:00 in the [ __ ] morning, bro. Caught
past 5 in the morning. [ __ ] me, bro.
These people need to stop their [ __ ]