What be live long?
Yeah. What be live long? Oh [ __ ]
Long not long. Oh gosh.
Just wanted to see if it's the same
people on YouTube. You know what I'm
like, mate. You know what I'm [ __ ]
like with this YouTube thing.
Yeah. Jesus. It was very cold this
morning. I went out. Bloody cold. It was
bloody [ __ ] cold.
Cold. Cold. Cold. Cold. Cold. Cold. Yeah.
Reason it was I had to come back and
then [ __ ] make the bed.
Now I'm actually getting sick of the
[ __ ] cold weather now to be honest. Oh [ __ ]
If you quit looking, well, I have quit
looking for like six weeks.
Still nothing to come. So, you know,
someone on Reddit said
if you quit looking
No, I think it's too cold now. December,
October's good. But now I think it is
just too cold.
I prefer um [snorts] yeah
it's too cold now, bro.
Where's Joseph Ferrar?
He's been awfully quiet. That's him.
Don't remind me of me when I used to go
[ __ ] Newcastle and [ __ ]
Been there, done it. Worn the t-shirt. Joseph Fra.
Joseph Ferrar. No. Been there, done it.
Worn the [ __ ] black and [ __ ] white t-shirt, you know.
Yeah, just messing my friend on
Instagram about this uh thing.
Maybe if you quit looking it will come
naturally. It won't come naturally.
>> Not even possible. How could it How
could it come naturally, bro?
How could it [ __ ] come naturally if
you stopped looking? Do you remember saying that?
Uh, you would have thought, well, I I
don't have any money. I'm skinn. I've
got 20 in my name, you know.
I'm Well, I've got 20 in my name. You
know me better than I know myself. So, I mean, yeah.
I would have thought with the amount of
money you people have, you would
actually get a life and not spend eight
years on YouTube self-projecting. But
hey ho, everyone lives their own life, isn't it?
Yeah, everyone lives their own life, lad.
Yeah, I've got 20 to my name, bro. Like
I said, you know me better than myself.
But I will say that you would have
thought with all of the money that you
people have, you wouldn't be sat on
YouTube every day self-reflecting your
life away for eight years minimum. But
you still do it. So yeah, it does it
does really really make you wonder if
you people really have the life and
money you say you have. How you sit on
it hating every day. It does really
really make a wise person wonder, you know.
Anyways, enough of the self-reflection
comments. Bye-bye now. Uh yeah,
got to think of some different things to say 2026,
different words or just the same old
repeating, self- projecting um
speculating people's lives that you don't know.
You going to be the same old in 2026 for
the god knows how many years. Well, I
say eight years. They've been doing it
since 2012, these people. Um, I wasn't
on 2012, but I know this because I've
heard stuff. So, they've been doing this
now basically on here now for
since I was [ __ ] since I was 15.
They've been doing this. Um,
so projecting comments.
Um, so yeah. So since I was 15 back in
the Skype days. So you be the judge what
lives these people really have. [snorts]
you be the judge.
Yeah, they've been doing this on air now
since 2012, bro. Um, these people
um and you would have thought now they
would have actually grown up and
actually got a life. But yeah, you be
the judge of what life they've got if
they're sat here doing this for years
and years and years on end. [snorts]
You you be the judge, bro, what life
they've got. since they don't like to be. Uh
so the Smokeoky Be didn't turn up today
and he got a free pass.
No one said anything about it.
Can't believe these people. Yeah. And no
one said anything about it.
And no one says anything. That's what I
told you, bro. They're biased on here.
They're not worth anyone's time. Look,
you've seen it once again. The little
[ __ ] out said he was going to come on
someone's door. He didn't. And no one
said anything about it. That's what I'm
saying. They're not worth anyone's time
getting into arguments with. They're
just fat, ugly, sad people. And even
when they and even when they get and
they take L's, uh, no one says anything about it.
This is exactly why people don't show
these people money. This is exactly why
people don't don't prove these fat,
ugly, biased people anything. You don't
need to prove yourself to any of these
fat, ugly self-reflectors. You know what
I'm saying, bro? I don't need to go out
drinking every week to prove that I can
go out drinking every week. I don't need
to show money for the millionth time. I
don't need to do any of that stuff
[snorts] to prove irrelevant biased people
wrong for the millionth time.
But yeah, he ran away and no one said
anything about it. So you be the judge.
They're all biased on it, bro. This is
what I'm saying. They're all They're all
biased. Like I said, if you're like I've
said for the millionth time, bro, if
you're not fat and ugly like them, they
don't like you. They don't like anyone
that ain't the same as them.
That's why they all get on so well
because they're all fat, ugly, and
hopeless. So that's why they they they
get on with each other so well.
And anyone that's younger than them and
you know is not disabled and better
looking, how to explain it, they have
problems with. This is what I'm trying
to say. This is what they're like on
here, bro. You know it. I [ __ ] know
it. And that's that.
You know, they are literally biased.
That's another example along with the
virgin thing. You prove you had sex,
they still call you a virgin. They're a
waste of time. They're a waste of
everyone's time on it, bro.
These little melts, they ain't got
nothing in life, bro. So that's that.
Yeah, they're all the same, bro. And
bomb. They're all the same. That's why
they they get on with each other so
well, cuz they're all fat, ugly, and hopeless.
what I'm saying, bro. That's that's that
is literally literally that.
They don't like anyone that's younger
and better looking than them and got a
better life than them. And let me tell
you what I mean by a better life. I
could go out drinking today if I wanted
to. I can do what I want today if I
wanted to, but I don't want to cuz I'd
rather save money because I'd rather
just stack money, no matter what money I
was getting. So, at the end of the day,
it's like they hate anyone that
It's hard to explain it, bro. You
wouldn't understand it. It's hard to
explain. But yeah, that's that.
That is that.
They're just sad people, bro. That's
what they are, is it? Oh, yeah.
Yeah, they all the same.
I went to get some breakfast earlier,
bro. It was [ __ ] cold outside.
Yeah. Oh, my tea's still here. Lovely.
This is why they do this, lad.
No one said anything about that [ __ ] not
turning up today. [sighs and gasps]
They're biased. They're waste of everyone's time.
They've all [clears throat] got their
own agenda. They're all [ __ ] idiots. Idiots. [snorts]
It's a good [clears throat] thing me not
going out today. Did anyone bet on the football?
[ __ ] that. I'm not getting [ __ ]
I ain't getting more mood swings, bro.
You're [ __ ] mad, lad. [ __ ] that. [clears throat]
I still ain't signed up to this porn
thing yet. I still need to do it. I
still ain't done it, bro. [snorts]
I will do. Don't worry. Oh [ __ ]
>> [clears throat]
>> This guy needs to stop blocking me and
unblocking me as well.
I bet some of them pubs are busy today.
Bet they're busy today.
But we don't want any more bad experiences.
This is the problem, lad.
We don't want any more bad experiences,
bro. So, just chill.
Here we go.
I need to put these bad experiences in
my folder, bro. Like, I put, you know,
nonsleg harassment on the folder. I need
to put this on a folder so I can just show people,
you know what I mean?
I can just show people
the [ __ ] I've been dealing with for many
years. But these are [ __ ] women.
I can't get out of my head. That is so funny, bro.
I'll be like making a tea and it will
pop into my head. >> [snorts]
>> [ __ ] copy copycat.
Where is this one with this [ __ ] [ __ ] here?
One second, please. Brother, I need to
Yeah, I need to put these bad
experiences in a folder.
Bad experiences with women. That's what
I put it as bad experiences with women.
>> [snorts and clears throat]
>> So yeah,
but yeah. Anyways, no one said anything
to this [ __ ] for not showing up.
Says everything and it tells you all you
need to know on here.
It tells you that you'll never ever win
with these people.
There we go.
Yeah. No one's gave him [ __ ] for not
showing up UK signing but you.
Yeah, no one gave him [ __ ] but you. Mad.
Like I said, that tells you that you'll
never you'll never win on here with
these jealous people. You'll never ever
win on here with these jealous greeneyed monsters.
Oh, bro, my [ __ ] arms hurting me, man.
Yeah, it just shows you you'll never win with these people. legit. Never.
I just put my
>> Yeah, you'll never win with these
jealous people in this community, you know. No,
never, bro. Never. No. Oh,
I'm a little copycat.
>> Brush my teeth.
>> I'm a little copycat.
>> Yeah, I know. They're buy It's like
that. It's like the Joseph Ferrar uh nonslover.
The bias nonslover. He's talking about
people not being able to take anyone's
words serious. But yet, I've turned up
to more people than anyone on here. and
his little boyfriend didn't show up
today. The little nonslover. Joseph
Fraud, the little nonslover.
Like, if I didn't know these people were
biased. Yeah. Listen, if I didn't know
what these people are about, I'd go to
Newcastle today and call the [ __ ] out.
Not now, but I would have went earlier.
I swear to God, if back a few years ago,
bro, if I didn't know what these people
are like, take L's, pretend it never
happened, bias, don't stop and [ __ ] I I
would have went there today and called them out.
That's what I used to do, bro. A few
years ago, then I realized that they
were all biased.
Then I gave up. Yeah. Yeah. They're all
little nons lovers. [snorts]
They're all little nons lovers. That's
what I'm saying. I would have [ __ ]
went there today and said, "Listen, meet
me. I'll laugh in your [ __ ] face. I
will laugh in your face and you'll do nothing."
If I didn't know they were [ __ ]
biased, bro. Like, but I know what these
people are like. They proving themselves once again.
You know, that's how you know you'll
never win with them on air, bro. You'll
never win with these people. Ever.
Never. Ever. Ever. Ever. Ever.
You'll never win these jealous people
and they last. Yeah.
Never ever ever ever ever ever
about we just laugh. You laugh at
yourselves, you [ __ ] spastics. And
I'm talking about them people. You laugh
at your [ __ ] spasticated selves.
Taking people's words seriously, bro.
You said that you was going to come out
today. You didn't come out.
I was waiting here all day.
You know, another little [ __ ] little
you know, and I'm not wasting time. I'm
not wasting money on these people
anymore to go and to go meet them cuz we
all know what they do. We literally all
know what these people do. It was the
same with the bomb. It was the same
move. I mean,
they should have people saying to Smokey
B that he's a [ __ ] house.
You know, there should be people saying,
"Oh, you're a [ __ ] house. You're a [ __ ]
house. You're a [ __ ] house." But no one
said anything about you. So,
yeah. Literally, bro. Yeah. Literally.
[ __ ] Joseph Far. He's a little nons
lover. He sucks dick every day. And I'll
say it to his face. And I'll say it to
his face as well if he ever wants to
meet me. I will say it to his face. And
he was saying about how, oh yeah, sod
London, Newcastle. I'm thinking, bro,
the only reason you're going to
Newcastle is because you can't afford um
so you can't afford and you don't have
the balls to come to London. You can't
travel outside your zone. You know,
you're you're a disabled man. And so
that's the only reason why you you're
going to Newcastle cuz you live in
between. You would never ever travel
more than 100 miles by yourself cuz you
know cuz you know you're a little [ __ ]
bro. You know. Yeah.
Yeah. Because they're biased. They're
little dick sucker. They're [ __ ]
They do they do the same with nonslegs,
bro. They they Yeah.
Yeah. They've been doing it for years.
They're biased. They're [ __ ] biased.
For [ __ ] sake, bro. I've, like I said,
I've proved I've had sex. People still
call me a virgin.
They still call me a virgin even though
I've proved I've had [ __ ] sex for
crying out [ __ ] loud. So,
that's that, bro. Yeah,
they're idiots. They're [ __ ] idiots.
Yeah, that Joseph Fro is another big
idiot. Fat slob.
Fat slob. You don't know what money
people have. You don't know people's
life. You don't know nothing. You don't
know [ __ ] nothing.
It's true though. UK side, they don't
know anyone's lives but their own. Am I though? You know.
Trust me. I've done more in my 28 years
than you've done in your 38 [ __ ]
years. Yeah. You silly pathetic little [ __ ]
[ __ ] little bias nons lover.
Be honest, bro. You shouldn't waste your
time on people that hasn't even spoke on
a panel. Smoking be spoke on a panel
before. That's why I thought I'd give
him some I'd give him some air time. But
he's proved that he's another [ __ ]
house. I had faith, you know. I did have
a I thought, you know, maybe maybe. But
they're all just [ __ ] houses on there.
That's what they are. They're just [ __ ] house people.
Yeah. No life.
Take the boredom over the bad experiences.
Uh be nice to go out, but I don't want
any more bad experiences, bro.
But I don't think it's a good idea.
No more bad experiences or women like that.
Not until New Year's Eve. Yep.
Just a bit like nons legs, isn't it?
With the shovel cole thing. Wanting to show off.
[ __ ] wanting to show off.
Don't find her attractive. You're gay.
Yeah. You just want to show off.
Showing off to the crowd.
Yeah, I was going to go out and cause
some madness greedy, but I'd rather stay
in. I don't want any more bad experiences.
What's the time? 6:33.
I could head to the local boozer,
you know. But nah,
I don't want any more bad experiences,
bro. [ __ ] that.
Going to have to sit here bored talking
to you [ __ ]
But it's better than having bad
experiences. Sure. It's better than
having bad experiences.
Yep. No one's called uh No one's called
Smoky B out for being a [ __ ] house, but
one person, Grezy.
So now, do you know why people don't
waste their time on these people? Huh? Mhm.
What do you mean that's not bad?
Well, it is bad because the [ __ ] didn't
show up and no one said anything about
it but one person. So, how is that not bad?
What? What do you mean it's not bad?
Well, it is bad because the [ __ ] said
that he was going to come on the door
and he never
and no one's saying anything about it.
So, we're reliving with we're reliving
these biased people again. What do you
mean it's not bad?
How is it not bad, bro? They're [ __ ]
proved to be biased again. No,
like I said, I'd be in Newcastle tonight
if I know if I knew these people. If I
didn't know these people are biased,
Greasy, I would be in Newcastle tonight
calling that Joseph Ferrar out calling
them a dirty pig fat non-sloving [ __ ]
that would do nothing.
You know, in real life, I'd go live and
and and say it, bro. But I'm not going
to because we know what they're like. We
know what these [ __ ] are like.
Trust me, we know that like they proved it again.
But that'd be lovely content for you,
wouldn't it, Grezy?
Yeah. In Newcastle calling that fat [ __ ]
out. You love it, would you, Grezy? Yeah.
Cuz I hate a lot of these people on it,
bro. Not everyone, but I hate a lot of
these people on it. So, back before I
back before Yeah. I knew they were
biased. I was like, "Oh, [ __ ] We'll
just travel here, travel there, cuz
we're going to get some credit." It it
used to be it used to be a buzz, you
know, but then when you realize everyone
on here is biased, then there's no
point. It takes the fun out of it, Reezy.
You know, it's like winning a match and
the crowd's not cheering. It just takes
the fun out of it. It takes the
adrenaline when they all buy little fat
nons. You know what I'm saying? So,
yeah. You understand?
It takes the fun out of it, you know?
Yeah. It takes the fun out of it, I think,
because the good thing about the victory
is seeing people go at these people,
Greavvesy. Oh, you didn't show up, you
[ __ ] house. You could sit back. You've
done your deed, Greavvesy. You've done
your deed and you can sit back for a
couple of days with a cup of [ __ ] and
see them get [ __ ] roasted for not
showing up. But if that's not going to
happen, then there's literally no point
in anyone wasting any time, any money, any anything. You know,
talking about me not going to America.
This [ __ ] [ __ ] ain't gone on my door
today. Yeah, he said he was supposed to.
He said he was coming
and then he never even went to London
and went live. But this [ __ ] gets a free
pass cuz they're all fat nons lovers.
This is what I'm saying. That's why they
like nunchers is cuz they're non legs
cuz they're nons themselves. Greavesy. Grievy. You know,
I'm not [ __ ] lying, am I, bro? [sighs] Gosh.
I could easily go out today and drink,
but I'm not doing that, bro. I want to
have a nice summer's holiday in July. So,
well, it's not even about the money. I
just can't be bothered. Literally cannot
I can't be [ __ ] I'm not going to be
short of money. I'm not going to run out
of money. I just can't be bothered. Greensby.
There's some all right people on it. You
know, Triple H is just a laugh. Steven
Howard. Steven Howard's a brother, you
know, man. He actually People can say
that he's trolling me. Yeah. He He can
say that he's trolling me. Yeah. But
brother, he's not. Cuz I've seen him
back me up on Timmy's. I've actually
seen the guy back me up on Timmy's live
stream. So, no one can even try and tell
me that he's trolling me.
You know, Grey might be trolling me. Oh,
well, it's just a bit of uh it's just a
bit of a laugh. Okay, whatever. I don't
mind a bit of a laugh, but I don't like
most of these people on here, bro. You
know, I don't like most of these people on here,
you know, the [ __ ] that they do is not
just YouTube, bro. It isn't just
YouTube. And that Steven Howard has
backed me up, bro. He has. So, how can
anyone say that they're trolling you
when the person has blatantly backed you up?
Yeah, but it's only harmless. Yeah, but
it's just a wind up. Yeah, but it's just
a windup, bro. I don't mind it. Yeah,
but you do it as a windup. I don't mind.
Yeah, I don't mind the wind up, bro. But
these people Yeah. on here, you know,
you know, we we've let someone we've let
we've let someone on here. Uh, [ __ ] off,
right, [ __ ] Uh, we let someone on here
uh the other day and they're talking
about dead relatives. Grezy, they're
talking about dead relatives. You're
thinking, "What the [ __ ] am I listening
to?" This clown is never ever going to
meet anyone. You got someone [ __ ]
saying that they're going to come on
your door. They don't come on your
[ __ ] door, you know? Really, man?
Yeah. I like some of the sayings.
They're funny, Grezy.
You know, like latching on to new
boobies and stuff. No, but these people
take it too far on here, bro. They take
it too far.
And like I said, they're all biased.
You could literally go to Belfast
tomorrow, right, and own that law J and
everyone would just pretend it never happened.
They used to do the same thing with
London Taylor as well. They've done it
to with both of us.
But yeah, that [ __ ] um
So you're not drink
What do you mean you're going Oh, you're
going turkey. Why are you going Turkey
in January? What the [ __ ]
So I'm just catching up with this [ __ ]
What? How you go? How you going Turkey?
How much did that cost? It must have
been cheap, is it?
Yeah, Dusty. Well, the [ __ ] never showed
up and no one said anything about it.
So, that tells you all you need to know
about this community.
Yeah, but why are you going in January?
It's going to be cold. No.
So, what? You're not drinking until
then? You're not
You're not going out until then? I could
easily go out right now if I wanted to.
I can't be asked.
I think we'll have an early night. I that's that. Yeah.
I was going to do a mad video greaves.
Yeah. So, the only two places I've not
been to in England is well in the UK is
one of the main places like Glasgow and
Blackpool. So, I was going to go to a
train station and flip a coin and say
either I go to Blackpool, I go to
Glasgow and see my dada
or I go and see my dada.
And whatever it went on, I would just go
like 7 8:00 in the morning and just wake
up and just [ __ ] do some content, bro. It
see my da
I think it be a laugh to be honest.
Can't deprive you of [ __ ] content.
[ __ ] poor [ __ ] You've been on this
channel now for a very long time.
But then I could be going on a train for
like 5 hours.
So, but I don't know. It's just
something to do, you know.
But Blackpool's probably well probably
[ __ ] in it
this time of year. We
What do you think of a video idea like
that? I was just thinking of things that could do,
you know. What do you think of that?
Do you like the idea of that?
C. Obviously, I have to run it by you first, Captain.
Oh, I was watching Jack Frost. It's a
lovely movie. Lovely movie. Grezy.
Yeah, I've never been, bro. I've never been.
I've been most places. I've just never
been there. Or Glasgow. I haven't been
Southampton either, but I mean they're
like just ones, you know.
I was going to go when I was in
Manchester, but the there was a train strike,
so I just stayed in Manchester um and
then went back to London the next day
cuz I was so tired.
Yeah, I was supposed to, but I just
never did. Never never never ended up happening. So, yeah.
So, what would you prefer? Glasgow or
Blackpool BG? So, what would you prefer?
You know, it either be one of them.
I don't know, man. I'd say [ __ ]
Glasgow, bro. It was like 7:00 in the
morning and we flipped the coin. I would
say definitely Glasgow, man. Cuz I get
to see Tam, my dada.
I'm used to long journeys, but I've been
traveling for years.
I've been traveling for years, bro. So,
doesn't bother me. Yeah.
Could find my dada. Grimly,
what do you think about that? Find the
dada. I used to go to a different city
every week, bro.
[ __ ] every week. Oh, [ __ ] [clears throat]
Look, I've had a nice little shower. I'm all freshy.
My fresh little clothes.
I had some piggies for breakfast.
My hair's growing back fast already,
bro. What the [ __ ] man?
Look, hair grows back so quickly. Sorry.
A lovely little film, Jack Frost.
A lovely little film, Grezy. Lovely,
lovely little film.
Have you ever watched it? It's basically
where the kid's dad dies and it comes
back as a [ __ ] snowman. Quite good to me. Oh.
This bed is lovely, man.
You should watch it. It's quite cute, we
quite cute. Me and Laney went for
breakfast early early out early in the
morning. 5:00 in the morning, 6:00 in the morning.
Yeah, we went to get some piggies.
So, I've had piggies twice today.
I've had piggies twice today. Yeah,
I should be wearing my little Grinch
socks, but they never gave me them.
I could go out now and get the Grinch
socks for McDonald's and then go out approaching.
[ __ ] that, bro. [ __ ] that.
Not worth it.
What do you think, Grez? Do you reckon
if I go out approaching today, I'll get a date? No.
Nah, I was thinking about that today,
but there's no point.
What's the point? You're not going to
get a date. You're not going to get
laid. So what's the point?
Yeah. Waxies. Yeah.
There's literally no point. All you're
going to do is just get more bad
experiences, bro. I go out New Year's Eve, but
that's basically it. I'm basically just done, bro.
I'd rather just live a boring life and
just save money.
done all my going out [ __ ] bro.
I just can't be bothered with it.
Honestly, can't be bothered with it.
I don't want any more mood swings. I
don't want any more bad experiences.
At least [ __ ] New Year's Eve. You
could justify it, bro. It's like a
special event, you know? It's like um a
special occasion. New Year's Eve is a
special occasion. At least you can kind
of justify going out. You can't just I
can't justify it, bro.
>> Just send me £1,000.
Send me £1,000.
Sorry, my phone just dropped. Yeah, send
me £1,000 right now. I still didn't go out.
I'm happy in my little nestles, Grezy. Oh gosh. Yeah,
Christmas session. Yeah, it's busy this
time of year, isn't it? It's busy.
I tell you when it will be really busy.
[ __ ] next week. That's when it will
be really That is when it will be packed.
It will be packed. Next week, which will be the 20th
That's when it will be chocker block.
Greavvesy. That That is when it will be
chocker. [ __ ] chocker.
Hello, Grezy. It will be chocker block.
Well, now it will still be busy, but it
will be really, really busy next week. [ __ ] rammed.
And you don't even need to go to waxies.
There's a place up the road in Rockford.
It's It's good enough. It gets busy and stuff, but
Roxy's obviously more busy cuz it's central.
What do you think, Grey? Go out. Stay in.
Staying definitely in it.
At least Franklin can't tell me he's got
a boyfriend. At least Franklin can't
give me bad experiences. No.
go out tomorrow. Why am I going to go
out drinking tomorrow?
What drinking? Why am I going to go out drinking tomorrow?
Why am I going to do that?
Well, I'm not doing anything tomorrow.
What am I?
Yeah, but why am I going to go out drinking tomorrow?
That doesn't make sense.
If one per if one other person tells me
they've got a boyfriend, I'm going to
end up on the [ __ ] watch list, bro.
I don't think I should go out. No,
to be honest. No,
I might go McDonald's. I don't I can't
be bothered, but I just rather save to
be honest. Honestly, I would just rather save.
If I'm completely honest with you, bro,
I'd rather just save and just Yeah, just
chill for a bit, bro.
Even if it's just for a couple weeks.
I bet is I bet is busy today, waxies.
And it's not even like I can't go. It's
not even money. It's just I just don't
want any more bad experiences.
Yeah, it is rammed. I know it will be
rammed. How busy do you reckon it will
be next Saturday, Grezy?
[ __ ] very [ __ ] busy. Very rammed.
It probably rammed even from Thursday to be fair.
Why? Because I said I'll end up on the
watch list. Grezy,
that's not then. [clears throat]
How do you know what I meant by that?
I'll end up on the watch list, bro.
Just the truth. I could go to Waxies
today, then go to the Swan in it, Dusty.
That will be busy, bro. That will be packed.
That will be [ __ ] rammed out, bro. Rammed out.
Really, bro? Really? Really? Yeah.
Waxi is going to be so busy you won't be
able to move.
And doesn't like it this time of year.
He says you can't even move. You can't
you can barely get to the bar.
You're hopeless, right? So, why do you
want to keep putting your hand on the
stove? It doesn't make any sense. Why
Why do you want to keep Have you ever
heard that saying, Grezy? Why are you
going to keep putting your hand on a hot stove?
You know, you know there's no one for
you. So, why why do you want to Why are
you going to put your hand on a [ __ ]
hot stove? It doesn't make no sense. Wait,
I see it. Bro,
what happens every time you put your
hand on a hot stove? You get burnt. So,
just think of it that way.
Get yourself to waxes, lad.
I love that saying, Dusty. I love that
saying. Put the stony on and get
yourself to waxes.
Get yourself to waxies, lad. Yeah.
Yeah, you will get burnt. [snorts]
Why do you want more bad experiences? It
doesn't make sense, bro. I got some
popcorn, so I might just watch a movie.
Someone on Reddit said that if I stop
looking for it, I'll find it. Rusty, if
I stop looking for it, I'll find it. Yeah. Oh
yourself down to waxes. Dusty, have you
ever been to waxies? That's why I met Finnish Izzy.
I met quite a few people in waxis. Finn
Izzy, someone that sent me nudes and Yeah.
Yeah. You know, bro
is bro. I went out last December.
So what? You reckon I'll meet someone if
I go out today? Dusty Greasy?
They're everywhere, mate. Simmons
[ __ ] They're everywhere. [ __ ]
Yeah, they're [ __ ] everywhere, bro. be fair.
What makes you say that, Grezy?
I could just go out and sit to Guinness, but
I'm not doing that, bro. It's pointless.
It is just pointless. You haven't had a
date since April.
You're hopeless. Simple as that. So yeah,
Peter belly above shagging and Laney
watching Cory downstairs. Grezy, that
made me laugh. Laney sat in the living
room watching Cory whilst Peter Belly shagging.
Yeah, you you you can come here, Grezy.
You're more than welcome.
Yeah, you're more than welcome. [snorts]
me lady. You lady king. You lane me.
you, Laney King.
[snorts] You know,
I might get some I might have some
digestive biscuits in a bit.
Some digestive biscuits. I like them. Yep.
Yeah, I might get some digest digestive
biscuits in a minute.
We got some left.
Nope, he didn't turn up, but no one said
anything about it. Yeah.
Is that okay with you, Grezy? Um, digestive biscuits
and [snorts] no one said anything about it
but you. And yeah, Greavvesy, you're
supposed to do the Meow thing.
Every time I do something that copies,
you have to do the Meow thing. Just like
if anytime nons legs comes on, you have
to do me out cuz the shovel cole thing. Yeah,
I agree with you. I was looking up
Shervel Cole yesterday and I think she's quite attractive.
I think she's attractive. Greasy. Yeah, [clears throat]
little copycat one. Bless you,
Greavvesy. You got bipolar.
I do feel bad for you, Greavves, though,
that you're not going to be with anyone
this Christmas. Bless you.
You're more than welcome to join the Laney household. Bless you.
Bless you, Gy. Yeah,
I got my pecker out yesterday, Grezy. Didn't I?
I got my pecker out.
I got my picker out. That was fun, isn't it? [snorts] Oh, [ __ ]
Laney told me I'd meet someone. That
troll account said Grezy.
Laney said that account must be busy or
something, is it? cuz it's not been on
for a while, has it, Grezy? Yeah, they
must be busy.
Yeah, they must be busy, bro.
Yeah. They must be busy over Christmas.
You know exactly who it is, isn't it?
When they come on, Greasy. Like, you
know, like even if they go behind a
different account, we know it's their
minute, Grezy. We know it's them 100%.
I know straight away.
I just I just want to know who it is. I
just want to know who it is, bro.
won't be on long
be on Oh,
won't be on long.
No, not long. Grezy.
No, no, no, no, no.
Although that is being a bit of a
copycat. Meow. You big stinking copycat.
I agree. You big stinking copycat.
Big stinking copycat.
That was funny.
You big stinky copycat.
That has been a little bit of a copycat, but gre
This woman said to me, "Greasy, tell me
if you agree with this or not." They
said, "You wouldn't have to try as hard
for someone who was meant for you. I
would just I would just let it be and
let it naturally come. You're you're still young."
I don't agree with that because I'm 28
and I've been trying for years.
Do you agree with that, Grezy?
Cuz they told me I was young like 10
years ago as well and I'm getting older now
and no one approaches me. No.
I don't know. What do you think? And do
you think it will come naturally if you give up? No.
What do you think? She said,
she said, "You wouldn't have to try so
hard for someone who was meant for you.
I would just let it naturally come and
that I'm still young."
But I heard that years ago,
like when I was 15, um, Greg and nothing's happened.
Even when I gave up for like six weeks,
seven weeks, nothing happens.
What's your opinion on that, Grezy?
I'm not so sure. What?
So why do you So you're trying to tell
me I'm not going to meet anyone then if
I give up?
Yeah, but people say it comes naturally.
Should I just give up for like 3 years
and see what happens?
Where is he?
I'll be waiting. Yeah,
I'll wait. You wait? Yes. Until I meet someone.
It will never happen. It will never Because
because think of all of the people I've
met that was from being a tryhard
USA is he that was all from approaching
and no no no no but the thing is it's
not even just that grievy it's the fact
that you actually have to approach. So
you have to like you're not going to go
somewhere and someone's going to talk to
you. You're going to have to approach.
That's the thing. Like you literally
have to. If you don't then, yeah, you
could I could go right now. I could be
in a social setting and no one's going
to talk to me. You'd be very very lucky
if someone comes and speaks to you,
but you you'd you'd need to actually
approach you would you would actually
need to start something.
You know what I'm trying to say? So, I
don't understand how they can sit there
and say that, you know, it will come
when that's ridiculous.
Maybe they mean like cuz even when you
go on Instagram and you and you and you
message people, they're still the same. So yeah.
Have you been waiting long? No, not
long. Just 17 years or so.
That's what I'd be saying. Grezy, have
you been waiting long?
No, not long. Just 17 years or so.
Right on Greasy. Yeah,
just 17 years or so,
which is the truth, isn't it?
Not a [ __ ] week. I'll wait.
I might just go out today and have a
drink and just wait until someone
approaches me. Grezy, you like the lush
content, don't you?
Yeah, you like the lush content.
Do you remember glue your dick to a woman's mouthy? Yeah.
Glue glue your dick to a woman's mouth.
Is that cute, Grezy?
Yeah, that would be lovely, Grezy.
That be lovely, mate.
I could have went out today, but we we
done the heads and tails, didn't we,
Grezy? We done the heads and tails [snorts] and Yeah.
What do you reckon will be better?
Drinking today or New Year's Eve? [snorts]
I don't know what I'm going out. What
point I'm trying to prove by going out?
I don't know what what you're trying to prove.
You're not ever going to meet anyone.
So, what are you trying to prove by going out?
I should have a [ __ ] date this week. Yep.
What do you think, Greavves? Do you
reckon if all women were flatchested,
you would ever want to be with a woman?
Me? I don't think so. No.
I like vitamins. I need the vitamins and stuff.
What do you think, Reezy?
But these women are racist.
I think a lot of the reason people don't
get with me is like I was saying greasy
is because I don't look fully white.
What do you mean?
I mean, yeah, but if you want to save
money, that's what you got to do, bro.
You got to make you got to you got to sacrifice [ __ ]
Because think about it, right? I can go
out this week, I go out next week, I go
the week after that
and then come next month and have money,
I'd still be able to go out and stuff.
But if I save money now, I get the
freedom of wanting to leave if I want to
leave. I get more freedom to do what I
want when I want and eventually you will
have to leave this country. So, you
know, it's like, well, unless you can
join the porn industry. I mean, you will
eventually have to leave. So,
it just makes more sense just stacking
the money up to be honest.
I'd stack the money up. Even if I was
getting four grand a month, doesn't
matter how much I was getting, I'd still
be doing it. So,
it's more of a do you want to go out? Do
you want to get more bad experiences?
It's not worth it. That kind of thing.
That's what it is.
You wouldn't understand Grezy. You
wouldn't understand that. Yeah.
Yeah. New Year's Eve is going to be chucka.
[ __ ] cha block. It's going to be
chucka [ __ ] block.
What are you doing? New Year's Eve,
Greavves, are you just staying in? Bless you.
It's okay. I'll just wait.
You wait. Yes. Until it's been made. [snorts]
[ __ ] madness, isn't it? Bless you then.
So, what do you reckon would happen if I
go out approaching today, Grezy?
I'll get numbers and stuff, won't I?
I'm okay. I'm just lying in bed.
I was going to go out. Um, but I don't
want any more bad experiences with
women, so I've decided against it. >> Yeah.
Oh, my [ __ ] back is [ __ ] Greasy. Uh, [snorts]
what are you up to, Captain?
[snorts] What are you up to, Captain [ __ ] Captain C.
Where's Steven? He's late for the show tonight.
God bless you then.
I was going to go out today, but I don't
want any more bad experiences with women, gentlemen.
So, I'm going to find a movie to watch.
No, I'm not drinking, bro.
I was going to go to a pub, but yeah, it's pointless.
I don't stay at home and drink. Yeah.
Why don't you have a drink, Grezy? Bless you.
God bless you. I like several cars.
I find her attractive. Meow meow meow [screaming]
boozy. If you don't find chevel co
attractive, you're gay.
If you don't find chevel co attractive,
you're gay, lad.
You're [ __ ] gay.
When's when's the next copycat statement
going to be made?
Are you still waiting for the next copycat statement? [laughter]
[ __ ] I hate cats. I do. They just copy people. Yeah. [screaming]
Is your name greasy?
Looks like a virgin [ __ ]
Looks like a [ __ ] [laughter] You [ __ ]
you absolute virgin.
Someone was like, "Oh, I should I should
approach I should approach Grezy because
it's Christmas and there's more
tourists." I said, "Nah,
I should have to approach. I should have
already found someone." Am I right?
Am I right, Dreams? I should have
already found someone in it. Huh?
No, I shouldn't have to go out and
approach. I should have already found
someone. What's your opinion on that, Graves?
I think I'm being realistic there.
This is all about
Yeah. [clears throat]
This is called
breaking a cycle.
You know what I'm saying? This is what
you call breaking the cycle. It might
seem very hard at first, but the thing
is with a cycle, it's very easy to keep
doing the same thing and the same thing
and the same thing with gambling. You
know what I mean?
How are you going to break the cycle?
You're going to try and join the pool
industry. If you can't join the pool
industry, you're going to have to leave the country.
You know, it's not easy for a reason.
It's not easy to break a cycle for that reason
because once you break the cycle, your life changes.
You go out today, you're just going to
keep going backwards and backwards and
backwards and backwards and back.
Right or wrong, we
saying right or wrong.
I can do I can do the Franks.
I can do the prank. [laughter] [ __ ]
walks. That's the Franklin walk.
I'm very good at it. Yeah.
Go to waxes. [laughter]
Go to waxies.
Oh, go to waxies.
>> [clears throat]
>> Oh, that's got ring to it.
Why do you want me to bring the virgin
[ __ ] Dusty, [ __ ] that. No virgins allowed.
That's the policy in that place. No virgins.
No skinned virgins.
But yeah, if uh it is all about breaking
the cycle, bro. It's all about, like I
said, I'll go out New Year's Eve. I will >> [laughter]
>> I love that. I love that. You know, you
know when Waxies is good. It's good on a Sunday.
It's good on a It's good on a Sunday.
Yeah, waxies is good on a Sunday, Dusty. Oh, [ __ ]
No, waxies is good on a Sunday.
You get loads of Irish women there, but
no one's interested. So, no one's
interested. They're just not interested
in this country, dusty.
I'm definitely signing up to this porn
thing. Definitely, bro. [laughter]
This ain't no life, is it?
No, I was comp I was contemplating.
Can't even say they were contemplating going out.
Um, but then I thought there was no point.
You're not on the drink today, are you, Triple? Look, look, Dusty. Look, Dusty. One sec. Look, Dusty,
I got the stony.
I could put the stony on the money jeans
and get to waxies, lad.
[ __ ] that. I ain't going to waxes.
I'm saving my money.
What I'm doing is I'm saving my money
till New Year's Eve.
I'll go out New Year's Eve. I'm going
out New Year's Eve. I will be going out
New Year's Eve. I'll go out New Year's
Hopefully, I'll hit by the pawn ping by then.
And that's it. Like I said, it's all
about breaking the cycle. Breaking a
cycle is is not easy for a reason cuz
it's so easy to keep doing the same
thing. And this shouldn't still be
happening at 28 years of age,
you know? Yeah. I'm not drinking Boxing
Day. I'll be drinking New Year's Eve.
I tell you the best. I tell you the best
month. Yeah. If you really want to try
to date. Yeah. Is probably March, April.
There's a few bank holidays there as
well. That's that's the best time.
Yeah. New Year's Eve. I'll go all out
New Year's Eve. Then I'll be done until midFeb.
I should have something booked by then
as well. So yeah.
You used to go out drinking a lot,
didn't you, Triple?
Yeah, I'm going to try I'm going to go
McDonald's tomorrow and try to get the
[ __ ] Grin socks.
Yeah, I'm going to get the grid socks.
I remember the last time I went to
Waxies on a Sunday, Dusty. I spent so
much money. Got a roast in her. That's
when I met that finished Izzy. Yeah. And
I was kind of low on money. Lucky I won
the football bet, bro. Otherwise, I
would have been I wouldn't have been
[ __ ] but I just would have had like
£700 left. Wouldn't have been [ __ ]
Still money in it. But you get what I'm
saying, bro. [ __ ]
It's expensive. I bought
dinner round the [ __ ] drinks.
[ __ ] almost 50 pound, bro.
And yeah, it is always the same. It is
always the same thing. So, yeah, that's that. It
only bad thing about New Year's Eve is
the drink prices go up.
That's the only thing I don't like is
the drink prices go up. Yeah,
that happens. Dusty. I've been to
O'Neal's New Year's Eve.
Yeah, a couple times. Where did I go
last New Year's Eve?
What did I do last New Year's Eve? I
think I might have stayed in.
It's not remember you. I don't understand. Oh, yeah.
Pretty much. Yeah.
Yep. Plenty of people that aren't
interested as well, Dusty.
I know only too well, lad.
Plenty of people that aren't interested.
Plenty of bad experiences to be had. No
thanks. I think the nesticles is a way
better option. Rezy.
Yeah, I think the nesticles is way better. Yeah.
>> [clears throat]
>> But that but at the same time I'm
depriving Greavves of [ __ ] content.
Poor [ __ ] You know what [ __ ] [snorts]
If I go out today,
if I go out today,
this account is going to come back by
Monday. Greavves. I'm telling you,
there's no way to change Peter Belly's
[ __ ] [ __ ] show. I know it, bro. If I
go out today, the count's going to come
back in it.
Yeah. You know all about Rockford, don't
you, Dusty? I went to this place called
Slug and Lettuce.
That's why I done the approaches in Slug
and Lettuce in uh Rockford. Quite It's
all right to be fair.
Still not as busy as Waxies, though. or
not, you know, but it's still pretty
decent with doing this local.
I'm telling you, the account will come back.
100% the account will come back.
Do believe me, [snorts]
they will 100% come back.
by the Monday is it?
Yeah. I got one number in Romford. She
was from South End. I messaged her and I
reply. Message her again. She weren't very enthusiastic.
She lives in South End.
I tell you, it would be good today.
[ __ ] Simmons. Simmons would be so
good today, bro.
Simmons would be good.
The good thing about Waxies is it's more
like um an older crowd, like people my
age. The music isn't as good as Simmons,
but the the age group
is what I like. Like that that Finnish
stupid [ __ ] woman was the same age as
me. I think I'm two months older. And
other people, they're roughly around the
same age or a bit older. That's the good
thing about Waxies. That's what I like
It's more of an older
crowd. Does that make sense?
Um, which I've noticed that with all the
people I've met there, which which is
what I like. But you go like somewhere
like Simmons, they're all a lot younger.
You know, obviously you do get people
that are a bit older, but yeah. I don't
know. I just noticed that with waxes. Yep.
Yeah. I like waxies, bro. It's easy to
get into as well. And they're not all
[ __ ] there like O'Neal's
O'Neal's. They go a bit OTT scanning IDs and
they go a bit OTT.
O'Neal's will be packed today. O'Neal is
my favorite place, but I used to love that O'Neals. Oh, mate.
Good times going to that O'Neals boy.
That [ __ ] O'Neals.
Loads of dates to be had there. Still single.
What's your favorite place in central Dusty?
Yeah, waxies. They don't scan IDs. That is strange.
Yeah, that is strange. Some of them don't. Yeah, is good.
I think the rules are stupid though.
They they don't let you in if you're by
yourself. I think that is I think that is discrimination
to me. I think that's discrimination.
If they don't let three or four people
in cuz the ratio then but I don't think
I think if they don't let someone in bad
I think that is that is discrimination
because you could just be new trying to
cuz I've met loads of friends. It's not
even just about women. I've met loads of friends
um you know in these pubs and stuff that
I still talk to to this day. So say you
just moved to this country or whatever
or you just want to make new friends,
you should be allowed to do that. I
think it's discrimination to be honest
with you because you can travel by
yourself, you can stay in a hotel by
yourself. I think it is discrimination.
That policy is definitely discrimination
and it defeats the whole object, defeats
the whole purpose, I think, of going out
because there might be a Thursday where
you just want to go out by yourself
after you finish work or whatever. Do
you know what I'm saying, Grezy? that
you know that you might just want to go out
and not even care about women and you
might just want to meet friends or you
want to make new friends or whatever
which you will do in these places. So it
is that is discrimination. I think
that's just my opinion.
It's a free country. You should be able
to [ __ ] you know, go where you want
when you [ __ ] want. You know what I
mean? So yeah,
they don't do it in a Weather Spoons.
They don't do it like them pubs, but
they do definitely do it.
It's like a club. Say, I wanted to go to
a club right now. Yeah. They'd say, "Oh,
I can't come in by myself.
It just doesn't really make a lot of
sense because they'd let me in with
what? Another guy.
That just doesn't make any sense.
Birmingham's the worst, bro.
Birmingham's the worst. When I was with
Monty, bro, this guy was on some kind of
power trip. They take the biscuit, bro.
They was like, "They weren't going to
let us in because we weren't with any
women." I thought, "What the fuck?"
He said, "Unless you have women, you
can't come in." I said this guy's
definitely on a power trip.
Definitely definitely busy.
Do you reckon Birmingham will be busy tonight? Dusty. Yeah.
Tell you where where it's going to be
really busy. [ __ ] Edinburgh.
That's where it's going to be busy.
That is what is going to be busy, mate.
And leads. I'm telling you right now.
Yeah. Leadeds in Edinburgh
going to be chocka blocked like a
motorway that don't [ __ ] that don't move.
Isn't that right?
Yeah, that is going to be they're going
to be the worst. What do you think, Grezy?
Lege is rammed.
Which is mad, dusty, because in London
you don't get lines like that. You know
lines that you see in Leeds, you don't
get that in London.
You know leads, right? When I went to
leads, you had to line up to get in
places. You don't have to do that in
London. So that's how you know people go
out more in leads than they [ __ ] do.
But leadeds will be rammed. I know it
will be. I [ __ ] should go then
[ __ ] meet [ __ ] David Campbell.
You can tell me more [ __ ] stories
about that little [ __ ]
What do you think? Me and David [ __ ]
Campbell doing a video drinking update.
But yeah. Um, yeah. Leads in Edinburgh. Defa
I went to leads in October, I think. Was
it October? Yes. And it was Bramen.
I didn't like the bounces in leads, but
I still think, you know, I'll give it
another chance to go up there. But I
didn't like the bounces at all. [ __ ] [ __ ]
That's another thing. You could go
dusty. You could travel somewhere, stay
in a hotel, and you wouldn't be able to
get in places.
It could happen. It can happen. Then
what are you going to do?
or get in some places. It can happen.
Yeah, definitely. That definitely can happen.
So, it's just not worth going out.
Simple as that.
Apparently, baby Guinness hasn't got any
alcohol in it.
Is that true? Yeah.
I need to go in a bit anyways.
person block, bro.
dismiss your struggles and [ __ ] block you. Yeah.
That's cowardly, is it?
There we go.
Fantasy stories is back people.
Yeah, I'm good. Yeah.
Yeah. This is fantasy stories people.
in front of us.
Yeah, something about No.
Yeah. Yeah. Whatever. [clears throat]
Yeah. If I went out today approaching,
I'd be getting more bad experiences.
[ __ ] depressing, isn't it, bro?
Now I feel like I'm missing out,
Grievous, dude. But I can't go out cuz
I'm going to have more bad experiences with women.
I don't want more bad experiences.
The [ __ ] collection is full.
The [ __ ] collection is literally full up.
because of my personality. Uh yeah,
really. You must have dismissed the uh
you must have dismissed the approaches
and the uh messages then.
No hard feelings though. It's not like
everyone else dismisses my struggles.
Another struggle dismisser.
That's just the norm now, isn't it?
That's what happens. Another one that
dismisses people's struggles. Yeah.
What the [ __ ] was that?
I won't. It would have happened by now.
If anything was going to change in this
country, it would have changed by now.
That's never happening. Not in this country.
It's never happening. I want to stop
talking about it now. Anyways, it's depressing, bro.
I'm going to try
got to think about uh what film to watch.
There's no point with this anymore.
I don't want to talk about this anymore
to press him any
thing about the 45year-old yesterday and
the single mom last week.
Dismissed it. Completely dismissed it.
I don't understand, Grezy. What's the
point of me being a candidate in this
argument or this debate when people just
got to dismiss everything I say? I don't
understand. What's the point of being a candidate?
I told you about the 45year-old, the single mom,
and it seems like it's gone in one ear
and out the other.
Why Why do you want to have a debate
with someone if you're just going to
dismiss everything that they say? I just
don't understand it. You've dismissed my
approaches. You've dismissed the people
leading me on. You've dismissed You just
seem to dismiss everything.
Why? What? What's the point of having a
a debate if you're just going to dismiss
everything someone else says?
It just defeats the whole object, you know?
So, yeah, that's that. Yeah. [snorts]
No, no, no, no.
Yeah. What's the point if you're just
going to just miss people's struggles mad?
It's all right, bro.
Yeah, it's all right.
It's all right. to be fair.
Yeah, hopefully. Anyways, Triple H,
these people think of new sayings
in um in 2026, lad.
Is that Red Star still saying the word M?
Jesus Christ. Are they still saying this?
These people need to get some new content, bro. [groaning] content.
Hopefully in 2026, hopefully 2026
will be the year, lad.
I'll be subscribing to L J. Um, and I
want to be seeing some new content. Yeah,
I'll be off soon anyways, man. I'm not
going to be I'm off in probably about 10 minutes.
Go sleep or something. Yeah.
Get yourself down to waxies, lad. If I
feel depressed, I'll just take some
cacodamal, bro. Probably just go sleep.
Codamal is uh is uh what you need if
you're trying to save and not be
depressed. Codamal is the one. Just take
like two a day. Should do the trick.
No, I just lying in bed, bro. Chilling. Saving. Saving [ __ ]
Yeah, I was going to go out today, but
no, I didn't do any football bets. There
was no um teams I wanted to pick. Yeah,
I've been sleep. Yeah, I went to get
some breakfast with my mom earlier, then
went to sleep. I made my bed, then went
to sleep. I was [ __ ] [ __ ] bro. It
was so cold.
I should be with someone at 28.
I should be with someone at 28 years of age.
I don't know what you mean by live like
what? Like not going out?
I mean, I can go out if I want to. I
don't like But no, you shouldn't have to
live like this at 28.
You shouldn't be single. You shouldn't
be sexless. You shouldn't be any of these things.
It's [ __ ] really, really bad.
Which is like, so what these people
saying, they're wrong because
they're they're talking about like
finances and stuff. So,
but yeah, you shouldn't have to
and you shouldn't have people on Reddit
keep trying to tell you that you're
going to meet someone when you're not as well.
But I am living this life. So, I starting it.
I should have a date today.
I should be on a date today, but I'm not. So,
it's nothing to do with luck. Unlucky is
losing money. This is more than luck.
This is more than luck. This is
definitely more than luck.
This is definitely definitely more than luck, bro.
Luck is winning money. Unlucky is losing
money. Luck is [ __ ] wanting to have a
boy baby and having two boys instead of
one. This is ridiculous. This is insane, you know?
So, I'll be all right anyways, bro.
Don't worry about me.
Cuz you want to go out, but you can't go
out because you know if you go out,
you're just going to have bad
experiences again. So, you're damned if
you do, damned if you don't. [ __ ] it
is [ __ ] up.
[ __ ] up. I'm leaving, bro. So, it
doesn't matter anyways. I'm I'm going to
try to join this porn industry and I'm
leaving. So that's that.
That's the end, is it?
Break the cycle once and for all.
Yeah. Hopefully I'll get in. So yeah. No,
no. The last person I spoke to was a single mom
and she just said something
unenthusiastic and that was it.
No one at all.
I'm probably going to go sleep in a
minute anyways. I'm just tired, bro. Get
this Saturday out the way.
I'm messed up, bro. I'll be up. Come on. Yeah, chilling.
Nah, bro. I'm good. I'm chilling. Yeah. No.
Who's this? No.
What is even the point of that, bro?
I'm not even ending the live stream. I
couldn't care less.
What is even the point of that?
Seriously, people only need to grow up.
I'm not even ending the live stream. I
couldn't give a [ __ ]
to be honest, bro.
I don't know and I don't care. Stop
bringing up nonslegs. No one cares about
him. Stop bringing these little clowns
up. I don't care.
But anyways, I'm not ending the live
stream, bro, cuz I'm not [ __ ] I don't
give a [ __ ] These people are here need
to just grow up.
So stupid, bro. What the [ __ ] Same
people doing the same [ __ ]
So yeah, that's me done, bro.
So yeah, that was the last person I've
spoke I spoke to. Anyways, so yeah,
that's 6:00 in the morning, 7:00 in the morning.
No, it was just like a cafe, bro.
No, I'm staying at home tomorrow, bro.
I'm not doing anything but staying at home.
Anyways, I'm gone. Yeah. So, peace.