Yo yo yo yo.
Oh [ __ ] Sorry man. I woke up a bit late.
Still talking [ __ ] Oh [ __ ] hell. These people
still talking bollocks. E. These people
will never ever ever ever ever ever ever
ever learn. Joseph still talking bollocks.
These people they need to they need to
give it a day man. They need to give it
they need to really give it a day off.
It's [ __ ] boring now, bro. It's
pathetic. [ __ ] me. Is this guy supposed
to be on holiday?
Jesus [ __ ] Christ.
These people really are pathetic.
Really, really, really, really, really
are pathetic, lad. They really, really
are. Really are.
Oh, Jesus Christ.
Brother, I just went on your thing. And
it's literally the [laughter]
it's literally the same people that's
been doing this for 7 years. Are you
going to get a life in 2026? Like that's [laughter]
that's a genuine question I'm asking
you. It's the same people that have been
doing this for seven, eight [ __ ]
years. What the [ __ ] When are you going
to get a life? Seriously, you come on
here. Yeah. Trying to call other people
a [ __ ] mto and all of this. Bro,
you've been you've been doing this now
for [ __ ] the better part of seven,
eight years, longer than that. But how
I've seen you on it and you're still
doing it. You're literally still doing
it, right? You I've done they've been
doing this, right? Since Peter Benny had
no [ __ ] beard.
Since Peter Belly had no [ __ ] beard,
bro. And And they're actually still
doing this. Like, when are these people
really going to get off YouTube and get
a life, bro? It's pathetic now, you
know? Yeah. They won't turn up. They're [ __ ]
[ __ ] They won't die up. They're
absolute [ __ ] bro. That's what they
are. Absolute [ __ ] Same as that
[ __ ] poverty Joseph Ferrar living
under poverty. He's exactly the same as
well. They're all the same on here, bro.
All the same on here.
So, [snorts] yeah, that's that.
Never turn up. Never turn up, bro. Will
never turn up. No, he edited his um
community post. If you're smart enough,
you would have clocked onto that.
So, it just makes you look like an
idiot. And that goes to show you've
actually got no life. See, if he
actually turned up Yeah. or he went live
in London, he would have actually got
some. But it just shows that he's a
keyboard warrior just trying to ruin
people's Christmas. It's sad to be
honest with you. And then you edited
your community post. Literally edited
edited your community post. And even Ben
Fury said that he needs to delete his
account. But as you can see, no one has
a problem with this guy [ __ ] it. No
one has a problem uh
uh no one has a problem with with this
because like I told you before, they're
all biased. So [snorts] that's what I
mean with these people, bro. And uh
yeah, what you mean, Joseph Fro, is you
and your boyfriend will never do
anything. You and your boyfriend will do
nothing. Mr. Scared to talk on a panel.
You will do nothing. just like your
boyfriend never done anything yesterday. So
that's why I think it's best for this
community. Leave the Mongs to one side.
Let them have their channel and then
just just have your own content, bro.
You know, that's what Yeah, that's the best thing.
I said Joseph Ferrar. I never said
Joseph Gavage, man. Open your [ __ ]
ears. These people are [ __ ] mongos,
man. I just went on your comments. It's
the same people doing it. Eight years
still ain't got a life.
sat on YouTube hating on strangers.
Still ain't got a life. Loser. Absolute losers, man.
I don't need you to defend me, but I'll
link you to the channel. I don't need I
can defend myself, bro.
I'll link you to the channel.
You don't need to defend me, but I can
defend myself. And have you noticed I
didn't delete any comments because I'm
not scared of dislikes and likes. I'm
not scared. I'm not scared of likes and dislikes. >> [snorts]
>> Yeah. Did you watch my video, Jensen?
They're all [ __ ] biased.
I just I just think they're just fat,
ugly people that jealous cuz you're
younger than them. That's what I think
with these people on here, bro. Along
with other things. I generally think
it's cuz you're like younger than them
and that and like, you know, the way you
are like a crazy [ __ ] That's what I
generally generally generally think. You know,
I generally think they're jealous cuz
you're younger than them. That's what I
think, bro. Personally,
when I stay at home and I don't go out,
that's by choice.
You know, they're literally, it's
literally by choice. When I don't go
out, that is literally by choice. So,
how can I be lonely and depressed when
I'm choosing to do that?
You know what I'm saying, bro? I'm
choosing to stay in.
I am literally choosing to stay in and
not going out drink. I could have went
out drinking yesterday, but I didn't. It
was probably for the best, you know. It
was probably, you probably would have
been hearing the same sad song today if
I went out. You would have heard it by
now if I went out yesterday. The same
sad song, same bad experiences. So what
if I don't want to go out? That's my
choice. You know, I don't have to go if
I don't want to.
This guy's flexing a [ __ ] motor
holiday. A motor holiday, bro. It's
probably like3400 pound and he's flexing
that. He's flexing a£3400 holiday. The
guy's The guy is [ __ ] the definition
of poverty. That Joseph Ferrar is
literally the definition of poverty,
bro. And he's trying to talk about me
with his fake ass pensions. Please, now
come on. It's embarrassing. It's really, really embarrassing.
It's really really embarrassing.
It's really really embarrassing now. Yeah,
basically, bro. Yeah,
just having a tea. I think I need a
Coke, bro. Jesus Christ. I woke up with
a headache. I woke up at [ __ ] 2:30, man. Jeez.
I didn't go to bed that late. Damn.
But yeah, when I don't go out, that's my
choice. That's because I don't want to go out.
That's because I literally don't want to
go out. It's not because I can't afford
it. It's because I don't want to go out.
Doesn't that make sense to to anyone? You know,
I don't want to go out. I can go out
right now. I can get on the piss today
if I wanted to, but I don't want to. So yeah. Yeah.
Oh, my back is hurting me, bro. [ __ ] hell. Yeah.
We shouldn't even use use money as an
excuse to saving to be honest because I
still wouldn't go out. I literally still
would not go out.
See, back years ago, two years ago, when
I actually had hope, I'd be like, "Oh,
let me go out. Let me go out." No matter
what it took. But when you know that
there's no hope, then you don't go out.
That's nothing to do with money. That's
literally because you don't want to.
That's literally because you don't want to.
But anyways, that Smokey Bee is a
[ __ ] [ __ ] He's a bully victim,
bro. Absolute bully victim. I wish I
[ __ ] screenshotted that, you know,
before he changed it. [ __ ] idiot,
man. Like, you're really And you say
that you got family, bro. And you say
that you got a life.
You say that you got a life and you're
[ __ ] sat on YouTube [ __ ] doing
this. And you say that you got a life.
Yeah. Yeah, right. You ain't got no
life. You know, just like Joseph Ferrar
ain't got no life.
Yes, Timmy. I'm a virgin. Yep. Yep. I'm
a virgin. A virgin that's proved they've
had sex multiple times.
Doesn't wind me up. It really It doesn't
w me up at all when you call me a
virgin. I just think it's silly because
people have literally proved they've had
sex to you and you're still calling them
a virgin. But it's just biased autism on
it, isn't it? It doesn't wind me up.
It's actually quite funny to be honest, you know.
It [snorts] is really It is funny. It is funny, you know.
Yeah. Okay, Timmy, whatever. Anyways, so
back onto this Smokeoky B, right? Yeah. Yeah, it no.
No, it doesn't wind me up at all. It
just means that you people need to grow
up. It doesn't wind me up at all. Do I
do I sound wound up because all we know
because all of this is self projection to me,
right? It's because you're a virgin.
It's like when Smokey Be says that I'm
skinn, he's skinned. No, it doesn't
welfing comments doesn't wind me up.
My [ __ ] arm is hurting.
Self-reflecting comments don't wind me
up, bro. cuz we know that you're just
self- projecting. So why why would it
wind me up? You're just talking about
yourself. So um yeah,
of course I don't. Yeah, I'm not I mean
I'm not scared of likes and dislikes.
Nons is he's scared of likes and dislikes.
He gets petrified. He goes mad over
them. Um and someone disagrees with him.
Me I I couldn't give a [ __ ] Triple H's
done a comment. It got 16 thumbs up. I'm
not about to delete it because I'm not
scared of dislikes. I'm not scared of
people disagreeing with me. That's why
no one needs to get blocked. You know,
say these Yeah. You ain't They ain't got no life.
They ain't got no life. They've been
doing this for like what? Since 2012.
Yeah. They ain't got no life. These
people ain't got no life other than to
come on here and hate. Yeah. So what,
bro? I did say that. It's the truth. If
they haven't got a life,
these people on here ain't got a life. So what?
Why are you talking about that, bro?
You see the same people for years. I've
seen the same people for years on here.
It's just the same 40-year-old
self-reflectors. It doesn't mind me up to me. Oh yeah.
See, look at look at one of these
comments, right? M owned again. He will
never learn. He generally has no life
experience and has never traveled. One
of life's all-time losers. But you've
said all of this before. This is just
the same repeating.
Like we've heard all of this before.
We've seen all of this repeating before.
You would have thought people with, you
know, a high IQ would have actually been
able to come out with new things. It's
just the same. It's just the same
repeating people. Yeah, pretty much. Yeah. No,
no. This Joseph Ferrar is talking [ __ ] again.
He's an idiot, bro. [sighs] Yeah. Joseph Fra.
Mr. Be Joseph Fra.
We're going to get some chicken and chips today. Timmy,
Timmy, Timmy, Timmy, Timmy, Timmy,
Timmy, Timmy, Timmy, Timmy, Jimmy, Jimmy. Stop.
It's just the same people doing the same [ __ ] Yeah.
Yeah, it's self projection, Frank. We
know this, lad. They all they do is
self-reflect on here. That's why it
doesn't m up. Just like when all of
these little 40year-old ugly people call
me a m. They're just talking about
themselves. They've been doing it for
years. It's about time they got a life.
It's almost 2026. I think they need to
get a life, mate. These people now,
they've been, you know, these people
have been doing this for years. They
have been doing this for years on here,
bro. These little low lives. They've
been doing it for years. Absolute years.
Years and years. You see the same
accounts years later.
Still doing the same [ __ ] Yeah. [snorts]
[ __ ] Joseph Fra is a [ __ ] idiot.
That holiday that he's going on, that
holiday, right? That holiday, that motor
holiday, bro. I could go on three of
them right now if I wanted to.
I could go on three of them holidays
right now if I wanted to. >> Yeah.
self projection, bro.
[ __ ] little shites on here, bro.
[ __ ] absolute little shitouses.
All this guy is doing is
self-reflecting. He is the only one
that's living under poverty. No one else
is. Only him.
They're saying that I'm living under
poverty yet I've got more than them and
I've got more money than them and
they're still still calling me poverty.
It's madness. The self-reflection on here, bro.
This gets worse and worse and worse
and worse and worse.
Yeah. Bust, bro. Yeah,
that's that, bro. Yeah,
it's the same people doing the same [ __ ] [snorts] [laughter] Yeah.
What did you get up to yesterday, Frank?
I just chilled in the nesticles.
You all right, Steven Howard? Captain, I
had to put that [ __ ] Joseph Roar in
his place. The poverty [ __ ] ridden
He's trying to tell me that I'm living
under poverty again when he's the one
that holidays to maltto in the [ __ ]
winter. Who the [ __ ] goes to molter in
the [ __ ] winter?
Yeah, I was going to go out, but I
didn't want any more bad experiences
with women, Frank. But that apparently
means that I'm skinn and I can't afford
to go out.
Apparently I can't afford to go out.
Yeah, apparently I can't afford to go out, bro.
Even though I literally can do whatever
I want, but I want to. So yeah,
that Joseph Fro is a clown. An absolute
A absolute clown, mate.
Oh, that Joseph Ferrar is a [ __ ]
clown dust there.
Yeah, I don't know what I'm doing today.
I'll probably go to the chicken shop.
I'll probably go chicken shop.
Yeah, I had a roast yesterday. Yeah.
People can be sick of their bad
experiences and not want to go out
and not be broke and not be skimmed.
People can generally generally be like that
or I can go out whenever I want. I can
drink whatever I want, but I don't want
to. So that's that.
I'd rather stack up money and leave.
That's what I'm doing. So what the [ __ ] You know,
I be all day long anyway. It's maybe an
hour and then I'm gone. So yeah.
a [ __ ] M. You're bragging about a mortar holiday.
You're You're bragging about going to [ __ ] Malta.
That's what I'm doing. I can't be
bothered to go out drinking and getting
more bad experiences with women.
There's no point keeping putting your
hand on the hot stove if you know
there's no one for you. So, you might as
well just stack and leave. I'll be out
New Year's Eve. I'll go out New Year's
Eve, but that's a special occasion, is
it? But other than that, nah, no point.
This is pointless. Absolutely pointless.
[ __ ] pointless, bro.
Yeah, it becomes addicting as well. It
becomes addicting. It becomes an addiction
after like the second week. You don't
want to go out because you just want to
keep saving. And I've been doing this
for over a year now. So, Joseph Fer, I
can tell you right now, I can go on
holiday whenever I want. I can go
drinking whenever I want. You don't know
how much money I've got. You don't know
nothing. You don't know [ __ ] all about
anyone. You know,
that's that [ __ ] idiot. Clown.
Yep. That's exactly what I'm like, Dusty.
I'm at over a thousand.
I'll be proper proper sweet when I get
my next payment and that's that. I don't
want What's the point? There's literally
no point. You're not going to meet anyone.
So, what's the point? There's no point going out.
There literally is no [ __ ] point, bro.
I used to just stay in save and gamble.
I used to save and then gamble.
So like I'd gamble, win, save, gamble,
win, save. That's what I do, bro.
I was smart with uh
it's not even just that. It's just a
waste of time. And all you're going to
do is get bad experiences with women.
That's all that's going to happen. So
there's literally just no point in going
out just to get more bad experiences
when you already know what you already
know the result. You already know the
You already know the [ __ ] result.
Um, well, because it's London, dust
deep. I I pay 78 pound a pint. But you
don't have more than five pints, though.
Yeah, but you don't have more than five pints.
That's why. Well, six pints. Well, they
can't water down the pints, but they
water down the rum.
But it is bad. And when I went to this
local place last week, it was £5. It was
£5 a Guinness. That was a bargain.
And even in central London, even a
Weather Spoon is like £7 something a Guinness.
It's like £8 a Guinness now though in
proper places. Yeah. But to be honest,
if you don't go out much, you're only
really spending £50
on the Guinness if you think about it.
It's the rum that I don't understand
because they water it down. I went for
like30 on rum and it didn't even hit me.
You stick to Guinness then.
But if you go happy hour, it's like£3
pound for a beer. In happy hour it's
like£3 pound a beer.
Also, you can get chucked out of places
for talking to people.
It's just not worth it. It's just not
worth anyone's time. There's no one for
you here. So, simple as that.
If there was a good horror in the in the
film, then I'd go.
Yeah, but not as much as Yeah, but not
as much as the rum.
Yeah, but not as much as the rum,
though. With the with the rum, they
definitely definitely water that [ __ ]
down, bro. With the Guinness. Yeah, but
you will drink a whole Guinness and it
will hit you. You can go for three, four
rums, it hasn't hit you. What the [ __ ]
So, yeah, they might do. Yeah, but not
as not not as much of the um
not as much of the rum.
Hence why it's harder to uh
um to notice.
Let's go for some chicken and chips.
Bust that. Stack some money now.
That's that. Like I said, I'll go out
New Year's Eve. That's not a problem.
But I'm not going out for then. It's
pointless. It's a waste of my time.
Yeah, he's on his little He's in his
little poverty holiday.
I was just saying I could go on four or
five of them holidays right now if I wanted to,
you know? I could literally Why are you
going to motor in the [ __ ] winter?
What the [ __ ]
To be fair, it's not a bad place to go
to be honest. Moto in the summer. I
would actually go in the summer to be
fair. To be fair, I was actually talking
to my mom about this. In the summer, I
think I would actually go.
Actually, I would actually go in the
summer. My sister's been there. Yeah,
there is loads of casinos. But he's
going in the winter.
It's not even like he's going like say
April. If you if you go April, I'm sure.
Okay. Maybe the winter's too hot. Yeah.
Uh sorry, the summer's too hot. But I'm
sure if you went like March, April, why
the [ __ ] are you going in December?
Dude, this I'm getting sick of this cold
now. I said I like the cold greasy, but
now it's getting too cold.
I'm constantly hungry. [ __ ] It's [ __ ] bro.
I like October weather. I like the
October weather. Now it's just [ __ ]
It's just too cold.
Constantly having to eat. It's [ __ ] horrible, man.
I stick to what I say. I like March and
April and October.
They're the best months. Yeah. Yeah,
there is loads of casinos in motor and I
know that cuz when I used to gamble
online there. Yeah,
my sister's been there.
My sister's been to a lot of countries. Bless you.
Bless you in life.
Get yourself down to waxes, lad.
Get down to waxes.
Get yourself down to waxies, lad. [laughter]
Grezy, do you want to go to waxies?
Get yourself down to waxies, lad.
Mobile experiences. [ __ ] that poor game of soldiers. [ __ ] that. Yeah, man.
There wasn't any uh good national leagues. Meow. [screaming]
You fat stinking copycat. [laughter]
You [clears throat] [ __ ] fat stinking copycat.
Um, there wasn't any good national leagues
um on Saturday.
Okay. Well, Grezy, I like shovel Cole.
I fancy shovel Cole. Grezy. >> [laughter]
>> You big I was laughing my ass off in bed
yesterday. I was I was remembering what
you said. You're nothing but a big stinking copycat. [laughter]
You big stinking copycat.
I don't know why that made me laugh.
You big sing.
I will never forget what Ant-Man said to
me. Greavvesy. He's like, "You watch
porn from the 70s? That is weird.
That is so weird."
I know loads of people that watch porn,
but not people that watch porn 70s.
[laughter] That's so weird.
It's the way you said it. Greasy finish. [laughter] Oh, bless. Oh gosh.
Yeah, Steven Howard's a pretty good [ __ ]
O, um, I was watching Ed Matthews. Uh,
nah, I'm not drinking, bro.
Dusty, I was watching Ed Matthews in
America doing some approaches
and the women were saying there they had
boyfriends, but people on Reddit said
that if I go to America, I'd pull
because of my accent. I don't think so.
I've watched a lot of his American stuff
and it seems it seems pretty similar to
here with the attitude,
the make boyfriends. It seems
it seems pretty similar.
No, I'm not going. I'm not drinking,
bro. I'm stacking. That's that.
But I bet Thursdays and Sundays are good
to go out around this this month. Yeah,
because of um
because of um Yeah, Sundays are probably
good to be fair.
around this time. Yeah.
Yeah. They told me to go to America.
Dusty on Reddit. They said go to America
or Canada. Yeah, right. That's probably
even worse than here with the attitude,
the westernity. It's like what Ant-Man
said. You can see the westernity in their eyes.
The dirty westernized look they give you. [clears throat]
That man said he hates going out around
this time of year. It's too busy.
Dusty. He said it's too busy. You can't
even get a drink. Yeah.
You said you can't even get a drink. Yeah. [snorts]
I bet Wednesday is probably a good day
to go out. Is it? What do you think? Wednesdays
because it's busy but probably not too busy.
What do you think, Dusty? Probably
Wednesdays, Thursdays, and Sundays are the best.
Yeah, probably. Oh, you there
meow. I'm calling you meow
meow meow meow.
You ready for your next copycat statement?
It's been made.
How do you know I'm on Franklin? That
the next The next copycat statement has been made. Reezy,
if you do not go out drinking every
week, your skin,
it's been made. You've been waiting and
it's been made. The ne the new copycat
statement has been made.
Yeah. So if you don't go out drinking
every week, it was made by Joseph
Ferrar. Your skin.
Yeah. The new copycat statement has been made. [laughter]
What does the cat look to do in the
photo? Greaves. You know the cat
downstairs. What's it looking to do?
It's looking for its next victim to
copy. No substance, no mind of its own. Just copying, you know. [snorts] Yeah.
Oh, I like lasagna. LJ's having lasagna.
I like lasagna. Do you like lasagna?
Where is he? I might I might have some lasagna today.
What do you think of that? >> [snorts]
>> I might get a lasagna.
Okay with you, boss.
I tell you what videos are really
addicting. Yeah, them GTA ones, Grezy. I
was watching so many of them yesterday.
Yeah. Where it says if you do this, this
happens in that GTA and that GTA and
that GTA. You know them videos. Grezy,
they're so addicting. You can literally
just be sat there just watching them.
They are addicting.
What happens in this GTA? What happens
in that GTA? If that happens,
it's very, very addicting, bro. Them videos,
you know what I'm talking about. them videos. Dusty.
Yeah. I don't have a microwave one. I
have a homemade one.
Yeah, that's what I'm saying. They're
addicting. There's loads of them. Yeah.
Greasy, I might um I might get a lasagna
today. Is that okay with you?
I have a lasagna. lecture greasy.
Is that okay if I have lasagna? Cuz LJ
had lasagna. Now I want lasagna. Grezy.
Yeah, I see LJ have lasagna. Now I want one.
Yeah, I'm on about the shorts, bro.
They're [ __ ] addicting
cuz I love GTA. So yeah,
I've got green eyes, Greavves. I've got
big green eyes.
You remember I call nonslegs the
greeneyed monster. [laughter]
The greeneyed monster virgin [ __ ] The
What color eyes do you have, Grezy?
My mama used to call me leopard eyes.
Leopard eyes. [laughter]
Yeah, I might get a tandoori chick. I
don't know what I'm going to have today,
actually. I'm not sure.
moves. I'm not sure. Yeah.
It's impossible to get laid in this
country. Speak to Spaz. No one's bloody
interested. You try to speak to someone,
they say they're not interested.
They give you their number. They [ __ ]
lead you on. [ __ ] same old [ __ ]
That's why Peter Benny didn't go out
yesterday, cuz it's always the same old
sad song. You either get told they have
a boyfriend, they're not interested, or
they just lead you on.
That's literally all that ever happens.
Well, I don't let him I I just let him
keep self-reflecting because he is a virgin.
Because Timmy is a virgin. So there's no
point going back and forth with him
because he is a virgin. Everyone knows
Timmy's a virgin.
It's just funny. I just laugh cuz he
actually is a virgin. So
Timmy's an actual virgin
just like Nons is a virgin as well.
They're both virgins. The two Virgin Marys.
When are you going to lose your Valentine's card?
Your Valentine's card. You like that one?
Big up Timmy if you bullied a woman.
Yeah, good. That's good for Timmy. I'm
glad he done that. These women are evil. >> [laughter]
>> You [ __ ] virgin. You [ __ ] virgin.
Oh, he looks like that virgin [ __ ] Yeah. Yeah, whatever.
I don't care what these people try to
call me. It's just self projection.
Just like when they call you skin, self
projection. It's all self-p projection
on it. I hate so who [snorts] cares.
It's just people talking about themselves.
I end up like Tim. Not possible.
Nope. That's not possible.
That's not possible. V. Oh, not V.
Technically, I'm skin. Technically, I'm
not, but okay.
It's fantasy stories. It's not Jaden.
Technically, I'm not skin, but okay.
Bro, listen. It's almost 2026. Are we
going to stop the skin talk?
Are we going to stop this self-p
projection skin talk now?
Right. How much money do I have right now?
One second. One second. You just said
I'm skin. How much money do I have right
now? The exact pound to the penny.
Right. Right. Right. Right. Okay. So,
how much do I exactly have right now?
Okay. Okay. Okay. Yeah. Benefits. Okay.
So, how much money do I have right now?
Exactly. So, shut up. You don't know how
much money people have. Stop self
projecting. It's almost 2026. Stop it.
Stop it. It's almost 2026 now. Stop it.
Literally, stop it. It's almost 2026.
Stop it. New words, please. I beg.
I've already played a money game and
beat these people multiple times. I'm
not playing it again. Listen,
listen, listen. It's almost 2026.
Please, can we have a new Can we have
some new sayings?
Right, we're not talking about me and
how much money I have anyways.
And your bands.
See you later.
That's fantasy stories.
That's not Jaden. That's fantasy stories.
All right, Ree, do you know something
Jaden said that made me laugh?
Yeah. Self projecting again. Self
projectors. All right. Do you know what
something someone said that made me
laugh? Greasy. It was Jaden. Do you know
what he said?
Monty was like, "Oh, you do know this
person is a non." Jaden replied, "No,
mate. However, I know you are one." [laughter]
I don't know why that made me die, bro.
He said, "However, I know that you're one [laughter]
on the comments."
I don't know why that made me laugh.
Well, I need to come off in 15 minutes.
So hopefully 2026, no more skin talk, no
more self projection. What do you think,
Dusty? Fingers crossed. It these people
are smart. They've got a high IQ.
So they think of different words on 2026.
Yeah, I used to love gambling.
I used to love gambling, Frank, but I
gave it up because of like the mood swings and
surprised I never went back to it to be
honest. All of the [ __ ] I've had from
women and that.
Yeah, I used to love it as well like
roulette and stuff, but not anymore.
After all the mood swings and [ __ ] it's like nah. >> [snorts]
>> You know what I mean?
I like gold.
I like shovel co.
I like shovel gold.
Hey, nature. You all right? I didn't go
out yesterday. I stayed in my little
nesticles cuz I didn't want any more bad
experiences with women.
Hope that's okay with you.
Yeah, I don't actually know what to eat today.
I think the Chinese is open.
What do you think would have happened,
Nature Girl, if I went out approaching yesterday?
People on Reddit keep trying to tell me
that I'm going to meet a woman, Nature.
>> Well, I'd rather just stack the money
now and leave.
Yeah, I'd rather stack money and leave.
What do you think, nature?
No, but people on Reddit says I'm going
to meet someone.
Some woman said yesterday that if I give
up, it might come naturally. Nature.
That's what they say on Reddit.
>> [snorts and clears throat]
>> Why? Why is it impossible in this
country? What makes you say that?
What makes you say it's impossible?
From what? Like my experiences, I'm guessing.
Yeah. Yeah. But people on Reddit say
that I'm going to find someone.
Nature. They say that I'm going to meet someone.
And they say that you can get sex
whenever you want. That's what they say on Reddit.
And from what I'm seeing in America, it
doesn't seem any easier there, too.
They say that you, you know, they say
that if you give up, you'll naturally
get someone, you'll find someone and stuff.
That's what they say. But it's not
possible, you know?
What's the point of having a dick,
nature girl, if you can't even use it?
I didn't listen nature girl. What's the
point of having a dick if you can't even use it?
Yeah, I haven't been out for a while.
Nature, I'd rather just save.
It's bother having a Willie if you can't
even use it. Absolutely pointless.
Only thing you can use it for is to pee.
[ __ ] pointless, lad.
That's what uh Morgan's ex said to me
that I need to find God.
That's what he said. Morgan's ex. He
said, "You need to find God, little man."
He said, "You need to find God." There
is no God. He doesn't exist. [laughter]
Yeah, Damon said that I need to find God. [ __ ] virgin.
You're nothing but a nasty little virgin.
Launch legs is a virgin. like to be the two virgins.
Why in nature? The two virgins. [snorts]
Two big virgins.
She said, "I need to find God."
They say you meet someone though. They
say it happens, Nature Girl,
and then they randomly block people on
Reddit. They randomly block.
Oh gosh, my little legs are hurting me.
Nature, I think I'm really I'm becoming really ill.
Peter belly is becoming ill. Oh gosh, [snorts]
I got to go get some fried chicken in a
bit from my favorite chicken shop.
It's going to take me a while to walk
there, but it's all right. Yeah,
Joseph Far is a [ __ ] little nod lover.
See, these people talk so much [ __ ] on
there. I'd love to see his passport
stamp seeing he doesn't have a passport.
[ __ ] they're absolute [ __ ] idiots
on it, bro. On this community.
Yeah, they told me to go to poetry
classes, dancing classes, virgins.
[ __ ] nonsense will never leave me alone.
That's why you never [ __ ] meet
someone with autism.
Especially if they're a [ __ ] virgin
like he is. They don't [ __ ] leave you
alone. [ __ ] skin virgin.
You know what I mean? [ __ ] virgin.
>> Oh, that Smokey Bee is a [ __ ] house,
Steven Howard. And no one said anything about it
except you, Ben Furvy, and one other person.
They're all biased on here, bro. They're all biased.
You lost before you even begun.
You lost before you even begun, bro. You
lost before it even started.
They're autistic. It's an autistic community, lad. [snorts] Hear that? Joseph Fur
scared to talk on the panel.
See, look at this, bro. Look at this. Steven Howard
never forget some random woman who'd
never met Poverty Pete named him the M
as even he's is even when he's groomed
haircut new gums is barely a two out of 10.
We've heard all of this before.
We've literally heard the same thing
before, bro. And it wasn't bothering or
it wasn't funny the first time you said
it because we all know that the people
that are behind these accounts are fat, ugly people.
See, it's just the same repeating with
these people. But they say that they've
got an IQ. They say that they're
intelligent, but all they do is repeat.
Surely to God, if these people were
smart, they'd think of some different
comeback seven years later. It's still
the same repeating.
When I was little Peter Belly and now
when I'm big Peter Belly,
it's just the same repeating. Same
repeating comments, same repeating people.
What the [ __ ]
No, it's not even just him. It's others
as well. It's repeating.
They're saying that I'm a M when I'm
literally better looking than them. How
does that make sense? How the [ __ ] do
It's sad. These people These people
really have got nothing in their life,
bro. It's sad. Sat on the internet for
years hating on people they don't even know.
They're sad. They live sad lives. They
got nobody. These people, bro. It's so obvious,
but they're funny comments at the same
time. Did you see old poverty Pete
again? These are the ones living under
poverty eating his roast pork. The
cheapest of all roast. They're not off a
garden table in his sister's room.
Brother, why are you not allowed to eat pork?
Okay. It's the cheapest.
Okay. And and actually his chicken is
the cheapest actually. Okay.
And what? I like roast pork. I'm going
to have some fried chicken in a bit. I
can afford something more than fried
chicken, but I want fried chicken. These
people are [ __ ] I tell you, bro, they
are they all look like that. Jamie
Thompson. They're all fat and ugly. This
is why they do this every day. They're
fat and ugly. You ask these people here
to put their cameras on, they won't do
it. They will not do it. You tell them
to put their camera, bro. They won't
even talk on the panel, but bro, they're that disabled.
They are. They're definitely They're
just fat and ugly.
They're fat, ugly, old, hopeless people.
That's all they are, lad. They got
nothing in their lives. That's why they
do this year. They do it every day as
well. They do this every single day for years.
But they're definitely the ones living in poverty.
That's definitely them. Skin is
definitely them. And Montto is
They That is literally their lives. That
So what? If you want to have a meat
cheaper than a certain other meat
because that's what you want, that that
means what exactly? They're just [ __ ]
fat ugly mongos that ain't got nothing
in life. Disabled little single bully
victims. That's what they are in here,
bro. Sad moronic little bully victims.
That's what they are.
I'm going to go to your chicken shop,
bro. I can afford something more than chicken.
if I want.
Not want to.
That's what happens. [snorts]
That's what happens, bro. when you want
to stack money.
So what if you eat roast pork? So you're
not allowed to eat roast pork because
it's the cheapest. What the [ __ ] bro?
These people can't even afford a roast
pork. They're eating beans on toast.
Another little self-reflector.
Look at this little virgin smoking me
again. His life is beyond tragic. He has
nothing achieved and will be lonely
forever. This guy's already lonely.
Self-p projection. It's amazing how bad
he's It's amazing how bad his life is at
30 years old. I'm not anywhere near 30.
Again, self-p projection. Haha. I'm a
couple of years older than him and we
live worlds apart. It kills him so much.
I mean, yeah, you're the one that's
making community posts every day. You're
the one doing videos. No, I'm pretty
sure I'm killing you. I mean, I'm I'm
pretty sure I'm killing you. You know,
you you little morons. We know what you
look like. We know you're fat and ugly.
Nothing you say about anyone bothers no
one. But you will still come on here
year in year out doing this. These
people make me remain unbothered.
They do not bother me one little bit.
They're fat, ugly life rejects that
ain't got [ __ ] all in their life. That's
what they are. Stad fat ugly people.
Now you see where I didn't go out
yesterday when I cuz I didn't want to go
out yesterday. These people can't afford
it. These people are so skinn that they
can't even do anything but jump on the
internet every day and hate on other
people. That's how skint they are.
That's literally how skint these people are.
They're so skinn that they can't do
anything but hate on other people that
they don't know.
That's literally them, bro. That's
literally all they do cuz they're too
skinned to do anything else.
[ __ ] talking about roast pork. The
roast pork was £8. Okay, you you you're
eating [ __ ] beans on toast.
Self-reflector. Little self-reflector.
Have a day off, man. Anyways, I'm going.
I'll be back later. Yeah. Going to go
get some food. So, I'll be back later. Yes. See
you in a bit. Yeah.