Yeah, I'm just going to wait for Grezy.
Yeah, I want to talk to uh Grezy.
this isn't the main video. The main
video is that uh it's going to be first January.
That's going to be like the proper
proper welfare check. Oh [ __ ]
Yeah, I'm going to do the welfare check
properly on the first of Jan. See if
it's the same people.
And if it [ __ ] is, then uh yeah,
we're using a Ben Furvy quote. I think
to be honest, yeah,
if you if I see you people on here the
first of January, I'm going to go [ __ ] mad.
I am going to go [ __ ] mad if I see
you people on here on the first of January.
I will be [ __ ] questioning [ __ ]
all sorts. I don't want to see any of
you here next year cuz I won't be.
No, I'm not subscribed to them clowns.
I am subbed from them. I am sub. Well,
I'm them. I wasn't ups No, I am subbed.
I'm not doing this for keyboard warriors anymore.
No, we're not we're not doing this anymore. So, yeah.
Any luck? You already know the answer to
that. Uh, so don't know why you ask
questions you already know the answer
to, but um
yeah, we'll wait for Griezy. Grievy's
going to love this. Oh my god. You know,
I was so tempted to [ __ ] do a video
on this. It's madness. Absolute madness. Yeah.
Yeah, man. It was boring last Saturday,
uh, Dusty. But then I woke up, I was
fine. I was like, "Yes, I didn't go out,
man. I was good." You know,
at least I didn't go out. It was worth
not going out, you know.
It was worth it. Trust me, it's worth
it, you know. [Music]
But no, I I unsubed from that Joseph Per
cuz he's just a little keyboard warrior.
I'm not giving him no attention. So just
like a lot of these people on here, I
don't go on their channels. I was only
subbed to him. So yeah, I unsubed from
that Joseph Raw like days ago, bro.
Cuz you're never like the thing is you
got to understand like you're never
going to win with these people.
So there's just no point engaging with
them. You're never going to win with
these biased people. There's just
there's no point, bro. Like I'm I'm on
and off here, bro.
Honestly, after this, I probably won't
be on until the 1st of January. I'll be
on L J's on the 1st of January, like I told you.
And I'm going to be like, same people,
same story. See you next year. Bye.
That's what I'll literally be saying. If
it's the same people, I'm that's exactly
what I'm going to be saying.
No, I just can't be bothered with it.
It's the same [ __ ] on here.
Oh, [ __ ] It's the same old [ __ ] on here, bro.
I unsubed from that. Uh Joe F. I unsubed
from He was the only one I was subbed to.
Yeah, cuz it's you're never going to win
with these bias keyboard warriors and
they're just a waste of time.
But I'll be on Lord Jays on the 1 of January
and I [ __ ] I hope these people are
not on here. They say that they're
smart. They say they've got an IQ. Well,
we'll see that. We'll see about that on
the 1 of January
if they really really have got a high IQ, right?
Is that right, Triple H?
Yeah. I can't be bothered with this place, bro.
money doesn't even come on anymore
cuz we know what these people are like
on there, bro. They're just [ __ ] idiots. Absolute idiots.
I'm going to make a tea in a minute. I think
I had a nice spaghetti.
Well, we'll see, won't we? Well, we'll
see, lad, won't we, mate?
You know, no, we want different people
saying different things. We want people
on here, just different people. Not the
not the not the same repeating people.
I can't believe this thing on Instagram,
bro. It was a madness. This thing on
Instagram is mad.
Yeah, no one cares, bro.
Just like no one cares about that Joseph
for all anymore. I'm done with these people.
So like engaging and arguing and [ __ ]
They clearly ain't got a life. They got
nothing to their lives. So, um,
yeah, that's that. Bam.
That's why I went on yesterday or today before that.
Oh, I was watching the documentary.
Yeah, good for him, bro. I'm not even
sub to him. I'm not going on his channel
ever again. He's a keyboard warrior.
He's a biased keyboard warrior. No one
cares. They You engage with them kind of
people, that's how you get brain damage.
You interact with them kind of people,
that's how you like lose brain cells.
Joseph Far them people, you literally
just lose brain cells by like um
engaging with them kind of people.
You know what I find so funny is that
they've been doing it for years. Um,
that's another thing. Like the last
thing I want to say is that these people
on here have been doing this for [ __ ]
years. You've seen the same accounts for years, bro.
And they say they've got a life. Yeah. Right, bro. Yep.
Do you know what I find so funny, Dusty?
So, I follow this woman on uh Instagram.
Yeah. and she does like things where she
embarrasses herself in public.
Like she embarrasses herself in public
and does like weird things in public.
And I follow her on Instagram
and uh you might have seen her and I was
like, "Oh my god." You might have seen
her, right? Then she does she does a uh
she does a um post talking saying that
uh she's um
she was seeing uh she'd been seeing this
guy for 3 weeks and um suddenly he hits
her with I'm not ready for a long-term
relationship. Guess guess what everyone
done in the comments? Oh, poor you. He's
immature. He's the problem. He's this.
He's that. And when I [ __ ] show
people my struggles, they don't even get
bloody acknowledged. They just get
dismissed and thrown under the bus.
That's how you know the game's [ __ ]
up. That's That is how you know the game
is [ __ ] up. When a woman has been
seeing someone for 3 weeks and it's not
even like she got cheated on or anything
like that, just the guy broke said, "Oh,
I don't want to pursue it." An amount of
sympathy comments from men and women and
yet you will show these people your
struggles and they don't suit them. Uh,
they play stupid. That's how you know
the game's [ __ ] up. That's how you
know the game's [ __ ] up. Um, I I I
couldn't believe that when I saw that.
Cuz if you went on a date, let's just
say you go on a date, right? Something
similar, and the person doesn't see you. Um uh
you know um and uh
and and and it's weirdo dusty and it
tells you that it is it is a gender it
is a gender thing. Um it is to do with
gender. Um it's not to do with you. It's
and at the end of the day sympathy for
what? She didn't get cheated on. She
didn't get beat up. Why is she getting
sympathy? And then she's lying in bed.
She then she was lying in bed. Right. I
might do a video on this. Yeah. Uh she
was lying in bed.
Um she was lying in bed. Yeah. Saying
about, "Oh, I'm feeling a little bit
depressed. It's this time of year. The
dating game is not going well." And I
think about And I'm thinking, "What
about me? What about me?" I I said this
to my mom. What what about this [ __ ]
here, you know, that's been up and down
the country getting [ __ ] after [ __ ] for
years after years after years. That
doesn't even get acknowledged. That
don't even get [ __ ] acknowledged. It
doesn't suit them, dusty, my my
struggles don't suit these people.
That is sickening, bro. And then there's
a guy, there was this guy, bro. He says,
"Yeah, what's sad, right?"
Uh, there was this guy, I think he's
from London, he done a video and he
says, "It's 6:00 in the morning. It's
really cold. You know what's so bad? You
know what's so bad is that you can't
even walk past a woman nowadays without
them being scared." And he said, "It's
wrong." And and he was trying to put
them on the pedestal. I turned around
and said like, "Bro, women are not
innocent. So you why don't you do a
video talking about how women get all of
this sympathy, but then when men
struggle with dating, all their
struggles get dismissed. you you should
do a video on that to make it a bit
fair. If you are going to do videos
saying, "Oh, it's terrible that women
are scared of walking past men on the
street and that," you should do a video
talking about how the dating game is
very very very unfair. Um, do a video on
that, you know? We we want to hear that
because that's that's a major problem.
Don't talk about [ __ ] women like
they're [ __ ] innocent. Um, you know,
and that's and they're not innocent.
They're not they're not innocent. If
they were truly innocent, they wouldn't
do the [ __ ] that they do. Um,
it's don't don't sit there and do one
video on them. And do do one on the
dating game, bro. Make it fair. If you
can make it fair, then we have no
problem with it.
Uh, brother, I'm not your mate. And [ __ ]
off. So, suck my dick. So anyways,
yeah, they're not interested in you
either. So [ __ ] off. I'm going to do a
video on this anyways because I don't
think we going to going to uh be on
here. So yeah. Yeah, they're not
interested in you either. And defending
them is not going to make them
interested in you.
So no one cares. Triple H. I don't care.
That's why I'm ignoring your comments. I
don't care, bro. I've not come on here
for this [ __ ]
I've not come on here to engage with
keyboard warriors, brother. I'm not here
to do that. We're done with this. It's
over. We've we we've been there, done
it, worn the orange and yellow t-shirt,
brother. We're not I'm not getting into
it with these people again.
Yes, but I'm not moaning about I am
moaning about how unfair it is, cuz it is unfair.
Brother, if you keep bringing him up,
I'm just going to time you out. Yeah.
Can you stop bringing these people up?
Otherwise, I'm just going to time you
out, bro. For a little bit. Last chance.
Last chance. Please stop it. I will time
you out. I've told you I've come on here
today for peace,
not to engage with the same people
that's been doing this for years.
Okay, moving on now. M. So, we're not
talking about people being interested.
We're not talking about people not being
interested. We're talking about the
biasness and the sexis sexism.
So, if you took your [ __ ] simp glass
glasses off for a second, uh, you'd
actually have heard what we're actually
talking about. We're not talking about
people being interest. We're talking
about how it's unfair. The dating game's
And these people that are giving women sympathy,
we are not talking about people being
interested or not being interested.
They're biased and they're sexist.
Uh they are racist. Women are racist.
We're talking about them being sexist
and then we're giving women sympathy for
just being a woman. We're not talking
about people uh being interested or not
being interested. Who's talking about
that? And yes, the women are racist. So what?
That's for another [ __ ] video.
They're sexist. They're racist. They're
everything. I make zero sense. Firstly,
I'm not your mate and I make 110% sense.
If you opened your ears, uh, you would
you would actually heard. I make
absolute sense and I'm not your mate cuz
I don't know you, [ __ ] So, firstly,
that's that. I'm not your [ __ ] mate.
I'll never be your mate. So, get out of
your get out of your brain, [ __ ]
I'm not mates with simps that defend
women. They're the worst kind of people.
I gave that guy stick on [ __ ]
Instagram. I said, "If you're going to
do a video on women, do a video about
how it's unfair, you know, for men."
Right? And you're getting time out now. Told you.
Told you, bro. So, yeah.
Anyways, I'm going to do a video later
on this anyways cuz Gregy might be busy.
I warned him. Stop bringing the person
up. I haven't come on here for weird
drama with keyboard warriors.
Bro, I told him you'll get a timeout.
You won't get blocked, but you get a
time out. I'm not in here for weird
drama with weird people, lad.
Nah, we're not doing that.
We're getting closer to 2026 now. It's
been going on for years now with these
people, bro. Years.
So, that's that. So you So I'm going to
do a video later. Um
I think it's absolutely disgusting to be
honest with you. I think it is absolutely disgusting.
Um I think people seriously Yeah. need
to respect themselves more and just
leave England. That's what they need to
do. They need to like that's what I'm
doing. I'm always I'm almost at the
savings now. I've got to book this flight
£850 to about £1,000. And I think that's
what more people should be doing, you
know, respect themselves and get the
[ __ ] out of any westernized country. Um,
you know, even if it's just for a bit,
because this is insane, bro. The amount
of sympathy this woman was getting just
cuz someone broke up with her, you know,
and it weren't even a proper
relationship. [ __ ] three weeks.
You don't need to know how much money I
have. You don't need to know that.
You don't need to know that. what money I have.
So, um, yeah, that's what people
seriously need to be doing. Bro,
you said I'm SK. You said I'm living
under poverty. So, you clearly know
people more than they know themselves.
So, you're saying [Music]
I'll be definitely definitely definitely
See you later, B. So yeah,
the flight 750 to about 1,000. Get that.
Yeah, that's it. Um,
then yeah, that's that.
Yeah, if you get a if you slide if you
stop off at China. Um, yeah,
it's not over 1 grand. It's 850 to
a,000. No, it isn't. And I'm not even
going to tell you the airline.
It's not over a,000. The flights I've
looked up, bro.
So, if you want to get indirect, it's about
six. If you want to direct it's about 8
850 to a,000 depending on the market you
go that I think yeah
so that's that you'll be a lot happier
you know when you're out of this country
at the end of the day you need to think
what's best for you you know you know
you're 28 years of age this shouldn't
still be happening
um so yeah bro
um it shouldn't be happening this still
shouldn't be happening at 28 years of
So that's that, bro. Yeah, [Music]
I've got the money as well, so it's not
a problem, bro.
See, it's all right. You know, Dusty,
when you're 24, 25, 26, you're still
like that age range where you're
thinking that you're going to meet
someone, it's going to change, then it
doesn't change, and you're thinking,
"What? Bro, we're going to go through a
whole another year of this [ __ ] again.
It ain't normal. It ain't normal." And
then when you realize how [ __ ] up the
game is and how women get all of this sympathy,
it's bad, bro. It really, really,
really, really is bad and unfair.
So instead of that guy saying about how
oh yeah it's bad that women can't even
walk the streets without feeling unsafe,
you need to do a video on how biased and
sexist uh this generation is.
You know what I'm saying? But
how biased and sexist this [ __ ] generation is.
It's not spoke about enough.
And I was talking to this woman earlier
on Instagram and they like to play dumb.
This is what they do, Dusty. They like
to play dumb. Um, oh, how they lend you
on? Like they play stupid. They play dumb. Um,
you know what I'm saying? They play
stupid and they they play really really dumb. Um,
like you've not shown them a load of
[ __ ] at what they've done. You know what
I'm saying, bro? Like they play like
Yeah, that's it.
Um, it's bad. It really, really is bad.
It's not spoke about enough, you know.
And there's loads and loads and loads of
women out there that's not scared of
men. So, stop. I don't know why that guy
is trying to white. I said, "Bro, stop
whining. Women are not innocent."
So simple as that. This woman
like got a load of sympathy just because
some guy said they didn't want to see her anymore.
Think about that, Dusty.
What if she was generally the problem?
Nope. Not one person blamed her. Not one
single person said it could be her. But
it's always you.
One more chance. Triple. Oh [ __ ] I lost
kill. One more chance, lad.
Uh uh to that account there,
um stop asking questions you already
know the answer to, lad.
What country am I in? England. What are
the women like in England?
You know it's never going to change
and you're going to get a timeout.
There you go. I told you I'm not doing
this weird drama with these people. You know
these weird people that will never meet
you cuz cuz think about it, Dusty.
Right. Yeah. I can retaliate to these
people. I can argue back and forth the
rest of this December, the rest of the
rest of all next year. And guess what?
No one's going to meet me. No one's
going to say anything to my face. No
one's gonna give me an opportunity to
meet them. So why what do I get out of
it? Think about it. I can go on Joseph
Farage. I unsubscribed from him, by the
way, and go back and forth and back and
forth and back and forth and back and
forth. But at the end of the day, bro,
they're always going to be a keyboard warrior.
You know, they're always going to be a
keyboard warrior. So, at the end, that
will never meet anyone. So, you could do
this for seven years and it would still
be the same [ __ ] So, they're not even
worth uh arguing with or anything like that. So, yeah,
but yeah, it is. And yeah, I generally
do think these women are racist as well.
Um, I think Ben Fury was right. So, not
only are they stuck up in cello, they're
actually racist. Don't tell anyone that,
mate. they [ __ ] call you a dael. Um,
that's another thing I'm going to bring
on the video is why is it okay for women
to have a couple of bad experiences and
moan and winge and everyone feels sorry
for them, but yet when you've been
dealing with toxic [ __ ] for years,
you're not allowed to have an opinion
without being called an incel. We need
to make a change, bro, in this society.
We need to make a change
cuz they're [ __ ] taking the biscuit now, bro.
I am going.
I am going, lad. I am going.
It's not just that, bro. It's, you know,
it's it's a new life for a little bit.
I'm not going to be living there. No
more stuck up women. No more being led
on. No more make believe boyfriends. You
basically be in paradise.
Uh, good for them.
So yeah, I'm going to do a video on this.
Um, but yeah, they could just be racist,
Dusty. Like what Ben Furby was saying, lad.
Um, they're just um they're just racist.
It could simply be cuz they're they're
racist. It's like Ben was saying um you
know, because obviously I look Turkish
and I've got a beard. It could generally
just be they're racist.
Um simply because you've got green eyes
and not blue eyes, you've got a beard.
It generally could just be that which
contradicts them saying that they don't
go for the way I mean they they not get
with somebody based on the most smallest
things. They're more sh they're the same
shallow as men.
But no one will admit it. This is what
I'm trying to say. Like they they they
are just as shallow as men dusty if not
more shallow. But no one will ever say that.
They will say oh no looks don't matter
to them as much. I mean, it goes more
than looks, you know. I'm not taking my
beard out. Nope. I'm not taking my beard
off. I should have to.
Nope. I'm not taking my beard off. No way.
Um, why would I take my beard off? Nope.
I'm not doing that. No way.
I've already been laid. I've already had
sex. So, go away sella.
Um, so yeah. Uh, I'm not taking off my
beard. There's nothing wrong with having
a short beard. I don't need to change
myself for anyone. You wouldn't change
You wouldn't tell a woman to change
herself for people. So, don't tell me to.
Uh, because you wouldn't tell a woman to
change. You wouldn't tell a woman to cut
her hair because she weren't getting any
men. So, don't tell me to change my tell
me to get rid of my beard just to get
rid of a woman. No, I'm not doing that.
My beard's clean. It's it's it's done
professionally at the barbers. There's
nothing wrong with my beard. And you
said that women don't go for looks and
stuff, so it shouldn't be no problem.
So, this is where they contradict
themselves. You know, this is this is
the this is the thing with this dating game.
Um, and another thing is Dusty. Yeah,
it's got it's got to be a race thing
because it's got to be a race thing
because obviously yeah, there's people
out there that you're not going to be
their type. Obviously, you're not going
to be pe um everyone's type obviously,
bro. But you should be finding people at
the same time. There's nothing wrong
with the way that you look. There was
certainly nothing wrong with the way
that you look years ago. So, at the end
of the day, there's no reason. So, it's
either they're racist, which I think
they are, or they've just got these
unrealistic expectations and they're
very physical as well. That's the only
thing it could be, bro. That's the only
thing it could be. So, um, that's that. yeah,
I think it's probably a bit of both to
be fair. Um, but it's definitely a
racist. So, they're actually racist,
something that we never we we don't hear.
Dusty, we don't hear that these people
are racist. Um, you know,
we don't hear any of this stuff.
We would You would never You You say
that woman's racist, [ __ ] hell, mate.
You You'd have people [ __ ] You get
the KKK after you,
you know. So, that's uh Bye-bye.
So, yeah, you get the KKK after you, bro.
It's not going to happen. It's not going
to happen in Thailand.
Um, it's not going to happen.
So, yeah, it could be a race thing.
Could be your beard. It could be Yeah,
that's what it is.
I think that Ben Fer is right, even
though he's hardly on here. So, that
says a lot about them, doesn't it? Does
that not tell you a lot about them?
If it is true,
it will never happen. It will never
happen in Thailand. Um,
nope. I don't go on anyone's channel,
bro. I unsubed to that um I unsub to
that uh Joseph Ra.
Nah, bro. I'm done with these people.
I'm going on L on the 1 of January and
that's it. just to see if it's the same people.
No. So, yeah.
So, that's basically where we're at, lad.
Yeah. It could be the beard. Yeah.
So, yeah, we should have to change that
ourselves for them.
You know, these people saying that these
women are not shallow and it's not look
so they go for. So, why should we have
to get rid of uh why should we uh have
to get rid of our beard?
We should have to get rid of our beard.
That contradicts what they say,
Dusty. That contradicts what they say. Yeah.
Oh, yeah, man. Yeah.
Don't know what's wrong with uh what's
wrong with having a beard, a neatly
trimmed beard, to be honest.
Yeah. Yeah, I was showing this woman
these screenshots, Dusty, and she was
like, "Oh, how did they lead you on? How
did they lead you on?" Uh,
why you asking me that when you
literally have seen what they've done?
And this is what I mean. It's just a
constant argument and all you will do is
end up with a [ __ ] you'll both end up
with a headache and then nothing happens
and it's all because you're a man. This
is what I'm trying to say.
You know, they don't even acknowledge
people's struggles and [ __ ]
madness, bro. Madness.
Why? I don't bother no more, Dusty. Just s
Get rid of the beard.
And you got this man saying, "Oh, I
think it's mad that I can't walk past a
woman without a woman being scared."
They're [ __ ] [ __ ]
Why are you Why are you defending them [ __ ]
They're absolute [ __ ] and he's And
he's [ __ ] defending them mad. They're
[ __ ] absolute [ __ ] bro.
Bad people. And he's [ __ ] defending them. Madness.
They're not scared when they're leading
people on via messages, are they?
They're not scared then when they're
[ __ ] leading people on. They can't be
that scared when they're [ __ ] playing
games with people over text, can they? [ __ ] [ __ ]
It's depressing this dating thing, bro.
The more you think about it, it's so
depressing, isn't it?
Sad, sad, sad.
That's why I don't try anymore. Dusty,
are you happy I don't try? Boss,
are you happy I don't try? Captain,
yeah, I was watching this black guy approach.
It was the same [ __ ] with him. I have a
boyfriend. I have a boyfriend. Stuck up.
Yeah, they were being stuck up to him as
well. They're being [ __ ]
Some black guy.
Why is this not spoke about Dusty about
their attitude and them being stuck up?
Why is it not
Why do um people not talk about it, you
know, about their unrealistic
expectations? the fact that they're
stuck up, the fact that they're rude.
Why is this never brought up?
You know, cuz it's a big big thing
nowadays. Um, you know, and it never
gets brought up.
Yeah. Well, it shouldn't be accepted.
But it's not Well, it's not accepted
though. It's dismissed.
But it's not accepted. It's dismissed
because if you say that a woman stuck
up, they'll call you an incel. So, it's
not accepted, is it? really by most
people cuz if you say that they call you an incel,
stuck up [ __ ]
because they like to talk about men's
attitude, Dusty. They like to talk about
the way men are, but they don't talk
about the way women are. This is what
I'm trying to say. Their stuck up nasty attitude.
Them being [ __ ] Them leading people
on, you know, they play stupid. When
when you when people when you show them
what women have done, they play stupid.
They choose not to acknowledge it.
Yeah, they're [ __ ] bro. Women are
absolute [ __ ] I don't ever want
anything to do with any of them ever again.
They're all the same scum scuming the
earth. Why do you think I didn't go out
last week, bro?
Why do you think I didn't go out last
week, bro? Cuz I couldn't afford it.
>> Really, bro? Really? No.
cuz there's no point.
Uh why are you get
why are you going to, you know, put
yourself in more bad experiences?
Why are you going to put yourself in
more bad experiences with women?
It doesn't make sense,
you know? It really doesn't.
And that 45 year old. I'm gonna bring
that 45 year old up in the video as well. Yeah. Yeah, bro.
No one ever mentioned that they're racist, Dusty.
until it happened. It kept happening
more and more and more and I thought,
"Oh, maybe Ben Fervy's right. He seems
all right on here. He's unbiased. He
tells me when I'm wrong. He tells me
when I'm right. He's never really on
it." And I'm thinking, "This guy might
be on to something." Yeah.
So then they've got you've got the
racism and then you've also got the
um obviously the unrealistic standards.
Oh, the fact that is because they are racist.
So, it's like either one, you know.
Yeah. Doing good, man. We're just
talking about the double standards
and that guy doing a video saying how I
think it's disgusting how women are
scared of men nowadays. I think it's
disgusting how women lead people on, but
no one says anything about that.
If you actually think about it, the
whole thing is just designed to
basically [ __ ] you over. If you think
about it, Dusty, they're sexist.
Definitely sexist. They're biased. Um,
they're racist as well. So, that's another thing.
Yeah, they're definitely definitely on madness.
No, no, no, no, no.
Yeah, Jensen, it's bad, bro. It's
really, really bad.
It's really bad. there.
The people on Reddit say you you can
meet somebody, Dusty. But Reddit's not
real life, is it? Reddit is in real life. So yeah.
Yeah. Reddit ain't real life. No.
No. Really? It ain't real life, lad.
What would you do, Dusty? You would just
leave in it.
You would leave, isn't it?
>> You could go out. You could take a break
and go out and not expect anything,
dusty. But that's easier said than done,
you know? Like, you can say, bro, that
like, oh yeah, I'm not expecting
anything. We know how it is. Yeah. After
a month. Yeah. And go out again. But the
problem with it, Dusty, is, you know,
you're going to get numbers. You're
going to get hung over the next day.
You're going to get the same bad experiences again.
And then um the same thing's going to happen again
cuz obviously your history is going to
add more and more and more to it. So
that's not even an option because you're
just going to go back to where you
started again. You're just just going to
keep going around in circles again,
you know, and obviously the alcohol is
bad as well the next day.
Bro, even 45 year olds will not get with
me. I had a 45year-old [ __ ] um making
excuses the other day, Jensen. I told
you about that, didn't I?
Yeah. You join the porn industry or leave.
Yeah, just join the porn industry or
leave. Simple as that.
I haven't had a date since April. And
this woman's complaining that she's been
with someone for 3 weeks and
he's dumped her. Imagine you can get a date. You know meow meow.
I can see a copycat. What?
Where? Where? Oh, sorry. I can smell a copycat.
Can't see them.
>> See you later.
Don't let keyboard noise on my channel. So yeah.
Yeah. Waxies. Yeah.
>> [ __ ] poppycat.
See, I was born with a [ __ ] mind of my own,
right? Another time out for you, lad.
Another time out for you.
That's why I think USA is he got with me
cuz um obviously USA wasn't fully white.
USA doesn't go for white men. He goes
for black men and well people that look Mediterranean.
So it definitely is a it is a race thing. Therefore,
I don't think I've ever been with
somebody with blue eyes with blue eyes
before. Have I?
Well, that American that gave me a
[ __ ] was blonde blue eyes. But for
the most part, no.
I don't think I have. No,
it's definitely a race thing.
You you need to go for people that go
for [ __ ] either Mediterranean people
or black people, but they're not white, basically.
Weird though. It is very weird. Very racist. You know,
I'm [ __ ] decent looking when I
[ __ ] look Mac. What the [ __ ] Can't
even [ __ ] find anyone. The [ __ ] bro.
Yeah, it's very rare you're going to
find someone nowadays, bro. Very rare.
Very, very rare.
Just not interested in Antman said
they're just not interested in this country.
No, bro. No takeaways. I had spaghetti
bonese. I'm stacking the money up.
Yeah, I'm stacking the money up, bro.
No, I don't. I had spaghetti bolognese
today. I'm addicted to saving now. I
don't want to spend. That's what
happens. Like we was talking about,
Dusty, you get so addicted, bro. You
don't You You don't even want to You get
to this routine of spending as less as possible
on food. Anyways, I can go out this week
if I want to, but I don't want to.
I don't want to, bro.
I don't want to. Like, that's that's not a problem.
But on drinking, but I'm not doing that,
bro. So, yeah. Pointless.
You don't know how much money I have now.
Maybe I have a few grand now. You don't know.
How do you know I don't have a few grand
already? You don't know me. You don't
know how much money I have.
And dusty, January is the best month to
save, bro. You can safely save January,
February cuz no one goes out until
March. Well, midFeb. So, you save this
month and you can also save next month as well
because no one goes out January. So, you
have that whatever you wanted to spend
on drinking, you could spend it on
something else because no one will be
out anyways. So, These are the months
you really need to start be stacking
this money now, bro. You know, [ __ ] this.
Maybe I already booked the flights.
Maybe I already did.
Even Adman said the same thing. Even if
he had to Even if he had to Even if he
had to, bro. Even if he had to. Yeah.
Even if he had to um say for 6 months,
he would do it.
Even if you weren't making extra money,
he said he'd say for six months just to leave.
Yeah, that's why I've been living like a
bum, bro. I've been living like a bum. I
used to do this even when I had a house.
I used to just live off like a bum, bro.
I'm not Well, I'm going out New Year's
Eve, Dusty. But I mean, that's kind of justified.
But even then, I'm going to be spending
as little as possible.
I want out of it, bro. I want out of
this [ __ ] Oh, bro. Oh, I need to go
cinema though on Boxing Day. [ __ ]
Yeah, I need to go cinema Boxing Day.
Saying that I want to watch the new
Spongebob movie as well. I'm going to go
cinema Boxing Day.
Sorry, I have to. But I've been waiting
for this film for months. So, but yeah,
just just just live like a bum. Yeah,
I need to buy a phone. It's like 250, so
I still have way more than enough. you know. Yeah.
I can't wait to leave, but I swear that
it's boring at first, but once you get
used to it, man,
you'll be out of it in no time. Trust Um,
it's called a bride. What's it called?
It's a horror film. I can't remember. I
always get mixed up, but I'll be
watching it definitely.
I'm gonna have to part with some money
on that day, bro, because I've been
waiting for this film for a long time. So,
and I quite want to watch the Spongebob
one as well, cuz I grew up watching
Spongebob Dusty, but it's not one where
I would actually like want to pay money
to see it.
Well, it's £400, but it will go to 250. So,
I've got this phone as well. I've got
this fold, but it's just blocked.
No, 250. No, 250 pound phones are not
crap if it goes on offer.
No, not 250. 250 300 pound phones are
not crap. It's the 150 ones that are
crap. And it's only until the uh it's
only till next summer as well. Uh next
summer I'll be getting the fold eight.
Um I'll be getting a fold eight in um in the summer.
So yeah, uh July it comes out. So I'll
be getting a new fold.
So that one's just like a temporarily
block, not blocked one. And yeah, I'll
be getting a fold eight. Definitely be
I'm not getting a fold seven. Pointless.
I don't, bro. I mean, I'm changing this
phone because uh it's blocked. So once I
get that fold eight, bro, I'm I'm going
to use it until it [ __ ]
until it breaks basically. So yeah.
No, I've never kissed a girl. I'm a virgin.
What iPhone you got again, Dusty? You
got the 17, don't you?
What's your opinion on these refurbished
phones? I don't know whether to get like
a refurbished iPhone or just get like a
Samsung brand new.
I don't really like getting used stuff.
Yeah, I got this phone. This is a uh
Fold six. This is
Oh, you got the same phone as my mom then?
Yeah. Antman's got iPhone 12.
Now, what I'd probably do, Dusty, is I'd
probably um use that fold eight for like
three years, then change. This is a fold
seven, but obviously it's blocked, but
the screen is kind of [ __ ] up on it
now. Um but it's still usable.
I don't know, bro.
Yeah, you got the same phone as my mom, bro.
Like I said, bro, I'd get a contract.
I'd get a year contract, Dusty. I'd get
a year contract for the fold because I'm
not paying £1,800 for a phone. Yeah,
it's only a year, £200 a month after the
year it's paid.
Yeah, but it's a year contract. So, a
year is nothing.
I I used to pay £70.
Like I said, you with them phones, you
either get a contract or you don't have
it at all
because who's going to pay 18,900 pound
for a phone, bro? That's [ __ ] ridiculous.
But yeah, generally, Dusty, yeah, like,
yeah, contracts are mad, but they're
only good if you want a really, really good phone.
You can't justify £1,800 for a phone,
bro. You just can't justify it. 1,000
1,200. I'd pay £1,200 for it, but I'm
not paying £1,800,
Dusty. That's ridiculous, bro. 18. So,
what what you reckon these refurbished
iPhones are good then, Dusty?
There's a iPhone 13. It's refurbished. I
might get that one. But the thing that
worries me with them is the battery.
The battery um scares me, bro.
What I might just do is get a
refurbished iPhone and then
just get the Fold 8 when it comes out.
Yeah, just get an iPhone 13
stuff I need to do and [ __ ] Saying that
though, Dusty, this phone's blocked, but
you don't have no problem with it
because there's Wi-Fi everywhere in
London. where there's Wi-Fi everywhere.
You can call with Wi-Fi. You can text
with Wi-Fi and everything with Wi-Fi.
So, it doesn't even seem that different.
Yeah, that's what my mom does.
Yeah, that's what my mom does, bro. My
mom does the same thing. I pay £33 for
unlimited everything, but obviously it
builds my credit up. So, I don't mind
paying I don't mind paying something
every month because at the end of the
day, bro, like trying to build my credit
up and when I want to get a fold A, I'm
going to get a year contract and just
pay £200 a month.
I'd rather pay £200 a month, get
unlimited everything for that year than
pay £1,900 for a [ __ ] phone. [ __ ]
that, bro. [ __ ] that. At least, you
know, in a year the phone's yours. The
phone's yours in a year. It's only a
year. You know,
I would buy the phone outright, but the
thing is, I can't justify £1,800 on a
phone. I can't justify it.
I really can't justify. And you know the
thing, do you know the thing is, Dusty?
They come out, they come out every year.
They come out every year, Dusty. So, you
pay 80,900 for a phone and then the next
year another one come comes up.
Well, you could pay £70 a month, but
that that means you're stuck on a
contract for two years.
Well, you can pay less, but obviously
the contract will be longer.
What are you going to do? Pay £1,800 for
a [ __ ] phone? Well, there you go then.
You know what I'm saying? So, like
if you want the phone truly, that is the
only way. Unless you get a 2-year contract.
You could get a 2-year contract, but
give me give me £1,800 if it's bum
change, bro. I'll send you my [ __ ] uh
I'll send you I'll send you my [ __ ]
details if £1,800 bum change, bro. [ __ ]
me. I'll buy the I'll [ __ ] put it
into the [ __ ] fund. If £1,800 is bum
change, give me £1,800.
[ __ ] hell. I could do with £1,800 extra.
That is so stupid, bro. Like, why why do
you even say stuff like that, bro? When it's ridiculous.
Yeah, I do have 1,800
and I I sure you can do a lot with £1,800, bro.
£1,800. Bum chains, is it? [ __ ] bum
chains, bro. What a stupid thing to say.
That is the most stupidest thing I've
ever heard, bro.
You don't know how much money I have.
£1,800 is is not bump chains, mate. I've
lost two grand before when I was getting
three grand a month. Only an idiot would
say £1,800 is bump chains. Is it is it
going to get Is it going to last you
months and months and months? No. Is it
considerably less in this day and age?
Yeah. But it being bum chains, bro. Really? Nah.
What do you think? Trip rates 1,800 pound.
Yeah, that is a lot of money, bro. For
some for someone that's got no bills.
That is a lot of money, bro.
Yeah, it is for someone that ain't got
no bills. Yeah, it is.
Yeah, it [ __ ] is.
Especially probably where you live. Yeah,
£1,800 is, bro.
1,800, bro. Well, obviously, bro,
because we're not all millionaires like you.
We're not all millionaires like you,
Indigo. Obviously, like you're a millionaire, bro.
You know, I think that's the only way.
Yeah, I think that's the only way. Yeah,
people would say 1,800 pounders bum
change is if they're millionaire
because I never see anyone talk like
this off this community. Triple H. My
sister's got thousands, bro. Thousands
and thousands and thousands. And she
would not give away £1,800.
You know, people that work. My sister
thinks £500 a lot of money. It's only
this community, Triple H, where people
say these weird things. And that's why
we say that they're fantasists
because everyone on here seems to be a
millionaire, a multi-millionaire, bro.
They all seem to have [ __ ] Taylor
Swift money. But in the real world,
that's not real, is it,
Trip H? That's not real, is it, lads?
If you think about it, that's not what
happened in the real world, you know.
Yeah. So that's why we call them fantasy basically.
Most people here just Most people just
get a phone contract and get a new phone
every year. I wouldn't get a new phone
I would use it when I get this fold A.
I'm going to use it until it breaks.
I love these Samsung folds, bro. I love
these Samsung folds.
They're [ __ ] ace, bro. They're
[ __ ] ace, but they're so expensive.
I'm on a fold right now. Power Fold 7.
They're lush. They're [ __ ] lush.
These phones are lush, bro.
Yeah, most people get a phone contract.
I could buy the phone, but you can't
justify £1,800 on a phone.
It's just you just can't justify it.
You literally can't justify it, bro. I
couldn't justify it. I could justify
a,000 1,200, but not 1,800.
I could pay £1,200.
I'm paying £1,800. Simple.
That's that then. So,
hi M. You're right.
Thanks for the spaghetti bolognese.
Mommy cooked me a bologn. A spaghetti
bonet today. My mommy's so nice to me.
Dusty Lane is so nice to me. My mama. Yeah.
Um, so yeah, lad. So yeah.
You want to get a flip? No. Get a fold, Dusty.
The fold's way better than the flip, lad.
And the flip. I've had a flip and I've
had a fold, bro. Like the flip. Yeah.
The thing with the flip, bro. And that
was also on contract. The thing with the
flip, bro, is when you open and close
it, this it [ __ ] up after a while. Get
a fold, bro. You should get a fold.
Definitely get a fold. Fold's better
than a flip, bro.
Trust me, I've had both of them.
One second here. I'll put a link up now.
I've had a I've had a um purple flip and
then I've had a fold. I upgraded to the
fold. I was like, "Yes, I've wanted
these one of these folds for ages."
Nah, trust me, bro. The fold is where
it's at, bro.
Trust me, man. Trust me. Folds are
[ __ ] the goat, man. Telling you.
But obviously the flip's like $850,
isn't it? So it's a lot cheaper than the [ __ ] fold.
But I'd get the fold, bro. I love them.
I love these folds. I love them.
If it wasn't for these folds, I would
just get a [ __ ] moderate range phone,
bro. It's only the fold I like cuz the
screen and that.
I remember that time the police come on
the door, bro. They were trying to get
my phone. I put the phone in the guard
and they couldn't get it. Peter belly
was one step ahead of them.
And yeah, madness. They've tried hard to
get this this little fold, mate.
But it ain't worked. Trust me,
they tried. Come on my doorst. I was I
think I was just about to leave the
house. They come on the [ __ ] door,
bro, in the old house. And I'm thinking,
oh, like there's a risk I'm going to get
arrested. So, I'm going to put my phone
in the garden. Put my phone in the
garden, bro. And I'm thinking, I hope
they've come out. It [ __ ] they've
come out empty [ __ ] handed. And they
did come out the court [ __ ] like two
days later. I went to the garden. The
phone was still there.
Almost almost, bro. But I'm one step
ahead of these [ __ ]
And they don't give your phone back as
well once they take it. The bastards.
Almost. Almost. Please see. Almost.
You need to wake up pretty pretty early
to, you know, catch Peter Belly, matey.
I just dashed in the garden.
They take your phone. They don't give it back, bro.
Nope. I was living by myself.
I was living by myself. It was a [ __ ]
hot day as well, bro.
[ __ ] baming hot day. It was
Nope. I was living by myself back in the old house.
The phone was still there. I was like, "Yay, phone. H yeah. Yeah. But
that's another thing. You shouldn't get
into back and forth with this little
police informant. They will never meet anyone.
Same with that Joseph Ferrar. You will
never meet anyone. He just wants to be a
keyboard warrior. So, you know, that's
that's the end of that, lad.
That's um that's that episode. So
they're not worth anyone's time, these people.
If no one's going to be normal in this
chat, then what's the point, bro? You
know, that's that. Yeah.
What am I going to eat? I'm going to
have some burgers tomorrow.
Yeah. I'm going to have some burgers tomorrow. Yeah.
I'm going to be bored on Saturday because obviously um
yeah, people go out Saturday. I can't
even go swimming cuz it's cold. I was
going to go in the summer and I'm bored.
Uh yeah, I'm going to come off again for
until the [ __ ] till until the first of January.
Yeah, I'm going to just save as much
money as I can, bro.
So, I've got the freedom of doing what I
want, you know? That's that's that it.
So, that's what I'll be doing.
I'll take some cocoa more on Saturday.
If I feel really bored, I'll take some
cocoa and go for a walk. Simple. I don't
give a [ __ ] bro. I'm used to this [ __ ]
No, I won't. I'll be live New Year's Day, though.
I'll be live New Year's Day. Same
people, same story. See you next year.
Ben Fury, that was a That was a That was
an ace quote. Same people, same story.
See you next year.
Triple H. Same people, same story.
Ronald Pump, you're better looking than
them. You've got a better life than
them. And you've got more money than
them. And it kills them.
Jesus Christ, bro. That's [ __ ] lovely, man.
That's what Ronald Pump said to me.
He's not wrong. Not wrong, lad.
There's a few quotes.
Ben Furby said, "Yeah, same people, same
stories. See you next year."
Yep. You said that on Timmy's.
You're you're better looking than them.
You've got a better life than them. And
you've got more money than them. And it
kills them. Do you remember that about Dusty?
That's what That's what he said.
Well, duh. Look at what I've done in the
past few years. Well, I don't do
anything now cuz I'm because I don't
want to do anything. It's cold and I'm
saving them. But you know,
it is true. It is true though. It
definitely is true cuz they never leave
you alone on their trip. It's the truth.
They will never leave you alone. It's
the same as what Ronald Pump said. It is
the truth, bro.
If you look at what most of these people
look like, [ __ ] Jamie Thompson,
they're just Yeah, they they ain't got a
life. And it's not my choice. It's when
I'm staying in and I'm saving money.
That's my choice.
You know, people like Red Star and all
these other people, that's not their
choice. They are skimped. They are
disabled. They can't do anything with
their lives. It's not by It's not, you
know, by choice. They're not doing it
for a month. They're not doing it for 2
months. They've been doing it years. You
understand? They've been doing it
[ __ ] years, bro. These people here.
And that's another thing you need to
think of, you know?
Because even if you cuz even if you beat
Timmy at a game of chess, it's it's like
he would just It's like playing a game
of chess is with Timmy is like playing a
game of chess with a pigeon. Even if you
beat the pigeon, it's going to strut
around the board and [ __ ] all over it
and pretend and act like it's won.
That's why there's You can't play a game
of chess with um with Timmy. Yeah.
That's what Tom Wood said years ago.
Yeah. There's some good quotes on here.
That's what Tom Wood said about with
Timmy. It's like playing a game of chess
with a pigeon.
It will just [ __ ] [ __ ] all over the
board and and pretend it's one even when
you've beat it.
H That's funny, bro. Oh, bless. Yeah,
Grey makes me laugh. You big stink. You
big stinky coffee.
Yeah. Yeah. Non legs is a copycat.
Yeah. He's definitely definitely a copycat.
See, I've like when Laney gave birth to
me, I was I was given Yeah. like a mind
of my own. I've never had to, you know,
try to fit in with a crowd. It's never
been my scene.
He said Chev was attractive to fit in.
He said it's a fit.
Sorry, that just makes me laugh. Sorry
for repeating, but it just makes me
laugh like someone would feel the need
to fit in with the crowd.
He follows the crowd. It's like, you know,
it's like, you know, New Year's Eve.
Yeah. In London when there's a crowd and
it goes and it goes towards London
Bridge. You know the crowd? It's like
you you you like me, I'll just stand
there and just do my own thing. But him,
he will follow it. He will follow the crowd.
Follow the crowd in it. Yeah. [Laughter]
Just want to feel left out. Yeah.
Madness, bro. Madness.
Uh hopefully he can get laid next year
and he won't be a virgin. Yeah.
So anyways, Indigo, can you give me
£1,800, please? Since you said that it's bum chains.
Can you give me [ __ ] £1,800, please?
Indigo is a millionaire. Yeah.
Yeah. Indigo is a millionaire, lad. You
can know that.
Oh, dude. What's that? Kings Cleans on
Instagram. The guy that stops people and
cleans their um trainers.
Yeah, I like that guy, man. But what's
going on with these [ __ ] jeans, bro?
Them old boot cut jeans, bro. What the [ __ ]
What's going on with them old boot cut
[ __ ] jeans, man?
What the [ __ ]
Yeah, I watch King's Clean. Yeah,
Timmy, join the paddle, lad.
Timmy, join the paddle.
Fingers crossed. First of January.
No more repeating different people. I'm
looking forward to it. Triple H. I'm
looking forward to the first of January.
It's going to be different [ __ ]
different people, different comments
because obviously they've got a high IQ.
They said so. Oh gosh. Yeah.
I was going to owe these people at the
money game again, Dusty. I was going to
I was going to get the 50s out, but we
don't play them self projecting games
anymore, do we?
Because people people ask you to show
money because they ain't got money.
They're little self projectors. Dusty,
we don't show show self projectors, buddy.
No, we don't do that. That's self projection.
Yeah, that's self projection.
Can you imagine you meet a woman? Yeah.
No age excuse, no religion excuse.
Could you imagine that? I can't ever
imagine that happening again.
I think back of the times years ago when
you never heard such excuses. It was lovely.
Now you all hear them excuses
all the time.
Yeah. I'm going to do a video anyways later. about us. Yeah,
I like sh
I like co
I can't get out of my head, bro. It's [ __ ] copycat. Dude,
never in my life has that [ __ ] made my
dick go hard. Never once in my life.
Never. [ __ ] never.
You know when people have had to rank to
stuff before, Dusty, you ranked to you
you've masturbated to people. Never once
have I masturbated to that [ __ ]
I'm not a big fat stinking copycat. That's why
Yeah, only people that copy do that.
Only people that follow the crowd. Are
you coming in? Um, Timmy
want to put the link up again.
Yeah, I'm sub from that Joseph for Dusty
because he's a little biased nons lover
and he comes from Lavy's channel.
Do you not understand what the whole
channel is? uh
based on that.
Yeah, I was on it the other day, bro.
One second, bro. Yeah.
Yeah. These people like Nons and Joseph
Ferrar, they're never going to meet you,
bro. They're never ever going to meet you.
These people are never going to meet
you, bro. Never.
and they'll never meet. They're just
little keyboard warriors.
The That's why I unsubdusted because it
was annoying me, bro. Just little
keyboard warrior trying to tell me how I
would do nothing.
You know how I would do nothing?
Like, do you know how tempted I was,
bro, to go to Newcastle the other day,
but we all know the same sad song with
these people. We all know what these
people do. They chat [ __ ] Even when
they take L's, they chat [ __ ] So then
that's why this unsubed, you know.
You know what I'm saying, bro?
They're all the same. Jo, non legs,
they're all the same on here, bro.
They're all They're all the [ __ ] same
kind of people. You know what I mean?
They will never meet anyone. They talk
about people. They don't know what
people do. They don't know how much
money people have.
And that's that, bro. Like, not worth it.
Let them humiliate themselves, you know? What's that? Yeah.
So yeah, bro.
No, no, no, no. Want some popcorn, bro?
You're right, Steven Howard. Captain.
Yeah, I was just saying I unsubed from
Matt Joseph for all a couple of days
ago, bro, cuz he's another little nunch.
So, they're not worth our time, these people anymore.
There's no point going back and forth
with these people.
So yeah, I just unsubed.
I blocked N's legs. I blocked anyone
that keep that kept bringing the [ __ ]
Virgin up. [ __ ] these people, bro. Yeah.
I just love how they think they know how
much money people have,
you know, they how they think they know
what money people have and what they
don't have and then even when they get
embarrassed like I Steven Howard, I can
go to the bank tomorrow and embarrass
these people again. But there's no
point. Been there, done it, worn the t-shirt,
you know? Been there, done it, worn the
t-shirt with these people, bro.
They will always talk [ __ ] no matter
what. So yeah. Yeah.
Joey the Nle's lover.
The Lavy lover. Steven Howard.
This KL can't even talk on a panel, bro.
And he's telling people what they will
do and won't do, but he can't even talk.
I bet he looks like that Jamie Thompson.
You notice it's a trend on here. They
all look like stinking.
It's very, very boring, bro. You show
them money, you beat them at the money game,
and then they ask you to show the same
amount of money the week after. It is
boring, bro. It's just one of their
little It's just one of their little
self-p projection things that they do on
here, bro. It's cuz they're skint. They
want to see money because they don't
have no money. That's why they ask
people to show money is. It is boring.
It is boring, bro. If people want to
think that I'm living under poverty, so
be it. I don't give a [ __ ] They don't
know me. They don't know how much money
I have. They don't know anything.
We've seen what these people on here
look like. Fat and ugly.
Like think about it, Dusty. Yeah.
Actually, no. I was on it the other day
before I un from him. I I can actually
get the comment back up. Right. With
this loser. Yeah. Right.
Where was it actually?
No, no, I did see that comment. Sorry. It said,
where did it say?
B and L made sure the M will never step
foot again. repeating steps, putting a
casino in the UK again. His lack of
finances mean he will never be able to
enter a casino again. And he's like,
"You are winning, bro. Let the big nose
lose and continue to lose." And see what
I mean with this, bro. Yeah, I could
easily go into a casino. I could find a
casino to go into, gamble 200, win or
lose, show me winning. But I don't need
to prove myself to these people. I don't
need to prove myself to these fat, ugly
people that don't show their faces cuz
they're ugly. Do you understand that?
like no one needs to prove themselves to these people.
And that's what it is. And that's that's
what uh they don't know what money
people have. They don't know what money
people don't have.
So, I don't know why they keep talking
like they know people's lives. It's insane.
It is weird. They're just fat, ugly
people that's got nothing better to do.
And it's like that Joseph Ferrar. He's
no different. He's another little low life
and that's that, bro. So, they're all
just fat, ugly low lives.
That's what they are.
They hate that you're younger than them,
you're better looking than them, you got
freedom unlike them.
That's what it is with these people, bro. No,
it's fat ugly people in it.
I can do what I want when I want to when
I want, you know. Yeah,
the savings is going all right. Steven Howard, captain. Yeah,
I had spaghetti bolognese today. Ly cooked me.
But there's no point getting wound up at
these people cuz they'll never meet
anyone. Never ever meet anyone.
Um, and that's that. So, they're not even worth
up about, man.
They don't know you. They don't know.
Yeah. Basically that's that
this nons legs tried coming in earlier
and blocked the [ __ ]
Like it's almost 2026. When are we going
to start meeting each other?
It's it's time we start meeting each
other. You know you know
what did you tell me, bro?
Yeah, I'm definitely doing this Thailand
thing though, Stephen Howard. I'm
definitely definitely doing it
cuz I shouldn't have to be trying to get
in this country. So that's that's that's that. But um
these women are clearly racist. Um and
that's that in it. So I'd rather just leave. Yeah.
They're they're fantasist on here as
well. Do you know this indigo? Yeah, he
said £1,800 is bum change. Isn't it mad
how they all talk like they're
millionaires on here, bro? But in in
reality, they've got [ __ ] all. They've
got literally no money and they talk
like who who the [ __ ] says £1,800 is bum
change? Who would even say that, bro?
Unless they're a millionaire.
They're such fantasists on here as well.
That's another thing. It's not. That's
also a big thing on here is they they are fantasists.
They really really are fantasists. No,
no one says that, bro. They say that it
doesn't get you far in this day and age
or it might go quickly or but I'm change really.
Oh yeah, he'll [ __ ] start going to
Thailand. To be fair, he won't be able
to afford it. He's too skinn. So it
might take him 5 years to be able to
afford it. I think he's too skinned to
go to Thailand. But yeah, he copies my
holidays as well. Oh yeah, that's another thing.
He copies where I go. Copycat. Yeah.
You'll be [ __ ] going Thailand next.
To think there was days where you never
got these excuses.
You're too old for me. You're too young
To think there was days where it never
happened like years ago. It's mad.
I'm going to do a video on the dating
game uh later. Stephen Howard, I hope
you watch it. I've got a few things to talk about.
Okay with you, boss.
Okay with you, Captain.
Why did you get that [ __ ] um You get
this budgeting loan every week, Steven Howard.
Sorry, every year. You get this budget
aling loan every year.
You know the budget alone people get.
Bro, I tried to get it last year. They
were [ __ ] asking me a million and one
questions and then you have to pay the
thing back anyways. I don't think I'd
ever get it again to be fair. The amount
of [ __ ] [ __ ] that they ask you to get
[ __ ] 300 [ __ ] quid is [ __ ] mad.
Yeah, they ask you, bro. I remember last
it was like oh it was last year I forget
the month and I got it out and they
[ __ ] trying to get that money mate. Jesus Christ.
I was like I don't think it's [ __ ]
worth it is it?
Yeah. And it's so hard to get now. Like
I was like oh yeah my fridge broke down.
No we don't cover white goods. This was
a year ago. And like, oh, okay. Um,
you know, can I And then it's I had to
call them up like three different times
to get that money. And I'm thinking,
bro, you're paying the money back.
You're literally paying you are paying
the money back. They will get that money
back. And yeah, and I've been reading on
Facebook other people that's tried to
get it and they've only been offered
like a 100,200 pound or they've been
declined. [ __ ] that.
It reminds me about the casinos trying
to get your money.
The only way you won't have problems
getting your money is if you just save
your own [ __ ] money.
Have you seen that dusty that [ __ ]
budgeting loan trying to get it out
nowadays? I had troubles [ __ ] last
year getting it out.
[ __ ] a [ __ ] trying to get it out, mate.
There's a gun.
>> Virgin. Who's this?
>> You're a virgin, >> huh?
>> You're a virgin.
>> I'm a virgin.
>> Show Show me some money.
No, bro. I'm a skin virgin. I can't >> say.
>> Yeah, I'm a virgin. Even though I put a
porno out there. Yeah, I'm a virgin.
>> Sat with your mom in bed at home doing nothing.
>> Brother, I proved I've had sex. How are
you calling me a virgin?
>> Day every day doing nothing.
>> Is that what you're doing right now?
Being a keyboard warrior doing nothing. >> Loser.
>> In your little cancel house.
>> You [ __ ] loser.
>> Are you the one in your little cancel
house giving it the big end behind the keyboard?
>> Yes, mate. Yes.
Yeah. So, shut the [ __ ] up then, you little [ __ ] >> House.
>> You little [ __ ] That's what I thought. >> Yeah.
>> Let me I've got a question. I've got a
question. How can I be a virgin when I
put a porno out there? Just Just curious.
>> You had a prostitute sucky little
>> No, no, no, no, no, no, no. You've just
said that I'm a virgin.
>> You are.
>> But how can I be a virgin if I would
have had sex?
>> Putting your 3 in [ __ ] absolute [ __ ]
>> in a prostitute.
>> Do you not think that maybe you're the
virgin? You threw up is not having sex.
>> Right. Do you think that maybe you're the virgin?
>> Of course I am. Yeah.
>> Well, you clearly are. Cuz I mean, if
someone's proved they've had sex and
you're still calling them a virgin,
what's going on, mate? Seriously?
>> Of course I am. Of course I am.
>> What? No, but seriously. Seriously.
What's going on, bro?
>> Seriously. Seriously. What's going on? You are
>> It doesn't make any sense how you can
call someone a virgin when they prove
they've had sex. Do you not realize how
stupid that sounds?
Oh, he left. What a [ __ ] bro. I'm
just curious, bro. I don't really care.
I'm just asking you, how can someone be
a virgin if they've actually physically
proved they've had sex?
Then he's left. Why is he left? What the [ __ ]
These people on here really are
disabled, in it, bro. I swear, bro.
[ __ ] bro. I swear they're disabled on
this community. It really are disabled.
really really really are disabled on here. [ __ ] hell.
What are you doing? You're being a keyboard warrior.
They're idiots on here, bro.
[ __ ] $1,800 bum change. What a [ __ ] idiot.
These people are [ __ ] idiots, lad.
Idiots. Idiots on this community. Yeah.
What day is the 26th? I bet it's a
Friday, isn't it?
I bet you it's a Friday
when that horror film comes out. It's
normally Fridays. It comes out of it.
Yeah. I have some popcorn now. Oh, I
just I had a cup of C.
Cup of C. Cup of C. Cup of C. So, yeah,
that um it's very hard before I was
interrupted to get that [ __ ] loan out nowadays,
even though you pay the [ __ ] thing back.
Rides with the casino trying to get your
[ __ ] money when you want. Yeah.
They ask you, "What do you need it for?"
And then we can only over there and
[ __ ] you know what I mean? It's like
it's as if you don't pay the [ __ ]
thing back. It's not like it's not like
you don't pay it back, bro. You know
what I mean?
Yeah. At least if you save your own
money, that can't happen in it.
No. No. I don't think I have biscuits. [Music]
What do you think of that Joseph Frost
even? He's a [ __ ] idiot.
He's a [ __ ] idiot. He's another nod legs.
You do nothing.
Yeah. He can't even talk on a [ __ ] panel
and he can't even tell people where he
lives. But you do nothing. He says
do nothing. I love that.
I absolutely love that, bro.
Oh, I need to get a haircut, you know. Yeah.
I need to get a [ __ ] haircut for um
New Year's Eve.
I haven't subbed. It's just [ __ ]
It's [ __ ] That channel is [ __ ]
Some of the same [ __ ] people on it. [ __ ] lad.
Same people doing the same [ __ ] I like chicken licking.
You're nothing but a stinking [ __ ]
copycat with no mind of your own. Where's Greasy?
You're nothing but stinking copycat with
no mind of your own.
Absolutely no mind of your own.
I've not had this popcorn before. It's
M&S popcorn, so it should be good.
Yeah, salted. I don't like the sweet one.
We one is [ __ ] stinking. [Applause]
>> I love popcorn though.
Can't beat popcorn and coke at the
cinema. That's me.
So stupid how Yeah.
So that woman that said was using
distance as an excuse to 45year-old,
you said that if she lived in London,
she still wouldn't get with me, is it?
Steven Howard, that's what you said, is it?
Yeah, they wouldn't get with you, bro.
They'd use another excuse. They'd say
you're too young for them.
They've always got their own little excuses.
No way, bro. No way.
Do you remember Dusty the excuse? I
can't get with you because you're not Muslim.
Oh, [ __ ] me.
Okay, I'll convert to Muslim then.
[ __ ] madness. They're so full of [ __ ] in it. It's unbelievable.
They're so full of [ __ ] bro. It's unbelievable. Flames.
I'm so surprised she didn't say I was
too young for her.
My funny enough, my friend messaged me
um I think it was the day before
yesterday and he says uh have you tried
older women? Have you tried getting with
a 45y old? I said uh well I've got a
little story for you. Um and I messaged
him it and he never replied back. I
said, I've got a story of them kind of people.
You're just you're just you've just
basically failed from the start with
that one because they're just going to
use your age as an excuse.
So, if you go for older women, that's
literally all that they're going to do.
Yeah, that's exactly what would happen. Go through.
I haven't I haven't heard distance as an
excuse for a long time, though.
Why that one for? No. Yeah,
they've always got excuses, bro.
They've always got excuses.
I had one before saying she wouldn't get
with me because I wasn't jabbed during the co.
Oh, I remember that before actually.
Yeah, it was when the co was going on
cuz I wasn't jabbed. Um, you know when
you got the jab? I got the jab. I don't
know if you got the jab. And she's like,
"Oh, well, I didn't get the jab. I think
at that point I didn't get it. Sorry."
So, she said because I didn't get the
jab. Um, that's why she couldn't. Uh,
oh, hey, Dusty. Do you know what I was
thinking about last night, bro? I was
thinking of that O'Neals, bro. Oh, I
missed that O'Neal's bro, so badly.
I used to go there two times a week.
That lovely O'Neal's.
That lovely O'Neal's bro in Water
Street. I was thinking about it a lot.
I miss that place, bro.
That place I do miss it, man.
That's why I met all the army lads.
I miss that O'Neal's. Um,
no, it was good. It was good, bro. I
used to go there Thursday, Saturday. I
always used to gamble and then go there.
I do miss that place a lot, bro.
I miss that place a lot, man.
I reckon I'd be out every week. If I
could go there again, I would be. But
I'll never be able to go back in there, Dusty,
cuz the bounces and the staff, they
never change. I would literally have to
go there at like 5:00 p.m. and stay in
the toilet. That's the only slim chance
I'd have of being able to go back in there. Um,
yeah, I used to love that place, bro.
Love that place. Just see, you know, win
the 50 notes, then go there. But that
was my place, bro.
It was a good place. I like that.
You've been there, ain't it, Dusty?
Always used to go there. Just love it, bro.
Yeah, it's a good place.
It's better than Waxies.
Waxies maybe Waxies may be a close second.
Yeah, wax is maybe a th seconds, but
that was a go, bro. That was a go.
You had three I had [ __ ] free as well.
Well, I always used to get the Americans
there, bro. I used to get them years ago.
Yeah, it's a good place where I can't
wear disguises, you silly goose. They
know me, mate. Everyone knows me.
They know exactly who I am.
The staff will never change that either.
The staff, there's a bouncer. He's got a
vendetta against me. He knows exactly
who I am, bro. They know exactly who I am.
The manager knows me. And there's one
bouncer. The other bouncers probably
won't say nothing, but there's one. He's
a [ __ ] bro. He's a proper [ __ ]
He knows exactly who I am.
And it's clear he doesn't like me, bro.
Even from the start. I remember before, bro. Yeah.
The manager was like, "You can't come in
for 3 months, Dusty. Don't
Don't come in for 3 months. Don't come
in for 3 months." I thought I'd try my
luck. Yeah. Um I thought I'd try my
luck. And I was hiding in the toilet.
In, out, in, out, in out. And the other
bouncers saw me, bro. They didn't say
nothing. And then as I was coming out
the toilet, he walked in and the [ __ ]
[ __ ] walked me out, bro. He's a bastard.
Absolute [ __ ] He was. No one else said
anything. No one else said anything, bro. Yeah.
Um, so it' be very hard to and I
wouldn't enjoy it because I'd have to
keep thinking, what if I get caught and
then, you know what I mean? So
they ban you for stupid reasons. Um,
you know, that's another thing with this
country. The country is just [ __ ] up.
They ban you for stupid reasons
as well. That's
the most stupidest stupidest reason they
ban you for.
But yeah, I did like O'Neal as well.
What about 5 years? You reckon I'll be a
What about What if I go into a casino now, Dusty?
What do you reckon would happen?
You might get in, but
the problem is is if you win money and
trying to get the money,
that's the problem is trying to get the
money from the places. [Applause]
You'll be [ __ ] No. No, you don't.
If you you can do it if you kept
winning. You can do it.
You can do it if um
if you keep doing a cash out machine
if you keep going on the cash out
machine. You can do it, but it's not worth it.
Nah, it's not worth it. You can do You
can do on the cash out machine, but
sometimes they're out of order and they
do it on purpose and then they could
void your ticket and Yeah. It's just all a scam.
So, you'll be [ __ ] then. Yeah.
Just like when I won that four grand. I
literally just unbanned myself like two
weeks before and then they gave me the
four grand in cash. It was [ __ ] lovely.
That was a Wednesday. I'll never forget
it. It's when I went out with one of my
army friends. He's do you want to come
out drinking? I said,
"Should I?" Okay. Then I went casino
before going home.
You're good, man.
Four grand for 150. So yeah,
the only way is online now, is it Dusty? only way.
>> I got
>> What the bloody hell do you want?
>> I've got a bone to pick with you.
>> You've got a bone to pick with me? >> Yes.
>> Okay. What's up?
>> Number one, where's [ __ ] to?
>> I don't know. He's probably just sick of this community.
>> And number two, why in the life of life
are you still crying about [ __ ] that
you can't get?
>> See you later, Rice.
See you later. Yeah, nice H M.
Will this Virgin ever stop?
Jesus Christ. Will this Virgin ever
stop? Steen Alwood lad you know
just self projection.
Should we read this?
This is self bro. This guy's self projecting again.
All right, bro.
This guy's self projecting again, bro.
All right, juvenile. This guy self
projecting again, brother.
He's self projecting.
Love the ugly latest flex. He's ugly.
Um, I have family unlike these Christmas
projectors. He's in his mom's spare
room. You're in a cancel bed [ __ ] with a
disabled girl that you don't [ __ ]
You're in a shitty little bed sit that
don't even have a spare room, you
[ __ ] [ __ ] Um, that makes it sound
like Yeah, that self projection, bro.
Everything that he writes is just
basically about himself.
>> Everything that they write is just about
their own lives.
That's what they do on there, lad.
You know how weird they are? Stupid. Do
you know how weird and disabled they are? Yeah.
Is that they will message each other
about me? Like one will be out and they
will message one other person about me.
They'll message each other, lad, because
they ain't got a life. This is what I
mean. Hey bro, you know that red star? He messages
people about me when they're out. You know that.
That's how you know these autistic
weirdos ain't got a life. They ain't got
nothing in their life. But being
obsessed every day will never meet
anyone. Will never ever say anything to
anyone's face. They'll just keep doing
this until they die. They will they will
die on here. These people, bro. They
will they will [ __ ] die on here.
They will die on here, bro. These people
they email each they email me message
each other and stuff. Did you know that, lad?
Oh, look. One second.
Passport surrendered. Can't leave the
country yet. The rest of us. Passport surrendered.
My passport surrendered.
One second. My passport surrendered.
I got my passport right here. You [ __ ]
Self projecting again. Got my passport right here.
M definitely definitely definitely not.
My passport's right here and I've got my
old passport there. Nope. My passport's
not surrendered. See what I mean with
these people, bro? They're [ __ ]
idiots. They talk so much about people
that they don't know anything about.
It's not It's not naive to think that
these people are going to about their
own lives. Bro,
can't leave the country. No, I can leave
the country whenever I want.
And I will be doing in a couple of months. Nope.
Yep. Apparently I got a passport. These
people really are idiots on here, bro.
Here, Stephen. They really are bong guys on here.
I just got my passport out. see an hour for you.
I can leave the country whenever I want.
I can do what I want when I want.
And this indigo is a little [ __ ]
[ __ ] as well.
I'll be telling that I'll be telling him
that when he comes back on there
is falling apart. No, no, no. Your lives
are falling apart.
Think of it, Steven. How long have these
people been doing this [ __ ] now on this YouTube?
No, no, no. That's your lives that are falling apart.
No, that's your lives. You don't know
anything about anyone else's life. I
just showed you I just showed my passport.
You just said my passport got
surrendered. My passport's right there.
What are you talking about, you [ __ ] clown?
Indigo, you little [ __ ] What are you
on about, bro? My passport's right there.
My life ain't falling apart, bro. I've
got plans. I'm doing stuff. Nope. My
life's completely fine. My life is
completely completely completely fine.
These people on here really need to get a lifelastics
next year as well.
My life is definitely definitely
definitely not falling apart. I'm
completely stable. I can do what?
Because I'm not out drinking every week.
What the [ __ ] bro?
My life's completely fine. I'm not the
one on the internet, right?
Having to try and wind people up every day.
Am I Steven Howard? Think about it, bro.
I'm not on here for eight years having
to try to wind people up every day.
Think about it.
Think about who who's whose lives are
the ones that really fell apart.
I'm not the one in here hating and
winding trying to wind people up that I don't know.
So they're [ __ ] idiot. Okay.
You see my passport? I thought I'd just
show it to you cuz it's on the side. Bro,
you want me to go to Newcastle and
embarrass this [ __ ]
Cuz if you want me to do it, Stephen, I
would right. I don't mind traveling to
the Northeast again, bro.
And embarrassing this little Joseph for
our little nonsubber. If you want me to
do it, bro, I don't mind doing it.
Doing it again.
calling him the nons lover that he is
and keeps screaming how he'll do
nothing. I really really don't mind. I
mean, well, I really don't mind, bro. If
you want me to do it, I don't mind.
You know, get a video out of it, you know?
I really really like my bike.
My life ain't falling apart. I'm not the
one on the internet trying to wipe
people up every day. That's not my life,
bro. I'm more than stable.
I can leave the country whenever I want.
I've got two passports. An old passport
and a new passport. Nope.
That's definitely definitely not my
life. And you know this indigo is a
little [ __ ] as well, bro. Look, we was
talking about a phone. Yeah. This is how
you know he's a little [ __ ]
because this is how you know he's a
little [ __ ] Because when I was on here
earlier talking about this £1,800 phone,
he said £1,800 is bum chains. Okay.
Okay, bro. If £1,800 is bum chains and
you got all this money, why are you sat
on the internet every day? I've not been
on for two days. This is my first time
on in two days. If you got all this
money, bro, [ __ ] being a millionaire.
Whatever. Yeah. If you've got all of
this money, if you have got all of this
money, right? So, if you have got all of this money,
then why are you on here every day?
Is that not a good question, Stephen
Howard? If they've got all of this
money, bro, and £1,800 is bum change. I
wish I was in a position to say £1,800
is bum change. Why are you on here every day?
Because they're idiots, bro. They're
fantasists. They're morons. That's why.
That's literally all they are. They're
just absolute idiots.
£1,800 bum chains, brother. You've never
seen 1,800 pound in your [ __ ] life.
Never in your life have you seen 1,800 pound, bro.
You got all of this money. Think about
it. If they've got all of this money,
why are they sat on here every day
trying to wind people up? Think about
it, bro. Ask yourself this question.
Yeah, that's what I was saying about
we're talking about contracts. Yeah.
And I said I'd never pay £1,800 for a
phone. I'd pay £200 a month for a year
like I get a contract, but I wouldn't
pay that much. And then he said, "£1,800
is bum change."
£1,800. If £1,800 is bum change, bro,
why are you on here every day trying to
wind people up? Is that a good question
or not, Steven Howard? I'm just
wondering, bro. It doesn't wind me up.
I'm just I'm just wondering why you do
it. If you've got all of this money, cuz
you must have some currency.
You must have some currency to be saying
that £1,800 is bum change.
Right. So, if you've got all of this
money, why are you sat on it every day,
bro? I'm not I'm not on it every day. I
wasn't on it two days. So, why? See,
they're [ __ ] idiots.
It's not bomb for you. You ain't got no
life, bro. Listen, you little [ __ ]
My passport's right here. I can leave
the country whenever I want.
Yeah, I can leave the country whenever I
want. I've got two passports. Try again.
You don't know anything about me, bro.
And guess what? Here's another thing,
right? Here's another thing, right? The
only person's life that has fell apart
is yourself, not my life. You're the one
that's been on here for years. You're
the one that's been on here for years
trying to wind people up. That only
shows you, bro, not me. You're the only
one's life that's fell apart. Not my
life. I can do what I want when I want.
You know, you don't know me, bro. Look,
you got the passport thing wrong, you
[ __ ] clown. Yeah, you've never even
seen £1,800 in your life. Yeah, there
you go. You just been shown a passport.
Apparently, my passport got surrendered.
Yeah, that's never happened
again. If you got all this money
Yeah, of course you do, bro. If you had
all of these things, you wouldn't be on
here, you little [ __ ]
Yeah, you wouldn't be on here, you
little [ __ ] Shut up. You've never seen
1,800 pound in your life and you don't
have 1,800 pound now. You don't have no
girlfriend. You ain't got no job. Shut
up, bro. You're on here every day. Shut
the [ __ ] up, you little [ __ ] The only
one's life that's fell apart is yourself,
Mong. And I can actually take a day off
of YouTube. You can't. Two days I ain't
been on YouTube. You've been on it every
day. You little [ __ ] [ __ ]
You little [ __ ] [ __ ] Stop talking
about people that you don't know. You
little [ __ ] [ __ ] fantasist.
Yeah. £1,800 a week. Yeah. Yeah. £1,800
a week. Yeah. More like 80 pound a week.
[ __ ] idiot. [ __ ]
Absolute [ __ ] [ __ ] They bro. That's
the only That's the only thing you can
say about these people that they're g.
Absolute fantasist. Idiots.
Moronic people. That's what they are.
That's really what they are. moronic fantasist.
I don't know what else you could
describe these idiots as, bro. They're
[ __ ] insane. They're mad. Simple.
Yeah. Will I really? No, I don't think so.
Because you don't have
I don't have 180. Okay, bro.
I can go out whenever I want. I've got
the money to go out and do what I want
when I want. So
why aren't you out? Why can't you take a
day off for YouTube?
Okay, same thing to you then. So why
don't you go out? Why can't you take a
day off of YouTube? Why have you been on
YouTube for years trying to wipe people up?
So the same thing goes to you then, bro.
If I don't want to go out and I want to
save money. That's not me. I've got
money. You don't know how much money I
have. You just said that I lost my
passport. No, sorry. You just said I had
to surrender my passport. Not me.
Definitely. Definitely not me. You're an
idiot, bro. Do you think you could
change the record next year? It's
getting very boring now.
It's getting very very boring now mate.
Do you reckon you could stop this [ __ ]
from next year bro? It's getting really
really boring now cuz I will be on
lavies. I will be on lavies
and on on the first of January. Do you
think you can just stop this [ __ ] now
and just get a life?
It's borrowing the [ __ ] tits off of
people now. It really is
[ __ ] £1,800 a week. absolute fantasies.
I can go out whenever I want.
I can go out whenever I want, however I want.
Just like when you tried saying before,
oh, I don't go out as much now because I
don't get as much money. Well, you don't
know how much money I have.
You don't know anything.
You don't know anything, bro.
That's what makes me laugh. It's
actually entertaining because you don't
know anything about anyone.
That's the thing with these people,
Steven Howard. They don't know anything about anyone.
That's why it is kind of entertaining, lad.
They really do not know anything about anyone.
That's why we just laugh at them.
They're the people to laugh at.
You know what I mean?
You don't know anything about anyone's life. [Applause] I mean,
but guess what, Indigo? You're going to
be alone Christmas. I'm not going to be
alone Christmas, but I bet you people
will be. I bet you people will be alone on Christmas. Yeah, your video
up to the clown. Crap. Oh man. Yeah.
You know when this
You go on this account, um, this
channel, Stephen Hen, and it's literally
the same people.
It's literally the same people, bro.
Who hasn't got a penny? Me? Who me?
Really, bro? Okay. You see the And it's
the same people. Wait,
it's literally the same people.
No, I never asked you to buy me a phone.
You said that £1,800 is nothing. So if
£1,800, you said it's bum chain. So if
£1,800 is bum chains, give me £1,800.
No normal person says £1,800 is bum
change. Only a fantasist like you. Cuz
that's what you people are. You're fantasists.
I'm talking like you're a millionaire,
but in reality you ain't even got a
[ __ ] pot to piss him, bro. Cuz you
kept saying that it's bum change. So I
said to you, if it's bum change, give me,00 pound,
bro. You know this account? Yeah.
Seaside [ __ ] has been made 10 years ago.
Same people. They ain't got a life. I've
se I've seen this account for years as
well. It's the same people. It's the
same people every day.
That's why I don't come on here much
anymore, bro. I won't be on there
tomorrow. It's just the same people
every day. Do the same [ __ ]
This change. Jesus Christ.
I think you need to stop taking drugs, man.
I think you need to stop taking [ __ ] drugs.
You need to stop taking drugs, mate.
Your [ __ ] fantasies fantasist. Absolute fantasist.
Nah, boy. You've never seen 1800 pound
in your life. Sad people.
Yeah, it's all self-reflected, bro.
Dusty, this guy was trying to say about
how my passport's been surrendered. My
passport's not been surrendered. That's
self projection, bro. What the [ __ ] I
got two passports. My old one and my
[ __ ] new one.
And you're trying to say my my life's
falling apart. What the [ __ ] You really are selfjecting?
If if £1,800 is no money to you, bro,
why are you on here every day without
any days off selfjecting? He's a
fantasist. He's an absolute fantasist.
Zero flights. Really, bro? That's self-reflecting,
bro. You're self-reflecting again.
That's what you're doing.
Anyways, are you going to get off of
YouTube next year, lad? Oh, what?
Are you going to get off of YouTube?
Are you going to be on here another year
doing the same [ __ ]
Let's make 2026 better. Come on.
Oh my god. You're boring, bro. You're
really boring. These people here are
really boring. Joseph Ferrar, Indigo,
they're just boring. You're all boring,
lad. Same people doing the same [ __ ]
Yeah, good for you. That doesn't wind
anyone up. You know what you're doing.
Yeah. On that Jo channel, it doesn't
wind anyone up. It just shows how
obsessed you are. That's why I don't
react to it because all you're doing is
just winding yourselves up. You're
making a fool of yourselves.
You know, I've got all of these
middle-aged people that's obsessed with
me. I don't care, bro. You're the one
showing yourselves up, you know? So,
like you always do. So, I don't really
give a [ __ ]
Same low life people that's been on here for years.
Some of these accounts, you've seen them
for years, Dusty. Seen them for [ __ ]
years. Like, seaside fugs been on here
years. They just shows they ain't got a
life. Some of these accounts were
created like 10 years ago.
They're all old fat ugly people, bro.
That's what they are.
Fat old ugly people. They ain't got
nothing in their lives. A minute.
Oh, you don't have a girlfriend, bro.
That's self projection.
The same reason you don't have a
girlfriend and you've never had a girlfriend.
So, anyways, what are we doing in 2026?
It's going to be the same [ __ ] for
another 10 years or what?
But I answered your question. I don't
have a girlfriend. The same reason you
don't have and you've never had a
girlfriend. That's self projection, bro.
We've been We've already been over this
a million times.
You people don't have a girlfriend. You
people don't have any money. You people
ain't got a life.
Yeah. You don't have a girlfriend. Why
are you self projection, bro? You should
know that in 10 years it's not made your
life any better doing this.
Come on, man. It's almost 2026. It's
boring now. Very boring. Yeah.
Yeah. Okay, bro.
Yeah, man. Of course you do.
I think you need to get a life, bro. I'm
coming off in a minute anyways. Oh, yeah. No. No.
Oh, this guy's a weirdo, man.
Are you still here? Um, Steven Howard,
I might be on tomorrow late at night
maybe cuz I'm going to do this video. So,
Yeah, I need to get some things off my
chest. Whenever I feel like I need to
get some things off my chest, I just do
a little video, bro. And yeah.
Yeah, they're idiots, bro.
They're just idiots on here, lad. That's
what they are.
Steven Howard, what do you think? Do you
think want is right? Same people every day.
Same repeating people.
Yeah, it was the same repeating people, bro.
They're so desperate to try to [ __ ]
They're so desperate to get a [ __ ]
reaction off of strangers. It's [ __ ]
sad. Even Joseph Fra, Dusty, he's
another sad [ __ ] Middleage people.
Yeah. Desperate to get [ __ ] attention off strangers, you know.
[ __ ] mental, mate. [ __ ] mental.
I've never seen anything like it.
What do you think of Joseph Raw, Dusty?
He's another [ __ ] Ly freak. Can he?
I don't know what to um title this video. Maybe um
we need to uh
say about I don't know um
we live in such a sexist biased world.
Yeah. Something like that.
I don't do videos very often. This savvy
guy does videos all the time, but I
don't do them. Only when I want to say
stuff on a video. Very rarely. Uh
the sexist and biased day and age that
we live in. Yeah.
Yeah. I want Grevy to watch it.
I'm going to tag Grievy in it. Yeah.
It's bad. It is bad. It is bad. It's
such a sexist world we live in. Sexist, biased.
And we're going to talk about how people
play stupid. Um when it's a woman doing
wrong, um they play dumb. Like you show
them evidence and then they just play dumb.
like they can't read or they don't understand English. So, yeah.
And the thing is, right, people say that
everyone has a type. Yeah. Um, Steven
Howard, but the problem with this is is
that they actually exclude themsel to that type.
like they actually exclude themsel to
to that type which is what the problem
is you know.
So yeah, they exclude themsel um to a type basically
people think this is normal lad. I really do.
you know. Yeah, you need to get a life.
You need to stop trying to [ __ ] wind
up people on the internet that you don't
know, you little low life.
Yeah, you need to get a life, you sab
bastard. You s little fantasist.
Yeah, same same to you, bro. You need to
take a day off of YouTube. Never mind a
life. You need to take a day off of
YouTube. Uh, you sad bastard.
You sad [ __ ]
Yeah, you need to get a life.
Same to you.
Same to you, bro. You need to get a life.
Talk about taking a day off for YouTube.
Might do you good. Might do you the
world of good,
you know. I'll give it another 10
minutes. Wait for Grievy. If you're not
coming, I'm off. Oh yeah.
All right, Grey,
I've got a bone to pick with you, Grezy.
I'm not very happy
about what's happened on this Instagram,
the double standards again. I'm not very happy, Grezy.
I'm not happy, lad. You know,
make myself a cup of [ __ ]
I'm not happy, Grezy. Oh god,
I'm not happy.
Can I tell you what happened?
Can I tell you what happened, Captain? Oh gosh.
Yeah, but you don't even know what happened.
You don't even know what happened,
you know. You
can see his shoulder again.
I'm going to do a little video. Greavvesy,
are you going to watch it? My little video. Greavves.
Are you going to watch my little video? [Laughter]
If you like my little video.
>> The virgin one.
O. Steven Howard.
Steven Howard. He's the virgin one. Not
that one. The virgin one.
There's two people with that [ __ ]
name on here, lad.
It's not that one. We're not talking
about that one. We're talking about the virgin one.
The one that's never been laid.
The one who's going to die a virgin. Virgin Mary. Oh,
now I'm going to do a little video
bone to pick me. You mean s
Indigo, I think you need to get late.
You and the Virgin need to take a day
off YouTube and get
you die a virgin.
You know, you going to die that virgin.
Die virgin. Like a virgin. die a virgin.
And trust me, mate, you don't want to
[ __ ] die a virgin like him. Like that
virgin [ __ ] from Kent. You want to be
like that Kent [ __ ] Still a virgin in
your 30s. Never had sex. Going to die a virgin.
Seriously, mate. Come on.
Anyways, I'm going to I'm off now. I'm
going to do this video.
send it to a couple of people
and see what they uh see what they think of it. Yeah.
And I won't be on here probably for a
couple days. Who knows?
It's just the same atmosphere.
It's just the same atmosphere when Steven Howard
the same people. The same repeating
I'm off anyways. Yeah, I'll see you whenever. Bye.
Love you. Slay.