Yeah,
just checking to see if you little
idiots are still in YouTube.
You know, a little welfare check
cuz uh [ __ ] it, why not? Yeah.
Yeah. So, I just wanted to see if it's
still the same people in YouTube
just like I'll be looking on the first of um uh January.
Just checking a little while longer.
I don't know how people can be on this
[ __ ] every day.
It's [ __ ] boring, man. It's literally
the same repeating people. I'm like just
about to go to sleep, bro.
So, I thought [ __ ] it. I just want
for a we bit, you
talking to someone, bro.
>> Yeah, I will, man. I don't really come
on here much um nowadays
cuz it's just the same [ __ ] bro. You
don't you hardly catch me on it. I'm
just about to fall asleep. I thought,
"Fuck it. I'm a bit bored, bro. Yeah, pretty much.
Yeah, I will be as well, bro. I will be
as well. Doing some videos.
[ __ ] went out. I had to do some [ __ ]
I had to do some stuff, bro.
Yeah, I went out. I saw some women, bro.
They all look so stuck up their own ass, Cory. Man,
they all look stuck up their own ass.
Madness. It bothers me, bro. It bothers
me. I don't even like [ __ ] being in
[ __ ] public nowadays, bro. But I had
to go out and do something. But yeah, I
don't even like being out in public now,
bro. It's just boring.
They bore me, bro. Yeah.
No, they're not cool.
Cory, I've got a story about an older one, bro.
Everyone's already heard it, but you
haven't. No, they're not cool, bro.
They're the same as well. I was speaking
to a 45year-old last week. Everyone's
heard it, but you they're not [ __ ]
cool, bro. They're the same.
A fresh start
with with what, bro? It's always going
to be the same here.
A fresh start with what? It's going to
be the same
every year. It's been the same every
year for the past [ __ ] six years,
bro. And next year is not going to be any different.
So that's that, bro. It will always be
the same here.
So that's that, lad.
So yeah. No, it will always be the same here.
Depressing waiting around for
everything. Stuck up women, [ __ ]
It would always be the same here.
January, February, March, April, May,
June, July, August, September, October,
November, December. Every year, every
month will always be the same.
Yeah, cuz my sleeping patterns [ __ ] So that's why Yeah.
We had to do something there.
It'll always be the same here, Cory. Always.
You know that. I know that. So,
they go out last week. Won't be going
out this week. Would I go? Was it last
week going out?
Use the last week of the week before. I
can't keep up.
I won't be out this week either. Yeah,
I'll be out New Year's only because I've
got plans and I don't want to go but
then I have to. So [ __ ] in it really
bores me, bro. Absolutely bors me. Yeah.
Don't know why you think January is
going to be any different. I don't know
why you think next year is going to be any different.
You have hope. Well,
good luck to you, bro. I know there's no
hope for me, but that's that.
Yeah, I was in a in a bad mood today,
bro. I felt like gambling, but I never
[ __ ] that. It's always a cycle when
you're in this country. It's always a
cycle. It never changes.
This is why you need to leave. Like,
people like me need to leave. I didn't
gamble. I was going to, but whatever.
Bro, this is the same cycle, bro.
He is dead.
Uh, next year, bro. Probably like March.
This is depressing, bro. This This
country is so depressing.
[ __ ] I hate this country, bro. I hate
the people. I hate the women. I hate
like bro the thing is there's no point
me going out now uh Cory cuz if I go out
I'm just going to approach someone to
ruin their life.
Like that's that's how you get in the
end with these people, right? You don't understand.
No, but let me tell you something, bro.
If this guy I was saying this to my mom
yesterday after the new year, if this
guy comes on here again and he tries to
tell me that I'll do nothing, I'm just
going to go to Newcastle the same day. I
don't give a [ __ ] If this guy wants to
chat [ __ ] I told my mom about this
yesterday one more time and try and tell
me I'll do nothing. I'm just going
Newcastle same day. Simple
because I've had enough of that fat [ __ ]
as well, you know? And I don't mind
going up north again. So, bro, like if
he if he really wants to go there, we'll
do it again.
Like, and I was saying this yesterday as
well, bro. Like, this [ __ ] was getting
on my nerves. And I'll kill two birds
with one stone. Honestly, I don't mind.
I'll kill two birds with one stone,
so it's not a problem.
Don't try and tell me I'll do nothing,
mate. When you're too scared to [ __ ]
talk on the panel, you little [ __ ]
You know what I mean? And that's what it
is with these people in this community,
Cory. They annoy you, but you can't get
your hands on them. They annoy you, bro,
cuz they're little weasels, but you
can't get your [ __ ] hands on them.
So yeah, if he comes on talking [ __ ]
when he comes back, I'm just going to go
to Newcastle and show the [ __ ] up for
what he is and kill two birds with one
stone. I don't really give a [ __ ] bro.
Like, I really just couldn't care less.
And that's it.
No more being a keyboard warrior. You
know what I mean? That's that. So, yeah. Yeah,
that's that, bro.
I had a spoon's breakfast.
I'm just not in a mood, bro. I'm in a
bad mood, bro. Like a a file mood. A
file mood, bro. It's not even a joke. I
wish I could laugh at it.
like a really nasty stinking mood, bro.
I'm not even joking.
That's what this country get you like,
bro. Why don't [ __ ] go out anymore? I
went out to furthest I've been out in
ages, bro. It's [ __ ] annoying.
Nope. I just, bro, you know I don't
gamble. So why are you asking questions
that you already know the answer to? I
literally told you I felt like gambling
today and I never Why would I do my
balls in, bro? What is it with you
people always thinking that when
someone's in a bad mood they've gambled
but if I gambled you would know about it?
Why do you say that when I continuously
say that I do not gamble
like that and if I have an urge rarely I
would I won't do it. So why do you ask
things bro? I seriously don't understand.
I really really really don't. That's self projection.
Bye-bye. But yeah, bro.
Yeah, that's bomb self projection, bro.
Uh, we don't want it on our channel. So,
yeah, bro. Like, I told you like over
and over and over. How many days is it
to Christmas? Ah, that explains it.
Yeah, it's six days to Christmas.
Yeah, it's six days to Christmas, people. Yeah.
I wonder why.
I wonder why, bro. It's six days to
Christmas. So, yeah. Anyways, bro,
listen. Uh, I told you what where's my
Christmas spirit? I don't give a [ __ ]
about Christmas, bro. I don't care about Christmas.
Simple. I don't care about [ __ ]
Christmas. I don't give a [ __ ] about
birthdays. I don't give a [ __ ] about
anything, bro. The only thing I give a
[ __ ] about is leaving this shitty country.
And that's that. I don't give a [ __ ]
about Christmas, bro. So yeah,
but anyways, um
what I was saying is Yeah. So why you
ask me if I've done my balls in when
I've literally told you I don't gamble, bro? Like
I've literally told you this, bro. And
you know, and you and then you ask me if
I've done my balls in. Why, bro? I've
literally told you that I don't gamble.
Does it like does it go in one ear and
out the other?
I literally told you that I don't gamble like that.
You asked me if I got my [ __ ] balls in. Serious. Nah.
Nah, bro. You just need to look at your
life and think, "What the [ __ ] bro?
That's all you need to do, bro. You need
to look at your life and think, why are
you still sexless? Why you still single?"
And by you, I mean me. Yeah, it's quite
depressing, bro, when you think about
it. Especially when there's no reason
for it. So yeah,
it's pretty depressing, isn't it? Really?
Really? At 28 years of age, it is pretty
like we're going into another year with
this [ __ ] Like we're going we're going
we're going into another year with this
[ __ ] bro. Another year of this
[ __ ] Really? No. [ __ ] that. Not
another year of this [ __ ] Not
another year of this. I'm out of here,
bro. March the latest.
[ __ ] that, bro. Not another year of this
This is Yeah, but bro, when did I last
do my balls in? What? Years ago? What?
About 10 years ago?
[ __ ] bro. What? Like 10 years ago, bro?
I haven't even gambled. Why? Why do you
If I gambled, I would tell you that I gambled.
And that's that, bro. Like,
it's just a [ __ ] life, bro. It like
that's it, is it? Yeah.
But yeah, that's self projection. Uh,
that comment. So, we don't reply to self-projecting idiots.
That's just self- projection. They do it
every every year around December time.
Um, so yeah.
Yeah. They ain't got a life, bro.
Because they ain't got a life. They They
ain't got a life, bro. It will always be
the same. It will be the same on the 1st
of January as well. They ain't got a
life on here. Do you not understand?
Monty will tell you better, bro. They're
fat, ugly people that ain't got nothing.
No life, no money, no friends, nothing.
They have got nothing.
That's why they do this, bro. They have
got nothing in their life. You tell me,
bro, people that are listen, bro, I'm
I'm talk to you on a level. Yeah. You
tell me normal people that have got a
life that comes on here for 8 years
hating on strangers that they don't
know. You tell me any people like that
that's got a life. None of them have got
That's why I don't entertain any of them.
They ain't got a lie. They don't know
me. They don't know anything about like
the ins and outs and what people have
and what people don't have, bro. So, it's
Yeah, they don't. And they've been doing
it for years as well, bro. They've been
doing it for years and they don't know
the people that they're [ __ ] doing
this to as well, bro. They're [ __ ] weird.
They're just fat, ugly people that ain't
got a life. Bro, I haven't done my balls
and I haven't even gambled. I went for
breakfast earlier and my sleeping
pattern's a bit [ __ ] up. Bro, we don't
need to do our balls in to tell the
truth about these people in this community.
Beside that, Joseph Far. Isn't this guy
supposed to be 38
and he's and he's doing this [ __ ] He
needs attention from men on the internet.
He needs attention from men on the internet.
Think about that. Attention from [ __ ]
men on the internet. Sad it really sad.
[ __ ] very very sad. Sad people, bro.
Sad stalkers and also stalkers as well. Yep.
That's what they are, bro.
He will never get off. He's another life
loser. Another one that's been doing
this for years. He's another life loser.
Yeah. Another one, bro. Nah, never.
Stop asking questions you already know
the answer to.
That's my little catchphrase. If anyone
says that, they're stealing it off me, bro. Yeah.
Nah, he will never sort his life out.
These people's lives are over. You don't
understand, Triple H. These people in
their late 30s, 40s, it's over for them.
They've got no hope.
That's why they just rather just hate on
people that they don't know every day.
It's because they're fat, ugly, skinn
people. They ain't got a life.
I haven't seen you in ages. Thought you
would have found someone. Really?
more. How would have I found someone?
Bro, what do you think that I might have
went in the shopping mall and someone
stopped pretending they had a boyfriend
or somebody gave me their number and
they stopped leading me on, you know,
the first time in 6 years. Really? I
mean, you may as well as me if I won the
[ __ ] lottery, to be honest with you,
bro. You might as well have asked me if
I won the bloody lottery.
What is Was was it supposed to suddenly change?
Well, I don't follow, bro.
No, I haven't I haven't been out because
I already know the result. No, I don't
even try, bro, cuz I already know the result.
But if I was to, that is what would
happen. And you know it would happen as
well. You know it and I know it. So,
it's not suddenly going to change.
No, definitely definitely not going to change.
So that's that.
Yeah, I don't give a [ __ ] bro, whether
I'm good-look or not, to be honest.
Reddit was giving terrible advice again.
Um, yeah, Reddit was giving terrible
advice again, Dusty.
Bad, is it? It is bad, bro. [ __ ] They
all say the same thing.
They'll be telling you the same [ __ ]
when you're a 70 year old man. They all
say the same [ __ ] on there, Dusty. Uh,
they just say the same thing. But no,
I'm not going out, bro. Uh,
it wouldn't be healthy for me to go out,
bro. Trust me. Yeah.
Oh god, bro. [ __ ] up. Going to sleep
in a bit.
New Year's Eve and that's only cuz I
planned and if I don't go out, I'll
never hear the last of it. If I didn't
have anything planned, probably never
again to be honest.
I'm just going to book Thailand next
month and leave. [ __ ] this. I'm not
having another year of this [ __ ]
mate. I'm 28 years of age. I'm not 25
anymore. I'm not 24 anymore, mate. You
know, this is [ __ ] this is ridiculous.
This is absolutely [ __ ] ridiculous, bro.
I was getting like mood swings on the
train as well. I was on the train
getting mood swings.
I just wanted someone to start, bro,
today. Any excuse, I would have punched
him through that glass, bro. I'm not
even joking. I'm not in a mood, bro.
Seriously. Seriously, seriously not in a [ __ ] mood. So yeah.
So yeah, if I go out now and I meet
someone, which I won't go out, I'll just
try and ruin their life. I'll just [ __ ] them over.
So you you wouldn't want to see Peter
Bell out, brother. You We get We grow
tired of this [ __ ] bro. We grow really
really tired of this [ __ ]
We really really grow tired of this [ __ ]
So that's that, bro. So yeah, New Year's
Eve. If it weren't for that, I wouldn't
probably wouldn't go out again.
Nah, I'll just leave. I'll just book
thingy next month and leave, bro. End of
funny story, right? Uh
Adman's girlfriend, Thai girlfriend, um
saw a photo of me and she was like, "Oh,
he's handsome." Adman obviously told her
the story, "Oh, yeah, he can't get women
in his country." And she she wouldn't
believe it. She wouldn't believe it,
bro. She wouldn't believe it. She's
like, "Nah, he gets people." He was
like, "No, honestly, he had the same
struggles as me. A lot of people don't
believe it. No, a lot of people don't
My friends never used to believe me." So
I showed them like approaching videos
cuz that's how stuck up these [ __ ]
are in this country that normal people
can't fathom it.
You know what I mean, bro? It's [ __ ] Yeah.
When I try, bro, I can't get out of bed
for like 2 three days. It's depressing.
That's why I gave up, bro. Cuz it was
too It's too depressing.
Way way way too depressing, bro.
You go out, bro, you're [ __ ] for like
three days. Depressed. [ __ ] that, bro.
I'd rather not try. Be in a weird world.
At least you don't get depressed.
So, yeah. Way better when you give up. Way better.
Way better. I'm just in a bad mood
today. I wasn't in a bad mood yesterday. So, yeah.
I mean, I'm 28 years of age. I shouldn't
have to keep trying. I've tried more
than anyone. I shouldn't have to be
dealing with this [ __ ]
It's just a cycle, bro. And I And I was
in a bad mood. Yeah, I was in a bad mood
today. And I thought I was going to
gamble, but I didn't. And I never feel
like gambling, bro. I was just about to
go in that bookies and gamble, but I
never. This is a cycle, bro. We're still
doing the same thing. Or not. We're not
doing it cuz we broke the cycle. But you
can understand how the cycle could
escalate again. What the [ __ ]
You know what I mean, bro?
Yeah. She didn't believe me. December.
She didn't believe him that I couldn't find anyone.
A lot of people don't believe it.
But I think they're racist.
I do think these women are racist. I
think Ben Fur is right. I think they're
racist. That's what I think it is. Racism.
Um, I'm sick of their [ __ ] as well. I'm
sick of their [ __ ] I've had enough
of their [ __ ] to last me a [ __ ]
entire lifetime, bro,
and beyond. So,
uh, other thing was, um, the other thing
um, can't remember what I was saying now.
I can't remember. [ __ ] was I saying? Uh,
yeah, that's what And these I I still
can't get over this double standards,
Dusty. It's It's just graining in my
head, bro. The double standards.
A woman cries
cries and moans about men. Oh, give her
Oh, she gets sympathy.
She sympathy. Sympathy, bro. She gets
sympathy. But as soon as you speak the
truth from your experiences, oh, you're
an incel. Oh, you're an insult. I was
telling I was talking to Izzy's
boyfriend about this yesterday. I was
like, I'm right and you know it. And sec
and secondly, right, you don't know
about Izzy about stalking. You don't
know what your ex done. Yeah. Before you
start coming on my phone. Yeah. I'd tell
him, "Listen, your ex was the one that
was playing [ __ ] games, so don't talk
like you [ __ ] know everything, bro."
And he doesn't It's like they're they're
so ignorant and in denial. Like they
they they don't
they're so ignorant. Like it's they they generally
It's mad. They will they will not have
it that a woman has done you over.
They will not have dusty that a woman
has led you on. They won't have it.
These people will not have it for love nor money.
Will not have that a woman could
possibly [ __ ] someone over. What is it
with these sexist bias people? I I want
to know, bro. Uh it's Facebook.
I was saying to him, "Oh, yeah. I think
these women are kind of racist and [ __ ]
like and he was like oh
like he just
it's just mad they don't think that like
madness bro the double standard is
insane. It is insane insane.
It goes to show you dusty that
like I said many times it's a gender
thing. So unless that they're trying to
call you an incel,
it's only cuz you're a man. It's not cuz
you're wrong. They don't think you're wrong, bro.
They're just saying it cuz
um they're just saying it because
yeah, they just defend women for the
sake of it, bro. No matter what evidence
you show them.
And it's scary that 90% of people are
like that, bro.
Because because and I'll answer it and
I'll answer it and I'll answer it and
I'll answer and I'll answer it. Right.
Okay. How did the USA easy thing end?
Firstly, these things was years ago.
These things were two years ago. I
haven't had a date since April.
I haven't had a date since April and I'm
28 and I don't have anyone now. So
that's that's the way I see it, bro. Is
that you're 28 and you don't have anyone
now. and you should do. So that's that's that.
Yeah. Look how that USAD thing ended.
So you know, was it really worth it? Not
really, you know. And
tell me what's happened this year, bro.
What have we had this year?
What have we had this year, bro?
Not even a [ __ ] date since April is a
[ __ ] joke, mate. [ __ ] absolute
Yeah, it doesn't matter, bro.
I'm in a bad mood cuz I had to print
something and it never even worked.
And it's just pissed me the [ __ ] off
having to wait around for everything in
this [ __ ] country and then having to
look at stuck up women up their own asses. You know,
bad experiences. Bad. It would always be
bad experiences, bro. You know this.
Good luck for the [ __ ] men nowadays.
Good luck. Especially if you live in London.
Good luck to them, Dusty. Especially if they're virgins.
It ain't good, bro. It ain't good.
Really ain't good.
It ain't good, bro.
And where I hate them so much, Dusty, I
won't even want to talk to one of them
cuz I hate them so much, bro. It gets to
that point where you're sick and you
grow tired of their [ __ ] bro. So, when
I say this, I don't contradict myself. I
went out two weeks ago. Yeah. Why? Cuz I
was forced out, bro. I kind of had to go
out. I literally had to go out otherwise
I would have not heard the last of it.
So I kind of had to go out. I didn't go
out [ __ ] willingly, bro. Did I? So
there's no point. There is no point, bro.
Just wasting my time printing something.
It don't even [ __ ] work. What the actual [ __ ]
What I find with this country, you've
always got to wait around for
everything. You know what? It's the
country that annoys me as well. It's not
even just the women in this country.
It's the it's the whole country itself
that annoys me. You know, the housing
thing, the waiting around for everything.
But yeah, plenty of stuck up women.
Yeah. Yeah. They're stuck up women.
Triple stuck up women up their own ass
with unrealistic standards.
So, no, you wouldn't because it's the
West. Same as America, same as Canada.
They're all [ __ ]
All [ __ ] [ __ ]
You have to always wait. You have to
wait around for everything in this
country. I hate this country, bro. I
hate everything about this country.
Women, weather, waiting around for
everything. How you have to fight for
everything. Just [ __ ] people that
aren't even just women. I hate this
country, bro. They're [ __ ] [ __ ]
If I if I was a millionaire, right, I
would I I I would do what Richard Branson does,
you know? I do what Richard Branson done.
I lived in an island. I'd have my own
island, bro. French dog. French trenchy.
That's what I do. If I was a
millionaire, that's what I do. Yeah.
You had the right idea, bro.
That's what I would do.
I like to stay away from people.
I'd stay away from people at this age.
I'd stay away from people, bro. Trust me.
I don't like being around people.
No, not really.
Nah, not really.
But no, the double standard trip is
sickening. It is very very very
It is very very sickening
how a woman is allowed to complain and moan
and everyone feels sorry for her and
everyone feels sorry for her. Uh
everyone feels sorry for her and then
when a man talks about his struggles an
incel. Do you not see the problem in that, Dusty?
Do you really not see the problem with that, bro?
I to me that's a problem that's that's
not spoke about in um today's society, bro.
One day you're going to turn on the TV
and I'm going to be on ITV [ __ ]
talking about this [ __ ] brother. Yeah.
No, it's not about them playing the
sympathy card. It's that they get sympathy.
That is a problem, right? And that it
needs to be spoke about, bro. And it
doesn't seem like anyone else is going
to do it but me because I think it's
quite frankly disgusting.
You know, it's actually disgusting,
right? How they're allowed to moan and
winge and generalize all men and
everyone [ __ ] feels sorry for them.
But you as much as say a woman's led you
on? Well, inel incel. I do not see the
problem with that, you know?
Yeah, I don't give a [ __ ] about him,
bro. He's just like Joe Zip. Another
keyboard warrior. I don't care.
Another one that will never meet anyone.
I'm not interested.
But you don't you don't understand,
Dusty. The problem with this.
They dismiss struggles. They make
excuses for them. It's a massive massive
massive problem. It's a massive problem, bro.
and 85. No, women aren't great. They're [ __ ] evil.
They're [ __ ] evil, mate.
And if I'd be going out again, I'd be
only out to ruin someone's life. So, I'd
be no fun, mate. I'd be no fun in the
party because I would just ruin
someone's life, bro.
And I don't mean kill them or I mean I
just [ __ ] them over and that you know
that's what I would that's the stage I'm at lad.
That's what I would do.
Get them before they get you in it dusty.
Women definitely are evil bro. But when
you say stuff like that, Dusty, they all
go for you. Oh, you're an ins. Oh,
you're this. all you that.
So, you know the game's [ __ ] up. Like,
you know you've lost from the get-go, bro. When
when you see the double standards and
that, lad, you see
you see that's how you know the game's [ __ ] up.
Because, dusty, what separates me
not getting sympathy and a woman getting sympathy?
What's the difference?
What's the difference? The difference is gender.
That says it all, bro. That's the only
thing. It's gender.
And we're supposed to just put up with
their toxic [ __ ] and not be able to say
anything, but they're allowed to moan
and winge. [ __ ] off, man. Yeah.
Women are great. Women are [ __ ] evil,
bro. And I've got no reason to lie. I'm
not a virgin. I'm not I'm not a virgin,
Dusty. I'm unbiased. I'm not a virgin.
Yeah, like I said, I just like to stay
away from people nowadays, bro. Just
better that way. I reckon
it's just better that way. Just stay
away from people. Yeah.
And that's that, brother. Oh yeah. So yeah,
this is Bomb by the way.
Hello, Bomb. You all right?
What's your opinion on the double
standards, Dusty? I think it's [ __ ]
gross. I think it's disgusting.
I generally generally think that someone
needs to talk about this.
Otherwise, I will, bro.
Cuz it gets on my nerves. I see it everywhere.
I just banned them.
They all need a life on here. They all
need a life, bro. Listen, cut the [ __ ]
some slack, bro. It's sick. It's 6 days
to Christmas. The guy's going to be
alone. The guy made made a story about having kids,
brother. The guy's a fat, ugly mong.
We've all seen what he looks like, bro.
It's 6 days to Christmas. Let him do
what he he wants to do, bro.
You know, let him do what he's got to
do. He's going to be alone Christmas.
He's going to be lonely this Christmas.
[ __ ] last year. Let's talk about this
year. This [ __ ] is going to be alone Christmas.
Just like a lot of these people on here.
So just let them do what they want to
do, bro. Let them do what the [ __ ] they
want to do.
It's their life, is it? So yeah. Um Yeah.
Yeah, sorry about that, bro. Um,
just a friend. My friend actually
messaged me yesterday to come out, but I never. So, yeah.
This account is bomb by the way.
S bastard. Sad. Sad bastard.
No, I'm going to try and stay up maybe.
So, what do you reckon is going to
happen the first of January, Triple?
happen the first of January, bro? You
reckon it's going to be the same people?
Same repeating people, lad.
same repeating people. [ __ ]
I know. They're sad bastards, aren't
they? They really are sad bastards.
Yeah. I I just think the double
standards is just sickening, to be honest. really sickening.
I just don't know how they can do it for
like years and years and years.
Like, bro, like [ __ ] They wake up, they
want it from the time they wake up to
the time they go to bed,
hating on strangers that they don't even
know. They don't get paid for it.
They don't literally get anything out of
it. They just bore people.
It's just madness, isn't it? Like
anything that they think they're doing,
they don't do it.
Like if they think they're bullying
people or whatever it is, like they
don't do any of that [ __ ]
They're just boring, bro. Just very boring. Yeah,
they've been doing it for years as well,
bro. They've been doing it for years.
They stalk me on Reddit as well, Triple
H. They literally stalk me.
Yeah, proper stalkers on there, bro.
They look out for my posts. Yeah.
Sad what they do.
It's what these people doing it.
Yeah, that Joseph Ferrar's another little nerd.
He's another little nerd. He thinks he's
smart, but he's not. Yeah.
I got be on now for a few days, bro. Anyways,
I can't believe the double standards.
I would love to know why it exists.
Why women can complain about men and
everyone feels sorry for them, but if
you call a woman evil, you're an incel.
I would love for somebody to explain
that to me one day. You know,
I would love somebody to explain
to me, bro. It's just
never not in this country. Never, never, bro.
Never. It will never change. It will
never change in this country. Never. So, that's that.
But yeah, Dusty, you call a woman evil,
you're an incel.
It's mad, isn't it? It is mad the way
the world works.
Like I said, we need to Someone needs to
talk about this, bro.
The double standards is not even normal.
Putting me on courses.
Oh, yeah. Something to do with I think I
saw something like that. Yeah. So,
you're not allowed to have an opinion
based on your experiences.
How's that fair?
That That's not fair, bro.
You see how that's unfair, Dusty? But
they're allowed to [ __ ] slag off men
and [ __ ] You know what I mean?
I would say anyone in the West, give up.
If you're getting these experiences
still at this age, I'd just say to them, give up.
Unless you want revenge. But if you
don't want revenge, just give up. That's
what I done, bro.
That's what I done. Trust.
Yeah, I think I saw something like that
on the TV earlier. It's madness. Madness
[ __ ] as [ __ ] But M.
They're just [ __ ]
But yeah, something needs to be done
about these double standards, bro.
It's not normal.
It should It shouldn't even be accepted.
It shouldn't be accepted.
I hate that word incel as well because
it's so overused.
Hate that word, bro. I really hate that word.
misogynist is better. Yeah.
The rest is done. Yeah, it's mad.
I feel sorry for any poor [ __ ] that
keeps trying, bro. I really do feel bad for them.
Yeah. Poor [ __ ] poor [ __ ]
No, it doesn't. No, it doesn't. If you
hate women, you're a misogynist.
So, no it doesn't.
No, it doesn't.
No. No, it doesn't.
Indigo, you are single. You're single and jobless.
Who you trying to kid, bro? Shut up.
You're jobless and single. You ain't got
a life. You're on here every day, lad.
Have a word with yourself. Stop it now.
Oh, sorry. No, I forgot. You earn £1,800
a week, don't you? My bad. I got the
wrong person. Yeah, yeah, yeah. You earn
£1,800 a week, don't you? Oh, yeah.
Yeah. Nice, man. £1,800 a week,
girlfriend. got sat on YouTube all day every day,
huh? Dreams do come true, eh?
Yeah. £,800 a week. Sheesh.
I disagree with the double standards
because when women moan about men,
everyone feels sorry for them. But when
a man speaks about his experiences, they
call him an incel. Strange. Interesting. Eh,
£1,800 a week. [ __ ] hell. What's that?
No, it's not an incel. And I'm not your
mate. Incels. I've never had sex. No.
No. No. No. No. No. No. No, no, no.
>> Women are evil. I've had sex. I could
probably get sex if I want to after a
while and I'll still tell you they're evil.
So, what what mate? I was still saying
they were evil even when I was having
sex. So, what was I then? So, no.
Women are evil. Simple as that.
I don't want to sleep with evil people.
And if I was going to, it would
obviously be to ruin their life.
If I was to
if I was to try to sleep with a woman or
meet a woman out, it would just be to
ruin their life. That's the only reason
I'd be doing it. But unlike them, I
don't have energy to do that, bro. And
I've kind of got a life, so I can't be
out doing that. But that is what I would do.
Yeah, I just say I do, bro. I'm a
virgin. I've never had sex.
Oh, [ __ ] I hope my charger ain't
>> No. Yeah, I just say I am, brother. I'm
a virgin. Yeah, I've never had sex. What
does sex feel like, bro? Oh, [ __ ]
No, that's all right.
How did you know?
Yeah, I know. I've never had sex, but
I'm a virgin. Yeah.
Yeah. I've never had sex. What does sex
feel like, bro? I've never had sex.
Maybe next year. Yeah.
So, what are you going to do, Indigo?
Are you going to get off of YouTube next
year? Are you Are you going to die on there?
I think most of these people are going
to die on there, bro.
They'll die on here, mate.
They'll [ __ ] die on here. They've
been doing this years.
They've been doing this [ __ ] years.
[ __ ] years, mate.
They've been doing this since I was
[ __ ] 14 on here.
Money Mike used to tell me. Okay, whatever.
No one cares about the incel word, bro,
because it's so overused. And we all
know that these people are sexist and biased.
So calling someone an incel is just like
calling a woman a [ __ ] It has no it
has no um meaning because when you
realize it's a gender thing, bro, it
doesn't mean anything
because we all know if a woman moans and
[ __ ] about men, everyone will feel
sorry for her.
So, at the end of the day, bro, that's
all you need to know
that it's a gender thing. That's why I
don't really give a [ __ ] We all know
that it's a gender thing and it's not a
personal thing and an individual thing.
It's double standards. They are sexist.
No, no, no. It definitely is to do with
gender. If a woman moans about men,
everyone feels sorry for her. If you say
about women, they call you an incel.
It's double standards, bro.
It's double standards. That's why it
doesn't bother me because,
you know, like I said, they're sexist
and biased. When I when you actually
realize how it's all about gender, you
realize, oh [ __ ] you don't give a [ __ ]
Yeah. You don't care. Like, they're just
they're just uh they're just sexist.
Like, that's when you realize it.
It's all to do with if you got a [ __ ] in
between your legs or not.
So that's why it's um they don't think
you're wrong. They don't think you're
the problem. They're just blaming you
cuz you're a man.
That's why that's what it is. There's no
other reason. That's why they do it,
bro. If you was a woman, they'd feel
sorry for you. I've seen it with my own
eyes. I saw it the other day on
Instagram. So yeah, they're just sexist. Double standards.
They all think women are angels, lad. I
don't I'm not asked what anyone calls
me, bro. Really
Triple H. I'm not Monty Man or Timmy.
Remember that, bro. Thank you.
Thank you, darling.
which is why I'm not reacting to you.
I'm not Monty Man or Timmy. Know your
level, bro. Know your level. Yeah.
Yeah, I'm really reacting, bro. Really?
Yeah. So, anyways, Indigo, are you going
to get a life next year?
Oh, what what's going on, bro?
get a life here or you still going to be Yeah.
Yeah, I'm just asking, bro.
No, not Triple H because the people on
here have been have been doing this for
years and they hate on people that they
don't even know. They live to hate.
People that they don't know. There's a big difference.
Yeah, my sleeping pattern is a bit
[ __ ] bro. Can't lie.
Well, I've been going sleep soon.
Yeah, I don't know what this is his
boyfriend's problem is. I don't know why
he still cares. He's not even with Izzy anymore.
And that's what people like. Some Some
people like that, bro. And it they just
think women can never do any wrong.
That's just them in it. Don't never change.
Don't never change, bro. Never change.
Yeah. Starting it.
Oh gosh, bro. Oh gosh.
I'll be on Lord J on the 1st of January
to preach. I'll have you know I'll be
there on the 1st of January, lad.
Just checking if it's the same people.
My little checks.
Oh, bro. These people in here are proper
disabled. Bro, you tell me what normal
person does this.
And these people are older than me as well. Yeah, bro.
Oh, [ __ ] hell. Oh gosh.
Anyways, I'm going in a minute. Yeah, I'm tired.
[ __ ] this, bro. Yeah.
I'm off. See they are.