What are the days? E mate. Yeah. Still
don't still don't see what the what's
there to be entertained about to be
honest. I really I really really don't.
I would love somebody to explain that to
me. There's got to be something I'm missing.
There's There's seriously got to be
something I'm missing here.
I don't particularly think losing 200
pound on roulette is uh is um
is entertaining, but they say it's entertainment.
Yeah, my ass, bro. [ __ ] miss miss
[ __ ] miss. How many times can it [ __ ] miss?
[ __ ] me, bro.
Yeah, I just had a roulette session.
Lost [ __ ] 200 pound.
Uh, nothing. I'm staying in bed just
like every other day is the same old
[ __ ] And I've canled Christmas as well.
Yeah, it was already half over Christmas
to be honest. And that's that. So, yeah.
I was talking about the [ __ ] casino
manager, kids, [ __ ] everything, bro.
They had to ban me. Yeah. I just said to
my mom, "They don't have a choice in
what you say. You want to wind people
up. You want to annoy people. I will say
what I want." Yeah.
I can cancel Christmas because I've
already done it. So, I think I can
because I just did. So, I just said I'll
I'll [ __ ] Yeah, just spread their
mouth open and piss all over them.
That's what I said basically. Just piss
all over them. They love annoying
people. They love annoying people these
places. So, stop moaning when people
talk about you don't have a say in what people say.
You don't have a say, [ __ ] So simple.
And no, it was online. >> So
>> yeah, get [ __ ] you dirty little
wanker. [ __ ] Dirty little [ __ ] The
site was lagging as well. Miss, miss,
miss, miss miss. [ __ ] miss. How many
times you do you not see a 5, 8, 11, and
20 and 23? You never see it. Whenever
you participate in the game, you never
see these numbers. It just goes on the same area.
four and zero section. It's [ __ ] madness, bro.
Yeah, never again. I think I do this
like every three, four months. I don't
do it at all, but yeah, I've cancelled
Christmas anyways, so it's [ __ ] my day
up. [ __ ] my whole day up. Yeah. So,
I was I actually withdrew 112.
Not when I'm playing it. No, because I
cover that number.
I swear if I was in a casino, but I
would have smashed that glass over that manager's head.
Yeah, these [ __ ] done me a favor, you
know, banning me, you know.
Yeah, my Christmas already kind of
ruined anyways, so I won't be going out
New Year's Eve. Got the money. Still got
plenty of money. Uh, nothing to do with
that. Believe it or not, people don't
have to be broke.
Yeah, I got [ __ ] royally. So,
yep, I would have ended up seriously hurting someone.
So, yeah, I lost £200. So, it's what whatever.
Yeah, I was going to put £200 on a
football bet. I was I was going to do
200 on a football bet on roulette cuz
Yeah, it's Christmas. So, yeah.
Form of entertainment. my ass. So,
yeah, I'm not going to keep chasing.
[ __ ] that. I don't I don't really do it
anymore. This is a one-off. I don't
really do it much anymore. This is just
a one-off. Once in a blue moon. Yeah.
This is once in a blue moon.
N's not a bad loss. How is 200 a bad
loss? It's just annoying.
Not really a bad loss. It's just [ __ ] annoying.
I don't do this much, bro. This is like
once in months. I don't really do it. So, yeah.
I was going to put it on a football bet,
but I just thought I'd do roulette instead. So,
yeah. Well, I probably won't be having
Christmas dinner because I don't care.
Don't want to. Simple as that. Yeah. Yep.
I'll be going back to bed soon. I'll be
in bed all day. Yeah.
Just continuously misses every number
that you better. What the actual [ __ ]
bro? I don't give a [ __ ] if I've got
money or not. It's not the point. I
don't care. I don't care about
Christmas. [ __ ] Christmas.
Someone inviting me for a pool table uh
to play pool. I tell them I just ignore
them. I don't want anything to do with
anyone. I'm happy the way I am.
So nah, I'm good, bro.
So I won't be doing nothing.
That's that in it. So yeah,
bad, bad, bad,
bad, bad, bad. It's not even about the
house. It's [ __ ] outright rigged.
It's outright [ __ ] rigged. It's not
even about the house. It is rigged.
It is [ __ ] rigged. It's not about the
house. It is fixed.
Bro, £200 nothing to me, bro. It doesn't
mean anything to me. So
that doesn't mean anything to me. 200
pound. It's just annoying.
Why? Why would I give a [ __ ] about 200
pound, bro? It's nothing to me. It's
just annoying. It could have been any
amount of money. It's annoying.
They are rigged.
They are rigged. You never see a tier
number when Peter belly gums on the
table. You never see it.
I have quit it. This is the first time
in 4 months I have quit it. I don't
really do it. Yeah.
So, yeah. How depressing is that? Eas roulette.
So, where's the entertainment then? Cuz
secular secular shot says it's a entertainment.
Where what's the entertainment, bro?
I don't see I don't see the
entertainment. What? Where's the entertainment, bro?
Yeah. I don't I don't see what where the entertainment is.
What's what's entertaining, bro?
Yeah, that's why you don't do it. This
is why I don't do it.
I closed my account down anyways. So, I
told them to suck my dick and [ __ ] their
kids and they b me. So, they're on the
thing on the chat as well. So, yeah,
that's the thing. Yeah,
that's that it.
I'll just probably chill and watch some
DJ videos and that'll be me then. Yay. Lovely.
This is why I don't gamble.
This is one of the reasons why I do not [ __ ] gamble.
Yeah, basically I won't be out New
Year's Eve anyways. So,
brother, I don't care what 200 is. I put
the money in because I could afford to lose it.
I don't care what 200 is. I've got a
pair I've got 210 lb trainers. I got 200
lb jeans. I don't care.
200 means nothing to me. You can use all
of these hypothetical examples. I
wouldn't do it if I couldn't afford it. Simple.
So that's that.
But yeah, I won't be doing anything
Christmas anyways. So,
what the [ __ ] bro?
It's not a lot of money to me.
It's not a lot of money to me, mate.
But that's what happens when people
don't know how much money you have. E.
Yeah. If anyone's going to gamble, I'd
advise you just gamble on the football
cuz what the actual [ __ ] bro?
I don't even know why I done that.
Well, I saved money to be fair because
if I went out every week, I'd be
spending more than £200. So, I mean, I
did kind of save money in it. So,
and I won't be spending anything next
month because it's January. So, I just figured Yeah. It's January.
Um, and you don't want to go out
January. So, I've got a whole month. It
was either football. Well, it's actually
£217. They charged me a £17 free charge.
Yeah. £17 to deposit £200. What the [ __ ] bro?
What the actual [ __ ]
Yeah. Basically, I woke up at 1:00 in the morning.
Yeah, I was going to put 200 pound on
two teams, but I never
I'm going to really That's kind of
[ __ ] a bit my savings up now. So, I'm
going to just eat the most cheapest food
I can now. Not that I need to, but yeah.
Still uh is what it is, it
[ __ ] hell, bro.
[ __ ] in it.
No, I didn't.
Because I felt like it.
Yeah, because I felt like it. That's why.
Yeah, it seemed like fun. It seemed like
a good idea.
Yeah, it was fun.
I don't know why I done it to be honest.
I don't do it much. I do it every few months.
Well, at least you know you can't win on roulette anymore.
It seemed like my fun at the time. So yeah. [sighs] Yep.
Yeah. And I knew that next month as well
I won't be spending any money because no
one goes out anyway. So I knew I knew
what I was doing.
I knew what I was doing
cuz you're not going to go out are you
[ __ ] in January. So you know I knew
what I was doing.
cuz I know I'll be saving [ __ ] tons of
money next month. So, yeah.
Yeah, I was talking about the manager's
kids and that Well, I was talking about
kids and [ __ ] Uh, you don't have a say
in what people say. You want to annoy
people. You want to annoy people with
that roulette. I'll say what I want. If
I had it my way, if I had one day to
live, yeah, they said, "You got one day
to live. You're going to die of cancer."
I'd burn all the casinos down. I'd
literally burn them all the [ __ ] down,
bro. All the place. All the I would
Yeah, I would. Yeah. that it
Yeah. But it's just a cycle in this country. [clears throat]
Yeah. This isn't a regular thing, by the
way. See, I tell you, if I gamble, this
is what I'm trying to say. If I gamble,
I will say I gambled. I didn't gamble
yesterday. I was in a bad mood.
I was just in a [ __ ] bad mood.
I didn't gamble yesterday. I gambled
just now, but I didn't gamble yesterday.
And I don't gamble regularly. Can't
remember the last time I bet on the
football. I haven't bet for ages. So
that's the way I see it. That's the way
I see it to be honest. I see it as well.
When was the last time you gambled? You
haven't been out for weeks. So,
you know, that is a way to justify it.
Yeah, you would have been spending more
than that. Bad [clears throat] experiences.
You probably would have killed yourself
by now to be honest if you'd kept going
out. So, yeah, that's the way. And I'll
be saving a [ __ ] ton of money next month as well
cuz again, no one goes out January. So,
I figured, yeah,
couple days to Christmas, why the [ __ ]
not? So, I'm not I won't be doing it again. So, yeah,
[ __ ] me, bro.
If I had went out, I'd be spending a lot
more than that.
And you have to do something in it. Yeah.
Why can't you win on it anymore, bro?
You don't need to feel sorry for me,
mate. I don't need sympathy. I don't want sympathy.
Someone was like, "Well, at least
they're honest with you." And I was
like, "Well, no, they're not honest with
me. They literally lead you on." How was
that being honest? They literally lead
people on. How was that being honest? Am
I missing something,
brother? Let me repeat myself for the
millionth time. I don't gamble often.
You not understand every 3 or 4 months.
So even if I act like this,
even if I act like this, right,
every 3 or 4 months, so be it. Cuz it
will be it for three or four months. So
I don't really care. Yeah.
You must be skint, bro. If you if you'd
feel sick losing 200 lb, you must be skinn.
Yeah, you must be skin [clears throat]
about they're honest with me. No,
they're not. They [ __ ] lead people on.
Yeah, I get what you mean, Dan. It
definitely is [ __ ] rigged. It
It definitely is [ __ ] rigged. It
[ __ ] is. Yeah,
it definitely is. You [snorts] said that
[ __ ] right. How it misses that amount
of times when you've got [ __ ] 80, 90
numbers covered. Makes you wonder, don't
it, mate? Makes you [ __ ] wonder.
It's all right. I'll just sleep the way. It's fine.
Yeah, it misses everything, mate. It misses everything.
But that's it. Life, don't it? It will
always do that.
This woman, another one on Reddit,
dismissing people's struggles. Women are
angels to these people.
Yeah, I'm not doing anything Christmas
and I'm not doing anything New Year's Eve either.
So, that's that.
That is literally that. Yeah. [clears throat]
What the [ __ ] bro?
I actually lost £217.
£17 was a fee.
It loves that loser number, doesn't it?
That loser number seeker.
That's its life. That's its life, bro.
Nothing's changed with that roulette and
nothing will change on this community. Yay.
Nothing will change with women either.
What's the point of wanting to live a
life, bro, where nothing changes? It's
so pathetic, bro.
And I was looking up. It seems pretty
normal at that age 28 for people just do
not want to do anything in life anymore.
Makes sense, doesn't it? Yeah.
I'm skinn for Christmas. Nope. I'm
definitely not skin. I've got more money than you.
Nope. Definitely. Definitely not skin.
I've got plenty of money.
Nope. Definitely. Definitely, definitely
definitely not. Must be talking about yourself.
See how no one's triggered, bro. Because
it's just self-p projection. It's the
same self-p projection with you people.
It's to the point now where it's just
like no one no one cares what you say
cuz everything you just say is about
yourself. Skin, lonely, fat, ugly.
That's you people. That's your lives.
You're going to be alone Christmas, not
me, bro. So pour off you little selfjetta.
200 doesn't mean anything to me. So I
don't know why you're laughing because
it literally doesn't mean anything to
me. I'm not skinn like you. So 200 to me is nothing.
you know 200 pound is nothing to me.
[ __ ] nothing to me.
Should have just gave it to Laney to be honest.
200 is not a lot of money, bro. What the [ __ ]
No, it's not a lot of money to me.
It's not a lot of money to me.
I'm definitely not kidding myself. It's
definitely not a lot of money to me.
I could lose another 200 pound right now.
It definitely isn't.
So yeah, otherwise I wouldn't do it if
it was a lot of money to me. Simple.
It was either 200 on the football or 200 on roulette.
Should have chose the football. I don't
need to do it.
I don't need to do it again. [laughter]
I've just used that as a figure of
speech. I don't need to. 200 is nothing to me. Simple.
Well, that's you, bro. Is it? That's
you. You're not me.
So, yeah, that's you, bro. You're not
me. So, yeah.
That's why everyone's different. So yeah,
and I know the whole of January I'll be
saving. Yay. So that's it. That's literally
the only thing I've done, you know, in [ __ ] weeks.
Ain't got out of drinking, no haircuts.
Yeah. And not because of the money, just
because I don't want to go.
Yeah. I don't give a [ __ ] I don't want
to do anything anymore anyways. I was
kind of already like this before. So
yeah, I don't give a [ __ ] I don't want
any more bad experiences. All I need to
do is leave now. I need to buy a phone in January.
I need to book this um thing in January
and go in either February or March. We
need to look. So, yeah.
No, I don't I didn't want to go out. I
don't want to go out. It's just I made
plans to go out.
Yeah, but brother, I don't really care
because the thing is uh UK asylum is I'm
not skint like him. So £200 is nothing
to me. So you can laugh at all you want,
but brother, it's nothing to me. So I
don't know why you're laughing when it's
nothing. Whether 200 in my account or
not is there. It's nothing to me.
So because I'm not skin like you. And by
you, I mean him and the people that
follow him. So I'm not skinn. So it's
not going to get to me.
That's why I'm on here saying this. It's
annoying because it's annoying losing on
a rigged ass [ __ ] roulette. I don't
give a [ __ ] about 200 pound, bro. So,
you can do what you want. We're not
skint like you.
And you can tell he's [ __ ] skint as
well. He's [ __ ] losing 40 pound on a
fob, bro. You can tell that this guy is
actually skint, bro.
You said New Year's was your only night
out at 9:00 p.m. Yeah, I said that
that's when I'm going to be going out
again because I planned it, but I
probably just won't go out to be honest.
I don't give a [ __ ] about going out here
anymore. I don't care.
I could have went out today. I can go
out today. Could have. I can go out
today. I don't want to. I'm not interested. Simple.
So yeah, you can laugh at 200 pound, but
200 pound's nothing to me, LJ, cuz we're
not skin like you. We're not skint, so
you're laughing at your [ __ ] self.
So yeah, 200 is nothing to me. That's
why I'm saying it out loud. You can clip
it all you want. So that's it. Yeah.
Nope. I just lost 200 pound on the roulette.
Uh, go away, bomb. You're boring. Uh, go
away, bomb. You're really boring now.
You've been proved wrong multiple
multiple multiple times. [ __ ] off. No
one needs to prove themselves to you.
So, yeah. [ __ ] off. No one needs to
prove themselves to you. Get that idea
out your head.
Same thing as L J. Same thing as all of
the other people that think that. Yeah.
No one cares what you think. You don't
know no one. Yeah. You've just said it
yourself. 200 a lot to you cuz you're skint. Yeah.
[ __ ] weirdo. No one needs to prove
themselves to you, bro. Yeah. Get that
idea out your [ __ ] head. It's the
same as that guy that says, "Oh, you
wear you wear colada stuff. You wear
colada stuff, brother. I've got receipts
on my email. Never use colada in my
life, but we don't need to prove
ourselves to you sad, lonely people with no life.
Get that idea out your [ __ ] head
completely that anyone needs to prove
themselves to you because uh you're
sadly sadly mistaken. No one needs to
prove themselves to any of you people."
simple. So, yeah, just get out of your head.
But yeah, um
New Year's Eve. Yeah, I won't be going
out New Year's Eve. Um
yeah, I don't know what I'll be doing. Probably nothing.
I don't know. Nothing there.
don't give a [ __ ] about Christmas.
But yeah, anyways, uh that skin [ __ ] is
self projection and it's boring. So
hopefully by the uh yeah, first of
January, you stop saying this [ __ ] bro,
cuz it's really boring now. And it's
part of why people don't come on here much anymore.
You know what I'm saying? Cuz it's very
very boring. It's clearly clearly self
projection because if you people had all
of this money, you wouldn't be on here
every day hating
unless you're saving for a car or
something. I mean, are you saving money
or because I think it's a coincidence
how you people on here call people skin
that you sat on here from the time you
wake up to the time you go [ __ ] bed.
It doesn't make sense, does it?
Yeah. You might want Santa Claus to get
you a mirror this Christmas.
But yeah, that skin thing is uh that's
definitely definitely self projection.
I also get money just after New Year's
Eve as well. So, bro, it's not about
It's like when you say, "I can't afford
to go out every week." I laugh at it
because you don't know how much money I
have. You don't know people. That's why
I laugh at it. You really, really,
really, really don't.
That's why, okay, whatever. Cuz you
don't know anything,
you know? Don't know nothing.
So, yeah, Mr. B. Um, roulette still the
same old rigged roulette.
Yeah, rigged roulette will never change. So, that's that.
Yeah, roulette's the same roulette.
In case you wanted to know, England is
the same England. Yeah.
I used to go on Tuesday. It's actually
Tuesday, not Monday.
See, the thing is with me, I don't even
feel like I'm missing out cuz done so
much [ __ ] in these years. You don't even
feel like you're missing out on the Christmas.
No, I just lost 200 pound on the
roulette, so no, I won't be.
um that like
that I don't even feel like I'm missing out.
Like I literally could just be sat here
until New Year's and I don't even feel
like I'd miss out on Christmas or anything.
Yeah, I lost 200 pound on roulette. I
was going to put 200 pound on the
football, but it was either football or
roulette and obviously I chose a
roulette. So, I don't know why, but
just chose roulette instead. It's whatever.
Yeah, same old with that as well.
That was the first time in months, bro.
Months. Three months maybe.
Not to me. It's not It's not a lot of
money to me. Maybe to you, but not to
Not to me, matey.
It was either that or I mean, I haven't
been out for a couple weeks. So yeah,
it was actually £217 actually cuz uh the
fees. So yeah,
it's not a lot to me, matey. [clears throat]
And yeah, I don't even feel like I'm
missing out. Christmas, New Year's Eve,
I don't even feel like I'm missing out.
But thinking about it, I'd rather lose
200 pound roulette than go out drinking
and spending that on haircuts and
drinks. Come to think of it, that was
probably a better idea.
Spending £200 hearing I've got a
boyfriend all night. [ __ ] that. Waking
up hung over, depressed. [ __ ] that.
So, I won't be doing anything January
cuz no one goes out. So, I knew I know
I'd be saving loads of money anyways. So, [ __ ] Yeah.
What else was I going to spend [ __ ]
200 pound on?
I get money soon anyways.
I don't have money. That's not
Yeah, it's [ __ ] up, bro. It's [ __ ] up.
I wouldn't anyways.
I didn't buy anyone presents this year except Laney.
I wouldn't buy anyone presents anyways.
Next year is about me. Me.
No one else. Me.
Well, it's already kind of started,
you know, now, but yeah, it's all about me,
But yeah, it's very easy to get into
that cycle again. Obviously, this was
the first time in 3 months, but it's
very easy to get into that cycle again.
And it's not a cycle you want to be in,
you know, bad experiences, then
gambling, and then bad experiences. [ __ ]
all that, bro. Just don't do nothing.
Just sit in bed and do nothing. Just
watch some films and something or
something like that. [ __ ] that.
And the reason I don't do anything is
cuz I'm 28 years of age. I don't need to
do anything. I've tried more than anyone
in the world. 28 is not an age where you
need to be going out every week.
That is not an age where you need to be
going out every week. You should be with
someone. This is what I was saying
yesterday. It's not an age
where people typically do this stuff.
You know, it's it's a young person's
game. You know, I'm not doing that.
All you need to do is is find a way to leave here.
That's it. [ __ ] going around in
circles the rest of my [ __ ] life. You cough, bro.
[ __ ] dirty [ __ ] roulette.
That's someone losing 200 pound. It
doesn't mean anything to me whether I
have it or don't have it.
Yeah, this a self projection, bro. Just
went on your tunnel.
I just don't care about Christmas.
I just want this year to end. To be
honest, I don't care about Christmas. I
don't care about anything. I don't care
about Christmas. I don't care about any
of that [ __ ] bro. So,
Oh, I thought I couldn't gamble anymore.
Oh, that's what happens when you talk
about people that you don't know.
Yeah, I thought I couldn't gamble anymore.
Shows how much you people know about
people's lives, eh? Yeah,
that says a lot. When you'd rather
gamble 200 and actually go out, that
says a lot.
That actually says a lot, bro.
That really says a lot. Man,
[ __ ] up, bro.
No, I'm doing nothing.
Just going to go chicken shop. I think
this is what happens. I think when
you've had enough bad experiences in your life,
I think you it creates a monster. These
people actually create a monster. It's
like what Ant-Man said. They've actually
created a monster.
It's the truth. It actually is the
truth. No, just leave him. He's just a
self projector, bro. Just leave him. We
all know that he's going to be lonely
Christmas and he's skint. Just leave him, bro.
Just leave him. Just leave the self projector.
The self-p projecting clown. Just leave him, bro. So, yeah,
just leave the self-reflector.
Oh, that's that's his life, bro. He's
skinn. He ain't got no friends. He's lonely
even, bro. He's a loner.
Fat [ __ ] ugly loner.
And the reason why he's saying about
£200 cuz £200 is a lot of money to these
people. These people on here were very
skint. So you need to know that. Yeah,
it's a lot of money to these people, bro.
Um, so yeah, they just basically create a monster.
That's what happens when you've had
enough bad experience in your life. This
is what happens, bro.
Um, and it probably will happen to most
people as well.
Yeah. Bad, isn't it?
It's not a lot of money to me. Might be
a lot of money to you, but it's not a
lot of money to me.
There really isn't a lot of money to me.
uh I'll explain it for the millionth
time because it's not about the money.
Losing is annoying. It's not about the
money. I could lose 50 pound. Why do you
ask the question when somebody explains
it to you and you're still not going to
get it through your brain? It's not
about the money. Just losing is annoying
on something that's rigged. So,
it's not about the money, which has been
explained about a million times, but
somehow it doesn't process in your brain,
you know. And I've still got money as
well. Uh because believe it or not, uh
gambling is not a form of entertainment.
I wasn't entertained this morning, trust
me. And I don't think the neighbors were
either because I'm pretty sure they
heard me. So, you know, it's this guy is
just full of [ __ ]
Uh I haven't played for 4 months.
This is uh and it's not what I say, it's
what I know. And I've not played it for 4 months.
So, what I played it four months ago.
Okay, sorry, bro. You know what I mean?
So, [snorts] and it is rigged. It's not
what I say, it's what I know. So, it is
[ __ ] fixed as [ __ ]
No, it's it's called uh it's called Spin Dog.
The site's called Spin Dog.
No, it's legit.
Just the fees are not good.
[ __ ] £217 I lost. What the [ __ ] bro?
£17 for the [ __ ] fees. The [ __ ] So, yeah.
But like I said, I'll be saving a [ __ ]
ton of money in January. So,
and I won't be going out anyways. No New
Year's Eve or anything. So, Boo.
What are you going out for, bro? For
what reason? What are you going out drinking for?
You want more bad experiences or what?
What are you doing, bro?
What? Do you want more bad experiences or what? Again,
by you, I mean I mean me. I mean [ __ ] me. So
yeah, I just could have put 200 pound on
two teams, but I never I just want a roulette.
I thought really had more of a chance, but
clearly it's the same old [ __ ]
No, I'm not doing a football bet. I'm doing nothing.
Cuz if I went out, I would have spent
about £200, maybe 170
haircut, drinking, and I'd be [ __ ] for
two days, hung over just to hear I've
got a boyfriend. Just seemed like a better option. Yeah,
it just seemed like a better option to me.
But no, I won't be doing anything you think, bro.
Yeah, [ __ ] Christmas anyways. I don't
give a [ __ ] about Christmas.
Bought Laney a present and that's it. I
don't give a [ __ ] My friends invited me
round today to play pool, but I'm not
doing it. I don't give a [ __ ] lad.
But yeah, that's why people in here call
people skin. Yeah, cuz they're skin themselves.
Yeah. There's more to life about women.
When I get revenge. Yeah. When I get
Yeah. Yeah. When I get revenge. Yeah.
Uh, I'm not buying the meat.
My mom's buying it.
See, I could literally be alone
Christmas and I wouldn't care. I could
be alone New Year's Eve and I wouldn't
give a [ __ ] I don't care
cuz I'm used to last Christmas. What
happened last Christmas?
I'd rather be back in that house by
myself. I think Christmas. I don't give
a [ __ ] about Christmas. I don't care.
I really don't give a [ __ ] about it.
I should have done that football bet now
instead. I think
I actually withdrew 112, but it was
taking so long to process. I just gambled it. Yeah.
But like I said, that's a one-off.
[ __ ] keeping them [ __ ] in business.
Keeping them casinos in business to feed
their shitty kids.
Think about it, bro. They're feeding
their shitty kids with people out of people's misery
to feed their shitty kids. Imagine that.
They're like scamming people. They're
They're ruining people's lives to to
feed their shitty kids.
That's why I brought their kids into it, bro. Yeah.
[ __ ] dodge as [ __ ] Yeah.
[ __ ] hell, man. Yeah.
Hey, Losing 200B. What a [ __ ]
200B is nothing to Peter Belly.
But it is nasty. That is disgusting, bro.
Very, very disgusting.
[ __ ] vile bastards. Yeah.
LJ [snorts] is going to be all alone Christmas.
The projection is going to get very uh
become very strong the next couple of
days with these people. So yeah,
I lost 200 lb from electric brakes.
Yeah, neither going neither will going
out change things. But the only thing it
will stop it won't change things. But
what it will stop, Mike, is getting more
bad experiences. It will stop the bad
No, I was talking about the manager
kids. Yeah, I was talking about the
casino manager kids. I said I'd [ __ ]
open their mouth and [ __ ] in their face.
Yeah, cuz I would do that. [ __ ] them and
their [ __ ] kids.
No, it's definitely definitely
definitely women. Yeah, I do I do blame
women. Yeah. Yeah, I do. They're
[ __ ] They're [ __ ] And there's
been loads of evidence provided. And if
you're too ignorant and you don't
acknowledge that, that's your problem.
That's not my problem, bro.
Yes. And I've provided lots of evidence
as well. And no, not going out won't
change things, but it will stop more bad experiences.
And it would stop. It will stop a cycle.
No, it was online roulette.
And yes, I I I do blame women. Yes,
they're [ __ ] They're [ __ ] I hate them.
And I provided evidence to back up my
claims, but it seems that 85% of people
are ignorant and they don't seem to like
acknowledging that. So, um, yeah, that's
So yeah, going out and getting more bad
experiences, that's not going to change anything either.
I I woke up at 1:00 to 4 in the morning
and I just chilled. I was talking to
Ant-Man and I was going to put 200 pound
on the football, but then I thought I
just put the 200 pound on the roulette.
Yeah, [ __ ] bro. Really [ __ ]
[ __ ] kept missing every single
[ __ ] spin. Get [ __ ] Dirty bastard.
Dirty [ __ ] bastard.
When did I last cold approach? When did
I last go out?
And why did I last go out?
When did I last go out? When did I last
approach and why did I um Yeah.
I don't give a [ __ ] about him, bro. I
don't give a [ __ ] about that virgin. I
don't know why you keep bringing him up.
I don't care about that virgin.
I really don't give a [ __ ] about that
little low life. Yeah. There you go. I
No, I went out 3 weeks ago. I think it
was 2 3 weeks ago and I was forced to go
out. So, that answers your question.
When was the last time I went out
willingly doing it?
And if I was to go out willingly doing
it, I'd be [ __ ] them over. I mean,
I'm supposed to go out New Year's Eve,
but I'm not going out now. So, it's as
simple as that. I didn't want to go out anyways. So, that's that.
They've created a monster. It's like
what Antman said. It's true. It's
literally true. They've created a monster.
And I'm done with the double standard
[ __ ] in that as well.
So yeah, I just don't I just don't do anything.
Why are you going to go out and get more
bad experiences? That doesn't even make sense.
Like it don't that does not make no
sense, bro. It doesn't make no sense. Um, yeah.
No, I just don't want to go out.
I didn't want to anyways.
No, I just don't want to.
It's not even about money. I can't even
say it's about saving money cuz that's
just an excuse. No, I just don't want to. Yeah.
Now sign up. >> [snorts] >> Yeah,
I don't think I will be out again in
this country. I really don't think I
will. I don't think I will. I think I'll
just go straight to leaving
in February. I think February, March.
It's not poor me. I'm completely fine. I'm leaving.
I'm out of here, lad. Either February or
March. I'm out of here, lad.
And obviously I won't be out of January
either. So yeah. Bye-bye, Nons.
See you. See, I don't entertain these
people. You see, I don't entertain these
stupid idiot, biased, ugly, skint,
moronic people. I just say bye-bye and
they get banned
cuz they just sell projectors, you see.
They're not worth anyone's time. So yeah. Yeah.
I might go KFC today, you know. I don't Yeah.
I don't need to recoup it, bro. I've got money.
I don't need to recoup it. I've got money, matey.
And I've got the whole of January to
save and and most of February as well.
So I'm laughing really.
Yeah. £217. What the [ __ ] bro?
Yeah. What is that £17 fee about as well?
That's a lot of money, bro. What the [ __ ]
But yeah, you know LJ, you just know
that he's skinned. I I was listening to
this thing about this £40. He is [ __ ]
skint, brother. He's skint. He was
trying to use money to buy trainers. He
is skint. He doesn't own property. He's
never subleted in his life. The guy is [ __ ] skked.
Yeah, I know the [ __ ] better than he
knows himself. Nons legs. Skint. There's
a lot of [ __ ] skint people on here,
bro. You know
he is skint. Nons legs skint.
No crying about it, bro. It doesn't
matter about crying about it. It is
annoying to be fair. And it is annoying
is lo It is annoying to lose any amount
of money, bro.
I will lose 20 pound right now and I go
mad on them machines. It's I don't it's
not about that, bro. But he is skint.
You can tell uh he he is just skin.
Uh his lifestyle doesn't match his
doesn't match his lies.
He is [ __ ] skinn mate. He ain't got
no properties just like nonslegs. He's skint.
They're all [ __ ] skinned, mate.
They're lying to themselves. Honestly are.
They really are lying to themselves, bro.
He does not have money.
He does not have money. People that have
got money do not beg on the internet.
He lit people that have got money do not
beg on the internet. Trust me.
Trust me. People that have got money do
not beg on the internet.
I don't have loads and loads and loads
and loads and loads of money. You'll
never catch me begging on the internet.
It's not worth losing my pride over,
mate. The guy is skint [ __ ] skinned. You know,
if he's not skinned, why is he on here
all day, every day, no life? Ask
yourself that question. Are you saving?
Like me, I'm saving. I'm I just can't be
bothered going out.
I mean, I've done more than he's done in
three years of my life. So, I mean, I
can answer you if you if you want. If
you got any questions, I can answer you.
Nope. Don't want anyone's money. I've
got my own money.
He is skin. He is absolutely skinn. He
is absolutely skinn. If somebody was
making money, they wouldn't be on here
begging for money, bro. If they were
making money. I don't make much money
anymore. I don't have loads and loads of
money. I've got enough money, but I'm
not a [ __ ] I'm not rich and I'm not
asking people for money.
No, that's [ __ ] That's deadbeat [ __ ] bro.
[ __ ] that. No, [ __ ] that, bro.
he's skint. He is skint. He hasn't got
money, bro. Trust me. Maybe that
Smokeoky Bee might have some money. I
don't really know. But this guy don't
have money. Just like Nons, he doesn't
have no money. He showed daddy's life
savings once for [ __ ] sake. Every time
these people have been pulled has been
show money, they've run away, mate.
Multiple times. We've seen it, you know,
and that's that.
She did it.
She did it, bro. So yeah, you can't win
on roulette now, mate. You can only
really win on the football. Yeah,
that's the only way you're going to win
nowadays. I think
I think you've probably got more chance
on a FBI
than online roulette.
I'd go as far as saying that. That is
rigged as [ __ ] bro. The amount of times
it kept missing. Oh my [ __ ] god. I
had 92 numbers [ __ ] covered. Still nothing.
Weren't having it at all. It was not
having it at all, mate.
Yeah, I should have put the 200 pound on
the football instead.
200 returns 554. That was a good return
of 200 pound.
>> Yeah, but the thing is with these
people, they don't show their losses.
That's the thing, Mike. I come on here
now, I say I lost £200. I don't give a
[ __ ] 200 is nothing to me. I don't give
a [ __ ] if people laugh cuz I'm not skint
like them. We all know that they're
laughing because 200 pound a lot because
they don't have 200 pound.
Do you understand? So these people like
Joseph Fer and and Spok they're not
showing their losses. We know it's all [ __ ]
So no football. No.
I just played just put 200 pound on roulette.
And what do you mean again? I haven't
gambled in [ __ ] months like this.
What the [ __ ]
And I'll probably do it again in three, four months. Yeah.
What the [ __ ] bro?
Yeah. No, I just played some roulette.
First time in months. Yeah.
It's not good, is it? Yeah,
imagine I kept going. Nah, [ __ ] that.
Yeah, that's like those with Ferrar and
Spok. They never show their losses.
They never show their losses. I come on
here and say I've lost cuz I don't really care
about 200 lb.
So yeah, I don't really care, bro.
Red Star such a loser, bro. I went on
his channel just now. Yeah, I said he's
got something to say about this roulette.
Yeah, this guy ain't got no life. They
really ain't got no life on it, bro.
They really, really ain't got no life.
This is literally their life, bro. This
YouTube is these people's lives and it
would always be. And believe it or not,
Triple H, it's going to be going on next
year as well with these people. Yeah,
they definitely ain't got no life.
What they do is they wake up at like
6:00 in the morning.
I don't I'm not going to be gambling
again, bro. I'm not going to be gambling
again. I don't care about Christmas
anyways. They're going to they wake up
at like 600 7 in the morning
and they just hate on strangers that are
better than them. And they've been doing
it for years. They've been doing it for
years, bro. Just just Red Star. They've
been doing it for years, bro. You're
thanking Joseph Far. 200 is nothing to
me. Whether 200 is in my account or not,
it's nothing to me. So, I I can thank you myself.
And they did not tempt me to gamble.
You did not tempt me to gamble. I
gamble. I wanted to gamble today because
of the football. You little clowns don't
bother anyone on here.
You little clowns don't [ __ ] with
anyone's head. I don't know how many
times I gamble today cuz I wanted to gamble.
Yeah, I made that choice to gamble myself.
You [ __ ] little mongos. Yeah.
Yeah, bro. That's that.
Joe didn't [ __ ] tell me to gamble.
Otherwise, I'd be gambling on the
property. You [ __ ] idiots. I lost 200
pound cuz I chose to gamble.
Oh, no. They definitely ain't got a life
on it. They definitely ain't got a life
on here. These people right sit on here
from the time they wake up to the time
they go to bed. They ain't got no life
on here. I don't come on here every day.
I don't come on here every day and I'm
saving money. I'm not going out and I'm
not doing anything. And even I'm not on
here as much as these people. So answer
that one. Triple H. If I'm saving and
I'm not really going out and I'm not on
here nowhere near as much as these
people, what are these people doing?
That's a That's a good question.
Nothing, bro. They're [ __ ] probably
bed bound, roombound agrophobic people here.
Oh yeah, they've been doing that for
ages, bro. They're just stalkers. That's
that's their life, bro. That's They're
always going to do that. S they they
wake up every morning, stalk people all
day on the internet, go to sleep. That's their life
because they're old, fat, ugly skinned
people. They've got nothing better to
do. They've been doing it years.
They hate that they're old and ugly.
That's what it is with these people.
They got [ __ ] all in life. What else are
they going to do, bro? To be fair to
them. What else are they going to do?
Yeah, they do it from the time they wake
up to the time they go to bed. This is
their life, bro. Stalking people on on the internet.
That's their life. They will never stop
as well. And they will never stop.
So yeah, that's their life, bro.
YouTube. YouTube and hating strangers.
hating on strangers.
Yeah, they're not sinking, bro.
Yeah. No, they're proper stalkers.
They're proper proper stalkers. They
will sit on Reddit and keep refreshing
the um the page
um the advice the advice subreddit.
Yeah, they're proper proper stalkers.
They're proper stalkers, bro.
Yeah, they ain't got no life, bro.
That Dam Thompson, that Red Star. Yeah,
they got nothing, bro.
Well, I can't get into any casinos. So,
yeah, that's not going to happen. That
wasn't going to happen. So, yeah.
Yeah, they ain't got no life. They're
just fat, ugly people. That's thie
jealousy cuz you're younger than them
and better looking than them.
That's what I think it is. I think it's
cuz I'm younger and better looking than
them. And um
yeah, that's basically just jealousy.
That's why they do it. That's their life
though, is it?
That's their life, bro. That's their life.
They got more time on their hands
than me. They've got more time on their
hands than me, lad. And [ __ ] I'm and
I'm not doing anything these days.
So, what life could these people
possibly have to be on here from the
time they wake up to the time they go to
bed? No days off. What life could they
possibly have on here? None.
So, [ __ ] hell. Is it 9:00 already? Yeah.
Yeah. That's their life, lad.
But yeah, the reason they laugh at a lot
like loss of money is because this money
is a lot to these people like Red Star,
Nonss, LJ, these people are skin. So if
they hear about someone losing 200, it's
a lot of money to them. So they think
that someone's actually at a loss.
Do you get it? Are you understanding it now?
you know, and that's why they do it
because if they
they would know that it's not, you know
what I'm saying, bro? Like
it's not like you have 400 and you've
lost £200 or you had 200 and you lost £200.
What if you had 3.2K and you lost £200?
They don't know how much money I have.
They don't know anything. So, they only
go off by their own lives cuz they're skint themselves.
That's why they do it, bro. They used to
do it with 80 pound as well.
I don't know, man. He's been run off
YouTube. He's been run off of YouTube by
these idiots in it. So, yeah.
Yes. I I got tempted to say cuz I looked
on the football in it.
cuz I'm £200 on a football, £200 on roulette.
If I put £200 on a football, it would
have returned 554.
I could still do it to be honest the
football. But no, [ __ ] that. I'm not
losing 400. [ __ ] that.
I'm not losing 400 quid. No way.
That's madness, bro.
And one day, imagine that. But that no,
the madness is over. Yeah.
Don't know where to go get a breakfast.
I can't be bothered to move.
No, I can't be asking move, bro. [ __ ] that. Oh, that
no no my hair goes back fast.
But yeah, Joseph never tempted me into
anything. I I already knew what his
channel was about anyways.
I already knew what these channel was
about. UK asylum. I already knew what it was about.
It was showing fake wins and only wins
to try to get me hooked to gambling. I
already knew what his channel was and
never worked. Never did. Never will
worked. I can I know these people, bro,
because where they're so thick and low
IQ, I know what they're about, bro.
See, Monty couldn't figure it out. I
already I already clocked onto that as well.
just like that stop and step. I already
knew what these You know what I'm
saying, bro? Like it's uh Yeah.
Fake people that can't even talk on the [ __ ]
people that can't even talk on a [ __ ]
panel, man. You know what I'm saying? So Yeah.
And he's trying to tell people that
they'll do nothing. Let him come on here
and try and tell me I'll do nothing
again, bro. But I I will show this [ __ ] up.
I'll say say it one more time and I'll
just come to you today, bro. It's not a problem.
Like, it ain't a problem at all, bro. It
ain't a problem at all.
They are scared of their own voice, bro.
He's a [ __ ] [ __ ]
And I tell him he's a [ __ ] to his face
as well. He's He's just a a [ __ ] He's
just a fat nonslover,
you know. And if I need to travel to the
Northeast again, I will do it again. I
will travel to the Northeast again. I
have no problem, bro. Been there several
times, you know.
And I'll get some [ __ ] whilst I'm at it.
So the women love Peter Belly there.
So if you really want to test that
theory, [ __ ] right? You little
[ __ ] nonsloving [ __ ] I'll just stay
in Middlesbrough, bro. I'll just stay
I'll just stay in Middlesborough again.
I don't give a [ __ ]
I'll stay there for a couple of days. You know,
I don't like most of the people in here.
Some people in here were right, bro. Like, um,
how hard can it be? He's all right. He's
a good guy. Um,
we've had many chats. Um,
there's a guy called Chris. Kieran's all right.
There's some all right people on here,
bro, but most of them are just idiots. Um,
what the [ __ ] is that tattoo virgin
boy's got? [ __ ] hell. And he says,
"Oh, if I got a tattoo, would that make
me a cop?" Well, I would never get a
tattoo because tattoos are [ __ ] ugly
personally and the only copycats get tattoos.
And no, again, if I got a tattoo today,
it wouldn't mean I'm copying. We are
saying that you're copying because the
first place that you went abroad was
Amsterdam and then we calculated the
odds of that and it's probably in the
millions. So, you're a copycat. You're
guilty of being a copycat.
And there's not one person I know that
went to Amsterdam as their f as their
first holiday. Not one person, bro. It's
like it's just not somewhere. Obviously,
people go there, but for people to want
to go there the first time that don't
[ __ ] prostitutes and don't smoke weed, you know,
it's like it's obvious that you was copying.
You're a little copycat. Me [ __ ] out.
You know what I'm saying?
Nah, nothing, bro.
Nothing at all.
Move out a relationship. No.
Me. Yo, you are a copycat.
What the [ __ ] is that ugly tattoo he's
got on him? You know
what the [ __ ] is that ugly tattoo?
Have you seen that ugly tattoo? [ __ ] hell.
Never seen the [clears throat] appeal to
tattoos ever. Never have. USA is he had
tattoos. I don't know why people get
them. They're [ __ ]
They're [ __ ] ugly, bro.
Why people get him, but I should never know.
[ __ ] nons probably got him to [ __ ] fit in.
O, listen Joe, you little [ __ ] Right.
If you you try and tell me, right, that
I will do nothing, I'm just going to I'm
just going to come to the Northeast
again and call you out. Simple. I'm I'm
again and call you the [ __ ] out after
Christmas and we will see who really
who's really the one that will do
nothing. I have no I have no problem. I
have no problem at all going back to
Middlesbr, bro. Go to new. I have no
problem doing this again.
So, if you really want to go there, you
fat [ __ ] I I really don't mind. I
really do not [ __ ] mind, you know.
And I'll call you a non-sl.
So, do you really really want to go there?
Cuz I don't mind. I really don't give a [ __ ]
Oh, okay. So, you'll do nothing then.
Okay. So, you'll do nothing. So, I will
come to the northeast and you'll do
nothing. Yeah. Thank you. Yeah. You'll do nothing.
Right. You'll do nothing. Just like your
boyfriend nonslegs will do nothing.
Yeah. Thank you. So, I think you'll find
that you'll do nothing.
Oh, and yeah, I lost 200 pound on the
roulette, by the way. Riged as always. I
was going to put 200 pound on the
football, but I've just put the 200
pound on the roulette. I wish I put on
the football now,
but yeah, I lost 200 pound of roulette.
First time in months. Oh well. Yeah,
I started it. [clears throat] Yep.
I could put 20 pound on the football,
but I'm not losing that.
No. Loads of cash now. I'm skip, mate.
I've got £50.
I'm living under poverty. No, I can't
afford to eat me. I'm skint.
No, I'm skint me. I'm skint me, lad.
Yeah, I got £50. Yeah. Do you want to
lend me some money?
£200's nothing to me, bro. Really,
really isn't. So, this is why when these
people are laughing, I'm just I'm just
loving it, bro. Because 200 really ain't
nothing to me.
So, it doesn't it doesn't affect me. You
know what I mean? I got leg skin. I got
LJ J skin. I don't give a [ __ ] bro. Really? Nope.
Not at all.
Not at all. I don't know what I'm going
to eat today.
I don't know. Uh,
[ __ ] knows. But yeah, I was doing the
same [ __ ] again, Joe. Loser number seeker.
I said to I said, "I'm going to [ __ ]
open your [ __ ] kid's mouth and piss
all over it. Piss in your kid's mouth,
you [ __ ] little faggot."
Lucky I wasn't in the real casino.
I think I would have caused a bit of a scene.
As you know, same old rigged area.
Same old rigged area, you know.
It will never change. It will never
change. I actually got down to 112 and I
thought I'm just going to take the 112.
That's how rigged it is. But I was like,
ah, [ __ ] it. Just play with the rest of
it. So yeah, that is fixed as [ __ ] bro.
Not 58 11 nothing.
Yeah, I don't think you can win gambling
nowadays on the on the online roulette.
Yeah, but then it's going to go on tier
if I do that.
Antman said these women have created a monster. [laughter]
It's the truth. Created a monster. It's
the truth though. >> [laughter] >> Yeah,
I was going to I was going to do a 200
pound both teams to score,
but it's not it's all right anyways cuz
I'm saving the whole of January. So,
I don't mind, bro. And I won't be going
out New Year's Eve, so I don't really
give a [ __ ] Yeah,
that is [ __ ] up, bro. Nah.
No, because then that's losing 500
pound, isn't it? I'm not losing 500
pound. [ __ ] that. No way.
No way. I'm losing 400 lb. Nah.
Hell no, bro. [ __ ] that. Nah,
I shouldn't have even gambled today. [ __ ] it.
[ __ ] [ __ ] It is Yeah. Nope.
No. Oh, I don't give a [ __ ] about Christmas.
No, the only person I bought for was
Laney. I don't give a [ __ ] about Christmas.
I only care about myself. That's my New
Year's resolution is to just care about
myself. Uh, that's my New Year's resolution.
It's about me, me, me, me, me. No, no
one's getting [ __ ] all. No one's getting
nothing out of me.
Not one person.
Nope. No one.
Not one single person is getting [ __ ]
all. The only person I bought for is Laney.
And that's it. I don't care about anyone else. So yeah,
that's the way to be in life. Really,
that is the way to be in life.
I could do it. I had the money.
Well, I do it cuz I just did.
I I do it because I just did. I had the
money. I have money. I can I can buy
[ __ ] presents, but I'm not doing that.
I'll I'll do it, Joseph, because I just [ __ ] did. So, yeah. Um,
I don't give a [ __ ] about anyone. I'm
supposed to go out New Year's Eve and
I'm but I'm not going out New Year's Eve.
I don't care. It's overrated. I really
don't give a [ __ ] Seriously, I don't
care, man. It's so same [ __ ]
I only went out only went out two weeks
ago cuz I was guilt tripped into going out.
That's the only reason I [ __ ] went
out. [ __ ] that. [ __ ] [ __ ] that
completely. I'm not [ __ ] doing that, bro. Yeah.
probably thought, "Oh, [ __ ] Here we go
again with a roulette in it." Don't
worry, lady. It's not going to be a
habit. It was just a oneoff.
She was probably like, "Here we go [ __ ] again." Nah.
No. Trust me, it won't It's not like that.
I'm saving money and um
yeah, so it's not happening.
Trust me, you don't need to worry about that, matey.
No, no, no.
Yeah. Should I get a spoon breakfast? No.
I'm just going to get some chicken and
chips, I think. Nah.
Nah, bro. I need to save money in case I
want to just [ __ ] off somewhere, you know?
You never know. USA is he might start
[ __ ] and I might have to uh I might have
to go over there. You know
that beat's going out drinking.
Oh, Franklin died. Uh, yeah.
Yeah. So, I I'd have to go over and
start some madness, you see.
This is bad, bro.
So, what? You can't win on online
roulette anymore? No.
You can't win on online roulette anymore.
[ __ ] hell, bro. Why not? What the
No, you can't. No.
I need to
Yeah, if you go out drinking today is
going to be [ __ ] rammed. [ __ ] ram.
Triple H. Imagine going to the O'Neals
in central London. That is going to be
[ __ ] cha block.
If I was going to go out drinking, I'd
probably go out today
and not New Year's cuz New Year's is
just way too busy. It's just [ __ ] and it's overpriced.
But I I'm not going out drinking. But
I'm just saying if I was going to
get money by New Year's Eve as well, so
yeah, but I still wouldn't do it.
It's time for a change,
Joseph. It's time for a change, lad.
No going around in [ __ ] circles. None
of this [ __ ]
[ __ ] this [ __ ] you know. Uh, [ __ ] that.
I fancy some piggies.
Not me. I'm not having a football bet. No,
I'm [ __ ] hungry, man.
I need to try and get that 200 pound
back. So, I have to be I'll just be
eating the cheaper things.
[ __ ] [ __ ] man.
It's so [ __ ] in it.
That is really bad.
But it could be worse. We could be skin light.
Yeah, we could be skint like Lord J.
Yeah, you can just tell we skint trying
to win money to buy trainers. He's like
the He's like legs. [ __ ] skin flint,
mate. Pair of skin flints. Pack of skin
Yeah, them two are definitely definitely skin.
Yeah, they're 100% skin.
Yeah, I'm not having a football bet. My
gambling day is done.
I bet this football bet comes in now as well.
200 returns 554.
That's a good return. That is 300.
Nah, I'm not doing it.
What's the point, bro? What is the point?
It's very stressful. This gambling
thing. The site kept lagging.
The site kept lagging as well.
Nah, [ __ ] that, bro.
It wasn't having it at all, mate. Yeah,
that was just a oneoff.
[ __ ] [ __ ] man.
Yeah. 20 26.
Yeah. I was going to do slow and kitty
minister. I was going to put 200 pound on it,
but I won't be doing that. So,
What the [ __ ] bro?
Trying to think what I can eat.
I fancy some piggies. I can't remember
the last time I brushed my teeth.
Couple weeks ago, maybe.
I need to stop brushing my teeth
cuz then it was just pointless going to
the dentist. Yeah, I think two weeks ago
I last brushed my teeth. Yeah,
it's been a long time.
I need to because uh what was the point
of getting the [ __ ] filling?
You know what I mean? Yeah. the uh
I brush them today.
[ __ ] life, eh?
What a [ __ ] life, matey.
Yeah, the chicken shop don't [ __ ]
open until uh
I was going to watch some Christmas
movies today, but with my mom, but I
don't think I'm going to.
Yeah, just get some chicken and chips and then
[ __ ] go bed in it.
Yeah, I [ __ ] bought it, man.
I think Mike is another one that
dismisses people's struggles. UK asylum.
Yeah, he's another one that uh dismisses
people's struggles, right? Yes.
That roulette is so [ __ ] annoying.
I hate that game, bro. Yeah,
I said to this stupid [ __ ] on
Instagram, "Stop ignoring. I'm going to
keep calling you." [ __ ] annoying as
[ __ ] They soon saw the message.
They soon saw it straight away. These
[ __ ] women are all the [ __ ] same, bro.
Let me call them. Stop annoying people, bro.
Yeah, I was going to do the same as you.
Four teams. Yeah, but nah.
Good idea though. I was going to do the same thing.
Yeah. And man told me about it.
No, I'm only going to eat once today. So,
yeah, just chicken and chips.
then I'm going to sit and watch some
Franklin [ __ ] and then yeah, go to sleep.
All the same, bro. They say exactly the same [ __ ]
I don't owe you a reply. I don't even
owe you. I said no one owes you anything
either. That don't justify
being ignorant. [ __ ] off, you stupid little [ __ ]
You stupid little [ __ ] [ __ ]
I hate these [ __ ] [ __ ] bro.
I don't even know why I have Instagram.
I don't even post any photos, man. I
just go on there, talk to people that I know.
I saw your comment about it being the same [ __ ] No.
Yeah, I'll just eat once.
The cheapest meal I ever made was like 2
pound50. It was pork shops.
You can actually eat really cheap if
you, you know, I for
You can see the westernity in their eyes.
[ __ ] it now. The eyes don't lie, bro.
The eyes don't lie.
You can see the westernity in their eyes.
UK asylum. You can see the Westinity in
their eyes. See, look at my eyes. Yeah.
They're just like normal.
They're like green eyes, right?
And if you see women's eyes, you can
actually see the westernity in it.
There's no like
pupil. There's no eyeball. Just
westernized. Dirty look.
You can see it in their eyes.
They're westernized as [ __ ] They all
they're all NPCs.
They're they're they're
on some they look like they're on some
[ __ ] kind of drug, bro. Have you seen
these approaching videos? They all look
the same. They're all robots.
Yeah, you can see the westernity in
their eyes. UK asylum. Yeah.
Yeah. What are you doing, bro?
I fancy some piggies.
Don't have any piggies. Yeah. Do
No. Do we have anything to eat? Nothing, can it?
It's not good, is it? Huh?
I said it's not good, is it? Holy
wants to go out, bro.
Yeah, I'll probably have nothing to be honest.
I can't be bothered to go out, bro, and
get anything. I'm No.
This red store is such a low life, bro.
You You just have to laugh at these people.
All UK signing. You know, it's the same
people doing this for years. You see the
same people doing this.
It's literally the same people. You see
the same accounts.
It's the same people doing the same [ __ ]
I do I do generally think most of the
people on here are disabled.
I think they're disabled. Most of the
people on here, bro. I really do think because why?
Yeah, they're just disabled in it.
disabled lowife people. >> Yeah.
Apparently, I lost my last 200 pound.
It's mad the stories that these people
come up with, in it,
they come out with a load of [ __ ] don't
they? UK asylum.
They come out with a lot of [ __ ] these people.
You sure these people are not disabled
on here, bro?
women UK asylum.
I hate women, bro.
Why do you think I don't go out? Why do
you think I don't approach?
No, they definitely are all disabled,
bro. They definitely definitely are.
You tell me what normal people come in
here for years doing what these people do.
You tell me what normal people do that.
They're [ __ ] disabled. They are
when they are.
Do you hate women UK asylum? I proper
proper hate them.
The reason I don't go out and approach
and try to ruin their life is cuz I
don't have the energy. Bro, we're not
all sad acts like them.
Yeah. I don't Yeah, I don't give a [ __ ]
I don't really care, bro.
I don't really care.
They're little [ __ ] rape victims. Anyways,
that's the reason why I don't go out and
approach and and try to [ __ ] one of them
over because I don't have the energy, bro.
We're not all low lives like them.
We've got better things to do than
[ __ ] lead people on and [ __ ] bro. We
can't all be like these people.
I sent them all my dick and my WhatsApp
got banned. dad to make a new WhatsApp.
So, I hate him, bro. I really do hate
him. And I'm scared to go out as well
because I will end up seriously hurting
someone, bro. Like, trust me, I will. If
I have to deal with any [ __ ] I'll
just glass them straight in the face.
No, I'm not in a mood. I had to go out
with my mom yesterday to print stuff
uh to print something. I was in a bad mood, bro.
I was waiting for someone to start. I
was just waiting. Any excuse for someone
to start, bro.
So that's what would happen if I go out.
Like if anyone, I'll just glass them in
their face and it won't be a joke.
You know, I've I've I've held back now
for many years with these [ __ ]
So I'm not [ __ ] doing this [ __ ]
That's why I just stay in, bro. I'm just chilling, you know?
cuz I don't want to deal with white
knights. I don't want to deal with
[ __ ] women. I don't want to deal
with jobs worth people. I don't want to
deal with people, bro. I noticed that as
I got older,
I wanted to stay away from people more.
But that's as I got older, you know?
I don't want to get into any kind of toxic situation.
It's just not [ __ ] all that. You know
what I mean?
It's pointless. Pointless. Yeah. So, yeah. >> [snorts] >> Um,
I hate the double standards. I hate
everything about Yeah.
And even if you look back on like what a
lot of these women done as well, like
the lies and the [ __ ]
they actually think you're stupid like
them as well.
Just toxic, just [ __ ]
I'm surprised I haven't really seriously
hurt someone, bro. I'm really really surprised.
I'm really, really, really surprised to be honest.
Must have some patience, eh?
[ __ ] that, bro. [ __ ] that.
Yep. Always and forever.
Yeah, it will always be the same.
I'm hungry. This chicken shop don't open till later.
Oh, [ __ ] me, bro. Oh, they're not falling asleep. Oh gosh. Yeah. Um, so yeah,
I'm not going out new year.
I ain't going out, bro.
No, I'm not going out. New year. I
changed my mind, bro. Oh, [ __ ]
Hey, go out.
I'll be in the nesticles.
I was going to go out. Yeah, but I'm not
going out now
cuz I don't feel like it. Yeah.
I'll end up [ __ ] hurting a woman if I
go out, bro. Or hurting someone. Trust me. basically. Yeah.
Yeah, pretty much. It's going to be
another [ __ ] year as well next year. H same
months, different year.
Same months, different year. Yeah.
It will never change. This community
will never change. Women will never
change. The [ __ ] in this country
will never change.
The waiting [snorts] around for
everything will never change. That's
another thing that annoys me about this
country. You've got to wait around for everything.
Oh, I love how Izzy's uh boyfriend
ex-boyfriend never responded to this
because I'm not an insult. I said, "But
when women complain about men, everyone
gives them sympathy. Says it all. Sexist
and biased." He never replied.
Of course, he never replied, "A little faggot."
Cuz he knows I'm right. He didn't. He
knows I'm right. What? They're sexist
and biased. What the [ __ ] bro?
The guy is a [ __ ] [ __ ]
An absolute [ __ ]
That's what he is. He's a [ __ ] Yeah.
It will never change.
It will never change. But
See, my eyes look normal. That these
women, their eyes, they look like
robots. Triple H.
They look like [ __ ] non-playing characters.
They Well, they are non-playing
characters. And they're [ __ ] as well. No, no.
They've all got the same attitude.
They walk around with the same attitude
as well. I noticed that when I was with my mom.
All got the same stuck up look.
[ __ ] [ __ ] That's what they are.
I am hungry. I don't want cornflakes. I
want something warm.
Remember trip eight's poor [ __ ]
Where's Grezy? Poor [ __ ]
Do you remember that 100 bridge? Poor [ __ ]
Them [ __ ] were laughing at us.
I remember that troll. Yeah. He said
that them [ __ ] were laughing at you.
Then I said, "No, it's us." And then he
rephrased it. Them [ __ ] were laughing
at you at us.
I ain't seen that account in ages.
They might be busy over Christmas in it. Trip >> [snorts]
>> But yeah, it will be a year in March
since I've had a date. Yeah, March,
April. a lot of time, a lot of money,
not even a single date. But women
complain when they get dates, when they
get dumped. It's mad, isn't it?
But you're not allowed to complain. If
you complain, you get called an incel.
So, you're not allowed to complain. They
can complain, but you can't.
Yeah, they they can complain, but you can't complain.
No, he's not allowed to complain. >> [snorts]
>> Got a nasty taste in my mouth. It's
probably brush not brushing my teeth for
like two weeks.
[ __ ] me, bro.
Yeah, I can't be bothered to go out, man. [snorts]
I can't wait. I can't [ __ ] wait.
I can't wait, mate.
Yeah, Antman's girlfriend finds me handsome.
That's good, isn't it? Yeah.
I shower every other day.
Yeah, man's girlfriend saw a picture.
She said I'm handsome and that. She said
she doesn't believe that I get these
problems with women. He had to explain
it to her, but she didn't believe it.
Yeah, that's how stuck up the [ __ ]
are in this country and and they're
racist as well. So people over there
don't believe it. So,
I wouldn't need to ride Antman's bird.
When I go there, I'd be get I'll be
getting my own women. Why would I need
to bang his bird when I'll be getting my
own? It don't make sense.
No, I didn't.
No, it's a different one. [yawns]
I hate this day and age, you know. I
wish I was born in the 80s.
I wish I was born in the 80s, man. [ __ ] Yeah.
No, no, no, no.
What a life, mate. What a [ __ ] life. Yeah.
And man said if he didn't leave, he'd
end up going back to prison. That's mad. Yeah.
Anyways, I'm gone. Yeah. So, I'll be
back later maybe.