[ __ ] it hell. Yeah.
these people in YouTube.
No one else. No one else. Only these people.
These skin [ __ ]
on your channel. Hopefully next year
will be different. No more no more repeating people.
Oh, them never on YouTube. No. [snorts]
I don't know why they come on here talk
about people they don't know and
accusing people and it's literally their
life. I don't know why they do it. I
honestly don't know why these these
bloody [ __ ] do it, mate.
Yeah, I went on Timmy's earlier. [ __ ]
[snorts] it's just the same [ __ ] with
him calling other people virgin when
he's literally a virgin himself. We've
seen all of this for the past [ __ ]
six, seven years with you boring people.
You've seen this for years now, bro.
[ __ ] man. [ __ ] hell.
He says, "Oh, like, oh, oh, well, I'm
winding you up." And I was like, "You're
not winding me up. You're just
projecting because you are literally the
virgin. And you're still coming on here
trying to call me a virgin when you're
literally the biggest virgin yourself."
And it's been confirmed multiple times.
So, it's not even winding people up.
It's just disabled. >> [snorts]
>> Which is why it's like the whole [ __ ]
the whole point of it is uh is um
this is pointless, you know? The whole
point of it is just pointless. He's
calling people virgin when he is
literally the virgin himself. Like that
is like not winding up. That is stupid
and that is disabled. Which is why
people call these people what they are
and they're disabled, you know? Definitely
a projector. Timmy's the biggest virgin going.
He is literally the biggest alltime virgin going.
People are [ __ ] idiots on this community.
[snorts] Can't believe they were on here
Christmas Day. That's mad. And that's
how other people they've got no family
and [ __ ] projection.
All right, we left. I'm having another one today.
I can't believe these people was on
[ __ ] YouTube Christmas.
[snorts] And they tried to reverse it by
saying, "Oh, well, you was live thinking
about the trolls." No, I was live to see
if you people was on YouTube cuz you
people say about people having no family
and all of this self projection [ __ ]
So, I come on to see if you people are
still on here.
All right, Timmy. Listen, bro. Um, I
don't even know if that's you. Let me
have a look. One sec. One second.
Timmy, listen. Oh, is you, bro? You need
to stop calling me a virgin, Timmy. It's
very, very disabled.
Um, it's not it's not bothering me. It's
not triggering me. I'm just saying that
it's making you look really, really disabled. [sighs]
You're you're calling someone a virgin
that's proven that they've had sex. It's
just it's just a word of advice. It's
just embarrassing, bro. And it's very
very disabled as well. Doesn't bother
me. I really don't give a [ __ ] It
doesn't bother me at all. It's just
you're just making yourself look stupid.
And when you're making posts about nonslegs,
which is good, bro. You're making
yourself look stupid by calling me a
virgin. It doesn't It really does not
bother me. I don't give a [ __ ] bro. I
don't ban you. But you're calling me a
virgin, but you're a virgin yourself.
It's silly, bro. It's almost 2026 now. Come on.
So, yeah. [snorts]
But yeah, and I'm not getting into nons
either. Waste of my time. So, yeah. All
right. Do you know what my mom said to
me? My mom said to me, "Oh, yeah. You
should take a picture of the presents.
Uh, [snorts] do a video on the presents
and the Christmas tree." But do you know
what I turned around and said? I said,
"Nah, because I don't need to prove
myself to these people." That's what I
simply said. Oh, my that's what my mom
said to me to me. I had a lovely ro
dinner today, bro. I'm having another
one uh tomorrow.
I said, I don't need to do that because
I don't need to prove myself to these
people, these self-reflectors. And it's
the truth, isn't it?
Yeah, I know he's obsessed. I know. I
know they're obsessed, bro. You just
need to ignore them to me.
That's what I'm doing, bro. I'm I'm
ignoring them. I don't give a [ __ ]
It's the same with that Red Star.
They're just keyboard warriors, bro.
They don't bother me, bro. I don't go on their channel.
Just all self projection with these
people. Everything that they do is just
about themselves. Everything they say is
Just like when I was live earlier for 5
minutes, it was pe people's on YouTube.
Then they tried to reverse on to me. The [ __ ] sausages.
They tried to reverse it on to me to me
when I was like, "No, I was on YouTube
for five minutes to see if you were
still on YouTube."
And they were on YouTube. So yeah,
it's a madness, isn't it?
I need to go to the dentist, bro, and
get another fill in.
No, I don't think he's funny. I think
he's a sad act, and I think he needs to
get a life. >> [snorts]
>> That's what I think. I I don't think
it's funny uh where someone has to come
on the internet all day every day for
years doing what someone like he does. I
think it's disabled.
Winds me up. He doesn't wind me up. He
doesn't bother me at all. If these
people bothered me, if these little
clowns bothered me, I wouldn't be on here.
No. No. He doesn't bother me. They they
don't bother me at all, mate. When I
when I've not been been on here for
days, it's just because it's the same
repeating people. It's boring, bro.
These people don't bother me. It's just
How come a bunch of people that talk
about themselves bother me, bro? I
proved today they were on YouTube
Christmas by being live for 5 minutes
before I went to my sisters.
I proved that these people have got no
one for Christmas to me. I proved it. Yeah, bro.
I don't got any channel.
It's like that Joseph uh that Joe, he
said that he's not going to meet me. He
does all this online keyboard warrior
[ __ ] but he says that he's never going
to meet me. So, I don't waste my time. I
don't waste my time on people that's not
going to meet me and they just want to
be a keyboard or like nons. I don't
waste my time on these people, bro. You
might, but I don't.
The only person I'm sub to now is Monty.
Yeah, it's Monty, bro. >> [snorts] >> Yeah.
Yeah. That Joe's a nod. I I said, "Bro,
I'll come to Leads the same day." And he
wouldn't meet. He said, "No, he's not
going to beat me. He's not going to beat
me. He's not going to beat me. So then I
don't waste my time with these people." Simple.
He doesn't have money. He doesn't have
money, bro. He's shown his daddy
savings. He doesn't have money. People
that have money don't live in a bedsit
and hadn't been abroad until they were
[ __ ] 30 that wears charity shop
clothes. He hasn't got money.
He's not got money. He wishes he had
money. He doesn't have [ __ ] all. He
doesn't have a He doesn't have a pot to
piss and which is why he tries to call
me skint cuz he's skint himself.
He doesn't have money, mate. He's [ __ ] skint.
Yeah, [snorts] just like that red star
skin. That's why they come on here every
day call another skint cuz it's what
they are themselves. Takes one to no
one. Boring as [ __ ] bro.
It's because they're It's because
they're nons themselves to me. I was
saying this to you before, bro. It's
because they're nons themselves.
That's why. Do you not understand it,
bro? It's It's because they're nons
themselves. They're pedos themselves.
Yeah. It's cuz they're nons themselves.
They're pedos themselves, bro. That's why. Yeah. [snorts]
So, what are you going to do? come to
London and fill the [ __ ] in. Well, he
doesn't live in London. Nowhere near
London. That [ __ ] is from nowhere near
my [ __ ] city. That ugly rat face
bastard. And then they're going to walk.
Yeah. And then they're going to call the police.
They're never going to meet you, bro.
It's just like that red star will never
meet you. They'll never meet. They'll
just rot on the internet for years and
years and years repeating the same [ __ ]
because they're nobodyies.
cuz they're nobody's lad. So
there' be no point coming here, mate. [snorts] Yeah.
You never know, mate. Maybe next year
he'll get laid.
Maybe he'll lose his Valentine's card
next year, mate. You never know. Yeah.
Yeah. I know he's a virgin. And I also
know Nons is a virgin. And I know Red
Star is a virgin.
The pack of virgins. Wait. My sister
made me laugh the other day. Yeah. She
went on his channel and she was like,
"What the [ __ ] is that tattoo? No wonder
you're a virgin."
She was like, "No wonder he's a virgin."
She even knows he's a virgin. Even my
sister knows. And my sister's not
involved in any of this YouTube. She
said, "No wonder he's a virgin."
Everyone knows the real virgin.
Never been any anywhere near inside a
female. Never have, never will.
And that was my sister saying that, my older sister.
She was like, "No wonder he's a virgin."
I swear to God, I didn't even bring it up. Yeah. [snorts]
[ __ ] hell, bro. Oh, yeah. to me.
I need to go [ __ ] dentist, bro. Oh, I
need a fill in. But yeah, it proves that
like these people are the ones I've got
no family, no nothing. I was at my
sisters today for hours. Lovely roast
dinner, lovely presents. These people
are on YouTube.
These people are on YouTube.
Yeah, not more repeated than you
bastards. That's why I don't come on
here much anymore
because you just think back and you
think, "Oh [ __ ] this is actually weird,
bro." Like these people, it's literally
their lives from the time they wake up
to the time they go to bed hating on
people that they don't know for years.
Wow. It really is weird, isn't it?
Yeah, it really is weird what these
people do, isn't it? I was first on here
today for five minutes. Yes. To see if
you people was on YouTube.
Yes. To see if you people was on
YouTube. Yeah. For 5 minutes, right?
Yeah. At 9:00 in the morning. Okay.
Yeah. And you people was on YouTube. Two people commented.
and 18 people was watching.
Yeah, I was seeing a few people still on YouTube
and you was you people was on YouTube. I
knew it all along. It was you people.
I could have you know what I felt like
doing just hunging on to my mom, you
know, like when you when you when you
get relief. It was these people all
along. Skin, you know, family. It was
devil all along. It was devil all along.
They were on YouTube. No laugh
with a Y.
Jesus Christ. Laughing at me now. You
people don't laugh at me. You laugh at yourselves.
[sighs and gasps]
Just like that. Joseph, what you people
do, man? You laugh at yourselves and you
don't even realize it. You are the ones
that sat on YouTube every day for years
hating on people you don't know. But
trust me, you laugh at yourselves. You
might not even realize it, but you laugh at yourselves.
Just like that, Joseph Ferrar. I said to
him, "Let me come to Leads today and
meet you." And he won't do it,
you know. Nope. I'm not self-reflecting.
I'm talking about you people on YouTube
every day. Am I lying when I Okay. Okay.
Am I lying when I say that you people
can't take a day off of YouTube? I've
I've been off of YouTube for days.
I've been off of YouTube for days. Can
you take a day off of YouTube? No. So,
no. I'm talking about you people.
Definitely. Definitely talking about you people.
But are you going to grow up anyways and
get a life?
You know, 2026.
Do you reckon it will be the time you
grow up and you actually get a life?
Are you going to grow up and get a life
in 2026, you reckon? Are you still going
to come on here, keep repeating talking
about people that you don't know?
You sure curious.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no,
no, no, no, no, no, no, no. You people
on here Christmas, you people are on it
all the time.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no,
no, no. I have when was the last eight
eight hours, bro. No one's been live for
eight hours. I've not been on YouTube
for days. You people have been on it
every day. I've got my evidence packed.
So, don't even don't even try that
[ __ ] Right. I was live today for 5
minutes, right? And it was 18 people and
people typing away. Yes, I'm I'm
streaming on Christmas day because my
Christmas is finished. I got my
presents, ate my food, chilled with my
sister, chilled with my friends, and I
got my little evidence pack that it was
you people all along. It was like a
relief. As soon as I saw 18 people and
people typing away, I knew it was these
people with no family. You didn't fall.
No one fell for my trap. Is that why
there was people typing and there was 18
minutes and there was 18 people
watching? No, no, no. You definitely
fell for the trap. You definitely fell
for the trap, mate. There was 18 people
watching and two people typing. You
definitely fell for the trap. You
definitely definitely did cuz there'd be
no one watching. There'd be nobody
watching. But Monty man copied my idea,
brother. I went live for 5 minutes.
There was two people watching. Sorry,
two people typing and there was 18
people watching. You people have got no
life but YouTube. You can try to keep
deflecting. You can you can kind you can
keep you can try to keep deflecting,
brother, but we all seen the real use.
We've seen you now. We've seen what you
people do. So you can keep trying to
deflect, brother. Evidence don't lie.
And that's why um Monty man went live
trying to copy my thing.
He's he's copying me, bro.
Definitely definitely definitely copying me
with that one because you saw I done the
same thing. So yeah, you can try to
deflect all you want, bro, but I saw
what I saw. So at the end of the day,
no, I literally woke up cuz I don't
really come on here much anymore. Um,
and I'm like, "Oh, let me see if these
people on YouTube Christmas Day. Let's
see." Cuz they've been talking [ __ ] And
it turns out they was. So, and they and
they weren't even uh they didn't even
come in and talk normally. Did they come
on straight away start projecting?
They come on straight away starting to project.
Yeah, brother. You was on YouTube
Christmas. End of You was on YouTube
Christmas Day. I was on Okay. Yeah, I've
I've said it. I was on YouTube for 5
minutes at 9:00 in the morning. Okay.
Yeah. And I left at 10:00 to go to my
sisters and I was out all day. Okay.
Okay. And and and your point was I was
live for 5 minutes. I went downstairs. I
walked back up and I saw you people on
YouTube. I added that to my evidence pack.
If you got family, why would you be on
here? I left to go to my sisters at
10:00 in the morning. I was on 9:00 for
5 minutes and you people came in. You
people came in. You were on your job.
You was on your job. >> [snorts]
>> You was on bloody YouTube. No life.
You were on YouTube. No life.
You was on YouTube. No life. Yes, it's
Heidi the Reigns. Like I said, bro, the
truth hurts. I know the truth hurts.
Yeah, bro. The truth hurts. And like I
said, in the new year, if this Joseph
Farrar [ __ ] comes back on it, I'm just
going to I'm just going to go to leads.
I'm just going to go to leads. I haven't
been up north for ages and see what this
fat cunt's about. I'll be like, you do
[ __ ] Do you know what though?
Yeah, you you uh someone even wrote on
his thing as well that you you hide your
location because uh you're petrified.
It's the truth that Joseph is petrified.
He's a fat ugly little nons legs lover
that will absolutely do nothing. and he
knows what's good for him. That's why
he'll never put his location up. Yeah,
it's true though, ain't it, Bob? It is true.
But yeah, um yeah, in the new year, bro,
I'll just I'll just go up there. I don't
mind, lads. I will really really just go
up there. I I've got no problem doing
that. Staying in a nice hotel,
you know? I'm not scared of any of these
[ __ ] people, bro. I hate them. You
know, even when my mom talks about I
hate these people. You don't understand,
Dad. I really hate these people,
you know. So, I'll just I'll just go up
there and we'll see who'll do nothing,
bro. We'll see who will do nothing.
[ __ ] stupid [ __ ] Little nonsleg.
You can't troll someone like me. I find
it very very offensive when someone
tries to underestimate your intelligence.
You understand, bro? I'm not [ __ ] Monty, man.
That's up, bro.
Yeah, that's self projection, bro.
Yeah. It's almost 2026, brother. Do you
think you can easy off, please?
Maybe easy off. [snorts]
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Nice, bro. Do you
reckon you could easy off, bro? It's almost 2026.
Can you stop it now, bro? It's very,
very boring now. You know, the self
projection. It's very, very, very boring.
Who the [ __ ] is that guy?
Weird. Yeah, you need to ease off, lad.
M. They're always on there, man. They
never stop. I'm surprised I don't get
bored challenge. I went um live 9:00 in
the morning for 5 minutes. I went to my
sisters at 10:00. Um and I thought, you
know what, bro? Um let me see who's on
and yeah, haters again. Christmas Day.
And they didn't even say, "Oh, merry
Christmas," or anything. They come on
straight away and they hated.
It's madness, bro. When are these people
really going to get a life?
[ __ ] They've been doing this for
[ __ ] eight years now, bro. That's why
I don't come on here anymore.
That's why I don't come on here anymore,
brother. It's a pattern with these people, you know?
Yeah. Hating on [ __ ] Christmas Day,
bro. Imagine that. I actually had fun. I
had some Guinness, had some nice food.
I watched the new horror film, by the way.
Oh, are you uh are you caring?
Yeah, that's what I will be doing, bro.
And I'll be disabling the likes and the dislikes.
Yeah, like I said I was going to do if
I'm on it. That's what I will be doing,
bro, to be fair.
And I'll just I'll just I'll start by
going to leads. I don't mind going to
leads again, bro. I don't mind going up
there again and calling calling this
Joseph Bar out,
you know, this [ __ ] fat [ __ ] clown
ugly fat fingers with a fat ugly misses
and see what he's about face to face
little nonslegs lover. But then again,
he's probably just like his boyfriend uh
nonslegs. Well, at the end of the day,
at least Timmy's calling him out now to
be fair. At least Timmy's calling him out. That's good.
That's good, bro.
But yeah, I know what you mean, Timmy.
No one does go for nons legs, do they?
It's probably because they were nons like him.
How do you know he's been on all day?
Unless you was on all day.
That doesn't make sense. How would you
know he's he was on all day if you're
not on all day? That's strange.
Yeah. Money man was being a copycat today. Little copycat.
Now you want to talk about copycats,
right? So I watched this horror film.
Yeah. And I [ __ ] started crushing on
this [ __ ] made hard, bro. And I
didn't even realize she was really,
really famous, you know? I didn't know
until I like looked up after that she's
really famous. I didn't copy anyone. I
didn't know who she was. Never heard
about this woman in my life once. Do you
know what I'm saying? Like I didn't know
anything about her. And a lot of people
don't like her. Um, in this horror film,
I'm not like [ __ ] nons
car. Oh, homo vibes. Gay, gay, gay. If
you don't like her, you're gay. That
would never ever ever be me. [ __ ]
funny enough, I was scrolling on [ __ ]
Reddit uh where was it the other day?
And someone had said if you didn't like
Rihanna back in the day that that you're
gay. See, it's just all copycats. The
copycats are out. It's just cop [ __ ]
Rihanna was never [ __ ] good-looking.
Enough to [ __ ] brag about. [ __ ] Rihanna.
What the [ __ ]
I don't know why these people put these
celebrities on a pedestal
just to fit in. It's [ __ ] ridiculous.
They literally put these celebrities on
a pedestal just to fit in.
But I didn't know this blonde woman
until I until I looked her up. I didn't know anything.
So, I don't copy and I certainly would
not say that someone's gay if they don't
like if they don't find someone
attractive. I don't copy people. I'm not
a little copycat.
Yeah. I watched The Housemaid and this
[ __ ] housemaid is I like this
housemaid and she's very famous. I
didn't know that. I didn't never heard
of her. Never heard of any of the two
before watching that.
Yep. I got Lely Ugg boots.
But I'm probably biased just cuz I love
boobies, you know, and she gets a lot of
hate and a lot of people call her ugly.
I don't [ __ ] sit there and say Chev
Cole's attractive to fit in. You're okay
if you don't like Sher Cole. What a [ __ ] copycat.
If you if you actually go on the Chevel
Cole thing, you will see that there's
very very few people there's very very
few people that will say Shel Cole's not
good-looking because they all copy each
other. They used to do it with Rio as
well. Homobo vibes. That's no homo.
Yeah, you should watch that horror film,
The Housemaid. It was It was good. It
There's too many sex scenes in these
horror films, though, bro. There's too
many sex scenes. It's not good. I went
to watch a horror film, not a [ __ ]
porno. And it was only [ __ ] 15 as well.
[ __ ] with your head. That does. [ __ ]
Yeah, it's um it's not good, bro. Why
have they always got to add sex scenes
in these horror films? Mad.
I haven't been out for ages, bro. I
haven't approached for ages.
What's that tell you, bro? What's that
tell you? [snorts]
I need to make a tea in a minute. I need
to try and get to the dentist.
I need a fill in. Uh, Autumn,
I need a little filling.
I think it's bad though like they put
like these porno scenes in a hor in in
horror movies because a a a lot of
people don't watch porn, right? I'd say
more people don't than do. There's a lot
of people that don't basically. And
there's a reason why they don't watch
it. So, you don't expect to go to a
horror fil watch a horror film and um
you know, see that [ __ ] you know? I
think it's bad. And they done it
multiple times as well. They done it
multiple times on this new horror film.
And they always make the woman Peter
Betty's type as well. It's like they
know my type and then they they [ __ ]
do it on purpose. I'm only joking, but
like the sex the sex scenes really
really need to stop. Um,
is he on you? Is this red star typing away?
What the [ __ ]
One second. Let me see.
You on YouTube?
All right. Listen, Red Star. Listen.
One second. I've just gone to my other account.
Do you know what? I don't care about any
of the things that you say, Red Star.
Do you want me to tell you why?
There you go. It's because
everything that you say is about
yourself. You're never going to meet
anyone. You're never going to give your
location. You're just a fat, ugly, bold,
disabled, low life. That's why people
don't get triggered over you. You can't
meet anyone. You can't even as much as
say where you live. So, how could
anybody get triggered over a little
coward m like you? They can't. You're
the one typing on YouTube every day.
You're the one making videos
because you ain't got a life. You don't
trigger no one. You don't bother no one.
I went on an unblocking spree today just
to show that you don't bother no one.
You're just a keyboard warrior. You've
wasted eight years doing this and it
hasn't changed the fact that you're the
bold one. You're the fat one. You're the
ugly one. And you will never ever tell
me where you live.
Nothing's changed in 8 years. It's
boring now. You're the one that's typing
in capital letters. You're the one
that's triggered. You will never ever
meet me ever. You will never ever ever meet me.
Everything that you say is projection.
We've all seen it with you people when
you've come on here and you've hated
people and then your camera's been put
on. And at the end of the day, we've all
seen what you ugly fat people [snorts]
look like. So, it doesn't bother us.
It's just self projection.
How about me? How about me and you meet
tomorrow? No, not tomorrow. It's Boxing Day. Um,
meet me on the 27th.
Let's meet on the 27th and we'll see
what you what you've got to say to my
face. You do a video showing where you
are and I'll travel anywhere you want me to.
Go on. Just just do a video saying where
you are and I will travel anywhere you
want. Wales, Scotland. And if you're not
prepared to do that, then the joke's on
you and you're a coward.
So you can spend another eight years
doing this [ __ ] bro. But at the end of
the day, it's not going to change that
the fact that you're the bold one,
you're the skinn one, you're the ugly
one. You can do it for another 16 years
and it's not going to change that
everything that you're saying is about yourself.
So there you go. So you don't want to
meet. Okay. So I terminate the
conversation. Simple. Same thing as I
done with Joseph Far. It's quite simple.
If these people are not going to meet
you, I'm not going to go back and forth for them.
Monty needs to stop copying me though.
That is [ __ ] pathetic. He definitely
got that idea for me. So at the end of
the day, yeah, if you're not going to
meet me, I'm not going to waste my time.
Same thing with that Joseph Ferrar. You
can hate all your life. No one cares.
You know, no one really gives a [ __ ]
you're a sad bastard, bro. Very sad. I I
called him out, bro, last week and he
won't meet me. That Joseph Ferrar won't
meet me, bro.
I've tried calling him that. He will not
meet. He's He's another nonslegs.
He's another little nonslegs. He talks
[ __ ] [ __ ] but he will never meet
anyone. He's [ __ ] probably in a
wheelchair. He's another nonslegs.
He's another nonslegs, bro. He will
never meet anyone.
They're all the same,
you know? They're all the [ __ ] same
on here. Him and these little fake wins.
Hey, let me tell you straight. Yeah.
What? Oh, that's another thing I saw the
other day. Jealous. Why would I be
jealous? I've got my own money.
No, he would never put his face out
there, bro. Cuz these people are fat and
ugly, so of course he's not going to put
his face out there, bro. Why would that
make me jealous? Because I'm I'm saying
that you're showing fake wins.
What? Bro, I've got my own money. I can
gamble whatever I want. I can do
whatever I want. I get money. I make
money. Brother, listen. I would love,
this is what I've tried saying multiple
times to these people, Bob. Yeah.
Is that uh I would love somebody, right,
to go to the bookies and rinse them out
and then the bookies go bust. I'd love
that [ __ ] Why the [ __ ] would I be
jealous? Because I'm pointing a fact out
where you're, you know, you're only this
guy. I'm telling you what this guy does.
Yeah, Bob. He puts his money in and he
and he and he acts like he's won.
Do you know what I'm saying, bro? Like,
he does not win that many times. And and
that's not being jealous. I don't need
to be jealous. I've got my own money,
bro. I can gamble whenever I want. I
don't give a [ __ ] Money doesn't bother
me. I've got my own money. But you know
what I'm saying, bro? Like, he There's
no way somebody can keep winning like
that, bro. That's facts. That's not
being jealous, bro. It's the same thing.
If I was to put roulette videos up and
people started coming saying, "Why the [ __ ]
bro? He doesn't put anyone through
anything. He just puts himself through
stuff by doing videos." He He He doesn't
bother me. That's why I haven't blocked
him, bro. He's just like Pat Mustard,
fat and ugly. He doesn't bother me. He
bothers himself. He has to come on here
every day embarrassing himself for eight
years. He doesn't bother me. He has no
effect. That's why I'm still here. He
has no effect.
Because you people on here,
don't bother me. You don't bother me.
That's why I'm on here. I'm unbothered.
People that get bullied, people get to
tormented, don't come back for more.
That means that you're lacking effect.
What you're doing isn't working.
Well, I'm surpris I'm still on here
because you people don't torment no one.
That's why I'm still on here. Cuz
everything you do is repeating. It's all
repeating. Think about it, bro. Yeah.
You done something right that tormented
someone years ago. You're coming on here
repeating yourselves every day. Every
day of your lives.
Every day of your lives, you are on
here. You're tormenting yourself. I feel
sorry for you. That's partly sometimes
why I come on here and like, you know,
give you some attention. Anyone can be
fat and ugly like you people and hate
all your life. Anyone can do that. Any
fat ugly people. Nope. He didn't get me
afflicted. And I'm not going over that
again cuz I've already explained it.
These people have not affected my life.
I've got a roof over my head. I've got
more money than them. I'm better looking
than them. So, I mean, the point still stands, bro.
So, no, he didn't. And we're not going
to get into that again. I'm not explaining.
Yeah. I'm desperate for attention. Okay,
I haven't been on here for a week, bro.
I definitely do have more money. Yes, I
do. I def death have got more money than
you people. Like I said to my mom, like
I said to my mom today, why don't you
put the Christmas tree up? Why don't you
put the presents up? Because I don't
need to prove myself to these people.
Bro, it's because it's all self-p
projection. Oh my god. PJ's evidence
pack. I do not understand with people
like Non Legs and Red Star, they're
[ __ ] ugly. They do this to make
themselves feel better about the fact
that they're ugly. Do you not
understand? Do you not understand what
projection means? I've explained it multiple times.
They do it because they know that you're
better looking than them. They know
they're ugly. And the only way they can
get over that is, "Yep, you're on
YouTube Christmas Day.
Yep, you people are on YouTube Christmas
Day." I mean, my Christmas is over,
brother. Listen, let's just stop the
self-p projection [ __ ] now. Come on. I
was on YouTube.
Yeah, they are PJ's evidence. They are
absolutely what they are. Listen,
listen. What they are, these people on
here. Yeah. Is they hate anyone younger
and better looking than them. These
people, okay, let me let me tell you
with these people, bro. Yeah. They are
fat, ugly people. They failed at
everything they've tried in life. And
that's why they come on here. I was on
here. Yeah. 9:00 in the morning. PJ's
evidence pack, bro. I come on here at um
9:00 in the morning for 5 minutes, bro.
Yeah. 5 minutes. Yeah. Um and they were
on here. They were on here, bro. And I
literally I went to my sisters at 10:00.
I literally said when I woke up, I would
go live for 5 minutes just to see if
these people on YouTube. And they were
on YouTube. They were on YouTube. Then
they tried telling me that I've got no
family. I've got no money. Everything
has always been projection with these
people. It always has been and always
will be. Brother, why do you think none
of these people will come on here and
show their faces because they're fat and ugly?
Because they're fat and ugly. That's why
they won't. This is why they do this.
They're fat, ugly people. Even my friend
has said this as well, bro. That's why
no one cares about these people.
I was live for 5 minutes. PJ's evidence
before I went to my sisters. I was at my
sisters all day. had food, got presents,
bro, you know. So, I was with my friend.
I PJ's evidence. I was with my friend um
with my sister, with my mom, ate food,
got presents. I got presents and
everything, bro. Like, yeah. Okay. I was
live for 5 minutes. I didn't I wasn't
even on 5 minutes. I walked down the
stairs and I walked upstairs and it was
the same people. And I felt like I felt
like hugging my mom. You know, PJ's evidence.
PJ's evidence pack. I wanted to hug my
mom. I was like, as a relief, it was
them all along.
And my mom, do you know what my mom
said? PJ's evidence pack. Do you know
what my mom said? She said, "Why don't
you show the Christmas tree and the
presents?" And you know what I turned
around and said? I don't need to show
these people anything. I don't need to
prove myself to these people.
That's another thing uh PJ's evidence
pack. These people think that you need
to prove themselves to them. I'm not
showing them nothing, mate. I'm not
proving myself to these people.
When they come on here, PJ's evidence back
and they show their face, then I'll
start proving stuff. I think that's
fair, isn't it? I think that's fair what
I said. They come on here, they start
showing their face, and I'll start
showing them money. I can show them
money. I've got money. I can show them
money. Can show them the Christmas tree.
I can show them everything that they
want, bro. You know, but we don't need
to prove ourselves to these sad,
pathetic, no family people.
But Monty is a big [ __ ] stinking
copycat, though. They're fat, they're
ugly, they're skint, they've been doing
this for [ __ ] years.
Like I said, PJ's evidence. I'll just be
going doing videos now, disabling the
likes and the and the comments, bro.
Yeah, you don't need to know how much
money I have. You don't need to know that.
And you know how better you feel when
you're not on here, PJ's evidence pack.
You feel so good, bro. You feel so good
when you're not on here, man. Because
obviously when you're surrounded by
repeating low-life people every day,
when you when you keep interacting with
these people, they kind of wear off on
you, bro. So like after like 2 3 days
you're like oh [ __ ] I actually feel
normal bro because that's how disabled
these people are bro. You understand? So
I'm not showing you any money. I can but
I'm not showing you any money. And stop
repeating yourself brother. It's almost 2026.
I can but I'm not showing you no money.
Self projection. Stop repeating. Time
for a new episode.
Time for a new episode. Episode, lad.
Yes, I can, but I'm not showing you nothing.
Okay. Yeah, I'm skin. Okay. Go repeat on
another channel. It's boring now.
See, this is what they do, bro. It's
just self projection from these
repeating people every day.
It's just self projection. This is Have
you noticed I don't really come on here
much? Uh PJ's evidence, lad. I don't
really come on here much anymore. I just
woke up at 3:00 in the morning. I was
like, "Ah, I want to show everyone that
these people have got no life on this
day today. I won't be live now for
[ __ ] ages, bro. After this, I don't
really come on much anymore, bro. Cuz
it's just the same repeating people.
I'm sure you've noticed that."
Yeah, I know I do, bro. I know I do.
Eight years they've been doing this. Uh
PJ's evidence back. Eight years, bro. 8 years.
Imagine that, bro. Eight [ __ ] years.
Okay, that's good for you. If you don't
think I have money, that's nice.
I mean, PJ's evidence pack, they they
called me a virgin even though I
approved I've had sex. I mean, come on
now, bro. I was on Timmy's um thing
earlier and he's calling me a virgin
even though I approved I've had sex.
What the [ __ ]
He's calling me a virgin even though I
proved I've had sex. Jesus [ __ ] Christ.
Am I seeing things, bro? Or is this actually happening?
[ __ ] And then you got this Joseph Farra
thinking that he's intelligent, but he's
not intelligent. I know what he's trying
to do, bro. Do you know you know this
Joseph Ra? I I clocked on what he's
trying to do.
with his little fake wins and that,
right? I know, bro. I'm too intelligent
for these people. Trust me, I I already
knew straight away, bro.
But he started sticking up for nons legs
and stuff like what he does is he he's
showing fake wins. That's not jealousy.
That's facts. Why would I be jealous of
a fat old ugly man, right, that's got
nothing in his life, bro? Why would Why
would I need to be jealous? Because I'm
point because I'm stating facts
that you're showing fake wins because
people do not win like that on them machines, brother.
It's not being jealous. It's talking facts,
you know. It's not, bro. Why don't I
would love people to rinse the bookies
out and and and make him go bust. I'd
love it. I would absolutely [ __ ] love
it. But it's not how it works. We know that.
If someone constantly kept winning on
football, you'd believe it. You know,
you'd believe it. If someone done a
single or they done a double, you'd
believe it. You know what I'm saying?
But it's not possible. This guy is not
winning like he's showing, bro.
There's another little nonsle lover,
another little keyboard warrior that
talks [ __ ] behind people's back but will
never meet anyone. You know, it's it's
what they are there, bro.
Madness, isn't it?
Weird people, bro. Weird people.
Uh, let me open the thingy.
Bro, that that dinner was so nice today, man.
That was [ __ ] banging.
Did you get a Christmas dinner PJ's evidence pack?
[sighs and gasps]
It was good, bro. Good.
Yeah, it's like nons legs. Your skin,
your skin. The only one that's skin is
himself. You can do this for another
eight years, brother. And it's not going
to change the fact that it's yourselves,
you know, cuz if these people had all of
this money, they wouldn't be on him
every day. Simple.
And if that Joseph Far thinks he's going
to come on one more time and wind me up,
brother, I'm going to try to arrange to
meet him for the second time.
Within the within the same day. The same day. Yeah.
Don't [ __ ] come and try and tell
people they'll do nothing. But I'll
happily go to leads, book a nice hotel.
You [ __ ] nonsloving [ __ ]
You dirty nonsloving [ __ ]
I'm used to it, mate. I've traveled everywhere.
I said to my mom as well, it's not going
to be a waste of time or money because
I've wanted to go back up for a while,
you know. It's it's not going to be a waste.
Trust me, bro. Go to the northeast
again. Have no problem doing that, you know.
I'm having uh dinner again today, bro.
It's going to be lush. >> [laughter] [snorts]
>> that Food was lovely, mate.
All right, Mr. I was watching some Mr.
Bean videos earlier.
You reminded me of you. Yeah.
Yeah. I went live for 5 minutes earlier,
9:00 in the morning. The first comment
was, "Oh, have you bought anything for
your girlfriend?" "Oh, wait." And I'm
thinking, bro, again, same self
projection. This person that's typing
this is probably a 40year-old [ __ ]
virgin who's never even been laid.
What the [ __ ] bro?
Yeah, they hated as soon as I went live.
Bro, I I showed what these people are
about today. Why am I live now? Because
my day is over. I've not long woke up. But yeah, [cough] [clears throat]
money makes me laugh. He's like, that's
five people that's got no family now.
That's five people that's got no family.
But yeah, I had 18 people on my live
stream and I never get 18 people within
[ __ ] 5 minutes, mate.
Never. Never. Not even on a Saturday. So
it goes to show, bro.
It goes to show. He said that's five people.
That's five people that's got no family this Christmas. >> [snorts]
>> Oh gosh.
Well, I know I was live for 5 minutes,
mate, and there was people typing and
there was 18 people watching. So,
oh my god, that woman in that film is sexy, bro.
[ __ ] hell. Any New Year's uh resolutions basically
Oh, I didn't drink all my cola.
>> Oh gosh.
>> Oh, you what?
You like my little evidence pack.
[snorts] My little evidence pack.
A little evidence pack.
Yeah, look. Got a chocolate.
I don't need 500. I got my own money, matey.
I got a chocolate.
Yeah. Can I have one?
looking rough. Why don't you come on
camera come and show what you look like, love? Darling,
why don't you come on camera come and
show us what you look like.
Let's see what you look like, lad. I
just made myself a cup of coffee.
You're going to give me £500.
Why don't you give it to someone that needs it?
Huh? Why don't you give someone Why
don't you give someone the money that
needs it, lad?
Why don't you give it to someone that
needs it, bro?
Like the skin virgin
that's in desperate need to get lagged.
Not me, bro. I don't need 500 [ __ ]
pound, bro. The [ __ ] Give it to the
skint virgin. Then he won't feel the
need to show daddy savings or daddy's life savings.
I think I can hear Laney watching my YouTube video.
Yeah, I think Laney's watching my
YouTube video that I done um earlier
about these people. Oh gosh.
[snorts] Oh gosh.
These people was on YouTube Christmas Day.
I can't believe it.
That's five people that ain't got a
family. I was dead when money said that. Yeah. Um
yeah, I just had some uh well, I just
had a chocolate.
Nope. I ain't drinking for a couple of
months, bro. So, I basically done this, right?
This is basically uh what the plan is.
Um I'm basically what I'm going to do is
I'm going to exhaust
every option I possibly can before I go
out try again. So, we're going to try
the pawn industry. Uh we're going to
look for other things. I'm going to
exhaust out every single option because
I don't want to try again. I shouldn't
have to try again. I don't want to deal
with immature um people and people that
play games. So, I think the only time
I'm going to try again is if I'm forced
to and I have no other option but to
that tells you a lot. That tells you a
lot, mate. At [ __ ] you know, 28
years of age, if you are considering
joining the [ __ ] porn industry and
not have to approach again,
you know, that's Yeah. It tells you how
fed up someone is, you know. I'm done. D
done, bro. I'm done. Done. D done, you
know. But if I have to do it again, I
will have to do it again, you know. But hopefully not.
Yeah. Really? Yeah. That's nice for you, bro. So,
it was that [ __ ] thing that triggered
me. That horror film, bro. Them sex
scenes with that [ __ ] woman. It was
triggering as [ __ ] bro.
That new horror film. Did you watch it? Um, Dusty,
the housemmaid was [ __ ] sexy, bro.
[ __ ] me. I didn't even know she was
really famous, um, until I looked her
up. Um, you know,
um, [clears throat] um, Dusty, I didn't
know, lad. That's why I looked her up.
See, I don't go by names. I didn't even
know the person's name. I didn't know anything, bro.
I didn't know. I didn't know about the
names and stuff, bro.
Yeah, they're not going to win, bro. I'm
not going to be approaching unless I
don't get into the pool industry. That's
the only way I'm going to be doing it
again. I don't want to do it again, bro.
Cuz they're all the [ __ ] same. That's
why I'm trying to [ __ ] exhaust like
every other option
before, you know, doing it again.
But yeah, I don't go by names, bro. I
don't say that if you don't like a
certain person, you're gay. I'm not a
copycat. I got a mind of my own.
This [ __ ] cat was following me
earlier, Dusty. It kept following me everywhere.
I think it was waiting for its next
copycat statement. [sighs]
Yeah, it kept harassing me. the [ __ ] cat earlier. Yeah.
Waiting for its next copycat statement. No.
Yeah, them them porn scenes in the
horror films ain't good, bro.
I don't know why they have them.
They done it a couple of times. They
done it a couple of times as well, you know.
Lucky there was a twist twist to the
horror film that made it not as bad, but
it was still pretty bad to be honest.
Cuz you should be getting sex. You
should have a sex life. [snorts] There's
no reason why you don't have one, you know.
Even sex once a month. Not really. You
should be getting sex at least once a
month. Oh, and I can't use um I won't
use escorts anyways because I don't want
to use a condom. So, that's out the window now. >> [gasps]
>> Why am I going to have sex with a condom
when you can? You wouldn't get You
wouldn't go in a bath with clothes on,
would you? So why would why the [ __ ]
would you want to use a condom?
[ __ ] that, bro. No, that's just that's
pointless. I'm not using a condom. So
I'm basically fat. So yeah, madness, bro.
I'm not using a condom. [ __ ] that.
[snorts] So obviously, like I said, it's
it's it's got to be the um
it's the porn industry that I have to go down.
I'm not using a I'm not using a condom, bro.
Yeah, them sex scenes in the horror
films aren't good, bro. They're a big trigger.
Yeah, you can do it in Thailand.
Well, if I can, I want to try and do
anything other than having to go out and
approach ever again because I I should
have to do it. I'm 28 years of age. I
should have to try again.
It's so toxic. It's very, very, very, very toxic.
Toxic. They're all the same. And I was
watching this approach earlier. Yeah,
Dusty. This guy appro he's he's in
Manchester. He's from London, but he's
in Manchester. He approached this woman
and she was like, "Oh, uh, I'm on the
phone. Can you walk away?" I would have
I would have told her, "Who the [ __ ] do
you think you're talking to?" Even just
hearing it, bro. Even when it's not even
when it's not Yeah. about you. It's Who
the [ __ ] are you talking to, brother?
They weren't even about me. They weren't
even saying it to me. Who do they think they are?
So many [ __ ] in this country.
So many [ __ ] in this country. It's
unbelievable. Men and women,
you know. Yeah. So, well,
what are you going to do? Keep going
that approach and getting the same [ __ ]
Dusty? It's not normal, bro.
That made that horror film was sexy,
bro. Like I said, I didn't even know who
she was. So I didn't even know she was
really famous until I went back. Whereas
was [ __ ] nons legs dusty. He was
saying [ __ ] shovel car was attractive
to fit in.
He was saying it to [ __ ] copy the crowd.
Homo vibes. I smell I smell homo. What
is it with these [ __ ] people putting
these [ __ ] on a [ __ ] pedestal?
Like I was saying earlier before you was
here, Dusty, they done it to [ __ ]
Rihanna as well. If you don't like
Rihanna, you got something wrong with
you. Why are they putting these [ __ ]
average looking people on a [ __ ] pedestal?
You know, I don't understand.
I don't think she is. I don't think she
is. And if you do, then that's that's
you, bro. And everyone's allowed their
opinion. But this [ __ ] is saying if you
don't find her attractive, you're gay. That's copying
that is literally copying the crowd.
I don't think she's hot at all.
Definitely definitely definitely
definitely not. You can obviously you
can. Anyone's allowed a preference, but
he was copying because he was saying
that if you don't find them attractive
that you're gay. That is copying.
It's like this [ __ ] you know,
housemmaid. I wouldn't sat there and I
wouldn't sat there and say, bro, um I
wouldn't sit there and say um
I wouldn't sit there and say, "Oh, if
you don't find her attractive, you're
gay." That's ridiculous, bro.
This is copying. That is literally copying, bro.
Look, Rihanna. Look, I'm looking her up
now. Yeah, Rihanna.
She's nothing special.
I think Rihanna's Rihanna's quite ugly
to be honest. She's got a big forehead.
But yeah, it's definitely definitely copying.
Definitely definitely definitely copying. Yeah,
definitely not for me. That sh
Definitely not for me. No,
that's a stupid thing to say to be honest.
Yeah, a lot of copycats out there, mate.
A lot of copycats out there.
The reason I said about this housemaid
is cuz obviously I like boobs and stuff
and I like the way their body looked. I
didn't know they were really famous.
They got 25 million followers on
Instagram. I didn't know this.
So, I didn't come across them and then
started saying, "Oh, you're gay. Homo."
You know, I can't believe he actually
said that. Fruit King. He's like, "Homo,
gay. Homo. I smell homo.
They all used to copy each other.
All used to copy each other, didn't they? No,
I've never found her attractive, man. Never.
She ain't got no tits. She ain't got no
ass. How can I find that attractive? Yeah.
You used to have thought I was ultimate drag. Really?
But then again, I suppose you probably
don't have a mirror, do you? To look in. So,
and yes, I have been on the um co
because I need a filling. So, [gasps]
and I've been having a toothache.
Nope. I'm not going out New Year's Eve.
I was going to, but no,
I need to try to join this porn
industry. I need to try a couple of
things and then if it doesn't work, then
I'll have to go out again. So, at least
I'm trying to break the cycle.
I shouldn't have to be, bro. At 28,
listen, you not you don't understand,
right? At 28, even 27, 28, 27, 28, 29,
you should be, you should be settled
down with someone. 24, 25, 26, you go
out. I used to go out twice a week. You
are supposed to be settled at this age,
not going out drinking all the time. You
pass that stage. And it's not cuz of
money. I've got money, you know, and and
I used to do it, you know, even when I
had less money. You shouldn't have to
keep doing this,
you know. At 28, you should be [ __ ]
settled. You know, priorities change. I
said this to my mom the other day as
well. You know, you shouldn't have to
keep going out trying. I've already tried enough.
So, that's why I'm, you know, obviously
thinking of other things. New Year's Eve is overpriced, overpriced, overrated.
I'll probably go out midFeb March to be honest.
That's the best best month is March to
go drinking. Yeah, New Year's Eve is
it's overpriced and it's um
it's overrated. Yeah,
in [snorts and clears throat] London
anyways. So, yeah, probably not.
You [ __ ] tried to go to [ __ ]
Edinburgh? Yeah, the hotels are like
[ __ ] £500 on New Year's Eve. Are you
mad? [ __ ] that.
So, yeah, I'd rather just wait till
midFeb March to be honest. I don't mind. >> [snorts]
>> Yeah. [ __ ] that, bro. [ __ ] that.
It's not nice when it's too busy.
No. Best day to go drinking is Thursday.
I used to always love Thursdays because
it wasn't too busy, but it was busy
enough. It was busy enough, but not too
busy. Does that make sense? And then if
you wanted to go out drinking on a
Saturday, you could just go on a
Saturday as well. Whereas, if you go out
on a Friday, you can't go on a Saturday
cuz you're still hung over. So yeah. [sighs]
[snorts] Yeah. That's the same with
Christmas though, isn't it? People
getting into [ __ ] debt over Christmas
for one day. Buying presents they can't
afford only for one day and then when
the day is over everything's back to normal. [gasps] I know.
It's madness, isn't it?
And then everyone's skinned generally. [laughter]
Everyone's skinned until like
midFebruary, March after that. It's
funny, isn't it? [snorts]
I got electric toothbrush. I got some I
got something to do with Guinness.
I got I got quite a few things to be honest.
You don't care about Christmas as you get older.
I was only excited for the food. The
food was [ __ ] banging, bro. Banging.
I had lamb and turkey.
And I said like the only way you're
really going to get a sex life where you
don't have to use a condom is is by
joining the you know the the porn industry
really that's what else are you going to
do what keep approaching and dealing
with their [ __ ] year in year out. I am
not doing that.
I am not you know I feel stable now you
know I don't want to go back to that [ __ ] again.
Toxicness the dickheadness the excuses.
[ __ ] that bro. I don't want to go. Uh if
I could possibly avoid it. Um
I will I'll do anything to avoid doing
that again. You know,
they're snakes. Um Fruit King, these
women, they're rats. That's what they
are. They're rats. They're snakes. And I
don't care, bro. I don't I don't hate
[ __ ] women. I just I'm just saying it
how it is, bro. Like, I'm completely
calm. I'm stable. I'm telling you how it is, bro.
You know, [sighs]
I'm just telling you how it is, bro. I'm
not a virgin like Timmy. I got no reason
to be [ __ ] uh biased, bro. They're
proper proper rats.
They're proper proper rats, bro. And I'm
And I'm, you know, I'm telling you it,
brother. You They actually are. They are
actual [ __ ] bro.
I don't talk about this. I don't moan
about this, bro. Like, ever. I'm just
saying it how it is, bro. Cuz we're
talking about the conversation,
bro. Stop bringing that nons up. No one
cares about that little keyboard warrior
nons. This is why I don't come on here anymore.
Cuz I'm sick of hearing about these
[ __ ] lowife people, brother. So,
that's why it's like I'll tell you a
story, fruiting. Yeah. So, there was
this there was this woman, bro, that I
used to rent um like rooms to years ago.
someone else rent a room to, right? I
was talking. It was on good terms. They
they live in Spain. I found out they
were in London. I said, "Oh, let's meet
up." And then they started ignoring me.
Message them again. They ignored me,
bro. I just blocked them. I was like,
"What the fuck?"
Like, they're very snaky. They're rats,
bro. They are. They really are. That's
not even me hating, bro. That's me
talking the truth.
Seriously, it is. And I'm not even I'm
not even contradicting myself when I'm
saying it. They they generally are they
generally are [ __ ] bro.
It would it would make sense for Timmy
to say this stuff and not believe it cuz
he's a virgin.
But I don't need to lie about this, bro.
I've been with plenty of women. Um, and yeah,
and do you know the mo you know the most
[ __ ] up thing about it? Yeah. I can't
I was speaking to this woman on Reddit
the other day. Yeah. And she says she's
jaded over the uh dating scene. This was
someone else. Even though she can get
dates and she can get sex. So if they
feel jaded over being able to get dates
and get sex
because obviously the people not staying
with them, how do you think somebody
feels if they can't even get a date or
get sex and have to deal with a million
and one toxic different things.
But no one has any consideration for
men. They don't give a [ __ ] This is
what I mean. It's the whole thing is
just like wrong. Obviously I understand.
Yeah. Obviously I understand. Yeah. that
like, you know, men are not supposed to
um complain if you're dealing with the
same thing, but you're not dealing with
the same thing as them. So, I mean,
you've got a right to say something
about it. They're [ __ ] moaning when
they can get dates and can get sex when
I ain't even had a date since March,
you know? Like, that's like what the
[ __ ] Think of the amount of time and
money that's gone into that. And but
they're moaning because,
you know, they're they're getting
they're getting dates and getting sex,
bro. And and they're moaning. So if they
if that's making them feel depressed,
how is that going to make a man feel if
they can't even get a date?
So think about like that, bro. That's
the way I think of it. It's just all
[ __ ] It's all toxic. Never.
Why would I do that, bro? [ __ ] that.
But I'm just stating facts, bro. Like,
why why, you know, how how is how is
someone else how is a man supposed to feel then?
I've got to go to a [ __ ] cinema
watching a sex scene
when I didn't [ __ ] choose to [ __ ] watch porn.
It's bad. It is really, really bad, bro.
It's really, really, really, really bad.
It's like I said, it's not that you're
uh it's not that you're um going through
the same thing as them and you're
bitching. You've had it a million times
worse than them and no one acknowledges it,
you know, and you realize how toxic it
is because when you give up, you'll know
you'll know how toxic it is cuz as soon
as you give up,
you'll notice a change in your mood
because the whole thing is toxic to
begin with. That's how toxic it is.
You'll know. Trust me, you'll know.
Anyone that's dating, just give up for a
week, week and a half, and damn, watch
your mood change. See? So,
they can get dates and they can get sex
and they're moaning. They're
complaining. That's what I don't understand.
[clears throat] Madness.
So could you imagine they couldn't get
dates, they couldn't get sex, and they
had to approach the way that you did.
They probably end up killing themselves.
So look at it that way, you know?
I don't understand it, bro. I really don't.
It's just all [ __ ] up, is it?
But yeah, that's why I don't try
anymore, bro. [snorts]
[ __ ] that. That's toxic as [ __ ]
the lying [ __ ]
you know. [ __ ] that. Ain't it, Bob? And
it's worse when they're lying because we
know that they're actually lying.
I know that they're lying. So, it makes
it worse because it's so obvious that they're lying.
So, when they're trying to say that
you're not Muslim and you're not this
and you're like, we all know that
they're full of [ __ ]
which is toxic. That's what I'm That's
what I mean by it's toxic. So that's that.
Not moaning. I've given up, bro. It
doesn't bother me. But I'm just saying, you know,
it is bad, bro. It's bad.
It will never change, bro. Never change. Yeah. So, yeah. Positive
mental attitude is not going to is not
going to change stuck up [ __ ] Unfortunately, brother,
that's not going to change the way women
are. Whether you're positive or
negative, they will always be the way
they are, lad. [sighs and gasps]
No, I was drinking Guinness earlier. I
was drinking a can of Stella and um
kind of Stella and beer.
Uh, sorry bro. Um,
can of Stella and then um I got some I
got two cans I got two glasses of
Guinness for Christmas and I just had
one. So, no, I just drunk some beer
earlier. But yeah, you can be positive
all you want, but you're not going to
change the way women are
whether you're positive or you're
negative. That's obviously why I'm
looking at alternatives. pool industry,
you know, obviously, you know, this is
this is mental, bro. And it's not even
that, Bob. Because even if you even if
you got friends, you still won't meet
anyone through friends. I've got
friends. I've had friends. You still
don't meet anyone through them.
Not everyone does. Some people do. Not
everyone does. Cuz everyone's just out for themselves.
Bro, you can't even trust your family.
For [ __ ] sake. And I don't mean my
family. I'm just saying generally. Bro,
you wouldn't even be able to trust your
family. Like your a family member could
throw you under the bus, you know?
So, I don't think friends are going to
introduce you to someone somehow. That's
just me being real, bro. Like, I'm not
going to sugarcoat [ __ ] you know?
That's just the way it is.
Cuz I know if I have to go and approach
again, I'm going to go through hell and
back to even get a date. And I'm not
prepared to do it. So, let's make sure
we exhaust every option before we we try again.
You know, it's bad. It is really bad.
It's that [ __ ] sex scene in that
horror film. It triggered the [ __ ] out
of me, bro.
It triggered the [ __ ] out of me, you know?
Bro, what the [ __ ] man? Yep.
Did I get bricked? What do you mean did
So yeah. Um if nothing else works and
I'll give up until March.
Um then obviously [clears throat] March
I'll try again on midFeb.
No, I was just watching this horror film
and this [ __ ] the housemaid was sexy, bro.
And she was [ __ ] the the the the
wife's husband. Mad, mad, mad, mad. See,
that can [ __ ] with your head. Stuff like
that. Which, like I said, that's why a
lot of people don't watch porn. I went
to watch a horror film that was 15. Not
a [ __ ] porno.
No, but you No, but you saw her boobs.
Bad, bro. Really bad.
[ __ ] hell. That was bad, bro. I told
my mom about it when I come back as well.
Yeah, it's [ __ ] sexy, bro.
Yeah, she was sexy.
And it's unhealthy cuz you know that's
not real life. And obviously if you want
a sex life, if you want to meet someone,
which you should have already met
someone by now, you know what you what's
going to happen again. It's just
negative. You're just going around in circles.
You know, when I lost that £200 on the
roulette, that was a one-off, bro. I
don't gamble like that. And to be
honest, if I had went out drinking, I
would have been spending more than £200
in the month of December. So, I didn't
think 200 was was a bad investment, to be honest.
So life's all about breaking them cycles, matey.
Well, obviously, like I said, if I have
to go out and try again, I will.
If I have to, I will. Well, I have no
other choice, but I'll do anything I
possibly can to to avoid it
because we know that's not the way
forward. We know that that yields like a 1% chance.
So, we know that it's not um
feasible in the long run, basically. So,
nah, New Year's Eve is overrated, bro.
Trust me, it's very, very overrated. I
ain't going out New Year's. I plan to go
out New Year's, but nah.
No, I'm not. I I'll go out midFeb March. [gasps]
No, I'm not I'm not going out New Year's
Eve, bro. Overrated, overpriced,
full of [ __ ] Nah.
Too busy, bro. Too busy. It's not good.
I shouldn't even have to be trying
again, mate. I should not have to be trying again.
I can't get over that. Me,
when you've had a break here, you don't
want to go back to it.
So nice having a break. Oh my god.
But I and I I do compare it to gambling
because at least if you gamble, you can
actually win. You know, there's a chance
of you winning. With this, you'll never win.
You got more chance of [ __ ] winning
the lottery than finding a [ __ ] woman
in this country. That's the thing about
it. It's it's madness.
Cuz if you gamble, you you can win. You
will not win doing this ever. Well, you
will. There's a 1% chance that you'll
meet someone, but but then what else can you do?
So, it's bad, bro. It is bad. Could have
met someone years ago, mate. Years ago.
I'm not wearing a condom in it. So
obviously I can't do escorts. So that's
not an option
cuz I want more than [ __ ] now. Yeah.
Even still it's a low chance.
You could go out and gamble. Think about it. Yeah.
People tell you to stop gambling, but
with gambling you actually can win. You
actually can win money gambling. If I
put £500 on roulette right now, you know
that I could win. There's a chance I
could win. I could go out New Year's Eve
and I wouldn't get nothing, not even a date.
So, it's s it's surprising people tell
people to stop gambling but not tell
people to stop dating when dating has
got worse odds than [ __ ] gambling.
Cuz think about it, if you didn't win
from gambling, you wouldn't keep doing it.
you you will keep doing it because
obviously you know you can win
if that makes sense
because you know you can win. There's a
chance you can win even though the
industry is very [ __ ] now. I'm sure
there's you can win on something. So you
gamble cuz you can win with dating. You
will never win. And it's been this way
for like two years. Two and a half. It's
been this way for two about two two and
a half years. Two years ago you'd be
able to get dates. you'd be able to get kisses.
There was actually hope. There's no hope
now. There is literally no hope now. But
maybe one, like I said, 1% chance, 16%
chance, whatever the chance is, it's slim. So,
so obviously that's why I want to try and
Yeah. Like I said, I'm having sex with
uh a condom. No,
you're a young man. Even if you got sex
like once a month, that's enough, you
know, once a month. At least you'd have
it to look forward to every month.
There's no reason as a young man you
should not be having a sex life.
That's the way I see it. As a young
person, there's no reason
to say that. There's people that are 36
and you know that are virgins, but still
it's not normal, bro. Really, is it?
But then I feel like, oh yeah, you can
go out and approach, but what's the
chance you're going to meet someone that
likes you, that gets with you, and gives
you sex? It's very, very unlikely.
Very, very unlikely.
Get a [ __ ] buddy, mate. You can't even
get a date.
Let's worry about getting a [ __ ] a
conversation and a date first and then
maybe we'll be able to get a [ __ ] buddy.
Yeah, maybe when we're able to get a
date, mate, we can maybe think of that.
Yeah. So, that's where we're at basically.
It's bad, isn't it? Really bad.
It isn't good, man. It isn't good.
Get a [ __ ] buddy. Good one, bro. Good one. Yeah.
Yeah, even if you got sex once a month,
that'd be all right.
Not [ __ ] I'm not getting an escort. I
only used to go go to escorts cuz I only
used to get [ __ ] So, to me, it was
the same thing. If you're only getting a
[ __ ] no condom, then it doesn't matter.
But if you wanted to be actually having sex,
I'd rather just have a wank. There's no
point having to use a condom. The
atmosphere is bad.
It's pointless, bro. I never ever used
to really [ __ ] these escorts most of the
time. The past year, I haven't really
[ __ ] them. I just got [ __ ] That's
probably why I went to them, you know.
It's not good, mate. It's not good.
Like I said, it's all right if you just
want a blow job, then yeah, get an
escort, bro. Why not?
But if you actually want sex, then nah,
I don't know why he's saying about I
would rather have no women that than
have what [ __ ] nonslegs has and
[ __ ] Joseph Ferau has.
You know what I mean?
No, bro. I'm not going out tomorrow. I
need a longer break. I need a long break
from this, bro. I need a long break. I
need to try to join the porn industry
before even entertaining the idea of
going out again. Trust me, God, bro. [sighs]
He's got to the dentist as well.
[ __ ] sake, man.
Bro, at some point I can't get anything else.
Do not see that as very, very unfair
that I have to go out and try again.
Like the problem is this is what I keep
trying to say where we're not saying
that it should be easy.
I don't know who's watching this. We're
not saying that it should be as easy for
us as it should for women cuz it's never
been that way. Never has, never will.
Before social media, um, you know, and
now there is social media. The problem
with it is is even if you try, you still
won't get anything but bad experiences.
So it's like you actually have to try
and then get bad experiences. It's not
like you try try and eventually get what you want.
It's like you try and all you get is bad
experiences. So what the [ __ ]
That's what the whole problem is. It's
not like, oh, I'm thinking of
approaching someone, but I'm a bit anxious.
Should I do it? Should I not? M and then
you force yourself to do it and then you
get a date. You literally will get
nothing but bad experiences even if
you're willing to put time, money, and
effort into it. That's the thing that
makes it wrong. You know, that's the
thing that makes it wrong.
If you're willing to put the effort in,
you should be getting something out of it.
Just like if you was to work, you get
money out of it. Just like if you was
going to the gym, you'd get something
out of it.
But you'll try and you'll just get bad experiences.
That's what puts people off, you know. So
yeah, I had a nice roast dinner. Oh,
Triple H, I was on um
I I was live for 5 minutes earlier and
they come on. Triple H. Same repeating people.
two people commenting 18 uh lurkers. I
was live for five minutes like I said I
was going to do and they were on YouTube.
Then I went to my sisters at 10 and I
had some nice lovely food, some
presents, had a laugh.
>> Yeah, these [ __ ] I told [snorts] you,
bro. I told you Triple H. I [ __ ] told
on your job.
>> Yeah, man.
And then Monty man copied my idea. Little copycat.
Monty man's such a copycat, mate. No, I
don't want a fat bird. But yeah, when
that Joseph Ferrar comes on, bro, I'm
going to start on him in the new year, lad.
I'm going to start on him.
Okay with you, Triple H. I don't mind
going to leads, bro. I'll stay in the Hilton again.
Yeah, it was I said it was cancelled,
bro, but I changed my mind.
I was just pissed off. Same people.
Same people, same story. See you next year.
year. Oh, that's a banger, bro.
Yeah, they were on YouTube, bro. On YouTube.
can't go off for YouTube, these people. Is it
man was live? He said, "Listen, I'm
going to go." He said, "Hey, he said
this trip to Rach." He says, "I'm going
to see who's on YouTube." And if if
anyone's watching me now, it proves
they've got no family. And he says,
"What? That's five people that's got no family."
He's a little copycat. He copied my idea.
I ain't even going to come on YouTube
today, bro. I just thought, [ __ ] it. I
want to do this experiment in it. I
won't be on tomorrow.
It's the same repeating people.
Yeah. And then they tried to reverse it
by saying, "Oh, you was on YouTube." I
said, "Yeah, I was on YouTube for 5
minutes to see if you was on YouTube
before going to my sisters." Yeah. Okay.
So, it just goes to show that it was
always projection with these people,
bro. Always projection. Always has been,
always will be self projectors. That's
why I don't really come on here anymore.
Cuz if that Joe comes on and winds me
up, I'm just going to end up going
there, bro. I'll just end up going to
leads. I really don't care. You know,
I've done it many, many times before,
you know. Don't sit there and try and
[ __ ] wind me up. Yeah, you fat
sausage fingered with your fat ugly
misses. Because I will just come there
and I will just call the [ __ ] out and
I'll get [ __ ] whilst I'm at it,
you know? I don't really care, bro.
Not a waste of money to me. Really
ain't, mate. I could do with it, to be honest.
You know, [ __ ] little nons leg lover.
[ __ ] sausage fingered fat [ __ ]
You need to watch this horror film,
Triple H. It was It was It was a good
horror film, bro.
It had some [ __ ] sexy maid in it,
bro. It's called a housemaid. She's
[ __ ] sexy, bro.
Mad should watch it, bro.
Yeah, they can't.
[ __ ] Nons was posting today, wasn't
he? But oh, by the way, you're going to
laugh at this. Triple H. My sister saw his um his tattoo.
No, I'm not going out tomorrow. I won't
be out now until February, March. Um,
it's not a long enough break, bro. My
sister saw his tattoo. Yeah. And she was
like, "No wonder he's a [ __ ] virgin."
She said it on the phone. She said she'd
be asking for a refund.
She says, "No wonder he's a virgin." No
hesitation, no nothing. I swear to God,
that's what my sister said. My even my
sister knows he's a virgin. All time
What the [ __ ] is that [ __ ] ugly
tattoo? Jesus Christ.
Jesus Christ, man. He was posting today. Yeah.
Yeah. These people ain't got nothing,
bro. I'm only like that. I woke up not
so long ago. Triple H. The food knocked
me out. I had a fun day. I did have a
fun day. [sighs and gasps]
Like I said, bro, first of January might
be different. You don't know.
So, I'm I give these people the benefit
of the down doubt. Laney says, "Oh, no.
It will be the same people." You know,
this, but I like to give these people
the benefit of the doubt, you know, Triple H.
Yeah. I like to give them the benefit of the doubt, you know.
Yeah. I literally No, Triple H. I went
live. I went downstairs to make a tea. I
left the phone upstairs and I went back
upstairs and there was 18 lurkers and
two people typing.
18 people triple. You don't get 18
viewers ever. Really? Not within 5 minutes.
Not within 5 minutes, lad.
It just goes to show that it was always
about them, wasn't it? It was always
about these people. Triple
That's confirmation, huh?
Yeah, it was always these people. Triple lad. [clears throat]
I need to watch Monty man's live.
He's such a copycat.
[ __ ] copying my idea. Real copycat.
All right. They were talking about his
kids again. Triple H. They said that
you're not allowed to see your kids. [snorts]
It's always kids with these people in
this community, isn't it? Always. >> [snorts]
>> These people are sick puppies, lad. Sick puppies.
Right. I'm going anyways. Yeah. So, I'll
be back. I don't know when. Not for a long time.
Yeah. So, in a bit.
Oh, I'll just stay for a little bit.
Yeah. He needs to get laid, bro. The
more I respond, the more he responds.
And then that's that's taking up time
that he could be using to get laid. Triple H.
Even my sister called him a virgin. I
wonder you're a virgin. She said, "No
wonder he's a virgin with a tattoo like that." Yeah.
So that tattoo you've got you got a
tattoo of Laney.
So you're you're trying to insult the
tattoo that you've put on your body.
You're not very smart, are you?
You're skinned virgin. But yeah, Triple
H. Yeah. Um, I'll come back in the new
year, bro. And if that Joseph Ferrar
wants to stop, I'm just going to go to
leads, bro. Would you like that content?
I'm just going to go there and call him out.
Is that okay with you, Triple H? I'm
just going to book a hotel, bro, and
just get on it and just call the [ __ ] out
cuz he's got a lot to say uh behind a
keyboard. This [ __ ] bit like his
boyfriend Nons legs,
you know, kill two birds with one stone.
Is that all right with you, Triple?
Uh, she just thinks he's a low life
virgin with like what I think. Yeah,
he needs to get a little part-time job.
Triple H. I think it'll do him the world
of good. Just a part-time job. It
doesn't even need to be fulltime. Just a
little part-time job.
Yeah. Timmy Timmy's calling me a virgin
again. Triple H.
Yeah, Jimmy's called me a virgin again, bro.
He doesn't know
that Ricky Millington account coming in, didn't he? Yeah.
So, do you reckon if I go to lead Triple
H, um, Joseph Ferrar will meet me?
Yeah, he's a little he's a little nonss
lover, bro. He's a little nons lover.
You see him comment on Red Star's
channel as well. He's a little nons, bro.
Yeah, I added that to my little evidence
packs for breach. You like that? PJ's
evidence pack. There's an account called
PJ's evidence pack.
So, do you reckon you could get
do you reckon you could get nonslegs a
part-time job? Triple
just a little part-time job,
you know? Maybe McDonald's. Maybe
just a little Just a little part-time
job. Do you the world of good, mate?
It was absolutely banging triple. It was
It was turkey and lamb. [ __ ] banging.
I need to go to the dentist, bro. I need
to get a feeling though.
So, but yeah, it was nice. It was
banging, bro. Really, really nice.
[snorts and clears throat]
Yep. I got a toothbrush. I got a
Guinness glass with bottles with two
glass bottles. Um, got a dressing gown.
Uh, I got a link set.
I got some after shave.
Yeah, I got quite a few things, bro.
The food was so good, bro. Oh my god,
the food was amazing, bro.
I'm having I'm having roast in it
tomorrow as well. Boxing day, isn't it? Triple Yeah.
Do you remember when Mr. G commented on
Nons's channel saying, "I think you
should get yourself a little job."
I think you should get yourself a little job.
>> [snorts and clears throat]
>> I have
Oh, bless you then.
Yeah, he said I think you should get a
You Mr. G said, "I think you should get
yourself a little job.
I think he should get himself a little job, Triple.
Can you get him a little job? Then he
would stop being so skint and he and he
wouldn't have to show daddy's life savings.
Oh my god.
I don't know why N legs keeps calling me
ugly when literally everybody will admit
that I'm better looking than him.
Strong strong insecurities, bro, from this virgin.
He needs to [ __ ] get off of YouTube
and get laid before he dies a virgin.
He dies a [clears throat] [ __ ] virgin, mate.
O, go and watch I'm going to link you.
Did you watch Monty's live stream earlier? Triple,
it was only It's only 1 minute and 44 seconds.
Watch it. It's only 1 minute and 44
seconds, bro. It's funny as [ __ ] Watch it.
Look, it's only 1 minute 44 seconds.
Watch it quickly, bro. It'll make you laugh.
It's only 1 minute 44 seconds.
It makes me die, bro. Go watch it. Yeah.
That's five people without a without a family
on a triple.
Did you watch it? Yep.
Yeah. You said that's five people that
ain't got a family in it.
Five people without a family, isn't it, Triple?
That's five people without a family. He
said, isn't it? [laughter]
He said he's just he's just come on to
see who's got a life or not. there. Triple.
Yeah, I've just come on to see who's got life. [laughter]
He copied me, bro.
[ __ ] little copycat. Anyways,
same people, same story. I'm off. See
you next year.
We'll see you, bro.