Bro, there's there's a lot of [ __ ]
disabled people on this community, isn't
there, man? Let's let let's face it.
Sad, pathetic, old bastards on this community.
See, it doesn't bother me, bro. I was
only pissed off earlier because of the
bookie thing. These these people don't
get to me. These little sad acts.
These little sad Dennis people that
ain't got a life. They don't get to me,
bro. I was pissed off earlier because of the bookkeeping
on a [ __ ] boxing day. You know, these
people really don't bother me. They're
just sad because the way you got a seat
with these people yet. Just just go back
and think of all of the people that got
exposed for their looks. Bomb Pat
Mustard, Gray Cat, [ __ ] There's been
a couple of other people. Yeah. Just
remember how many of these people got
exposed for what they actually were. And
we we made we made the assumption before
they got exposed. And that's all you
need to know when you think about these
people. They're fat. They're ugly.
They're skint. They got no life, you
know. And that's why they do all of
this. They hate anyone younger and
better looking. That's why there's
there's no um
reason to get like I rate these people.
I was just pissed off earlier, bro, cuz
this [ __ ] annoying shop. But these
people really don't bother me, bro.
These sad losers ain't got no life.
It's very is is concerning to see how
many people are obsessed with me just
cuz I'm younger and better looking than
them. It's madness, bro. It really is
mad to think how many people can um be
obsessed with, you know, people that
they don't know. like just just pointing
out facts, you know, just straight facts
with it, you know, it's madness.
I could bloody throttle that Timmy
Aldridge. I could
bloody throttle that Timmy Aldridge.
I don't know who's up, man. But yeah,
[ __ ] throttle that [ __ ] I could get
me on there with these losers.
And this is all cuz you're better
looking than these people as well.
You're younger. You're better looking.
That's what it comes down to with these
people. It comes down to hate and jealousy
with these sad people.
Did anyone do a football bet yesterday?
I done a for both teams to score. Yeah,
I got two out of four. So, I thought I
was pretty close to be honest. I only
put 20 pound on it. Yeah.
Yeah. 20 pound on it.
I just got done this today. [ __ ] Hopefully. Yeah.
Why the [ __ ] would I be jealous of some
fat, ugly, wrinkly slob when I've got
more money than him? Which I literally
said this about multiple times. Like,
people can call you out for showing fake
wins and believe it or not, not not be
jealous. You don't have anything I want.
I'm younger. I'm better looking. I've
got more money than you. I've been with
more women than you in case you want to
bring your woman up. So, bro, like, you
need to back up what you're saying. If
you're going to accuse someone of being
jealous, you really need to back up. You
need to back it up.
Like me. Like, I'll say these people are
jealous because they won't leave me
alone. They harass me every day. They
won't leave me alone. The fact that like
their faces have been put out there and
they've always been uglier than me. So,
I mean, I can back up when I say stuff.
There's no point saying something if you
can't back it up.
If you've got no evidence to support
what you're saying. So that's that
[ __ ] sad people in this community, bro.
These people have really got to be
disabled to sit on here and do this
every day for years. They've really
really really got to be disabled on here, bro. Sad sadax. No. [snorts]
Yeah. But like I said, I've warned
everyone about this community anyways.
If you're younger and better looking
than these people, they'll never leave you alone.
I've been saying it for ages, bro.
I've been saying it for [ __ ] ages.
With these slobs,
you'll notice that they'll never put
their cameras on. These people, they'll
never ever put their cameras on. They'll
never show what they look like until
they get exposed like two years later
cuz they're all fat and ugly. These
people fat ugly bathrooms.
Fat ugly people that ain't got a live [snorts] one instead.
These people was on YouTube Christmas.
These people was on YouTube Christmas, bro.
That's the madness.
Then they tried to say, "Oh, I was on YouTube Christmas."
Well, they were on YouTube for 5 minutes
before leaving to go to my sisters.
[ __ ] me now, bro.
Yeah, these people are [ __ ] man.
Don't know how they're so jealous of
people that they don't know. I just find
it icky, you know.
Joseph Fro showing fake wins, but
apparently I'm jealous. Even though I've
got more money, I'm better looking than
him, but I'm jealous of a 250 win. Yeah,
I'm younger than him. I've got more
money than him. Every single woman I've
been with is better than what he's with,
but I'm jealous.
I'm jealous apparently. Yeah. Seriously.
I mean, you asked why would you put
losses up? Because it's a gambling channel, you know,
these people are just proper proper disabled.
Like I said, I could f with that [ __ ]
Timmy just for getting me on.
They're just skin ugly jealous people
that ain't got a life. That's what they
are. what they are
that they got no family. I proved that
Christmas. I proved Christmas they had
no family. I was live for 5 minutes
before I even coached my sisters and I
didn't even I was even looking at the
screen and they're trying to talk about
other people that were better than them.
Come on. Get up
to talk about people that are better than them. Oh, [ __ ] Yeah. Saw a s
That's not all.
So, when are you people going to get on
for YouTube anyways and get live?
When you going to get off YouTube? Yeah.
Yeah. Self projection.
I told you Christmas these people were
going to be alive. Yeah.
Sad 40y old losers that elite on to
anyone that's younger and better
looking. I've noticed it with these people.
Prove me wrong. Come on camera.
Come on camera and show your faces.
Prove Peter Bailey wrong. Come on.
Just like that Joseph Fer [ __ ] fat
little nons lover. Little online
harasser but we'll never meet anyone.
Little [ __ ] house. Just like Lav's boyfriend. E.
Little online harassers will never meet anyone.
These people lonely. Christmas [ __ ] lonely.
They're just some people that they don't
even [ __ ] know. You know,
they're just some people that they don't
even [ __ ] know. Mad. mad.
I ain't mad with that.
You people ain't got no life. You've
been on here since 2012.
201 [ __ ] 12. You people been on here.
[ __ ] no life, man.
And all you do is throw yourselves up.
All you do is bully yourselves.
You don't bother me. I was pissed off
earlier because of um the books. I was
already about you
fire to fire. These little clowns don't
bother me. These little self projectors,
these little nerds on here, these little virgins, you know. [ __ ] bugs.
When you use your face to me,
when you going to get live
the skin virgin,
the open virgin When are you two going
to get laid, man?
Where's going to get a line?
I was live yesterday. I could have
showed money, but I'm not showing these
people money cuz that's self projection.
you if people show you money, you still
call them a skin.
You're still going to call people what
you are every day.
So that's why I didn't show the Christmas tree.
I'll throw it now because Christmas is over.
But look, I put all the presents upstairs
cuz I don't prove myself to people. I
don't need to prove myself to these fat,
ugly people that talk about themselves.
Cuz no matter what you show them, they
will continuously keep talking about
themselves. These little nerdy old wrinkly [ __ ]
You have to understand these people are
at a level in life. They're at a certain
level in life. Ugly, fat, no money, skin.
So basically, they're trying to bring
you down to their level.
They're trying to bring you down to
their level. You see,
he's a virgin one.
Yeah, good for you. No one cares. People
I've seen you people for what you are, bro.
Sad, lonely, no life at YouTube. How
long was I off from YouTube for, bro?
Over a week the other day. Was it
sad with your lives?
trying to bring other people down to your level.
>> I can show money right now, but still
call you skin.
So, whatever you show these people,
they're always going to call you what
they are cuz it's self projection.
It's about time these people started
putting their cameras on and showing
what they look like. The fugly moners.
See what I mean, bro?
>> [clears throat]
>> Yeah. Yeah.
Yeah. We're just talking about a unit
that would sell for debt, too. By the
way, you didn't you people didn't piss
me off um earlier. I was pissed off at something else.
I was just adding fuel to the fire. So
you people on here don't bother me
because I know deep down that you're
talking about yourselves. I know what
you people look like when your cameras
get put on. So when you realize with
these people it's just self-reflection
then it doesn't bother anyone because
they're just talking about themselves.
I was pissed off because of the book you
just said wasn't these people like those
are for about a little low light showing
fake wins. We know what these people are
about, bro. They don't bother us.
They really [ __ ] don't.
I put it as this. All the people that
have come on here in the past doing this
have always been fat and ugly when
they've been exposed.
They've always been fat and ugly. Bomb,
Gray Cat, Pat Mustard, there's been a
few other people as well.
Um, so that's what you have to think
about with these people. You see,
these people's also on YouTube Christmas
as well, yet they tell other people they
got their family, so make it makes sense.
Oh, [ __ ] That up. They're on YouTube quickly. So, yeah.
When are you people just going to stop
your [ __ ] Seriously, bro, when are you
really going to stop your [ __ ]
When are you going to stop this self
projection [ __ ] Let's do that. I'm
trying to have a normal conversation.
It's boring now, bro. Very boring.
I went live on Christmas for 5 minutes
playing. You said, "Oh, what did you buy
for your girlfriend?"
Well, you don't have a girlfriend.
You've never had a girlfriend. You've
never been with a woman. [snorts] Self rejection.
Why you always try to bring people down
to your level? It's not my fault I'm
younger than you. I'm better looking
than you. It's not my fault, bro. It's
just the way things happen. It's just
the way life is. It's not my fault I've
got old, wrinkly, and ugly like you people. Yeah.
Trying to bring people down to your
level cuz you're obviously at a certain
level with life. You're trying to bring
other people down to your level.
I can't believe you people was on
YouTube Christmas Day.
I can't believe that
and then and then and then [ __ ] Monty
Man copied me.
Then Monty man copied me with that idea.
It's like everything that these people
say is in reverse. You got no family.
They got no family. Your skin, their
skin, everything that they say is just themselves. They're bitter,
bitter, fat, ugly people
that are jealous of anyone that's better
than them on this community. That's what
it is on this community there.
That's what it is with these people in here.
I was at my family's Christmas. My
family was here yesterday as well. Why
are you saying people's family hate
them, bro? Cuz your family hate you.
How's your girlfriend players? How's your girlfriend?
Oh, wait. You don't have a girlfriend?
But you were trying to say I never had a girlfriend.
You don't have a girlfriend.
You ain't got a girlfriend yourself. So
you're mocking yourself by saying that.
Why do you do this, bro? I really wonder
why you do this.
I really want to know what you get out
of doing this every day.
Same people every day on YouTube [ __ ] [ __ ]
players. Where's your girlfriend?
What's your girlfriend's name?
Oh, yeah. That's good, man.
that Christmas tree up. That's nice for
you, bro. You want a medal?
But players, why are you telling people
they ain't got a girlfriend when you
ain't got a girlfriend?
You didn't ask me.
Where has Where was projection?
Where was projection got you in eight?
Where was projection got you in 8 years?
I'm trying to help you be a better you.
You know, I don't have to be doing this,
but I am. You know
where has projected got you
in 8 years? Nothing. You're still skit.
You're still lonely. You're still fat.
You're still ugly. And I'm not. So where
has it really got you in all of these years?
The bottom of this
>> [clears throat]
>> I see a lot of hate and jealousy on this community.
That's what I see.
That's what I see. A lot of hate and jealousy. Lonely Christmas.
Hey, stop ignoring me.
Players, stop ignoring me.
Why was you on YouTube Christmas?
Why was you on YouTube Christmas Day?
Did you not
Yeah. Why was I on YouTube Christmas to
see if you people was on Christmas?
I was live for 5 minutes. I walked
downstairs, walked back up, ended the
live stream. I wanted to see if you
people were still on YouTube and you
was. And you [ __ ] was.
self projection as usual from these people.
Sad sad people in this community. But
he's asking me what do I buy for my
girlfriend when he don't even have a girlfriend. Self projection.
It's not. You can self project, bro, for
another eight years and it's not going
to change the fact that you're all of
these things, fat, ugly, no life. It
ain't going to change it. It's always
you and will always be you. Trust me,
you can do it for another eight years.
You're just wasting what life you have left.
Whatever's got you in all of these
years, nothing. You're still the same old loser.
players. Um, no
about I'm streaming cuz I'm a monk.
Yeah, I was streaming to see if you
people was on YouTube
and he was. You have Asian people watching
all pretending they weren't on
Christmas. Sad, sad bastard.
These are sad bastards on this community
wreaking a jealousy every day
cuz people are younger and better
looking than you and got family. That's
where I think the jealousy comes from.
>> You can ignore me cuz you're not right.
That's why you're all the [ __ ] know
I'm [ __ ] right. Yeah,
you people ain't got money. You people
ain't got a girlfriend. How you talk
about anyone else? Absolute idiots. Hello.
What do you get out of coming on here
for years hating on people that you don't know? Answer me.
I want to get to the bottom of this
before we get to the new year.
What do you know? Your life ain't improved.
Like Joseph Ferrar, he can keep trying
to tell me that I'm living under poverty
when he's the one that's living under
poverty. It's not going to change the
fact that he's the one living under poverty. You know
what do you get from harassing people
every day that you don't know? It just
shows you to be gener [ __ ] It doesn't
bother no one else. Don't bother me. You s bastards.
Little low lives. All cuz someone's [ __ ]
Just talk about these idiots on here.
These little self projectors.
It's like you, Timmy. I I I I like you a
lot, you know, but you need to stop
calling me a virgin because Timmy, the
only virgin is you and Nonss. You are
the alltime virgins, the Hall of Fame
virgins. You're the biggest virgins
going you two and then you call me a virgin.
When you're a pair of virgins yourself,
it's all you. And we was talking about
how I was live Christmas and people was
on here. It proved that it was them all
along with no family. It was them all
along. It was s It was sad news, you know.
All right, Timmy, you need a New Year's
resolution, bro. You and Nons need to
get some puni. You need to get laid.
Get some sex down. You and him need to
get sex, bro.
See me, I don't really like have much of
a sex drive anymore, bro. I don't really
care. But obviously I'm not a virgin
like you were launch
the two alltime virgins.
You know what I mean?
Timmy, I could imagine being a virgin at
your age. Oh, he's the two virgins.
Biggest virgins gone. I could imagine
Timmy and I love you, mate. I mean, I've
known you for years to me.
I think you and Virgin boy need to get
some [ __ ] or you die a virgin. I don't
want you die a virgin, mate. [ __ ] me. I
wouldn't want my [ __ ] worst enemy dy
in a virgin.
That you never had sex. Two virgins to
me. Do you think I want you to die a virgin?
You think I want you and nons to [ __ ]
die a virgin? Never experience sex in
your life? Why do Why do you think I'm
trying to help you get laid, mate?
Yeah, mate. I want you to get liked. I
was the same with [ __ ] nonsense,
mate. I don't I don't hate I want him to
have sex. Everyone deserves to have sex,
you know, once in their life or whatever.
You know what I mean, bro? I think you
and non-slit definitely get laid. You
need to lose your vard. You'd be more content, you know. You know,
I can't believe he's going to be that
31y old virgin. I can't believe it, mate.
You know, I just can't imagine someone
being in their 30s and never having sex
that skinn one. He's the skint one. The
new one to me.
That skin [ __ ]
Timmy, he's going to die a virgin. A skinned virgin.
You're telling me to worry about my own
life, lad. [ __ ] that.
He's the new one. The virgin one.
There's two nons on this [ __ ] community, bro. you know.
No, but seriously, you and him
definitely need to get laid, bro, before
you die a virgin. You two are going to
die a virgin, bro.
I don't want to see you die a virgin to me.
You and Nons, the two virgins. [ __ ] that.
I don't want you to die a virgin, bro.
Why player? Why Why do you keep ignoring
me? Cuz you know I'm right.
Where's your girlfriend?
Oh, wait. You're a virgin,
brother. Where's your girlfriend? You
can't answer me cuz you know I'm right. Self-producting [ __ ]
Single old ugly people hating on someone
younger and better looking than them.
Sad [ __ ] bastards.
Sad sad bastards on here.
Where's your girlfriend? You didn't go
on to that, did you? Self-projecting [ __ ]
These people are a bit like uh Reddit moderators.
These little nerds. No girlfriend, no family,
trying to talk about other people. [laughter]
players. Where's your girlfriend?
Where's your girlfriend? You little projector.
You was on Christmas players. Lonely.
Lonely as [ __ ] No family. No girlfriend.
And you wanted to project that on to me?
Someone [snorts] that's got a life? Madness.
Where's your girlfriend?
Where's your girlfriend when you're on
YouTube at [ __ ] 9 minutes to 4 in the morning?
So many self projectors in this
community, bro. It's funny as [ __ ]
So many self projectors.
You can't even answer me, bro, cuz you
know I'm right. sad bastard.
Yeah, it's mad as community to me, bro.
And you know the maddest thing is Yeah.
You know, even if you don't react to
them, they will still do it. You know
that gender people will never leave you
alone. You know that.
So even if you even if you don't react
to them, they will still do it. They'll
never stop. Even if you don't react to
them, they will never stop.
I'm just I'm just letting you know that
they will never stop ever. So when all
of these people say they do it for
reaction, no, bro. Because even, bro,
it's like, bro, you know when you go
around in circles, Yeah.
You've had the same conversation.
They will never stop, bro.
They're jealous of something in life.
These ugly people. And I don't know
what, bro, but they're jealous of something. Yeah. Madness.
Definitely jealous of something.
I just think it's mad.
Yeah, exactly. Players, you know that
I'm right about you.
Got no girlfriend
and you're trying to project your [ __ ]
onto me, you sad [ __ ] Timmy, why is
there so many sad, ugly people in this community, bro?
Why can't it just be a normal community?
I just don't want to I just want to know why.
That's why I don't really come on here
much um Timmy anymore, bro. I wasn't.
This was like the second time he on in
like a week
cuz it's just the same repeating people
to me. It's just the same repeating
people, bro. Same repeating fat ugly
people that ain't got a life.
It's the same atmosphere, the same
people. Why do you Why do you think I'm
not on here much, Timmy? Have you
noticed I'm not on here much?
Because it's the same [ __ ] people.
The same repeating people. [ __ ] that.
You're right. Doss diaper.
I'm just talking about these self-reflecting [ __ ]
You've come at the right time.
Yeah. self projectors compared to
compared to most of these people on here.
Why have I got so many middle-aged
people obsessed with me? Darth Sniper.
Why have I got so many people obsessed
with me? And don't say they do it for a
reaction cuz I don't want to repeat
myself again. So, why have I got so many
[ __ ] middle-aged strangers that are
obsessed with me? H
You know what I mean?
Why do these people do this to me? Huh?
It's not for reaction cuz even if you
ignore them, they'll still do it. So,
it's not for reaction. So, we can't even
use that excuse anymore.
What do you think it is?
No, I'm just wondering, bro. I want to
know what it is. Cuz they say they're
not jealous. Okay, whatever. So, why do
they do it then?
They've got all this money. They're
better than everyone. everyone's skin.
So, why are they on here every day doing this?
I'd like to know.
I need to go dentist, bro. [ __ ] dentist. [sighs]
I like shovel.
Yeah, little copycat. When I'm around,
you little copycat.
You little copycat.
You little cubby cat.
Homo vibes. If you don't like show, you
gay homo. Little copycat.
Little copycat. I'm going to do a video
right now of this little copycat.
putting a video up. One second.
Nope. Even if you don't respond to them,
they still do it. Timmy, you can't even
use them. You can't even use it as a reaction anymore.
No, Timmy. No, no, no, no, no. Even if
you ignore these people, they will still
do it. It's not for reaction. Stop using
that as an excuse. It's not for reaction.
No, no, no, no, no. It's not for reaction.
Cuz you could ignore these people and
they would still do it. I used to say
the same thing to London Taylor. I used
to say the same thing. They don't do it
for reaction, bro. People doing
something for reaction is coming in and
[ __ ] with you for a couple of seconds
every other day. No, no, no. That's not
for reaction, bro. There's a fine line
between obsession and jealousy and
someone doing something for reaction. I
know because I've been on your channel
millions of times.
Trust me, there's a big difference.
There's a big difference.
Oh, I done a video of the little copycat.
Oh, look at my new video,
Timmy. Look at the little copycat. [snorts]
I want to unblock uh nonslegs. Do you
reckon he's Do you reckon he's awake?
I have [ __ ] unblocked you, you skinta.
Showing daddy's life savings. Come on. I
want to know why you saying shovel girl
was attracted to fit in to look big. Come on,
I've unblocked you now.
Come on, you ratfaced ugly [ __ ] with
your fat ugly girlfriend.
I'm ready for you. I'm [ __ ] ready for
the lot of him.
You ratfaced [ __ ] skin [ __ ] with a
broken arm. You can't get You can't get
more mad than me, mate.
You little copycat.
Yeah, little chubby cat. No mind of your own.
What do you think, Timmy? Do you like Shival?
[ __ ] hate that name. Hate that
person, man. I'm not a copycat. I got a
mind of my own.
I got a [ __ ] mind of my own, Timmy. You understand?
I've got a bloody mind of my own. And I
don't do things to fit in, you know?
They all used to copy each other
cuz the names associated with a with a
footballer, you see.
Yeah. A little copycat.
You little copycat.
You little copycat. I'll harass as many
women as I want to and you and no one
else is going to do anything about it.
No white knighting on this channel,
mate. No whiting on this. No white
knighting on this channel, lad.
No [ __ ] white nighting on this channel, matey.
[ __ ] women. They're all scumbags, bro. I
don't talk about it anymore cuz I don't care.
Where's the little copycat?
Where's the virgin? He doesn't come on
here much anymore, does he? The skint virgin.
>> [clears throat]
>> Don't be sorry. Women are [ __ ] Um,
Timmy, don't be sorry, bro. Women are
[ __ ] I watched an approach video
the other day and she was being a [ __ ]
to this guy.
Nah, bro. It's all right. It's all
right. It's all right.
Women are [ __ ] bro. Don't be sorry, man.
Women are [ __ ] Trust me, bro.
Don't be sorry, bro. You don't need to
be sorry. It is what it is. Women aren't
innocent, bro. I just don't talk about
it cuz I I don't care. Yeah. Oh [ __ ]
Where's the virgin, [ __ ]
Where's the [ __ ] virgin?
Where's the virgin [ __ ] bag that got
starved by his mama?
Where is he?
Where's that [ __ ] starved child that
got starved by his mom? I didn't get
stopped by my mom this Christmas
talking about my [ __ ] dead dad cuz
your dad's a nons and your mom disowned
you. You got no family
cuz your dad was a nons.
You know what I mean?
[snorts and clears throat]
I'm not I'm not I'm sad now to be very sad. Very upset.
I'm [snorts] very upset now to be [laughter]
Britney don't want nothing to do with you.
She don't want nothing to do with your
ugly ass. She never did it. Leave her alone.
Yeah, but Timmy, you don't need to be sorry, bro.
Timmy, listen. On on a serious note, you
don't need to be sorry, bro. Women are rude [ __ ]
You know why I don't talk about it
anymore, Timmy? Because I gave up. So, I
don't need to talk about it anymore.
It's I'm not asked.
I gave up. That's why I'm like, you
don't need to be sorry, bro.
Women are evil. You don't need to um
you don't need to be sorry, bro. Just just
the way women um treat people and stuff
and the way they talk to people, bro,
they're they're [ __ ]
They're [ __ ] I know you're trying
to do the right thing and that, bro. But
no, they are definitely [ __ ] bro.
I just don't care anymore. That's why I
don't moan about it.
I got better things to be doing, bro.
Like, but I still feel the same. I just
don't care anymore, bro. You know
I gave up to me. So I knew they were
evil. That's why I gave up. Yeah.
There was there was this guy. He
approached this woman, bro. The over
there. I watched it. This black guy. And
this woman was like, "Oh, I'm on the
phone. Walk away. Get away from me. So
at the end of the day to me, bro, like
don't feel bad,
the only thing I feel bad about is not
[clears throat] doing is not doing um is
not doing more in some of the situations
that I've been in. I don't take back any
of the things that I've done.
Trust me, bro. You don't need to be sorry.
You know, bro. So,
no, I think you done the right thing to me.
They If they can be rude to people the
way they're rude to people, then that's that.
Yeah, she was like, "I'm on the phone.
Move away from me."
Like, who the [ __ ] do they think they're
talking to? That poor innocent guy, you
know? [ __ ] them, bro.
And I've had sex and I don't care about
it anymore. I've gave up with dating and
I'm still saying it, bro. West Hunts. Yeah,
I don't know why Timmy's um saying sorry
for the train incident.
You should have done more to me, mate.
You should have done more.
It's all right for them to be [ __ ]
and be rude to people. No, no, no, no,
no, no, no. Never would I say sorry, bro.
Like, when I was on a train with that
mouthy [ __ ] I should have knocked her out.
But I had I said what I had to say. I
was half asleep. I I should have done
more to be honest. I should have knocked
the [ __ ] out in front of everyone.
And you're [ __ ] regretting what you
done. Jesus Christ.
You thought about getting a little job, Timmy?
Just a little job.
What do you think?
little part-time job.
I was thinking about legs. Yeah. Getting
a little part-time job. Get him off
YouTube. Get him some money. Won't be
skint anymore. He might get laid.
Just a little part-time job. Get him out
of the house. You know
what? Do you think
a little part-time job? Get you some
money so you don't have to show daddy's life savings.
Do you think
[ __ ] saying she will call attractive
to fit in? You [ __ ] copycat.
Never ever ever
am I ever going to hang around with
someone that copies. [ __ ] that little
copycats to look good.
We [laughter] go.
You nasty copycat with no money your own.
He literally went in college, bro. Next day. Yeah.
and he was about to punch the guy, you
know, for bullying him. And he was like,
I go, "I'm not playing. You're gay.
You're gay." And obviously cuz I was his
friend at the time. Um, he was calling
me gay, you know, because he was being
bullied for it. That's why he kept
talking about sh. They even mentioned it
on the in between us as well. They all
used to copy each other.
You're gay. Gay. She's attractive. Gay
What the [ __ ] What the [ __ ] was that, bro?
You little copycat.
You little copycat with no man of your own. Yeah.
Oh, you little copycat.