Oh, what the [ __ ] is up with these
[ __ ] self-reflectors of this
community? These broke as a joke
40-year-old bums that never made it.
What is it with these people on here, bro? Seriously,
what is wrong with these 40y old broke
as a joke people? They claim they're not
[ __ ] disabled, but all they [ __ ]
do is come on here and and repeat
themselves every day.
You know what is wrong with these
40-year-old broke as a joke low lives?
You would have actually thought after 8
years these that's just how disabled
they are on here. They're so broke and
so desperate. They have got nothing but
a [ __ ] app. You know, I was just
reading some of their [ __ ] comments.
And Smokey B, you don't bully no one.
You Milton Ke waster. You were supposed
to come on my door when I slagged off
your misses. You [ __ ] And you didn't
show up. Ugly boy. You're another bomb.
Ugly boy. I tell you what. Yeah. Come to
London today and go live anywhere and
I'll meet you. I'll put my coat on right
now. You ugly boy from Milton Kees. You
ugly skint Milton Kees with your fat
ugly misses and see what happens to you.
Come and meet me today then. You [ __ ]
broke as a joke Milton Kees with a fat
ugly misses. I'm slagging off your
misses and you'll do nothing. And I'm
saying I want to beat you today. Come
on, bro. Let me bully you in real life.
Let me give you a slap over your ear.
You fat ugly [ __ ] Come and meet me
today. [ __ ] stupid [ __ ] Bro, come
in. You fat ugly [ __ ] Come and meet me
today, you [ __ ] bum boy. Broke as a
joke. Got six grand to your name in your
[ __ ] 40s. Let me smack your teeth
down your throat and see who you're
bullying. Yeah, you were supposed to
come on my door two weeks ago with your
fat ugly misses, you fat [ __ ] and you
didn't come. Yeah, you told everyone on
YouTube about how you was going to come.
Yeah. None of you fat, ugly, broke as a
joke people are ever going to do nothing
but sit on the internet and keep talking
about yourselves. Keep calling yourself
skin. Keep calling yourselves a mother.
Keep putting yourselves down every day.
Yeah. Cuz you've been doing it for
[ __ ] 8 years coming on here bullying
yourselves and you're so disabled that
you don't even know that you're just
bullying yourselves. You're talking
about yourselves. Yeah. About I'm done
bullying, brother. You've never bullied
no one, you fat, ugly [ __ ] You were
supposed to come in the door with your
fat ugly wife, six grand to your name,
skin boy, but you didn't do anything. Yeah,
you understand. You fat ugly bun runaway
boy from Milton Kees. Yeah, you've been
doing this. You done this last summer,
brother. I will meet you today. I will
meet you today, fatty. Yeah, just as I I
said the same thing to Joe. Yeah, meet
me today so I can show everyone that
fat, ugly face and show everyone that
what some of you people look like on
here. Hideous, ugly, broke as a joke.
Meet me today, bro. Meet me today.
Simple, bro. Anywhere in London you want
to go, I'll meet you. Come on, fatty.
Come on, Mily Keens boy. I'll bully you
in real life. I'll give you a challenge
in real life. Come on. If you got kids,
I'll talk about your kids. I don't know
if you've got kids. I'll talk about your
kids if you want, bro. I don't mind.
Yeah, I will show everyone what you're
about. Another fatty, another jealous
[ __ ] on YouTube, another low life, broke
as a joke. And yes, six grand. Broke as
a joke. Come and do something, bro. I'll
meet you today anywhere in London you
want. Come on. Come on, fatty. Come on,
Milton Ke's boy with six grand to his
name. Come on. I've slagged off your
woman and I want to meet you. Come on.
What are you waiting for? Come on. I
want to bully you in real life. Not on
YouTube. In real life, bro. I will get
your ear. I'll give you a couple of
slaps. I'll piss in your mouth. Yeah,
you dirty Miltony Keen wannabe London
wanker. Come on. Let's meet, bro. I've
got all day. I've got all the time in
the world, bro. Come on. You know, do
not come here acting like a bully when
you're running away for people fatty
with six grand to your name. Six grand
to your name. Skint. Yeah. [ __ ]
[ __ ] bro. I hate these people,
bro. You don't understand. Listen,
brother. You don't understand how much I
hate these people here. Yeah. Look at
all of that [ __ ] that I done with that
Jo. You know what I'm saying, bro?
Come on. Meet me today. Stop being a fat
wanker. Runaway. You were supposed to
come on my door two weeks ago. Was it
two, three weeks ago? It was two weeks
ago. I was going to smack your teeth
down your throat, big man. You was
coming on the internet talking about how
you're going to come on people's doors.
Bro, I was going to smack your teeth
down your throat in front of your woman.
I was waiting for you all day. You
chubby little ugly [ __ ] Just like Red
Star. You're all the same on here, bro.
Middle-aged, ugly, broke as a joke,
hating on strangers every day for 8
years cuz you got nothing in your lonely
lives. Am I lying? Tell me. Tell me I'm
lying when I'm saying all of this stuff.
Save your energy, bro. You don't need to
try to bully no one because you could
never bully a guy like me. Someone like
someone from Milton Kees that's got six
grand to his name in his 40s could never
bully a guy like me. Someone like you, a
fat ugly bum could never bully someone
like me. Just like Joe won't meet me,
just like Red Star won't meet me just
like you won't meet me. You're a pack of
middle-aged ugly people that ain't got a
pot to piss in YouTube your whole life
which is why you choose to keep it on
here. Yeah, [ __ ] [ __ ]
These people, bro. Watch when I catch
one of these people. I hate these
people, bro. You don't understand. I
[ __ ] hate these people.
How many times have you asked them to
meet you? These fat, ugly people. You
talk talk about other people being
bloody keyboard warriors. Have you seen
your [ __ ] selves?
Bunch of fat, ugly, self-reflective, self-reflecting
40year-old people with [ __ ] all in their
life. So, they're trying to bring other
people down. It's not my fault you
people have been bullied all your life.
It's not my fault that you people ain't
got your skin. You ain't got no life.
It's not my fault you're the life's
losers. Don't take out on me, bro.
[ __ ] hell. Don't take out on me that
you're life's losers. Don't try to bring
me to down to your level. It's not my
fault you're in your 40s, ain't got no
money, ain't got no life, life has
failed you. That ain't my problem, bro.
Sort your life out. It's got nothing to
do with me.
That's not my problem.
that you're middle age and you got no
hope, you got nothing. Don't take that
out on me, bro. You don't know who I am.
Go [ __ ] fix your own life. Cuz it
hasn't changed in 8 years what you
people have done, has it? You're still
skint. You're still lonely. You're just
older now. That's all. That's all you are.
What lives have you got? Yeah. Coming on
the internet every day, hating on people
that you don't know. Where's all your
money, bro? Where's your life? Come on.
Let's be so real about it. What have you
people really got? You're sat on YouTube
hating on people that's better than you,
younger than you, better looking than
you, got more money than you. Y What is
your life? Like, what is these people's
life, bro? Come on. Hated on people that
are younger and better looking than
them? These people are old, fat, ugly,
lonely people. How many times have we
gone on L's stream and we've seen it?
The same lonely people. No friends
talking to each other. Lonely ass
people. Ugly ass people. How many times
have we seen the same [ __ ] bro?
Ugly 40 year olds trying to bring people
down to their level. Like I said, that's
why none of you people will come on
camera cuz you're fat and [ __ ] ugly.
Like I've said millions of times, if I
went on a if I went on another
community, I could show my face. You
can't. It's the same with that smoky be.
I'll meet him today, bro. I don't mind.
You know, the [ __ ] ain't blocked on my
channel. Make sure he's not blocked on
my channel. I'll meet you today, bro.
Anywhere you want. Can't go anywhere in
London you want. Cuz I'm not even, you
know, technically London. Anywhere you
want and I will meet you.
You fat ugly chubby [ __ ] Please do. I
could I could I could I could do with it
today. Meeting one of you people here.
Is he blocked? Yeah, he is blocked. I've
unblocked him now. There you go. You're unblocked.
You sad. Look, you can tell by your
hands that you're a fat [ __ ] You're another bomb.
You're all the same. All fat, ugly
losers hating on people that's better
than you in life. I'm not even lying.
You can't even type cuz you know I'm You
know what I'm saying is the truth.
You're all broke. You're all skint.
That's why you're on here every day.
You're boring. You're skint. You ain't
got nothing in your lives. That's why
you continuously come on here bullying
yourselves and self-reflecting your
lives onto other people. Tell me I'm
lying. You can't even tell me I'm lying
because it's the truth.
Because it's the truth. Sad, fat, ugly
wasters thinking that they can talk
about other people. Oh, please. Come on
now, bro. I don't think so. I really,
really, really, really don't think so.
I really really don't think you people
can judge anyone else, you know.
Talking younger and better looking
that's got more than you. Make it make sense, bro.
Oh, and actually has hair unlike you as
well cuz you're all baldy bastards.
Ain't got no [ __ ] life.
Yeah, it's the truth.
people trying to bring people down to
your level. You are the ones that ain't
got no money. You're the ones that use
this colana. You are the ones that are
skin. Everything that you say is about
yourselves. You're bringing yourselves
down. That's all you're doing. Go get a
job in a hairline of yours. Yeah. Like I
said, bro, you ain't got a job and you
can't even come on camera. Your life is
tragic. Your whole existence is tragic.
Happened to come on the internet for 8
years. hated on someone younger and
better looking than you.
Do you know what I'm saying? You get a
job. Again, this is the same four losers
that are doing this. They're so disabled
they give themselves away. Brother, your
whole life is tragic. A middle-aged man
sat on YouTube hating someone younger
and better looking. All cuz you're skin.
All cuz you're lonely. All cuz life
hates you and you failed at everything.
Don't bring your hate onto me, bro. It's
not my fault you people are fat and ugly
and ain't got no money. That's no one
else's fault but your own, bro.
No, just these people. And like I said,
you're unblocked, Smokey B, brother.
I'll meet you today and I'll bully you
in real life. I'll bully you in real
life and I'll bully your wife in front
of you. Come on, big man. Come on, you
fat [ __ ] big man. Come on. Come on, big
man. Right. I'll meet you today.
Anywhere you want me to meet you, I will
meet you. Come on, bro.
Yeah, bro. No one's showing you, buddy.
Go look at your own money. Oh, that's
right. You ain't got no money. That's
why you're asking other people to show
you money because you ain't got none cuz
you're skint. If you had your own money,
you would be able to you would be able
to see your own money. But you ain't got
no money. You're a skint middle-aged
waster. That's why you want other people
to show you money because you ain't got
none. Cuz your life's losers. Your
life's wasters. No job, no girlfriend,
no money. You got [ __ ] all in life. Tell
me I'm lying, bro. Tell me I'm lying.
Tell me I'm lying. You can't because
it's the truth. Sat on YouTube, no life,
no girlfriend, no money, never had a
woman, and you're trying to talk about
other people when you're sat on YouTube
every day. Make it make sense, loser.
You know what I'm saying, brother?
No, I'm saying what describes you ugly
people. That's why you can't come on
camera, cuz you're fat and ugly. If
there's a reason, listen, listen,
listen. There's a reason why you people
do not come on camera. It's because
you're fat and ugly. And I'm talking
about you. I'm talking about you fat,
ugly people. That's why you can't put
your cameras on. Because you're fat, and
ugly. Am I lying? Tell me I'm lying,
bro. Come on. Tell me I'm lying. Am I
lying when I'm saying you're fat, ugly,
and you're bored? Am I lying? If I'm
lying, put your cameras on then. Join
the hangouts and put your cameras on.
You're asking people to show you money
because you ain't got no money. This is
your autism. Your skint autistic ugly
people that come online every day. I'm
projecting. Okay. Well, if I'm
projecting, join and show your face. If
I'm projecting to join the hangouts and
show your face.
Yeah, but listen, brother. I'm better
looking than you people. I'm better
looking than you fat, ugly people. You
people in your 40s, you're fat and ugly.
I'm I'm doing better than you people,
bro. You people are old, fat, and ugly.
So, I'm doing a lot better than you
wrinkly old bastards. You know what I'm
saying, brother? You can't put your
cameras on cuz you're fat and ugly and
you know it. That's how I would always
have one over on you people. That's how
I No one cares what you people think. Do
you know why no one cares what you
people think? Cuz every time people like
you have come on here, you've always
been fat and ugly. Every time it's
always been fat and ugliness. So no one
cares what you say about anyone, bro.
You people are fat and ugly. This is why
you do this. You're ugly bastards. Ugly
bastards. Losers with no hope. And you
can't even tell me I'm lying because I'm
not. You're fat [ __ ] ugly losers that
can't show your faces cuz you know
you're ugly. All you all your life is
Yeah. is coming on here every day hating
on people that are better than you.
Younger, better looking, more money.
That's your lives. Cuz you're wasters.
You ain't got a job. None of you people
on here have got a job. None of you on
here have got a job. You're [ __ ]
wasters, bro. You're low. You're lower
than [ __ ] homeless people. You're the
lowest of the low. you lower than
homeless people. I I'd even say that,
bro. Yeah, 100%.
You know what I mean? [ __ ] ugly
40year-old wasters on YouTube. You're
supposed to be [ __ ] You're older than
me, bro. You people are supposed to be
older than me, brother. You're in your
40s. No girlfriend, no job, no kids.
That's yourself, brother. You've just
You've just described yourself, but a
younger age. You got the age wrong,
brother. You're in your 40s and you're
all of them things already. You're a
waster. Like I've said before, bro,
everything that you say is about your
own stinking lives. It's all
self-reflecting with you ugly people.
Right. Let's get it right here. Yeah.
We've seen me with a with women. We've
seen me with jobs. We've seen me with
money. We've seen me with friends.
That's your stinking self. You need to
stop typing out things that are about
yourselves. I know what you are already, bro.
You ain't got no house, no girlfriend,
no money. We know what you people are.
You don't need to keep talking about
yourselves. You don't need to keep
talking about your skin selves every
day. We are aware of what you are. Skin,
no job, no girlfriend, no prospects. We
know what you wasters are. You need to
stop talking about yourselves. It's not
going to change what you are. You keep
telling me what you are, but you're but
you're in your 40s, you're not 30. It's
not going to change the fact that you're
like a life's loser. So, you can keep
saying what you are, but it's not going
to make it any better. Instead of
telling me what you are every day and
you know that this is the same three
people doing this, you know, the same
disabled people, brother, like I said,
you're talking about yourself. No money,
no life, no misses. That's yourself
again. You're self-projecting.
Stop talking about yourself,
brother. You need to stop talking about yourself.
You seriously, seriously, seriously,
Chubby, you need to stop talking about
yourself. You need to stop putting
yourself down. You might want to
actually do something in your life
that's going to get you these things,
bro. It makes you happy, brother. I'm
younger than you. I'm better looking
than you, and I've got more than you.
Why would it make you happy? You're a
waster. There's nothing funny about your
situation. You're a sad, lonely,
pathetic old man. No girlfriend, no
money, and you're happy about someone
younger and better looking than you. I
would have thought that would have
teared you apart, bro. Yeah, you are
already bored. Every No, everything I'm
saying is about you people. Is about you
fat ugly people. Everything I'm saying
is about you life ugly people. Jobless,
no girlfriend, no money. Okay, let's
let's go by let's go by the facts,
right? I've been seen with money. I've
been seen to be better looking. I've
been seen with women. None of you people
have. It's definitely definitely
definitely about you ugly people. It's
definitely about you fat ugly people
hating on people that's younger and
better looking than you. No, no, no, no,
no, no, no. Chubby, it's definitely
definitely definitely better looking
than you. But do you know what makes me
happy? That you people are in your 40s,
no girlfriend, lonely on YouTube, no
money, no confidence. You don't even
leave your house, you little wasters.
You people in this community don't even
leave your house. You ain't got no
friends. You ain't got no prospects. You
ain't got no job. You just repeat the
same [ __ ] on the internet every day
because you're [ __ ] life losers.
You're the ultimate losers. You really,
really are, bro.
You really are the ultimate life ugly
losers. You could talk about my nose all
you want. I've got better nose than you.
I've got better looks than you.
Like, we know you little wasters was
lonely Christmas. We know that you're
fat and ugly. Let's go by evidence.
Let's go by evidence. Every single one
of you that have come on here before and
hated have all been fat, ugly, and
skinned. Let's go by the evidence. You
was on YouTube Christmas, brother. We've
already gone by the evidence with you
lonely people. With you lonely skid
losers, we we've already seen what you
are like. Yeah, you are a skid loser.
Yeah, you are.
Yeah, we know you're a skid loser. Yeah,
we know you are. But what am I? We We
know you are, bro.
Yeah, at least at least I got a
Christmas dinner. You people was lonely
Christmas with no family. You people was
alone all Christmas. No family. Even
Monty saw it as well.
Yeah, bro. You was You was You was
lonely Christmas. You was lonely with no
family. See, I'm going by evidence. All
right, listen. Smokey be Why don't you
meet me today, you skip [ __ ] Why don't
you meet me today, you fat ugly [ __ ]
You were supposed to come on my door two
weeks ago. You were supposed to come on
my door two weeks ago, you skin [ __ ]
You [ __ ] ugly skin [ __ ] Bring your
fat ugly misses as well. Bring your fat
ugly misses, brother. Bring your misses.
I'll punch her face, get her pregnant,
and make you watch. And you'll do
nothing. Smoking me. I'm talking about
your woman. And I'm calling you out. And
you're not going to do nothing. And
You [ __ ] skint ugly milk keens boy
showing six grand to your name, bro.
Really? Really, brother? Why do I need
to show you two grand in order for you
to beat me? I've snagged off you. I've
slagged off your misses and I've wanted
to meet you. Come on, bro. Seriously,
brother, I've already shown you more
than two grand. Stop being a little
[ __ ] Come and meet me today. Anywhere
in London. You don't even need to come
on my door. Just meet me anywhere in
London and I'll bully you in real life.
I'll bully you in real life. Not on
YouTube. I'll bully you in real life.
Come on, bro. Come on, brother. Anywhere
in London and I'll smash your face in.
Come on. Today, bro. Please. Anywhere
today, I will meet you, brother.
Anywhere today, I'll knock your teeth
down your throat. That's a promise, bro.
That is a promise. Let me come and smack
your teeth down your throat and show
everyone what these ugly people look
like on YouTube. That's what I thought,
you little [ __ ] [ __ ] That's what I
thought, Smokey. You skint ugly misses,
ugly life. And if you've got kids,
you're so ugly that your kids will
probably have Down syndrome. I'm talking
about your life, your misses, and you'll
do nothing. And I've offered to meet you
today, and you won't beat me. You will
not meet me cuz you know I'll bully you
in real life. You know that. You know
that I'll bully you in real life, bro.
You ugly, ugly, Milton Keem skid wanker.
You ain't got no money. Why do you keep
calling people skid when you ain't got no money?
Why are you calling people skid when
you've got no money yourself?
You ain't got no money. You're skint.
You showed six grand. You're skint. What
are you in your 40s, brother? And you're
showing six grand. Why do you want to
see two grand? You're skint yourself. So
I don't know why you keep asking people
to show you money.
But like I said, Smokeoky B, you'll
never meet anyone in real life cuz you
know what's good for you. cuz you know
in real life you'd get humiliated and
bullied off of YouTube. You know, you
know what's good for you, little boy.
And I don't want you to come on the
door. I'll beat you anywhere in London.
It's not coming on the door. I don't
want you to come on the door. I'll meet
you anywhere in London. But you know
that I'll smack your teeth down your
throat, you little [ __ ] Just like
these keyboard warriors. Just like these
keyboard warriors. These little skin
flints, these little self-reflectors.
I'm banning these people now. Anyways,
this is the same self projector behind several accounts.
Brother, spoke to me. I spoke about your
misses. I spoke about your unborn kid.
And you're not doing nothing. And you're
claiming that you bully people.
You're claiming that you bully people.
You chubby hand, ugly wife, ugly kids,
if you're going to have them. And you're
not going to meet me. And you're
literally not going to meet me.
What a loser. You've let me talk about
your wife, your unborn kids, and you're
not going to do nothing. And you bully
me. Come on, brother.
Why are they saying that the dinner was
undercooked? Because these people was
alone on Christmas.
That uh because these people was alone
on Christmas, brother.
Uh Smoky B doesn't have any money. Uh he
does not have any money. Let you trigger
me, Smokey Be. And I've shown what you
really are. someone that will never meet
me. You sad bastard. You will never ever
meet me ever. You sad sad melting kings
skint ugly wife little [ __ ] that will
never meet anyone.
That's what you are. You're nothing but
a skint fat ugly [ __ ] with an ugly wife
and you will do nothing. Simple. Yeah.
You ugly ugly wife. Ugly unborn kid.
Ugly ugly man that has backed down for
me and you'll do nothing. All you do is
bring up money because you know I'm
right. All you do is bring up money cuz
you know I'm right.
I've already shown you two grand. I've
already shown you two grand before and
you didn't meet anyone.
You know what I'm saying? I've already
shown you two grand. I've already showed
you thousand. Then you still didn't come
on my door. Nice self projected. You're
not being shown nothing, matey.
You're not being shown nothing. This is
your way of getting out. I have said
multiple times, I will never show you
self projectors money ever again. I will
never show you skin self projectors
money. And you would need somebody to
show you money for you to come on
someone's door. You're just a a [ __ ]
house. Smoking me. A [ __ ] house,
brother. I can show you, but I don't
want to cuz you're self projectors. I'm
not playing the money game. I've already
beat you at the money game. I don't need
to play it again.
I can show money, but I don't need to
prove myself to fat ugly people. That
was not what happened when I was born. I
am not showing you because I don't need
to. I want to battle you and smash your
teeth in. I don't need to show you money.
You know, you sad ugly wife, ugly unborn
kid, ugly man. I'm saying all of these
things and you won't meet me.
I'm talking about you and you won't meet
me. You're asking me to show you £2,000.
You've already been shown thousands.
You've already been shown money multiple
multiple multiple times.
Nope. Nature, I am. I have got money and
I'm never shown you people money again.
Cuz every time people show you money,
you run away. So no one cares about your
opinion. And I'm not your mate. Every
time you have been shown money, you have
run away. Right? A a wise person learned
from their mistakes. I will never show
money ever again. And I've got money. I
have got money. And I'm not showing you
money. I refuse to show self-projected
ugly people anything. I'm not showing
you any receipts, brother. Listen, I'm
not showing you any receipts. I have not
proven myself to fat ugly people with
nothing. I will not do that and I will
not be doing that. Yeah, simple as that.
Same thing with the receipts. It could be anything.
So, yeah. Uh, your opinion is wrong,
mate. I am not showing you anything,
mate, because you have been shown money
time and time and time and time again.
You have been shown money time and time again.
You know what I'm saying? Listen, Smokey
B. Beat me today. Hey, bring your fat ugly misses.
Yeah, my mom's saying these people would
never change either. Look, he's run away
again. He's run away again. They will
not meet you. This is what I mean with
they are [ __ ] so disabled. These
people in this community, you know that
they're proper, they are properly
disabled, aren't they? That
mate, even if you don't react to them,
they still do it. They will not leave me
alone. These people,
>> mate, even when you don't react, they
still do it. They are jealous of me for
whatever reason. These
>> No, no, no, no, no. Let me repeat myself
again. Even if you don't react to them,
they still will not leave you alone.
They will not leave you alone ever.
You know what I mean?
I'm saying to you, as I've explained to
many people before, even if you don't
react, they don't leave you alone. I
promise you, these people do not leave you alone.
>> What is it? Why would they leave me alone?
>> Because I know actually,
>> right? And I'll explain it again. Right.
Right. Okay. Let me explain. Okay. Okay.
Right. I'm I'm trying to explain it
again for the third time. Even if you
don't react, they will still never leave you alone.
>> I will tell you again. >> Yeah.
>> They know how to finish someone.
>> But and I've explained to you for the
fourth time now, even if you do not
react, they still won't do it.
>> But what I'm trying to what I'm saying
to you is if you don't react, they still
don't leave you alone. No reaction. They
still will not leave. ARE THEY JEALOUS
of me or something?
>> Okay. Are they Are they jealous of me?
Are they stinking jealous of me or something?
>> Right. And I' and I've just explained to
you five times. Right. And I've just
explained to you five times that even
when you do not react, they will not
leave you alone.
>> Right. Okay. Yeah.
>> This situation makes me want to go get.
>> Right. And I'm trying to explain to you
as I've explained to people in the past.
still not leave you alone. Mom,
this is what
>> Okay. Right. Right. And Okay. So, if I
Okay. Right. So, if I don't react to
these people for 6 months, they will not
still be doing it. Yeah.
>> So, it's jealousy then. So, is it
jealousy? I've told you it's a thous you don't listen.
>> You know what I mean?
>> You just don't listen to me.
>> But why are they so jealous of me? I
don't Why are they jealous of me? I
don't understand. Why are they so
jealous of me, Mom? There's nothing
special about me. I'm just like a normal person.
>> You know what I mean?
>> Cuz I'm just going to I'm just going to
I'm just going to end up going to one of
these people's cities. I'm just going to
end up doing it this week. I will be
doing it next week. 100%. I'll be doing
it next week. I'll be doing it next
week. I will be doing it next week. I'll
be going to Milton Kees and I'll be
going to this leads and I'm going to
talk about this guy's wife and I'm going
to talk about his kids in his city. Oh,
yes I am. I'm going to talk about his
kids. I'm Yes, I am.
>> This little Milton Ke fat [ __ ] I'm
going to go there as well. That's what
I'm going to do. Yeah.
You know what I'm saying?
Smokey be this fat ugly [ __ ] Didn't
this guy say that he was going to come
in the store two weeks ago? This fat
ugly skinned [ __ ] with six grand to his
leg. This ugly [ __ ] in Milton Ke with
his ugly fat wife. I don't know how many
times I've slated this fat ugly bully
victim [ __ ] and he would not meet anyone.
You [ __ ] ugly fat wife. [ __ ] Milton
kids boy. Your kids, if you ever have
children, they'll be so ugly like you.
Ugly kids, ugly life. And you know where
I live and you will not do anything.
You're not going to take anything off of
anyone. Shut up.
>> You're not going to take nothing. You
[ __ ] fat Milton Kees wanker. You fat
ugly wife. You skin bastard with six
grand to your name. [ __ ] off out of
here, man. Stick to bullying Timmy. You
[ __ ] Milton Kees [ __ ]
You [ __ ] Milton Ke fat ugly [ __ ]
Fat ugly chubby [ __ ] The milky kids.
Well, guess what? Anyways, at least I've
got a bum. Unlike you smoking me, you've
only got your fat ugly MS who I was
going to slap up if you come in the
door. You ain't got a bum. You've only
got a fat ugly misses. Your fat ugly
life. Fat ugly old kid. Let me talk
about your mom. Let me talk about your
kids and you won't do nothing. [ __ ]
You ain't even [ __ ] got a mom. You
ain't even got a mom. You [ __ ] ugly
[ __ ] You ain't got no mom. [ __ ]
chubby hand. Fat ugly [ __ ] No mummy.
Fat ugly wife. I've been talking about
your [ __ ] all day, bro. Skinned ugly
[ __ ] with six grand to his name. Showing
six grand like he's got money. This
Smokey B actually think he's got he
thinks he's got money.
This melting bro, what do you win? Being
a fat ugly gun.
Win, brother. You were supposed to come
in the door and you were scared to come
in the door. What have you won? What
have you won? Being a [ __ ] Being the
world's biggest [ __ ] that ran away.
You posted that you was going to come in
the door and you never. You said that
you was going to come at the door and
you never you want to you want be the
world's biggest [ __ ] that run away but nothing else you know
I don't know why you say that reaction
stuff they don't even if you ignore them
they will still do it
these ugly lonely skinned people still
do it because they ain't got nothing
they ain't got nothing in their lives
anyways it's all right I'll be going to
leads next week anyways brother so it's
all right Yeah, no one cares about your
opinion, nature girl. We all know that
you people are skinny. Yeah, no one
cares about your opinion. The facts is
that you're skinny. Anyways, I'll be
going to lead and meet Kings next week
anyways, so it's not a problem. And oh,
I'm going to be having fun with these
people. I'm going to be have I'm going
to be having fun with these people. I'm
away next week. Not a problem out of
New Year's Eve. I think I'm going to go
Yeah, I'm going to go New Year's Eve, bro.
I'll be going I'll be away New Year's Eve.
I'm going to talk about that Joe F. I'm
going to be talking about that Smokey.
Oh, I'm going to have a Phil day. My
mouth is going to be so dirty. I'm going
to own that. Joseph Ferd, the nod. I'm
going to do him as well. I'll be I'll be
away next week. Anyways,
yeah, Nature Girl, no one cares about
your opinion. We already know the facts
that you're skin. I hate these people.
So, this is going to be worth the money
next week. This is going to be worth the
money next week. That's Smokey B. I'm
going to talk about his fat wife, Mrs.
and I'm not going to stop. I'm literally
literally literally I'm not going to
stop cuz I hate these people. You don't
understand, Grezy, how much I hate these
people. Now, Joseph, I'm going to say
you will do nothing. You dirty ugly dogs
legs lover. You dirty dirty ugly dot
Yeah, I'm not going to [ __ ] stop. We
are not going to stop until I get one of
these people. I embarrass them.
Yeah, you're talking about yourself again.
Talking about yourself again. Yeah. No
money. No business. That That's
yourself. Lonely ass. That's your lonely
ass self. You're talking about yourself.
You're talking about your lonely
asselves. Anyways, I'll be I'll be away
next week. Anyways, Gy, I'll be going to
these two places next week. Anyways,
let's see what these people are about in
real life. These fat ugly [ __ ]
These fat ugly bastards. These little nonsers. Yeah.
You people don't bully no one. You fat
ugly people don't bully no one. You
bully yourselves. You're in your 40s.
Fat, ugly, and you ain't got no life.
Any bullying you think you've done,
you've been bullied in real life. You
people have been bullied your whole
lives. That's why you're so used to the
word bullying. You've been bullied your
whole lives. You skin ugly people.