Yo, just wanted to check to see who's on YouTube.
That's all I've come here for. See if
it's the same people
or if they finally got lives. [snorts]
New Year's Eve, these people finally got
off of YouTube. Finally got a live,
you know. We'll see how many people join
or if they're on YouTube,
you know, that's what I want to see. Yeah. [snorts]
Just wanting to see it's 7:43.
Oh, that's one person straight on YouTube.
Yeah, I'm done anyways from tomorrow. So
I thought might as well [ __ ] you know
the country had had a year out of us
again you know so just wanted to see you on YouTube. Oh
you people on YouTube. [snorts] Yep. Yeah.
Yeah, bro. I'd do nothing today. If I
had it my [ __ ] way, I [snorts] would
if I had it my way. I'd do absolutely
nothing today but watch a movie and have a takeaway.
We all don't. We don't like a let down,
do we? None of us die. No. [clears throat] Yeah.
Had a nice takeaway today. Oh, it was lush.
It was [ __ ] lush. It was
nice mixed um Indian grill.
I woke up in a good mood and I started
having these bad mood swings again.
>> Yeah. nothing to do with money. That's
[ __ ] That just goes to show how
like the people on here were just
[ __ ] like obsessed with money if they
think it's that. They're absolute clowns, bro.
Clowns. Absolute clowns. Serious, bro. No.
Who followed me? Followed me.
You can see someone's unfollowed you on
the Grammy calls.
Yeah, I woke up in a good mood and I
started went on Reddit and I started
getting mood swings, you know.
Reminded me of that Joseph Ferrar. He
really doesn't know anything. He really
really really doesn't know nothing.
Trust me, he really doesn't. Jesus Christ.
I don't know a damp thing.
I'll just go for I'll just have a
takeaway and just chill. But I've got to
go out today. I've got to go for a mill.
I said I was going to store it.
Yo, bro. Going to go out for a meal
later. I don't want to, bro. I just want
to chill. I just want to have a takeaway
and chill. I don't want to I You know
what? I woke up in a good mood. Yeah.
For like an hour. Oh, let me go out
drinking today and I was like, "Nope,
not doing it." It's the same thing every
time, bro. Like, you think about doing
it and then you just don't because you
What is the point? There's literally
there's there's no point. I've got
money. Got more than enough money to do
what I want. I get money again today as
well, but nah,
no point, bro. There's no point getting
more bad experiences. I could win the
lottery right now and I feel exactly the
same way. This is what this Joseph Fard doesn't understand.
Um, he thinks it's to do with money and
it really, really is not. It's got
nothing to do with money. Um, when I was
on less money, bro, I used to go out all
the time when I was on less [ __ ]
money. When I was on like [ __ ] 800 a
month. They don't know nothing, bro.
These people in this community, they
seriously don't. Is this reminding me of
them? You know, they're clowns.
You're ill or you're what?
Yeah, I'm I was going to drink, but then
I thought there's literally no point
because it's just going to be more bad experiences
and I'm going to need to like try to I'm
going to have to try and join this um
porn industry thing tomorrow as well.
It's the first of January. So, I said I
was going to do it.
So, definitely definitely tomorrow when
I wake up 100%. So, I'm just going to go
to a restaurant I think. Yeah,
I'm sick of it. Me, mate. I'm very very
very very sick to the backseat of it.
So maybe a steakhouse. I might go to a
steakhouse, you know. I don't know. I
don't know. Well, so yeah. But yeah.
Yeah, I won't be drinking. I was going
to, bro. I woke up in a good mood, but nah,
it was just going to go keep going round
and round in circles, and it's never
ever going to be any uh different. And yeah,
so and I'd be and I'd be contra and I'd
be um I'd be contradicting myself as
well by doing that.
I'd be contradicting myself. So
I definitely won't be drinking beer.
I definitely won't be. Yeah, man.
I had a takeaway yesterday. It was nice,
bro. Nice as [ __ ]
Yeah, probably I'll probably just go
Indian. Probably just have an Indian. Yeah.
Yeah, like I said, I woke up in a good
mood. Now I'm in a [ __ ] foul mood,
bro. A dirty, stinky foul mood.
[ __ ] mood swings again, bro. It's not nice.
Nothing to do with money at all. I got
money today. I had money anyways.
Doesn't mean anything, you know.
Seriously. Seriously, seriously.
I'm not dealing with bad I'm not uh I'm
not dealing with bad experiences again.
Just thinking of your bad experiences in
the pasture approach,
you know, just thinking of bad experiences.
And it's going to continue if you keep
going out in this country. That's another thing.
Yeah. And I was on Reddit and it put me
in a foul [ __ ] mood. It just goes to
show money don't mean nothing. I got
money today and I'm getting more money
today as well. Doesn't mean a damn
thing. But Joseph Fro doesn't know what
he's talking about, bro.
He does not know
what the [ __ ] he is talking about, bro.
That guy does not know anything,
you know. And these people don't know
anything as well, you know, on here.
They're just idiots, bro. I'm starting it. Yeah.
No, I didn't have plans to drink. I
wasn't going to drink. I wasn't going to
drink at all. Um
I wasn't going to drink. I was going to
go to a restaurant and I woke up and I
was like, "Oh, let me drink. Let me go
out and drink today cuz it's going to be
the last time for a while." Then I just
decided against it cuz it's just going
to be more bad experiences and I'm just
going to end up seriously just hurting
someone and it's just not worth it. It's
just not worth it, bro. You know,
I shouldn't have to keep trying. I
shouldn't have to go out drinking. I'm
28, mate, not 18. And that's what I'm
sticking to, bro. And it's been that
stuck that way for a long, long time,
you know? I've stuck that way now for a
very long time, and I it will
continuously be that way.
I don't think I'll ever try again, bro.
Seriously. Seriously. The last time I
was forced out. That's why I was I was
guilt trip guilt guilt tripped into
going out basically. So in other words,
I had no choice.
I don't know yet, bro.
A nice one,
but I won't be drinking.
I got Netflix as well. Mom's got
Netflix. We was watching Netflix
yesterday. Some horror films. It's quite
good to be honest, man. You know.
So, yeah. It's got nothing to do with
money, bro. Nothing to do with money.
Money does not change my mood. I don't
give a [ __ ] about money. I've got money.
Doesn't Doesn't change your mood. If you
win money, it might change your mood. I
don't know why that is. Maybe if you win
money, it does. not getting money, not
having money, it doesn't doesn't change
anything. It literally does not change
nothing. Don't change my mood.
If you win, it does, but not if you not
if you don't win. I don't know. It's
hard to explain it.
I don't know, man. He needs to get
himself a little part-time job.
I was going to comment that on um the
community post yesterday, like maybe
getting a part-time job as one of your
New Year's um resolutions,
you know, £50 a day or whatever. You
know, might you might be able to get
yourself some money and you might be
able to build a fund to be able to um
copy more of my holidays.
You know, if he if he gets a little job,
then he might be able to afford cuz he's
skin obviously um he might be able to
afford to go on more holidays.
um more the more of the one my holidays
that he he copies. He likes to copy cuz
he's a little copycat. Just a suggestion
as a New Year's resolution. Little
part-time job, you know, maybe working
at a calf or something, you know?
I'm always thinking of other people,
aren't I, Triple H? Things that they can do.
Just a little part-time job. Nothing
wrong with a little part-time job,
Triple H. You know, I've worked. You
work. What's wrong with working? You
know, get you out of the house. Yeah.
He'll be on YouTube stalking because
he's a fat bastard. But hey, bro,
listen. The reason I went live today,
yeah, is because it's the 31st and I
might as well. But, bro, from tomorrow,
we're done with these people. I'm not
mentioning any of these people. I don't
care about any of these people. I'm done
with them, bro. They're not. And and let
me tell you something, Triple H. Do you
know the reason I didn't meet that Joe?
I tell you exactly why I didn't meet
that Joe. Yeah. Because they're all
biased, right? How many times has have I
gone to places and tried to meet people
and then people have dismissed it?
That's the honest reason why I didn't
travel there. That's the honest reason
why I didn't go there because it would
always be they would always do the same
thing like just continuously talk [ __ ]
and dismiss it. Like you could spend the
whole of next year trying to meet these
people, arguing with these people, and
all you've done is wasted a year. You've
just wasted a [ __ ] year. That's all
you've done. You've wasted another year.
I'm done, bro.
Do not argue with autistic biased
people. You just give yourself a
headache. That's what you do, bro.
They're autistic. They're biased.
They're low lives. And that's that's it.
We said what we had to say about these
people on here. That's it, you know. That's it. And yeah,
but yeah. What do you think about him
getting a little part-time job to
approach? Doing the world of good.
Then he'd have his own money to show,
not his daddy's life savings, which is
[ __ ] bum change. What do you think, bro?
Little part-time job.
Yeah, be good, bro. Be good.
You remember Monty man's live trip
rates? That's five people on this
community without a family. You know,
that's five people on this community
without a family for Christmas. I was
dead. He said, "I've just gone live to
see who's going to jump on." Yeah.
And that'll prove that these people have
got no family for Christmas. I was dead.
Why did you see LJ [ __ ] flexing a
[ __ ] 640 pound watch? Oh, the scenes.
Oh, the skint scenes, bro. I've never
seen something so skint in my life.
Oh god, he's such a wannabe, isn't he?
Triple H. He is such a wannabe. I own
six properties. Everyone's skin. I've
got all this money. You ain't got
nothing, mate. You ain't got nothing.
You're just a beggar on YouTube.
He's literally got nothing. He's got
nothing at all. Don't know why he
pretends. I don't know why these people
don't just be real.
[ __ ] skin, isn't it?
These people, [snorts] all right, Triple
H, remember when I said to Monty, why do
these people um call other people's
skin? And he was like, because they're skin. [laughter]
Cuz they're skin.
What did [clears throat] Monty call
them? Waste, isn't it? [laughter]
Yeah, bro. Made my bed um yesterday. You
can't see me cuz it's quite dark. [laughter] Yeah,
you should comment on his community post
trip and say, um, when are you going to
get yourself a little job?
He gets triggered over the word job.
Yeah, he's full of [ __ ] bro. He's
absolutely full of [ __ ]
He's such a low IQ troll. That Joe is so
low IQ. It's unbelievable.
He's a low IQ troll.
That's what he is, bro.
Just so low IQ.
Can't you see what he's trying to do,
bro? He's He's showing like only wins to
try to get me gambling. And it's not
going to work. It's not going to work,
bro. He's a He's another Lav Mong. You
know what that means, bro? He's a Lavie Mong.
That's what he is.
He's just a Lav Mong.
If people was winning like that on Fog's
all the time, bro, the bookies would be bust.
The bookies literally would be would be bust, brother.
Yeah. He doesn't lose. Yeah. He must be
the only one that keeps winning.
And what he's doing, right, is he's
showing only wins, right? So then when
someone says something about it, he
accuses them of being jealous. Do you
not understand what the trap is? But
it's so obvious what he's doing. Like,
and we all know that he loses. We all
know that he's down longterm and he is
only showing the witness. That's not
being jealous. That's facts. Okay, how
about this then? How about this break? Yeah.
>> Why don't you ask him to go live playing
these properties every session that he
does? Cuz we can't say videos cuz then
he'll just put like the wins up. Tell
him to go live every time he plays one
of these properties and see what happens
and see how many times he loses because
with the videos he can just put um he
can just put wins up, you know. So yeah,
trust me, bro. Bro ain't winning like
that. He's only he's he's only putting
um wins up. And I don't have to be
jealous. I'm I'm younger than him, bro.
I'm [ __ ] better looking than him.
I've got money. What's there to be
jealous of? Pointing out the obvious.
Pointing out the obvious is not jealous,
bro. You know,
pointing out the obvious is not jealous.
Now hopefully hopefully they won't be
doing it for another year because they
did say they did say that they have
they've got a high IQ. Didn't think they
Triple H. They did say that they've got
they've got a high IQ. So if they've got
then obviously um if they've got a high
IQ then obviously
um they won't be on here doing this next
year will they?
Remember all of the times they said that
they don't show their faces because
they're smart, right? Well, we'll see
how smart they are next next year, which is tomorrow.
Same people, same story. See you next year. [laughter] Oh,
that is a banger. Same people, same
story. See you next year. [laughter] [snorts]
Yeah, it was funny, is it? [laughter]
Same people, same story.
See you next year. [laughter]
Love it, bro. Love it.
>> [clears throat]
>> You know, uh that LT was on my case. You
know, remember I done that video to
Autumn uh the other day, he was
commenting he was on my case, bro.
Yeah, that guy likes to try to look good
for women. Bless him.
Yeah, he likes to try to look good for
women. That one, that is [ __ ]
pathetic. That is, bro. That is that is
pathetic, bro. At that age, trying to
look good for women on [ __ ] YouTube.
You don't hear from the [ __ ] for god
knows how many months and then as soon
as you're going at a woman back that's
going at you, he's there. [snorts]
I hate women, bro. You don't You don't
know how much hate I wake up with every
day. Like, you don't understand. Oh, he
was saying that. Oh, he's he's he's
driving to London and for for me to meet
him and that. You don't understand, bro,
how much hate I've got for them. Like,
you really, really don't understand.
Like, you think it's a joke. No, she's
not. She's a proper ma. That's what she
is. She uses filters. Don't go at me,
mate, and then cry when I go at you.
You're the one that's using filters.
You're the one that's using filters, mate.
She's [ __ ] stink. Why? Why is he
trying to look good for women anyways?
I'm not even trying to wind the guy up.
I'm I'm asking the question. Why are you
trying to look good for women, bro? It's embarrassing,
you know, if you're going to do that
[ __ ] bro. At least do it in real life.
So then I could actually respect it. Why
are you doing it on the internet? It's
these people. I I don't understand them,
bro. And I don't think I ever will
understand them. I don't know what
they've got. I don't know what's wrong
with them, but these people that try to
look good for women, I will never
understand it. Never ever understand it.
Just one of them things I'll never understand. Yeah. basically
and this is how you know Triple H I'm
not saying about him even though that is
pathetic but with these people in this
community yeah do you know how you know
that they've got no life no social life
because of what they when they're trying
to like get with Autumn and they're
messaging her and that that's not that's
how you know they ain't got a life cuz
if they had a life they'd be able to be
able to talk to a woman in real
You know what I mean?
They'd be able to talk to a woman in
real life and and stuff and meet people
in real life, but they don't they don't
have life, so that's why they do it. Me, Autumn's stinking. You know,
I don't know what he is, but all I know
is he tries to look good for women. And
that's not even me trying to wind anyone
up. That is the truth. You're straight
on my [ __ ] when I'm going at some fat
and paloompa. Don't go at me. Yeah. And
don't think if you don't think I can go
at you back, I'll go at you. You know
what I mean? Don't comment on me when
I'm not even fat. That photo I don't know like
when that photo was took, but brother,
I'm not even fat. You are fat. You use
filters. So [ __ ] don't go on about me.
No, she doesn't. She's a fat [ __ ]
She's a fat ugly punt. That's what she
is. And she uses filters. >> Yeah.
I need to get revenge on women, bro. I
think that's when this shit's going to
end with me. You're talking about when
is this [ __ ] going to end with these
people? When is this going to end with
me, bro? I think I definitely definitely
need revenge cuz I'm in a I'm in a bad
mood today as well, bro. You know,
I'm in a bad mood today.
I'm in a bad mood today, bro. See?
And I stop.
But yeah, I won't be drinking today anyways.
And the only reason I'm going out for
the meal is cuz I don't want to be that
person that lets people down cuz I know
how annoying it has been in the past. So yeah,
bad ain't it, bro? It's bad.
Yeah, I saw money comment on Ed Matthews
um live stream. That was a comment where
it ended, but he commented on it. Nope.
I don't need to gamble, bro. I've got
money. I don't need to gamble. And even
if I won, I'd still be in a bad mood. I
would literally still be in a bad mood.
Money doesn't dictate my mood. It might
do Joseph Ferrar, but it doesn't me. It
doesn't dictate my mood. Money don't
dictate my mood. My mood.
So that's that. It really really
doesn't, lad. It doesn't. It doesn't. It
doesn't dictate my mood.
Put money today. Getting more money and
doesn't doesn't really change anything.
It doesn't really I told you. No. So
yeah, I won't be gambling. I don't need
to gamble. I've got money. I don't need
to gamble. For what reason? You know,
just shows that these people don't know
anything, though. It Yeah.
[snorts] So, yeah. Yeah, bro.
So yeah, I'm going to try and join this
thing um tomorrow when I wake up
[snorts] and yeah, hopefully we can stop
going around in circles.
Yeah, that's true. But I'm not going to
go out. Even if I win, I'm still not
going to go out, bro.
I would just save. I I I wouldn't go out
even if I won.
>> [clears throat] >> Yeah.
Yeah. Cuz Joseph Ferrar said, "Oh, maybe
it's because you don't get as much money
now." No, I was depressed when I was
living in the house. And when I was
still getting money from the house, I
was still depressed. [gasps]
I was still depressed. Maybe not as
bitter, but I was definitely depressed.
And then when I was on less money, when
I was like 24, I was better. When I was
getting £800 a month, I was still going
out. And I had no mood swings, though.
Nothing. Money don't dictate my mood. It
might do for Joseph Fer, but it doesn't me.
It doesn't me. It really, really doesn't
You know, I hate [ __ ] women and I
want to get revenge badly, bro. Badly.
Like, you really don't understand. You
think it's all a joke?
You know, it isn't a joke. Cuz if I had
went out today, right, and I was I would
just try to ruin someone's life. So
there's there's literally no point.
There's no point, bro. I would just try
to severely [ __ ] up someone's life if
they was to ever meet me. That's how you
get when you're older. You get bitter,
bro. You don't understand.
This country, the people in this
country, they make you bitter. So yeah.
Yeah. Nice pinch. Is a nice pinch. Yeah.
Well, I wouldn't go out.
You win money, bro. Yeah, winning money
is good, but that's the only time it
feels good is if you actually win money.
I don't know why, bro.
It's either high or low in it.
But yeah, money doesn't uh
doesn't mean anything, bro. Yeah.
Have enough money to do what I want when I want. That's that. So yeah,
I was still worrying even when I had the
house. I've always been a worrier and
[ __ ] you know.
So it doesn't really matter, bro. me.
I should have to be trying. I woke up
today in a good mood, [ __ ] maker. I was
like, "Oh, let me go out and have a
drink cuz this will be the first this
will be the last time until March." And
I just went against it.
I went against it, bro.
Yeah, but I wouldn't go out. Even if I
won three, four, 500, I wouldn't go out.
That's what I'm saying. I still wouldn't go out.
It's the same when I used to win the
football bets, I still never went out.
Even when I won them, I'd win a football
bet, wouldn't go out. Won another
football bet, wouldn't go out, and then
two weeks after I'd go out. I'm sick of
it. I am sick of it. You don't
understand. I am sick of it,
you know? And the only reason I'm going
out for the meal today is cuz I planned
it. And I'm not going to [ __ ] say no
to food. That's one thing I'm not going
to say no to. But I'm not doing it, bro.
I'm not drinking. I want to I want I
want to leave this I'm out of this
country, bro, next year if this porn
thing don't work.
Yeah, it doesn't matter if it's on for
free or not. It doesn't I don't give a
[ __ ] about that, bro. Been there, done
it, won a t-shirt. I don't care.
I really don't give a [ __ ] This
shouldn't still be happening at 28 years of age.
should not still be acting at 28 years of age,
you know, but it is. I'll be 29 next
year. What the [ __ ]
What the actual [ __ ] Stop maker and
this shit's still going on.
I'm not dealing with that toxic. No one
needs that toxicity and negativity in
their life, you know? And that's what
you're doing when you're dating. It's
just negative. It's toxic. It's boring.
You know, the drinking's bad as well.
[ __ ] all that, bro. [ __ ] all that, you know. Yeah.
Yeah. It's mad, is it, bro?
Anyone would think you're skinned the
way you're going on. Nah.
Nope. It will be the same old sad song
and I'm not getting a haircut. I need to
get a haircut as well. I'm not doing it,
bro. It's not happening.
I said I don't mind going for a meal,
but I will not be drinking.
So, that's that. I'm not doing it. It's
not happening, bro. Simple.
Going out, having a haircut, dealing
with the same old [ __ ] getting a um hangover. Um,
for what reason, bro? There's no reason
for it. There's no reason why I should
even have to try again. That's that. You
might think I'm acting like a spoiled
brat, but I'm not. I'm not. I'm really,
really not. It's the truth, you know.
And that's that. That's it.
Yeah. that Ed that Ed Matthews was in
Blackpool, wasn't he? I've never been to
Blackpool. It's one of the only places
I've never been. So, yeah. Yeah.
Yeah, bro. Not this.
It's a madness.
You're too old. You're too young.
You're too old. You're too young. You're
not a Muslim. I was speaking to this guy
in Belgium. Uh he's from uh Belgium.
Well, he lives in Belgium. I know he's
from Belgium. And I was telling him and
he didn't believe me. I showed him my
approaches on my other channel. I
haven't showed him my messages yet. And
he he wouldn't believe me. He says,
"What? You're handsome. You can't you
can't meet anyone."
And he wouldn't he wouldn't believe it,
bro. Some people just don't believe me.
The tendants never used to believe me
about these stuck up [ __ ] in this
country. They never they wouldn't
believe me, bro. They believe me
eventually when I show them enough evidence. Nah.
No, I haven't I haven't seen that. Well,
at least my tooth fake's gone. Yeah.
Yeah, my tooth fake's gone, which is good. Yep.
How do you think Tim Aldridge gets
money? Do you do you reckon it's just
benefits? Triple, it's just benefits,
isn't it? [laughter]
Would you say it's just benefits? Yeah.
Benefits in it.
He says he makes money other ways, but
he [ __ ] doesn't. That's [ __ ]
isn't it? [laughter]
Never play a um All right, [ __ ] maker.
You know what? Yeah. Never ever play a
game of chess with Timmy.
Never ever play a game of chess with
Timmy. That's one person you never play
um a game of chess with.
Never ever play a game of chess
with um Timmy. [laughter]
[ __ ] that. Cuz even if you beat him,
he'll just [ __ ] It's like a he'll
pretend it's he'll pretend he's one
like a bird. He will just [ __ ] all over
the [ __ ] chess table and then act
like it's one. Even if you beat him.
Even if you beat beating beating Timmy
at a game of chess is like um beating a
pigeon. It will it will [ __ ] all over
the chest table and act like it's one. [laughter]
That's what Tom Wood said. No, but my
favorite quote is same people, same
story. See you next year.
Same people, same story. [laughter]
That was my favorite one.
And I like when Grezy calls me a big fat stinking copycat.
[clears throat] A big fat stinking copycat.
Yeah. A big fat stinking copycat.
>> [clears throat]
>> You're a big fat stinking copy.
Why? Why? Why? Why? Why? Triple H. Why
did Nle say if you don't find Sher Co
attractive, you're gay? Do you remember? [laughter]
Do you remember why he said that?
Yeah, I will do, man. Might as well in
it because I I am done with these people
um from tomorrow 100%.
Cuz otherwise he's just going to carry
on and carry on and carry on and carry on. So So
why did Nons say that anyway? Triple H.
Such a weird thing to say, isn't it?
Why did he say that? Mhm. [snorts]
You didn't want to feel. Is it because
he didn't want to feel left out? He
wanted to fit in with the valve.
Did he want to fit in to a brooch?
Nah, he's banned. He's not getting
attention on my channel. Nah, he's a self projector.
No, I don't let self-reflectives on my
channel. I'm a bit like Monty. [laughter] Yeah.
He's skinting in a [ __ ] skint.
He needs to get himself a little
part-time job. Trip,
why don't he get himself a little job?
Get him some money so he won't be skinned anymore.
What do you think,
Trip H? If he gets himself some money,
if he gets himself a job, he'll get
himself some money. So, obviously, he
won't be skinned, you know. What do you think, lad?
Who the [ __ ] is this?
>> What the [ __ ]
Who's this weirdo?
>> Hi. Hello.
>> Yeah. Who's this?
>> I'm trying to turn my phone up right
now. Oh, [ __ ] What's going on? >> Hello.
>> Hello. Yeah, we can hear you.
>> Oh, hello. >> Yeah.
>> I can see like the voice projection
thing going like crazy. But hello.
>> You can hear me?
>> I can't prove that's what's happened.
I'm in the show apparently.
>> Oh man, he's he's talking [ __ ] Why
don't he get himself a little job, Triple?
Why don't he get himself a little job?
That's what I don't understand. Why he
don't get himself a little job? Triple
get himself a little part-time job.
What do you think? a little part-time job.
We're doing good, you know. Get him out
of the house.
A little part-time job.
Nothing wrong with a little part-time job.
You know, never hurt anyone. Working.
How's it Triple H?
because that's their life. It doesn't
matter what they want, bro. They ain't
got a life.
They call other people skit when they
skit themselves. It's funny, bro. Like
they judge other people, but they're
literally life's losers. And they try to
judge other people.
They try to judge other people, but
they're literally life's losers.
That's what makes me laugh, bro.
Literally life's losers, but then they
try to judge other people.
It's the trying to judge other people
that makes me laugh.
Virgin boys on a grand a month.
I [snorts] got faith though. I think
he'll get laid next year. He'll finally
lose his virginity.
Next year. I think
I reckon he'll definitely definitely get
lane next year. Surely he'll lose his
virginity next year. [snorts]
Maybe he'll die. Maybe he'll die of virgin.
Maybe he'll die of virgin. You don't know, man.
Uh, Joseph Far sticks up for him, but
Joseph Fra says that he doesn't like him.
Yeah, Joseph Ferrar really needs to make
it make sense.
He really needs to make it make sense.
He says he doesn't like someone, but
then he sticks up
um for them.
Yeah, make it make sense.
There's an account here that says you
was bluffing too and he's still scared
to show up too skinned to get a train.
And this account is called OJ and it was
joined 10 hours ago.
A 10 hour ago made a couch triple. Ah,
Because he's an absolute virgin. That's
why he's an absolute virgin.
Yeah. No one wants that [ __ ] mate.
No one wants that skin [ __ ]
And he's [ __ ] skint as well. No one
wants a skin ugly [ __ ] with no teeth. [snorts]
Why? Remember when I put the photo up of
the cat and someone said looks like that virgin [ __ ]
Do you remember it looks like the
greeneyed monster virgin [ __ ] Dage of Ra [laughter]
looks like the virgin.
That's another [clears throat] one that
made me laugh. [laughter]
I ain't see that account for a while.
Yeah, looks like the virgin [ __ ] [laughter]
Gregy said that the cat was um waiting
for its next copycat statement. >> [laughter] [gasps]
>> waiting for its next copycat statement.
Looks like that virgin [ __ ] [laughter]
You [ __ ] virgin
valentiz virgin boy.
Yeah. Can't believe you used to call me
a virgin. Is he the [ __ ] virgin
himself? Biggest virgin going. Skint one at that.
>> We always used to argue and at the end
he said [ __ ] virgin. I said you're a
[ __ ] virgin yourself. You virgin
virgin [ __ ] You know what I mean?
You're the biggest one yourself, you
skin [ __ ] And I'll say it to I'll say
it to your face as well.
Uh I have been asleep, bro. I woke up
Yeah, I woke up, bro. Uh
10 to 4, I think. I think it [snorts]
was 10 to 4.
You [ __ ] virgin.
And you can show this disabled girl a
million times and it still does not mean
you have had sex. You're not allowed
anywhere near that girl sexually as
she's got disabilities.
You're not allowed near her sexually.
You are a [ __ ] virgin.
Don't be calling pe Don't be calling him
a virgin. Triple H.
Don't be calling him a [ __ ] virgin.
Joseph Far might start crying. Bam, bam,
bam. You know what I mean?
>> I don't hang around with skin virgins.
I'm older now, mate. Sorry. I don't I
don't hang around with skin virgins.
Sorry, I can't do that. Triple, I don't
hang around with skin virgins.
Is that a deep enough voice for you, mate?
No, I can't argue. I I can't hang around
with skin virgins. They cramp my style,
mate. [snorts] Sorry, mate. And I don't
like copycats, people that follow the
crowd. That's not a bit of me, mate.
I don't like people um that accuse
people of being gay because they don't
follow the crowd. They're not my kind of people.
Oh, bro, you should have [ __ ] heard
what he used to say. He said, "You can't
deny she's attractive. You're gay. If
you don't find her," I said, "I'm
telling you, she's ugly and I've had
more women than you and I've had more
sex than you, you [ __ ] virgin." You
can never have like a different opinion
than this [ __ ] People with autism, you
can't have like a different opinion than
them because they become very very obsessed.
I said, "Well, I'm telling you she's
ugly and I've had more women than you,
so how could I be [ __ ] gay? You skin
You [ __ ] skin virgin."
What you used to say, bro.
You [ __ ] bur.
You [ __ ] skint flint. You [ __ ]
skint flint. You [ __ ] skint.
You virgin. You can't she's attractive.
That's what he used to say. Well, she
isn't. And I've had more women than you, you [ __ ] Um,
I'll just go and toilet. One second, lad.
Yeah, I'm happy for him, bro. I'm happy for him. The bridge
is [ __ ] stupid.
He's stupid [ __ ] stinking.
I can't wait for this meal today. No,
I'm saving my appetite for the meal triple. Yeah.
>> [groaning and screaming]
>> Oh, [ __ ] hell. He He might get lame.
He might lose his virginity.
You never know, Triple H. He might lose
his virginity. Lad'll
ever have sex, experience sex or never.
I don't like Joseph Ferrar. He's biased. Triple H.
He's so biased. Joseph Ferrar,
he's so biased.
That Jamie Thompson is another loser,
another jealous loser. I mean, look at
him, bro. Look at the state of him. And
he's talking about me.
How these people try to talk about anyone else?
I shall never know.
She don't want to know you. She don't
want to know you. She don't want to know
you. She don't want to know. Y
>> Yeah, you're too faced as well. I've
seen you talking [ __ ] about me as well.
Yeah, you're also too faced. Doesn't matter, bro.
You're too faced as well.
Yeah, you was the account that was made
um 10 hours ago. You're also too faced. So what?
Yep, you're too faced as well.
Yeah. The only one that's skinn is you,
mate. That's self projection.
Self projection doesn't bother me,
brother. You're just talking about yourself.
That's what makes me laugh is that you
people, right? Listen, listen. Let me
let me let me chat. Right. Right.
Listen, listen. Right. This is what
makes me laugh.
is that you people come on here every
single day calling people this, calling
people that, calling people this,
calling people that, but you are the
ones that sat on YouTube 24/7 and I've
seen it with my own eyes. You go on a
lavy live stream and you'll see the same
people. And I was thinking to myself,
Tiff, right? Hold on. No, no, no. This
is This has got to be I'm seeing things.
This isn't the same people that are
telling me that I'm skinn, that I've got
no friends, that I've got no life. No,
no. This is these this this these can't
be the same people.
Triple H. These can't be the same
people, can it? The ones that are sat on
YouTube, no social interaction with
anyone from the outside world. Nah,
they're definitely This got to be
different people in it.
I was thinking, bro, it's just funny
because these people are on YouTube 24/7. 247
every single day.
Yeah, he's skinn himself. Nons is is the
skintest [ __ ] ever. [snorts]
Showing daddy's bum chains life savings.
Never had a bird.
>> That's projection, brother. I've been
with plenty of birds.
All different kinds of birds. Uh a robin
bird, a pigeon bird. I've been with
loads of birds, man.
That's self projection.
Everything that you say everything that
you say is self projection, bro. So
yeah, keep keep it coming. You was alone
on Christmas. You need if you need to
say something that isn't about yourself
to be took seriously. Yeah. You need to
say something that's that's not about
yourself. I'm going for like a 50 to 70 meal today.
What are you doing today? Sat at home on
YouTube. No life.
I'll do a video of the meal later.
Triple H. These people will be sat on YouTube.
Well, to be fair, it is New Year's. New
Year's Eve is overrated, but I mean,
they do this. They do this every day, to be fair. Yeah. Madness.
No, I don't like dodge legs.
I don't like nonslegs. Nons is a
copycat. I don't like copycats. I can't
be friends with a copycat.
When he was when he started talking about sh.
He was trying to show off. He's a little
copycat. He's a little copycat. That
trend has been going donkeys, mate. That
trend has been going donkey's years.
They all used to call each other gay
rates and little copycats. >> [laughter]
>> They'll copy each other, you know.
You're little copycats.
Little chubby cats. I just want to tickle them.
You can't the noise. She's attractive.
You [ __ ] gay. Homer.
I can't get over that, bro. I literally
can't get over the desire to want to
copy someone else.
Bullied by you people? I don't think so.
You people bully yourselves. Sat on
YouTube 24/7. No life, no friends. No,
you don't. You bully yourselves, but
that's about it.
You people have always been bullied. You
don't bully a man like me. You don't You
don't bully a man like me, mate.
Nah, you don't bully a man like me.
Don't bully a man like me, mate.
It's not right to preach.
[ __ ] [snorts] idiots.
This is funny, bro. You finished?
You finished or what? You finished?
Oh, do you want to see it? Trip H. I'll
put up if you want.
Do you want me to put it up?
Yeah. You're banned. See you later.
You want to see it? I can pull it up if
you want, captain.
Oh, coie dokie doie.
Oh, coie dokie dokie.
Okay, one second.
Oh, coke doie dokie.
Branch, are you on the hokey dokie
tonight? [laughter] Uh,
>> are you on the hokey dokie?
The hokey dokie.
Hokeie dokie doie.
Hoie dokie doie. Doie dokie.
Doie dokie doie. You want the coie dokie? Doie. Yeah.
Right. One second.
>> Oh, God's sake.
>> One second, brother.
say today is lucky. Would you agree to approach?
Yeah. Anyone that's born today is lucky.
Christmas [ __ ] new New Year's Eve birthday.
Who's this clown? Hello.
>> [ __ ] you, [ __ ] >> What?
>> [ __ ] you.
>> You You bully me, do you? [ __ ] you,
>> I love being bullied. Really? Do you
bully me? Do you? Really? I don't think so. You >> [ __ ]
>> Yeah. [laughter]
What a weirdo.
Yeah, that was my Christmas dinner.
What the [ __ ] was that all about?
[ __ ] weirdo. That was my Christmas dinner.
>> Nothing wrong with it.
These people just jealous they didn't
get a Christmas dinner. Think about it.
breaks. How many of these people do you
think got a Christmas dinner this year
on this community?
Not a single one of them. Go figure.
Go and figure, bro. Go and figure.
Yeah. I know. I don't like them too dumb, bro.
I don't like them too done. And it
doesn't matter, bro. These people didn't
have a Christmas dinner, did they? This year.
Think about it like that, bro. These
people didn't even have a Christmas
dinner this year. No.
These people didn't have a Christmas in
it this year. Triple.
No, they didn't have a Christmas in it
this year, did they? Next
I'm I'm bit hungry, you know, bro, but
I'd rather wait until later.
Save my appetite for the meal, you know.
It's your birthday soon. Triple H. Bless you.
birthday next month, isn't it?
Bless you then if you're born January.
Bless you in life if you're born January then. Triple. Whoa.
Yes. You born January.
Unless you in life. [laughter]
Oh, that's funny, bro.
I'm not sure.
I'm just looking at USA Izzy.
Oh, USA Izzy's has lost some weight.
She's still an absolute stoner.
USA Izzy's is a stoner.
She got a [ __ ] worse hairline than
me. Well, my hairline's not even bad,
but how the [ __ ] can a woman be receding
more than [ __ ] me?
I'm not even receding. But yeah, still.
What the [ __ ]
Yeah, bro. Where my little All Saints
top? Waiting for my little supper later.
I'll be looking forward to my little supper later. Yeah, bro.
Yeah, man. What the [ __ ]
That's a madness, bro.
I look rough. Or is it a beard?
Or is it a beard, lad?
The beard and the hair.
Yeah, I'm just looking at USA. Izzy,
I like that little thing she's wearing.
She's [ __ ] she's receding. She's [ __ ]
she's going bald.
The beard's not that bad. Yeah. >> [laughter]
>> Now look at that cat. Such a little copycat
looking. He's waiting for his next copycat statement.
You are a man.
No, I never. No.
Hello, Ben. You're right.
Uh, the weather is [ __ ] horrible,
Ben. I was going to go out today
drinking and approaching, but I don't
want any more bad experiences with
women. So, I'm just going to go for a meal.
I'm just going to go for a lovely meal.
Same people, same story. See you next
year. You said that on Timmy's, didn't
you, Ben? You said it on Timmy's, didn't
you? Same people, same story. See you
next year. [laughter] This is the same
people every day. [clears throat] [laughter]
Do you know Do you know what? Do you
know what Bonty man said? He said it's
the f it's they do it first thing in the
morning. You can't even He said yeah
that you can't even have a bowl of
cornflakes without hearing the word
skin. He says you'll do this. Yeah. You
you you'll you you'll go to have a bite
of cornflakes with a spoon and before
you put it in your mouth, your skin. [laughter]
You remember that comment? Yeah. He
said, "Just as you're about to have
breakfast, you come on here skin before
you even put the food before you even
put the food in your mouth." [clears throat] [laughter]
Yeah. Before you can even take a bite, your skin
I'm going to have some cornflakes
actually, which I shouldn't really be
Oh, I can't have cornflakes cuz there's no sugar.
Sorry. I can't have cornflakes without sugar.
So, yeah, I forgot there's no sugar, is there? Yeah, [laughter]
that's funny. It
look my little face.
Look at that face. Look how cute that
face is. Ben, you can't tell me that's
not a cute little face.
You can't tell me that's not a cute little face. No,
I'm having a way. One sec. Yeah. >> [snorts]
>> Oh, [ __ ] hell. It is [ __ ] freezing, bro. Oh, gosh.
Hopefully they won't be saying skin next
year, will they? Triple H. Why do they
do that every day? Say skin. Say like
your skin. Your skin. Why do they do that?
And then they will continuously sit on
the internet all day every day.
They must be talking about themselves, isn't it?
I think them they're getting themselves
confused with other people. Yep. Yeah, bro.
So, what happened with Britney and N
legs then? Um, Triple H was she just not
interested in him? Was [laughter]
she Was she just not interested in him? >> [laughter]
>> She just don't want to know you. She
just don't want to know.
She literally just don't want to know you.
He don't want to know you in life.
He just don't want to know you in life.
I'm not sure why, but you just don't
want to know.
Just don't want to know you're in life.
Looking for his next copyc
I love it. I love it. Me, bro. I love
Oh, this person's birthday is on
Christmas. Imagine your birthday being
on Christmas. That is madness, bro. Your
birthday being on Christmas. [ __ ]
That is mad.
Yeah. Restaurant where he shot himself
the next day.
Yeah. [ __ ] embarrassing little virgin.
Everyone was [ __ ] looking. Yeah.
Indian restaurant. Nando Chinese. Yeah.
That's what he was telling me about his
father. His father's got a very, very dark past.
Mick Jonathan Robinson. A very, very
dark past. You could even ask his stepdad.
Yeah, I warned him. He wouldn't have any
of it. He wouldn't have any of it. A
[ __ ] virgin. He wouldn't have any of it.
I've got a question. Uh, triple. How
comes when I call um nonslegs a virgin
uh Joseph sticks up for him, but then
when nons calls me a virgin, no one says anything.
That's not fair, is it? I feel left out.
I feel really It makes me feel really
left out. It makes me feel really left
out. You don't understand.
It makes me feel so left out.
Makes me feel left out.
We've all got a biased agenda on here. Not fair.
I feel so sad.
>> Yeah. No. Oh, you know um Spoons
breakfast Triple H. You know they do it
on a uh you know they do it um in a
fryer like an air fryer.
I'm sure it's an air fryer they do it,
don't they? So I won't be um So I won't
be having it again from Weather Spoons. Yep.
Just like he was saying Shel Cole was
attractive to fit in. No, he just said
that to fit in.
Yeah. He said that she's attractive. He
said that to fit in. Yeah.
Yeah, bro. It's I don't like [ __ ] air
fried stuff, man.
I didn't realize it was air fried.
You [ __ ] virgin. >> [snorts]
>> Did that want to know you. She don't
want to know you in line. She don't want
to know. She don't want to know. She
don't want to know you. She don't want
to know you. Don't want to know. She
don't want to know you.
She don't want to know. She don't want
to know. She don't want to know you. >> [snorts]
>> [ __ ] in there like you used to.
Like you used to. >> Hello.
>> Show us your money,
>> you bastard. Show us some money, you
skinn bastard. Why don't you show somebody?
>> Show us survivor skin bastard.
>> Yeah. Why don't you show somebody?
>> You're [ __ ] queer. >> Huh?
>> [ __ ] queer.
>> Listen. Listen. Why don't you show us some money?
>> Show us a fiver. You skin bastard.
>> Yeah. Why don't you show us a fiverr?
>> Show us first.
>> No, no, no. You show us some money.
>> You [ __ ] don. Cuz you ain't got none. Skid bastard.
>> Yeah, you are skid bastard. Stop talking about yourself.
Oh, he left.
What the [ __ ] [laughter]
I don't know yet.
Oh, did they? That's nice for them.
Oh, that's nice for them.
Anyways, I'm gone. Yeah. So, yeah,
I might be back later.
Um, [ __ ] Yeah, in a bit.
I might do a video of the bill that I go
for and Yeah.