Oh god, bro. You know what? I think this
is what most people do on here, you know, honestly. Hey,
Yeah, bro. Um, I just played the FBI. Oh
my god, they're so rigged. See, I I
actually tell you I actually tell you
when I gambled, bro. Jesus Christ. I
actually tell you when I gambled. Yeah,
and they're still fixed as well. [laughter]
My my my my logic was actually thinking,
yeah, so they took enough people's money
um you know, Christmas time, December,
so they're going to pay out surely. You
know, it's January. They're going to
start paying people some money back. Oh,
no. Same old rig story, Dusty. Um I put
£100 in um and I played it down to 40.
Not a single bonus on Frankie. Not a
bonus to be seen. Not a bonus to be had.
Not a bonus to be sniffed at. Uh like
you would like you would sniff cocaine.
Then I put the 40 on the roulette. Got
it to 140 and it took all the money
trying to get another spin. You know,
miss miss. I just spat all over the
machine. Um I punched it and then I just
spat all over it. Oh my [ __ ] god.
You know, they can't help themselves.
Done my pipping. Nope. I've got plenty
of money. Plenty plenty plenty of money.
I've got plenty of money. Um, and that
was only £100. See, I told you they're
fixed as [ __ ] They are literally so
fixed. Eggs for dinner. Nope. I'm having
a roast dinner today. I don't know what
you're talking about,
bro. Dusty, they're so fixed. They
literally branch out for losing numbers.
It's [ __ ] fixed as [ __ ] Don't
forget. Yeah. £140 we got up to. So,
let's just say you got £140. That's a
lot of money for a two pound spin to
keep continuously missing when a when a
green was on 30%.
Yeah, it's definitely definitely
definitely 1 million% fixed.
I've got money. Get more money today,
the next day get money next week. Got
plenty of money, matey. Joys of not
knowing about anyone's life, I guess. Oh, £100
and you can [ __ ] off. You're a hater.
Yeah, sorry, bro. Uh,
not even a single bonus, bro. So, £60,
not a single bonus, but it's more than
60 because they give you base game wins. Uh, yep.
Oh, diddy. No one cares about that fat
losser. And you would have thought dusty
today that they would pay some money
because of it being new year. Yeah, this
is normally the time they start giving
back, but nope. They can't help themselves.
They can't help themselves for one day,
Dusty. They can't help themselves.
They cannot help themselves for one day.
You would, you would have thought, oh,
you know, maybe win something, you know,
whatever. Nope. Took the whole 100. Not
a sausage. And I think I got to 142 and
nothing. Just lose, lose, lose, lose,
lose, lose, lose. Um because Dusty, um,
what I show about gambling is real. I
don't put up fake wins like Joseph Ferrar. Yeah.
I can't believe you still can't get a
bonus on the [ __ ] Dusty
I said to the woman, "How much money did
you take December?"
Um just wondering because obviously I
didn't gamble like December and that bro
uh and I was like
nope I don't feel entertained. And I
spat all over the machine and yeah,
I spat all over the machine and that's that.
Punched it and spat all over it. I hurt
my [ __ ] hand as well. I don't feel
entertained at all. I went for a
breakfast and I thought, "Oh, let me try
cuz it's a new year in it." So obviously
you would have thought now they would
pay some money back because they took
enough people's money last month and I
didn't even need to gamble to know that,
you know. Yeah. form of entertainment my ass mate.
So yeah, I just it was only £100, so it
doesn't matter. It literally doesn't
matter. I don't like losing. Simple.
Yeah. And that's that.
You know, if I just lost on the slot,
Dusty, I don't think I would have been
pissed off. It was that roulette. It was
winding me up, bro. It was [ __ ]
winding me up that [ __ ] roulette. But
yeah, that Jo is a faker. I don't need
to be jealous. I've got plenty of money.
Um, and I've got money coming in. So, I
don't I don't need to be jealous of
anyone. I assure you I don't need to be
jealous of anyone, lad. Um, I'm just
stating facts. You know, you go most of
the hours, no one's even on there, you know. So, yeah.
New year cancelled. Well, I'm not going
out this month. I wasn't going to go out
anyways. I didn't go out yesterday. I
slept through the [ __ ] fireworks.
But yeah, if I was going to go out
drinking today, I wouldn't have done it.
I would I would have just went back
home. See, if it was a form of
entertainment, Dusty, that would not
have that should not have that effect on
you, cuz I've got money. I've got a bill
coming out, which is going to be paid
for. That is gambling responsibly. What
I done today is gambling responsibly,
Dusty. That is what you call gambling responsibly.
More than responsible. Um, and it still
affect me like, so there you go. There
is no gambling responsibly. today was
So why is it annoying you? You got
money. You got plenty of money. So what?
What? There you go.
I thought, you know, today, Dusty, today
would be the day, you know, first of
January. But nah. Nah.
140 down to nothing on that roulette.
That is bad.
That That is really bad, bro.
And £140 is a lot of money, bro, on a
two pound roulette. It is. That is a lot
of money on a two pound roulette. 140.
That's a night out, bro. What the [ __ ]
Obviously, I put 100 in, but I got it to
140. But still, the point is it went
through all of that money. Most of that
money to try to get another spin.
Bad, bro. Bad. I couldn't even get a bonus.
Couldn't even get a bonus, bro. Madness.
Uh, Lad Brooks, someone owes me 40
pound, by the way. So, I'll be getting
that today. Yeah,
it's not good, bro. It's not good. And I
thought I'm not going to be going out
January cuz January is dead. And I knew
what I was doing, but yeah, still can't
win. Still can't win to save your life.
But Jo seems to always win. I'd love to
know how he's doing it, bro. I love to
know how this guy is always continuously winning. Dusty,
no way, bro. No way. I can tell you if I
went gambling last month here on their
machines and I done it every week, I
would lose every time. I I would be
confident to bet money on it, I would
lose every time.
I don't spend my money on gambling. That
was a one-off. Well, I lost 200 two
weeks ago, but I didn't go out December.
Well, I went out once and yeah,
it's bad, bro. It is really bad, you
know. And if I Yeah, the more if I had
put more money and I if I I would have
probably just lost all my money today.
If I kept doing 100 100, I would have
just lost all my money, Dusty. There was
no way I would have come out a winner
today. But this Joe seems to always win.
Nah, it's [ __ ] bro. I'm telling
you, it's [ __ ] And I would love
that to be true because I hate these
industries and I'd love somebody to [ __ ]
them over and find a loophole to [ __ ]
them over, but it's not. It's not true.
It really, really, really is not true,
Dusty. You know, you go in You go to the
bookies today. Yeah. Yeah. New Year's
Eve is a Bro, New Year's Eve is a mug's
game. Think of it. I didn't even I fell
asleep and I didn't The fireworks didn't
even wake me up. New Year's Eve is a
mugs game, bro. It is literally a mugs
because I I would love anyone to to take
money from the bookies and [ __ ] them
over. That's why because anyone that
[ __ ] them bookies over is is a legend
in my opinion. But listen, Dusty, um New
Year's Eve is a Mugs game. New Year's
Eve is a proper proper mugs game. You
have to pay to get in places. It's full
of [ __ ] Rampack. The drinks are
more expensive. It's a mugs game. It
generally generally is a mugs game, bro.
New Year's Eve is a M's game
and then the next day we're in a new
year [laughter] like that. New Year's
Eve is a Mug's game, bro. Trust me,
that's why I didn't go out. So, I knew
even if I lost this £100, I would have
saved a fuckload of money. So, um yeah,
what the [ __ ] Dusty?
Even if I had won like 100 150, I would
have been happy in this day and age to
you know, even won 100 150. Nah, nah,
it's not happening, mate. You are not
winning nothing. You're not winning nothing, mate.
At my age, I stopped doing that [ __ ]
ages ago. When you was my age, what 28?
I stopped that at like [ __ ] 26, 27.
Yeah, I stopped all that [ __ ] at 26, 27. Yeah. Yeah, bro.
They can't help themselves.
Even on [ __ ] New Year's
Day, they can't help themselves. These
machines, imagine that, bro. And they
and think of how much money they made,
you know, uh, last month. Absolute
shitloads out of people. Not me, but
other people. And they're still doing
it, you know, even in the new year.
They're still doing it.
So, I won't be going in that lad books
again cuz I spat all over the machine. So yeah,
it's not good, bro. It's not good.
But yeah, 28. You used to go out at my
age. I don't think you went out New
Year's Eve when you was 28, mate. This
is a time where you kind of stopped going out. That's bad. Yeah,
I ain't been fabric for ages.
Yeah, fabrics. I ain't been for ages. I
kind of I got bored of it, bro. At 20 at 26.
I stopped going out regularly at about 26.
But don't forget, Dusty, I probably I
probably have been out more than you.
I probably have been out more than you
to be fair.
I stopped going out like regularly.
Yeah, probably on my way to 27.
I don't even drink anymore. Like [ __ ]
Oh, bro. Trust me, I have. Dusty, trust
me. Trust me, brother. I have. Yeah.
Trust me, I have. I have. I used to go
out three times a week, bro. I used to
gamble all the time. I used to drink all
the time, brother. Trust me, I have. And
at and at 26 and at 25 26 27 I had more
money than you. Trust me. Trust me, bro.
And I'm not even trying to argue with
you. Like I'm not even saying I'm better
than you. Trust me, you never trust me.
You never, bro. I've been up and down
the country. I used to go out three
times a week
spending £800 on nights out. Trust me,
bro. You You really haven't.
You really, really haven't.
Trust me, bro. You really haven't. But
now more than me.
You might have been abroad more times
than me. You might have been abroad more
times than me. I wouldn't argue that. Or
you might have done cocaine or
something, but you haven't been out more
than me, bro.
Trust me. What do you think I got up to,
bro? With all that money, huh? Just sat
in all day. But it doesn't really matter
anyways. I was bored of it. Yeah.
I used to go out Thursdays and Saturdays
and then it was like once a week, then
it was every like two weeks and three weeks.
You know what I mean?
I just don't see the point in it anymore
going out. I really don't see the point in it.
It's not good, bro. Is it? I don't know
how Timmy still does this gambling
thing. I don't know how he still does this gambling
the way he does. I fancied it today and
that was a one-off, bro. Like, that was
you know? That was literally a one-off, man.
I know, bro. It's a mugs game. New
Year's Eve is a mugs game. New Year's
Eve is is definitely a mugs game. You
have to pay to get in. The prices are uh
the drinks are more money and it's just
rampacked. It's just for the [ __ ]
It is literally a mug's game. New Year's
Eve is a Mugs game.
It is. And I've been out New Year's Eve
and I've never had a good night New
Year's Eve. It's literally a Mugs game.
New Year's Eve, they literally take
advantage on that day, bro. And there's
not real any there's not a real There's
not any relevance for it really. It's
just a year. It's just a day before a
new year. There's nothing really special about it.
It's mad. My favorite, like I said,
March and April on Thursdays.
Thursdays in March and I was telling the
Weatherspoon staff about this earlier
when I had breakfast.
I like April. I like March.
Midweek. That's what I like. Whenever
you go out, if you had people I have had
people to go out with.
I have people to go out with and I still
wouldn't go out. And we're not getting
into that self-p projecting conversation
again either because we're not having
haters on this channel. It's a new year
now. It hasn't it hasn't been a great
start to the new year because of that
[ __ ] roulette. But yeah,
I still wouldn't go out. So yeah.
do I really?
I know. But I just went there anyways
cuz I was hungry.
I just went there anyways cuz I was
hungry. So, and I wanted to uh Okay,
that's a hater little projector. We
don't have these people on my channel.
Yeah, I did say that, but I was hungry,
wasn't I? So, and I wanted to go to the
bookies. So, yeah, they open at 9:30 today.
I had a bagel yesterday. It was [ __ ] lovely.
Why? Because you have to bet big on the football.
You got to bet big on the football. That's why.
And the odds are [ __ ] now. The odds have
got worse on um
there's nothing to be positive about
with the football. The odds are really
really [ __ ] now and you need to lump on
money to be able to win and then you
risk losing a load of money.
You know what I'm saying? They've
caughten on. The odds are [ __ ] now on
football, bro. The odds are [ __ ]
Yeah, you can do that. Yeah, but it's
it's very unlikely to come in.
Yeah, you can do that, but it's very
unlikely that's going to win.
Very unlikely. It's hard enough to get
[ __ ] two, mate. So, the odds are
[ __ ] [ __ ] now, bro.
Like if I put 180 on the double both
teams to score it's like 500 and
something but then I risk losing 180 [ __ ] pound
and it's not worth it bro like cuz you
can go on roulette with that online and
turn it into thousands. Maybe maybe it's
unlikely but there's still a chance.
This is [ __ ] gambling period. The
gambling is just [ __ ] That's why I
don't I really don't do it much. I
really don't. This was a one-off because
I thought, "Oh yeah, first of January,
let me let me be the first one to clean
up on these machines." But nah. Nah.
£140 I got it to and it [ __ ] took all
of that money. What the [ __ ] bro?
It's not a problem for me because I
don't gamble much. So, I didn't need to
have that resolution because I don't
gamble much anyways.
I don't gamble much anyways. So, I
didn't need to have that resolution. It
hasn't been a problem for a very very
very very long time.
But it's not a problem for me, bro. So,
I don't need to have that as a as a resolution, you know?
I ain't, bro. I gamble very rarely
unless you want to clap the football. I
just fancied it today cuz it's like a
new year, so I thought, oh, let me get
let's get off to a good start, honestly.
And then obviously I lost 200 two weeks
ago, but I didn't go out December.
That was kind of like holiday and [ __ ]
So, I'm I won't be gambling, bro. I'm
not going back to that [ __ ]
It's hard to win now. It's very hard to
win. I thought I would have won today,
bro, being the first of January. But nah,
even if I won, 150, I would have been
buzzing because it's so hard to get wins
nowadays, dusty, that any win you get,
it's like, oh, because you know how hard
it is. Back in the day, you used to be
able to win all all the time. Now you
can't win much. So when you do win,
you're like, oh [ __ ] You know what I
mean? That's that's how bad it is.
That's really how bad it is. Well,
unless you go to a casino. I might go to
Nottingham. Next time I gamble, I might
go to Nottingham.
I might go to Nottingham Casino book
hotel and see what's up.
Maybe March or something. I don't know.
But very hard to win. So any win you do
get you're thankful for. If I won £250
right now, £300 now, I would be buzzing, bro. Buzzing.
It's very hard to win now. Very hard to
win. Very hard to win money.
It is very hard to win money nowadays.
But this Joseph Ferrar's videos that um
what he's showing is [ __ ]
It is generally generally generally
generally [ __ ] You know, you don't
really see many people on the machines
now because they know
I know. I know. What he's doing, uh,
Matty, is he's trying to troll. What
he's trying to do is trying to get me
into gambling. Do you not understand
what his channel's about? I I clocked it
ages ago, bro. His whole channel is
showing fake wins or not showing when he
loses to try to get me to gamble to do
my balls in. And it's not going to work.
It's not going to work. I susted him
ages ago as soon as he started sticking
up for non leg saying about how he's not
a virgin because he's got a girlfriend.
I susted him and when I went on his
channel, bro, I'm not stupid. I know
what he's doing. I know what he's doing.
He's a lavy bog. And if you ever see him
on L JS, he only talks about me. He's obsessed.
Yeah, I know, bro. You don't need to
tell me, bro. But I already know. I know
exactly what he's doing. I know exactly
what he's doing, bro.
You're smart that you figured it out.
You're smart, bro, cuz I figured out as
well. I I I know what he's doing. I
generally know what he's doing, bro. Trust me.
Same with that Smokey B. What? You
turned £100 into two half grand. Yeah,
right, bro. But in this day and age,
really, did you? Nah.
Um, yeah. And another thing is, um,
yeah, when he I'm saying this is what I
said to him as well, does if you win,
put the full videos up. Well, no, you
could. No, don't put the full videos up
because then you will only show wins. Go
live and gamble. And then if you're
winning, then I'll be like, "Okay, fair
play. You're winning. Go live before you
go on these machines and gamble
like what LJ does. and we'll see how
much money you're really winning. And if
you're not doing that, then you know.
Yeah, basically. Um,
yeah, exactly. I don't I don't really
care about the guy, but just stop acting
like the big man when you're not a big
man and stop telling people that they've
done nothing when they've done more than
you will ever do.
And they're trying to say that we all
laugh at you, brother. Trust me,
whenever I go on that L J's channel, I
laugh at all of them. sat on YouTube,
ain't got no life. I've got more laughs
out of you than you would ever have out of me.
So, I got a lot I've got a lot of
stalkers, bro. A lot of stalkers. That's
just YouTube, though, is it? They'll never stop.
They will never stop, bro.
That's what happens when you're younger
and better looking than these people. I
guess it's kind of funny, bro. It's
nothing really to get annoyed at.
They're just sados. Simple. Yeah.
>> [clears throat and snorts]
>> So, I lost 100 pound today, bro, but I
wouldn't put any more in. It's the guilt
that always used to get me, you know, the guilt.
And I really don't gamble, bro. It's very rare.
If I got a couple of more hits on that
[ __ ] roulette, I would have won, bro.
I had three pound on 11.
Just a 300 to one on 11 mate. Oh, [ __ ] me.
You know, got over a 17, but no, it
weren't having it. It weren't having it
for toffee, mate. Not for toffee in a
candy shop. It weren't having it at all.
Yeah, I wasn't going to put any more
than that. I weren't going to put any
more than that. Some of those be buddy
as well. So,
I get buddy next week as well. So, it's all good. Um,
I still feel a bit guilty when I'm doing
it though. I always feel guilty cuz you
know it's bad.
I don't know. Like,
you just know it's bad, is it? So,
whenever you do it, you just feel guilty.
I don't know. I can't explain it, bro.
It's a weird feeling.
You just feel guilty.
Yeah. So did I, mate. So did I. I put
£650 in last year and I didn't even get a bonus yeah.
Nah, 100 pound is nothing, bro.
100 pound is nothing.
When you started getting past 150,
that's when it starts becoming like, yeah, you know,
that's when it starts like I was going
to do 150 and then do two pound spins,
but I couldn't. I can't be losing 15,
bro. I can't be wasting money like that, you know?
And I shouldn't do it anyways cuz look,
I spat all over the machine. But I could
have got nicked today. I could have
actually got nicked, you know.
I could have got nicked, bro.
Yeah, I could have got nicked.
No, it's not even that. With me, it's
just annoying losing. Nah, it's not even
that because I know that it's only £100
and if I had went out drinking, the way
I see it, right, the way I can justify
this is if I went out more December, I
would have been down more money by going
out drinking. So, it's not even that.
It's just losing on it. It's just losing
on it. I just don't like losing.
Everyone's different. I just don't like losing.
You know what I'm saying? With me, it's
sort of money. I just don't like losing.
People like me really shouldn't gamble,
to be honest. And that's why I don't.
That's why I very rarely do. That's why
I very, very, very rarely do,
you know. That's why I very rarely do. [clears throat] But
the only the only thing I used to think
of Dusty is when I lose is oh I could
have gave that money to someone
you know I could have gave that money to
lady but it's not that they've got my
money with me it's more like I know
they've had other people's money all of December
they've had enough people's money bro
and it weren't my money they had but
they had other people's money and it's
like what the [ __ ] bro. You know. Yeah.
So, it depends. If you obviously if you
gamble regularly, then you would see it
dusty in it. If you gamble like twice a
week or once a week, you'd be like, "Oh,
they've got my money." But if you gamble
once or twice,
then you know it's it's irregular in it.
So, you don't really see it like that.
Yeah, maybe they were. Maybe, bro. That
was probably a good time to gamble to be
honest. New Year's Eve.
Yeah, maybe. But they definitely
definitely don't around Christmas. Stay
away from them. They lead up to
Christmas. Stay away from them machines.
Stay the [ __ ] away from them. If you
want to gamble after Christmas, gamble
after, like you said, New Year's Eve.
That's not a bad idea to be fair. But
stay away before Christmas. Stay the [ __ ] away.
Trust me. And I'm telling you from experience.
Yeah. They might not do, bro. But I tell
you one thing, Dusty, they definitely
definitely don't pay before Christmas.
And they definitely definitely don't pay before Christmas.
Trust me, I know that for a fact. But I
just thought that they would have paid
today. Obviously being um being like I
said, new New Year's Day, you know,
nothing. Yeah. I don't see it because
they don't they rarely ever get my
money. So I don't see it like that.
I don't see as though they've had my
money to be fair
dogs. Yeah, I know about it. They used
to have one in Chinford.
They used to have one in Chinford, bro.
But um I don't know if it's still there. Yeah.
Well, I hope that's true cuz I lost 100.
So, I hope that's true. See, I don't
mind hearing about people winning. I
like people winning. It's just that Joe
F is full of [ __ ]
That's just that's just the difference
that it's uh
Oh, was it Wolfenste? I knew it was one of them.
Listen, listen, listen. Um, if you have
one, then that's good, but we just know
this Jo is full of [ __ ] That's that's the thing.
And what he's trying to do, Matty, is
saying what he's trying to what he's
trying to do, Jo is
how. So when you have this opinion,
because it's the right opinion that he's
showing, you know, fake wins, he's going
to start calling you jealous when that's
not jealous. That's not jealousy, bro.
You know, um it's not um it's not
jealousy. It's fact. So obviously if
someone calls him out on it, he's just
going to say, "Oh, you're jealous. Oh,
you're jealous. Oh, you're jealous."
when it's not. It's like if I put up
gambling. Yeah. And um I was only
putting wins up, does that mean
everyone's jealous of me for saying,
"Well, how comes this guy never loses?"
That's not jealousy, bro. When these
people could have had more money with
me, these people could have had more
money, they could have more money than
me, and just because they have an
opinion, it doesn't mean that they're
jealous. You need to really make that make sense. You know,
you don't really hear many people
winning on him anymore.
Brother, do you think you'll have a
girlfriend next New Year's Eve? Same
question to you. [ __ ]
Same question to you, bro. Do you think
you'll have a girlfriend next New Year's
Eve? I can ask you the same question.
Do you think you'll have a girlfriend?
Oh, you've got a wife. Oh, you're
another one that's married. Not another
one. Surely, you all seem to be married
on here. Jesus Christ. You're married.
Oh, wow. You all seem to be married on
here. See you later.
Bye-bye now. [clears throat]
So, um yeah. And when I lose gambling,
bro, I think of like really negative
things. I get like I turn like a demon,
bro. I don't like losing. I don't like losing, Dusty.
I do not like losing. No.
Yeah, they're all married on here apparently. They say
Yeah. You think, oh, do you know what,
right? You know that man, Dusty, right? Someone commented
Um, someone commented and I'll tell you
what I said, right? I got a lot of
thumbs up by the way. This is how you
know this community is biased.
I've done my second what losing 100
pound. Okay, you can tell yourself that.
Anyways, let me read this. Yeah. Um,
this guy wrote um to Oreo man. I bet
savvy guy will get a woman in 2026. All
he has to do is start approaching and
playing the numbers game. I've replied
straight away to this. This was first
figuring him. I turned around and said
to him, um, he won't. I've been
approaching women for years and it's
always the same thing they do and say, I
quote, I have a boyfriend. I quote, I'm
not interested. Or they give their
numbers and lead you on and play games.
Sadly, a different year. Sadly, a
different Sadly, a different year won't
change women. last year I only had three
dates in the whole of April for the
whole year. It's truly impossible. I
live in London and approached thousands
of times. Then he responded, "This
should be at least his new year year's
resolution." Obviously, cuz the guy
scared of approaching. That's why he's
saying this. I turn around and said,
"It's not suddenly going to change,
brother. I gave up and I feel so much
better for it. It was so toxic and
depressing." Then the guy, the older
man, replied to me saying, "I can say I
don't approach black women anymore. I am
done with black women.
What is so mad about this is if this
guy, he's 37, actually tried, he would
still be in the same position. That's
the maddest thing is he's never tried.
He's never approached. He moans and
winges every day. But the thing is, if
he actually tried, he would still be in
the same situation.
Look at the situation I'm in.
Look at the situation I'm in. And I've
gone through money. I've gone out. I've
look look at the situation I'm in.
So, you know,
it wasn't about owning anyone, bro. It
was about telling them that like trying
doesn't work. It's not about It's not about owning.
I just said it isn't suddenly going to
change. It's a new year. It's not
suddenly going to change. And I don't
want to be negative. I'm not trying to
be negative. I'm trying to be real. You
know, it's not going to change. Women
are not just going to change. um
winning. It's not just suddenly going to
change. I'm sorry, but it ain't. You
know, you can change yourself if you
want. You can go to the gym. You should
do all of them things.
Yeah. I spat on the machine today. Me, I
just spat on it. But it's it's not going
to change. Women, they're never going to
change. They'll always be the same.
So, yeah. I spat all over the machine here.
I spat all over it.
People like me shouldn't gamble.
People really shouldn't People like me
shouldn't gamble, bro. Really shouldn't. Yeah.
Yeah, I thought I was going to win like 150.
No, I don't think so. They'll probably
just ban me.
I feel sorry for the member of staff.
She was a black woman and obviously it's
not her fault and that I didn't want her
to think I was like threatening her and
that, but um No, they wouldn't they
wouldn't call the police.
Yeah, but there's no point because if
you break the machine,
they're just going to they they've got
them all in shard.
I've actually broke a machine before
twice. No, I wasn't pissed off with the
staff. I was pissed off with the machine.
No, no, don't. If you smash the machine,
all they're going to do is just
just fix it very quickly. So, there's no
point in that really. And then you could
get nicked and then you've got to go
caught. It's just pointless. And you got
to play a fire.
But I've smashed machines up before like
twice. Not a lot, but I have done it
They never got me for it ever.
Never. I'm surprised I've never been
done for criminal damage. You know, I'
I've damaged a lot of [ __ ] I have
smashed bench tops up. I have I remember
there was this one time. Yeah. I'm not
going to tell you what bookies it was.
I'm surprised they never ever dump me
for it to be honest. I tell you the
story. Yeah. When I was, how old was I?
19. I was 19. Yeah. I lost a 50 note.
Yeah. I lost a 50 note. Um it was around
the summer time when I was talking to
Money Mike back before they were two
pound a spoon. I lost a 50 note.
Obviously 50 was a lot of money back
then. It's still a lot of money now. I
literally, bro, went back with a weight
bar. I done I put the whole windows in, bro.
I put the whole windows in. [laughter]
It broke. But I literally threw the
weight bar and cracked the whole thing.
It didn't go through.
So, but they never ever and and I still
went in after that after a long time, obviously. So, yeah. [snorts]
Yeah, I done it. It didn't go through,
but it it it cracked. The whole thing
cracked like the window, you know, like
the window where the paper is where it's
like advertising betting.
One big crack, bro. Imagine them people
in the shop. So yeah.
Am I addicted to gambling? Nope.
Not at all. I rarely gamble. >> Nope.
was last year, brother. That was [ __ ]
That was like 10 years ago.
Last year. It was like 10 years ago, you silly goose. But yeah,
no, I'm not addicted to gambling, bro.
I just don't like losing.
Timmy's addicted. Yeah, I'm not [ __ ]
addicted. I don't know. I just fancied
it today, you know? I thought I was
going to win
first of January, but none
mate couldn't Huh?
[ __ ] now. I'm not missing out on food. Uh 10:54. Yeah.
Yeah. Peter bet he didn't win. Uh 100 pound.
Yeah, only 100.
But I'm not going out the whole of
January. So, if you actually see it with
me, when I gamble, I actually save money
as opposed to going out drinking. If I
went out, what's the day today? Oh, it's
Thursday. Imagine I went out drinking
today. Oh, it actually is Thursday. It
would be completely dead. Saturday,
completely dead. It would be it would be
dead now for like a month and a half.
Yeah. If you went out drinking today.
Yeah. It would be dead.
Not a soul will be out in them clubs.
No, they're skint now until uh February.
That's what they are. Yeah. Definitely. Definitely.
Yeah, people won't be out there until
mid mid um Feb
9:30 they were open
they open at 10 which never made no
sense cuz there's loads of B.
One second. My brother used to work in
Lad Brooks. This may sound stupid, but
it's true. Bookies want you to keep in
the shop playing football.
Really? I've never heard that one before.
[snorts] You know that self projection?
We don't have self projectors on this
channel. So I don't
So I don't gamble wins. I use it. Yeah.
I gamble today.
But no, I don't gamble much. I just
gambled today cuz I thought it was going
to pay out.
Why are you people getting excited over
losing £100, bro?£100 is literally
nothing to me. I could lose £500 right
now. It would be nothing to me. You need
to chill out. Yeah, everybody knows that
you're a crazy [ __ ]
Yeah, everybody knows that you're a crazy cat.
Why are you getting happy over someone
who's 100 pound, bro? What the [ __ ]
This gambling is just a mugs game, plain
and simple, bro.
Why not, bro? Because I I keep it real.
I like to keep it real, unlike Jo.
What kind of person would I be if I
didn't come on here and talk about the losses, you know?
Because you never win. That's the thing.
I don't mind, bro. Okay. Okay. I'll tell
you. Right. So, the past two months, I
would have lost £300, but in reality, I
would have saved a lot of money because
I hadn't been out drinking. But I went
out drinking once last month, so I don't
really care because I'm saving money
this way. I'm actually saving money.
So that's I'm actually saving money.
I've saved [ __ ] tons of money, bro. So yeah,
it ain't good though, man. It ain't good.
When I have last good I haven't, bro.
The last good win I had was online 100
to 500 and that was
like two months ago. I I haven't When
was the last time I played a FOB back
then? Ages ago, bro. I don't play them.
Not being able to pull girls. Oh, I can
pull girls. I just don't want to waste
my time on them because they're all evil
and they're all NPCs and they're all the same.
Uh, any advice? I used to be addicted to
them as well. I used to spend like £500
a month on them.
I can pull girls, more girls than you,
but I don't waste my time on evil
people. I don't waste my time on evil
NPCs. No thanks.
Yeah, I don't waste my time on evil people
cuz that's what women are. They're evil.
So, um yeah, it was the roulette two months ago.
I put £100 in. I took 500 and something out.
But honestly, honestly, the industry is
finished. Like it it generally is it is
It is [ __ ] finished.
It is. I I I don't think of I can't
think of anything you can win except the football obviously,
but you got a lump on it.
I don't know. I don't know how you can
win now. I don't think you really can. I
might go to Nottingham and try the
casino in Nottingham at some point.
I don't know, bro.
It's just [ __ ] in it.
[ __ ] You can't win now.
Well, I started on the slots. I put £100
in. I played it to 40 pound and went on
the roulette. I couldn't even get a
bonus to save my life.
I couldn't get a bonus to save my life.
But I know it's nothing. These people
are getting excited. I lost £100 and
that's nothing to me. I could lose a
grand and it still be nothing to me. Yeah.
[ __ ] madness, bro. What the [ __ ]
>> Yeah, I started off on fish and frenzy.
I played it down to 40
because I'm not stupid and I'm not
putting any more money in. Simple. [snorts]
Nah. No chance. No chance, matey. I
shouldn't have even done that to be honest.
Yeah, I'm 100 pound down.
You can't win to save your [ __ ] life, bro.
It's £300 down something.
Yeah. Yeah. 300 pound is a lot to lose.
Yeah. Yeah. 300 a lot to lose. Yeah.
Anything over 150 is it? Yeah. Bad.
I reckon you could win on that global
draw roulette though. I reckon you could
win if you timed it right.
What do you think?
That USA is he's got a really bad
receding hairline, man.
He's receding badly.
But yeah, all night spas and stuff.
Yeah, they ain't got no life, bro. These
people ain't got no life. I'm done with
them anyways. I'm not reacting to these
people anymore. But yeah, they have got
no life. [snorts] But YouTube,
they've got no life.
Yeah, I was thinking that 100 to one roulette.
No, I don't want to blow job Bar quest.
I'm asexual. Thank you very much.
Yeah, I've been asexual a long time
now. I'm asexual.
Yeah, I'm asexual. Me, lad.
No, I'm asexual, brother. because of um
because of uh if women can't be normal
cuz they're not normal, then why are you
going to waste your time at norm on
people that can't be normal and not evil?
Why why the [ __ ] would you waste your
time? They prove they they're all the
same. They proven they're all the same
time and time and time again. So that's
that. And yeah, I am doing hotel videos
and food videos. I am
not January though cuz it's dead January.
Yeah, there will be videos to come.
100 to one roulette. What in the in the bookies?
[snorts] Yeah, that Joe F is showing. Um
that's what I think he does as well.
Puts money in and pretends he wins. Definitely.
Definitely definitely definitely bro. What?
Can I bark rest?
Nah, women are evil, bro. Women are evil [ __ ]
They are evil.
I hate women, bro. With a passion. I can
actually I can safely say that.
Men are not for me. I'm asexual. Do you
know what asexual means?
Do you know what asexual means, brother?
It means you don't like neither.
maybe, but I'll never take drugs. So,
uh, I definitely definitely am asexual.
I definitely definitely am.
Yeah, I struggled to get women, brother.
I've pulled more women than you've had hot dinners.
I've had more women than you've had hot
dinners. Make it make sense.
I have been with multiple multiple
different women that weren't escorts.
Make it make sense. And I hate them.
And I [ __ ] well hate them.
And I'll never bother with them ever
again. I hate them scumbags. I hate
them. I hate the double standards. I
hate them. I hate what they do. I hate
everything about them. The scum of the
earth. They're worse than pedophiles.
Yeah, they're worse than pedophiles,
I'd say. Yeah, they're scum of the
earth. All right, Braquest, they really,
really are scum. Like, I know you laugh
at it, but no, they really, really are scumbags.
They really are scumbags.
I puss above my weight. You're probably
self- projecting, brother.
You're probably uglier than me, lad.
You're probably You're probably talking
about yourself there.
Just just uh just a thought. Yeah.
Anyways, we're not having negativity on
my chat. So, if you want to keep it up,
I'm just going to ban you. We're not
having this this year.
Nah, I'm not gambling anymore.
We're not having negative uh negativity
on my chat.
No, I don't want you, Bar Quest. I don't
want you. You're not my type.
No, you're not my type, bro.
Yeah, whatever, bro. No one cares. None
of these skanky women in London are
above me, bro. None of these skanky
women are above me.
Never have been, never will be.
The issue is they're stuck up [ __ ]
with unrealistic standards. There's
nothing left to try to figure out.
They're just [ __ ]
I've already figured it out. I don't
know why you're trying to I don't know
why you're trying to waste your time
figuring it out. I've already figured
out with the scumbags.
I'm not talking about this anymore. I'm
not I'm not talking about this.
I have given up forever.
Bar quest, you know, I woke up yesterday
in a good mood. Then I then I started
having a foul mood. I started really
like having these evil thoughts.
Like really dirty mood swings. Yeah.
Yeah. Dirty dirty stinky mood swings.
Seriously, bro. Yeah.
Dirty stinky mood swings, bro.
like the feeling of wanting to get like
revenge on women and [ __ ]
>> Yeah, proper Yeah.
Why would you Why would you try with
women again? That's like That's like
entering a desert with dangerous
animals, bro. you you know that's what
it is trying to date yeah and dealing
with women you're just you're just going
in the jungle with with animals with
dangerous animals that will attack you
think of it think of it like that think
of that analogy
it's like going into a jungle with
[ __ ] gorillas lions [ __ ] the lot
you wouldn't walk into a [ __ ] desert
a jungle with dangerous animals would you
that's literally what it's Yeah,
literally, bro. Literally.
Yeah. I lost 100 pound on the fog te's, Mr. Bean.
Yeah. Yeah, I lost £100, bro. 60 on the
slots and 40 on roulette.
Yeah, weren't having it for toffee.
Christian frenzium global draw roulette
and I spat all over the machine.
Mr. Beat all over the machine. All over. Yeah.
Yeah, I sp all over it.
None. You're all [ __ ]
That's who the best gambler is on here.
None. Cuz you're all [ __ ] [laughter]
You're all [ __ ]
Do you want my opinion, Best?
D [ __ ] [laughter] H
Yeah, they are open. They were open at 9:30.
I went to Weather Spoons. I got a breakfast.
Yep. And then I had a little gambling
session. Mr. Bean,
do you want my opinion, Zippy? Ah,
they're all [ __ ]
That's so lazy. That word is so vulg, [laughter] [clears throat]
man. I love it. Yeah.
Yeah. Sorry, Bar Quest. I'm not
interested in you.
I'm not. Why you going on about some
girl that don't want you? I'm not. [laughter]
Do you remember that one?
You remember that one? Bar quest. I'm not.
I'm not. [laughter]
You are Oh, you virgin. Do you remember
you skint virgin?
He was like No, he was like this. He was
like this. He was like this. Yeah,
he was like this. Yeah,
look, he was like this. He was talking.
So, basically, I met her parents and
then I went home and then I discovered
that she had blocked me. She randomly uh
Uh, stop going on about some girl that
don't want you. Uh, I'm not.
At least I didn't go to this door like PJ. [laughter]
You got about some of the doubt, weren't
you? You skin virgin.
You skint [ __ ] Showing daddy's bum
change life savings. You skin [ __ ]
Ah, bro. That's a classic. I'm not.
Oh no. Stop going on about some girl
that don't want you. Oh no.
You are you skin virgin.
You skin [ __ ] [laughter] Oh,
I'm not. Oh, I still smell like half the
shave. Oh gosh. I'm going to have a nice
sleep today. Bquest.
Why don't any of you people come on camera?
My hair. Why don't any of you people
come on cam? Red star. All night spas.
Why does none of you people come on camera?
Always wonder that.
No insults for me, lad. Just wondering
why do none of you come on camera. D.
Yeah, I'm having a roast later.
Someone's cooking it.
Da da da. Yeah, that's another thing.
Yeah, I I went at Autumn cuz she was
going at me and I said, "At least I
don't have to use filters like you." And
then LT came to a rescue like Superman. D
just showing off. He was showing off.
Bquest. He was showing off.
We don't go on camera because we aren't fully autistic.
You're not fully autistic.
You're Wait, let me read that. I don't
think I've read that right. We don't go
on camera because we aren't fully autistic.
So, if you're not fully autistic, why do
you come on YouTube and repeat the same
[ __ ] every day? Just a question.
No hate. Just wondering if you're not
autistic, why have you been on the
internet for 10 years calling people skin
um every single day for for over 10
years? Just just wondering if you're not autistic. Just wondering.
But yeah, um he he went straight to her
rescue. I said that, listen all, you can
talk about me all you want, but you're
the one that uses filters. And he was
straight to her rescue. Um, even though
I hadn't heard from this [ __ ] for
months, I have not heard from this [ __ ]
for Yeah. literally months, uh,
Barquest. And as soon as I went um and I
defended myself against this [ __ ]
fatty that uses filters, he was straight
to a rescue,
just showing off, you know.
That is that is some beta male behavior,
bro. When you have to defend women on
the internet, you are even defending
women in real life, that is beta male
[ __ ] bro. So to do it online, that is like
that is pathetic, bro. pathetic.
You know, that's why he gets all these
G. So, why the [ __ ] are you defending
some fat [ __ ] that uses filters? She
was going at me. She was going at me.
Yeah. No one asked her. No one asked her to [ __ ]
um [ __ ] go at me on Red Stars. She
was going at me, so I defended myself.
Yeah. Yeah. They they they think by
showing off to women that that women are
going to like them. It's got to be
autism with a lot of people do it, bro.
They defend women, but women don't like
them. And they and they can't get it
into their thick heads. They generally
think that defending women is going to
um is going to uh
is going to make women like them. It's
autism, you know? So, you're not the
only one on it with autism. It's like [ __ ] nons.
I like Shay
if you don't like Sham Co. Do you
remember? Did Do you remember? Do you
Do you remember? I I like Sh. You're
gay. You're gay. I know. I was like, I'm
gay. I've literally been with more women
than you, you little [ __ ] No. No.
She's attractive. You can't deny it. [ __ ] copycat.
You know when he was trying to fit in?
Do you remember? Do you remember when he
was trying to fit in?
He didn't want to feel left out. [laughter]
Bark, he wanted to follow the crowd. He
said, "You can't deny she's attractive."
Well, I [ __ ] can. She's ugly and I've
had more women than you, you skin
virgin. That's what I said then and I'll
say it [ __ ] now. Bro, they do the
same. Do you not understand? We Bro, do
you not understand, Bquest? That they
done the same thing with Rihanna. They
done the same thing with Rihanna. I was
reading the other day on Reddit and I
was like, "Oh yeah, if if you look at
Rihanna when you don't get hot hard,
there's something wrong with you.
There's something wrong with you. That's
what they say. There's something wrong
with you." They all used to copy each
other. It's called a copycat statement. [laughter]
A copycat statement. And that's what And
I put a cat up. Listen, I put a cat up
on the picture. Um, Barkrest and some
account said that looks like the virgin [ __ ] >> [laughter]
>> I was dead. He said, "That looks like
the virgin fucker." [laughter]
You know what I say? Say, "No, look,
look. It's the copycat. It's the coffee."
He's like, "That looks like the virgin fucker." [laughter]
Do you get it? But I pressed the virgin [ __ ] [laughter]
Oh, one second. I'm just having a slash. Oh gosh.
I had to stop um taking sugar barest
because I've got uh I had some cavities.
I had a cavity in my mouth. So about to
stop taking sugar.
I've reduced it. Well, I've reduced it a
lot because of the uh old cavities.
Feeling a lot better now. One sec.
You can't beat having a nice pee. >> [laughter]
>> Why' you block me on everything? Bar quest.
>> Yeah. Why? Do you know why I hate bar
quest? Is seen these sex scenes in
horror films? Have Have you heard of the
a horror film The Housemaid?
I watched it uh not last week, the week
before and there was these sex scenes
and it was like 30% of the movie and it
was constant, mate. These sex scenes
over and over and over again. It's like
it's trying to mock you, you know? It's
trying to mock you in it. Get under your
skin. Get under your last nerves.
You ain't seen it. Well, it's basically
a horror film and uh yeah, just just sex scenes, bro.
Not good for the mind.
Yeah, not good for the mind, bro.
It's not It's not necessary in hobbies,
but they have it. And I'm thinking, hold
on, Bess. People don't watch porn
because of unhealthy because of how
unhealthy it is, you know? So, why am I
going to watch horror seeing [ __ ]
basically porn in it? And you saw you
saw nude scenes as well. It looks like a
virgin [ __ ] up. >> [laughter] >> Yeah.
Any football bets? Nope. Not today. I
lost £100 on the machine. So, not today. No.
Um, so Bret, why was why was Nons
talking about Shen?
Why was he saying if you don't find her
attractive, you're gay? Do you remember
why he was saying that?
Weird thing to say, isn't it?
Why was he saying that? [laughter] What?
Well, first what with the crowd. [laughter]
I'm dead. I'm dead. You didn't want to
feel left out. [laughter]
So, what you're basically Why did you
know what agrees? He said to me, he
said, "You're nothing but a big fat
stinking coffee." [laughter]
You're nothing but a big fat stinking coffee. Meow. Meow. Meow. [laughter]
He didn't want to feel left out, did he?
Yeah. I was watching some horror movies with Laney.
Laney likes horror. Well, she doesn't,
but she doesn't mind them now.
Yeah, I like horror movies. [laughter]
I like I like horror movies. Oh, [ __ ] [laughter] Yeah, man.
Have you gambled, Brest? Have you been
you've been on the slots? No. >> [sighs]
>> All right, Captain.
Yeah, I had three dates last year, uh,
Bark Quest, and they were all in April.
I only had three dates last year. Do you
know how many times I went out last year?
But people on Reddit say that you'll meet someone.
They say that you'll meet someone on Reddit.
I had this 45year-old playing hard to
get a couple of weeks ago at Brest. A
45y old playing hard to get. Imagine
that. Someone that can't even give you
babies if you wanted them.
This generation's [ __ ] up, mate. I had
three dates last year. Yeah.
And I used to have someone come around
me give me a [ __ ] but I kind of fell
out with them. So, it's somebody I met
from a couple of years ago, but I fell
out with them. She started being a [ __ ]
So that's the only person I had. And
obviously I don't do escorts anymore. So yeah. Yeah, bro.
Yeah. Three dates I had. [snorts]
It does suck. Yeah.
Oh, bless you then. Bless you.
You remember USA Izzy's dad messaging me bar crest.
See, I don't think um LT was wrong
getting involved with that. I can see
where he's coming from cuz obviously
it's what I was saying. I don't think
he's a s for that. But he's definitely
definitely a s with that alim. 100% that
is sing. That is definitely sing, bro.
No, that is sing. That is definitely
sing 100%. Now that is yeah,
you know, and this is how you know these
people on here at Barquest haven't got a
life and they don't get women because if
I wanted to talk to a woman, I would
just go outside and talk to a woman and
get someone's number. Not saying I could
[ __ ] them or date them, but that's how
you know the people on here that haven't
got a life because the way they go on
like with autumn and stuff, that's how
you know they don't get [ __ ] If
anyone's do or or like don't have the
confidence to go and speak to someone
and don't have any interaction outside of YouTube,
that's how you know basically because if
they got [ __ ] they wouldn't be
caring about a woman on YouTube.
That's a that's a telltale sign, bro. So yeah,
I could never I would never ever get
with a woman on YouTube. Never. Never.
Why would I? Why would I? If I live in
London and I can just go and try to meet
someone, you know, in London, why would
I? It doesn't make sense. Why would I?
That's just opening a can of worms.
Really, if you think about it, when you
could try to meet, obviously we know
what women are like, their [ __ ]
but you could try to meet someone
outside and have it away from YouTube.
Why would you get with someone on
YouTube? It doesn't make sense. It
literally doesn't make any sense, bro, at all.
Yeah. So, I'd never get with a [ __ ] on
YouTube. Natalie G wanted me. I didn't
want her. She's with Monty now
because your shit's going to get out there and
it's like, why? If they had a life,
these people on here, they wouldn't care
about some woman on the internet,
you know? That just goes to show that
they're ugly, fat, and have got no
interaction with the outside world. So
yeah, that's that. I need to message
someone. Hold on.
So yeah, you'd meet me. Oh, bless you.
Nah, I can't meet you, Barz. cuz you you
would try and touch me.
You you don't you don't know anything
about me, Brist.
Okay. When's my birthday?
You don't know my birthday, do you?
If you want to meet me, you you should
know some stuff about me.
When's my birthday? Nope. Wrong.
Sorry, wrong, mister.
When When's your birthday?
Nope, it's not November.
My birthday is not November, matey. Almost.
When's your birthday?
Yeah, my birthday's October. Yeah.
Yeah, mine's October.
When's When's yours?
No. Okay. What month? Not not not the
Not the day or the year. What month?
Mine's Mine's October 27th. Um,
I think April.
Either April or March.
I think it's either April or March. I
will go I think April. Yeah. Oh.
What about me, you, and USA Izzy Bar
Quest? We could all snuggle up together. [laughter] Me?
Me? Me, you, and me? Me, you, and USA
could all snuggle up.
What do you think of that? On the sofa. [laughter]
On the sofa. Eh,
what do you think? [laughter]
Oh, do you remember Timmy Aldridge Park? Timmy Aldridge. [laughter]
when he met Monty Man not so long ago.
He was like, "I'll knock him out. [laughter]
I'm going to knock him out. God bless.
I'm [laughter] going to knock him out.
All right. Do you remember Ben Furvy? He
come on the 1st of January. uh one year
B West he went on Timmy's and he was
like same people same story see you next year [laughter]
we call him Filthy Ben same people same
story see you next [laughter] year
I died bro when he said that and then he
come off for like 11 months same people
same story it's true don't it is oh I
know Quest. I know. Park. I know. Don't
be mad. It's the same people every day.
Same people every day. Is it
quest? It's the same people.
It's the same repeat people.
That's five people without a Christmas
on this community. That's five people
without family this Christmas. Did you
see Monty man's live stream? He said he
went live on Christmas. She said, "I've
only gone live to see who's going to be
watching me, who's going to join."
Yeah. I've only gone on to see who and
if anyone's watching me, that means
they've got no life. They've got no
Christmas life. That's what he said. [laughter]
He And then five people join. And he's
like, "That's five people in this
community without a family." I was [laughter] dead.
Anyone who's watching me now? Yeah. He
copied me though. He's a little copycat.
Died on that on Christmas. He's a He's a
little He's You know what? Yeah. You
know this nonslegs. Do you know what he needs?
He needs a little part-time job.
That's what he needs. What do you think?
A little part-time job will do him the
world of good. Get him out the house.
What do you think? little part-time job,
you know, perhaps like working, you
know, in a calf or something, you know,
to get your money up so you don't have
to keep showing your dad's life life
savings. What do you think?
Oh, bless you.
Oh, same people. Same people, same story.
Same people, same story. See you next. [laughter]
I love Filthy Ben. Big up Filthy Ben.
Yeah, same people. Same story.
O, do you remember the quote about Timmy Brest?
That one was a [ __ ] banger, you know.
Oh, I do remember the quote. He uh Tom
Woods basically said, "Yeah, playing
arguing with Timmy is like playing chess
with a pigeon. Even if you beat it, it
will [ __ ] all over the the chess table
and act like it's one.
It's like playing a game of chess with a pigeon.
Even if you beat it, it will strut
around and [ __ ] all over the chess chess
table, but act like it's one.
That was good as well. [laughter]
Yeah, he could. What do you think? Yeah.
Yeah, I think so as well, Febbe. Just
Just a little part-time job. Get him out the house.
What do you think? No, it will get him
out the house.
Yeah, we'll get him out the house, mate.
Little part-time job.
What do you think? Yeah, the breakfast
was nice. Just a little part-time job.
Never hurt anyone. Little part-time job
would do you the world of good, mate.
You've never worked. Why don't you work?
Why don't you Why don't you get yourself
a little job, you skin bastard?
Yeah, just just a couple of hours. earn 50 quid.
You know that virgin has never worked.
I've worked Quest. I've done Uber. I've
delivered um I've delivered uh for Uber
in central London and I've done a lot of
hours. I've worked.
I've worked, mate. I have [ __ ]
worked. He's never worked. And mate,
that was hard. That was that was hard.
My hands were all [ __ ] swollen
after it as well. Yeah, just a little
job, you know. It doesn't matter if you
earn, you know, £40, £50, £80 because
the thing is Bquest, you've earned that
money. It feels good, you know, earning
money. The only the only better thing to
winning money is earning
your own money,
you know, earning Yeah. earning your own money,
you know. So it doesn't matter if it's
£40,50 that's your money that you've
gone to work for and you've you've made
you know but you you've you've never had
a little job have you nons legs a little
part-time job little50 a day in your
pocket so you won't be so skinned and
you might be able to go out more you
I don't do it anymore bro
I'm not saying what I do belly makes money, matey.
[snorts] Yeah, that's that.
But yeah, um what I was saying is
what phone have you got, BQest? I'm
going to get the Fold 8. It should be
coming out July. It comes out every
summer. I'm on the Fold I'm on the Fold
six, so I'm going to get the Fold 8.
I know, mate. When I earned money, bro,
I didn't even want to spend it.
I didn't even want to [ __ ] spend it,
to be fair. Um,
and definitely didn't want to gamble it either. So,
wow. You're rich, mate. Is it? Getting
the newest iPhone.
You're very rich then, aren't you, Mark?
Yeah, you're very rich getting a new iPhone, matey. Nope.
No, I'm not.
How much was it?
>> You're right.
Oh, so it's a contract.
No. So what what have you paid? So what
is it then? You've paid it. You're going
to pay it off in free.
Yeah, maybe. So, what you what is it in?
You've paid it installment.
What? So, you just paid it one off. You
just paid the full price for it.
I don't understand what you mean, bro.
I like hanging around with people,
Bquest, where they think the whole world
is against them.
Where the [ __ ] did you get one grand?
Oh, credit card. Oh, yeah. Nice, bro.
Oh, nice. Yeah. Yeah.
Yeah. I like the fold, bro. But I don't
know if I can justify 17,800 pound for a phone.
I don't know if I can justify that, bro.
I want the fold eight when it comes out,
but I don't know if I can justify it.
H and I don't really want a contract.
So, I'm not sure, bro.
[clears throat] I'm not sure what what
the solution is.
[snorts] Yeah, you you get you get a
grand a month, mate.
8900 is a lot of money for a phone, bro.
Like I said, I'd pay a,000. I'd pay
1,200, but $1,800 for a phone. Really?
You're on a grind a month? Quest?
Nonsense could do a little part-time job.
That larger is [ __ ] skint. He's skint
[ __ ] skid flint. Why not buy it
outright? Because I can't justify £1,800
for a phone.
I can't justify it. Yeah,
I've got to get a phone today. It's
£325. Um, Bar Quest.
Um, it's the one I used to do the Uber
on. It's not It's not a bad phone to be
honest. Obviously, it's not a flagship,
but you know, I've got this flagship
phone, which is blocked, but and I could
just Yeah, it's it's actually a good
phone to be fair. For the price, it is.
Yeah, he could do with some Yeah, he
could do with extra body. Yeah, cuz he's
Cuz he's [ __ ] skinn. He's [ __ ]
skink. He's [ __ ] skink.
He's [ __ ] sky's
is [ __ ] skint.
He's skint [ __ ] skin flint.
He's skint than a [ __ ] skin flint.
>> Yeah, I I have to. Yeah, but I'll need
to buy a phone at some point. Barquest
for when I go traveling. So, the £325
phone is perfect.
Yeah, it's perfect, isn't it? cuz um I
could use this
as my main one and then that but I will
need to at some point but not it's not
not in a hurry but yeah
because obviously I can't you see when I
used to go on dates
uh it never used to affect me because I
would just use the Wi-Fi and say oh meet
me here meet me there the only thing you
can't do is call or text without Wi-Fi
that's the only thing and and in London
obviously there's Wi-Fi everywhere. So,
but obviously say you wanted to travel
or go on a plane, how can you do it,
you you'll have problems with that when
you're trying to travel and that and
like say you stay in a hotel somewhere.
Say for example, you stay in a hotel and
you need to use Google Maps. You can't
So, you know what I mean?
Yeah. But it's not it's not urgent, you know.
You're on a grand a month, Bquest.
You're on £1,000 a month. Bless you. You
want a grand a month? Bless you.
Bless you in life. Bless you.
Well, I need to go to Blackpool. I need
to go to Glasgow.
I still need to go to a couple of places more.
I need to go to two places more. Bro,
you don't get 3K above, you silly goose.
You don't get free, you don't get free
glad a month, you silly goose.
I used to get free glad a month. Um, and
even that wasn't enough.
So, whatever money you get, Bar quest,
you just adjust. You adjust to any money
that you get.
Whether it's a grand, two grand, three
grand, four grand, five grand, no matter
what money you get, you just you would
just adjust to any money you get. So, it
really just never makes a difference
really. Obviously, unless it's £300 a
month, you can't live off 300 pound a
month, but if you had to, you would.
That's what I'm saying, you know.
Yeah. I used to get three grand a month
and used to just go Yeah.
Yeah. Basically, yeah.
These people on here says they say they
can't live on 11,200 a month after bills.
That's ridiculous, bro. They're talking
like £1,200 a month. Yeah. Half the
bills is a small amount of money. Half
the bills. Really? And these people
don't even live in London. Of course you
could live off [ __ ] 1,000 11,200.
Half the bills.
Yeah, that's what I'm saying. Yeah,
these people are idiots. I'd be
surprised if people that work are left
with [ __ ] £1,200.
I'd be I'd be very surprised, bro, if
people that if people have that money um
are people that work have [ __ ] 12,300
disposable each month. I'd be very surprised.
Yeah, I used to get 3k a month, bro.
Um and I never I only had like two
bills, but you just spend more. But the
more you get, the more
the more more you get, the more you spend.
I just don't go out drinking anymore cuz
like I said, all women are the same. So yeah,
pointless. Absolutely pointless, mate.
Bless you, Best. If you've got a little
So you've got a job then, Bar Quest.
You've got a job.
You reckon you could get nons part-time job?
So you reckon you could get nonslegs a part-time job? Why not?
What do you think, Dusty?
Nons's getting a little part-time job.
What do you think? A part-time job. Part-time job.
Oh, he's too disabled.
Well, mate, he needs a little part-time job.
He needs a part-time job, mate. Part-time job. Yeah.
Do you think nonslegs is jealous of me? Um, barrest. [laughter]
What makes you say that bar quest? I've
got a lot of people on here that are
obsessed and jealous of me, bro.
That's just the internet for you, is it?
This Jamie Thompson messaged me um
uh he messaged me uh saying, "This is
how you know these people ain't got a
life." He said,
"Oh, I blocked him." He said,
"Basically, happy new year, um, you
skint." I said, "What have I told you
about calling yourself a skint?"
That's what I reply back with.
I said, "What have I told you about
calling yourself a skint ma? It's not
nice to talk about yourself like that.
It's a new year. You would have thought
these people would have been bred about
talking about themselves.
Yeah, these people talk about
themselves, bro, every day. Yeah.
Yeah. They like to talk about themselves
for some reason.
Little self projectors.
Isn't that right, Barrist? Self projectors.
I put my little camera on B. Look, my
beard's gone quite long. >> [snorts]
>> Sorry, I was just being silly.
>> I was just being silly, Bquest.
>> So, do you reckon if I go out today
drinking and approaching
um I'll land a date? Best
checking out the date.
Why? But people on Reddit say that I will.
Bark rest. People on Reddit say that you
can get sex whenever you want.
So why do people on Reddit say that you
you'll meet someone then?
No. I tell you when I'll try again. If I
try again, I'll try March, April.
That's the only time you seem to be able
to get anything. But I don't I probably
won't even try then to be fair.
Yeah. On Reddit they say that like
dating apps work. They say dating apps
in the summer. I didn't get a date at
all in the summer.
No, I done a lot of approaching in the
summer and I didn't get nothing.
I didn't get [ __ ] all. Let me try and
think. The summer. Yeah, I went out a
lot in the summer. I didn't get nothing.
Not a sausage.
Yeah, I did cuz I was still at the old
house in the summer. I did go out in the
summer quite a bit actually. Nothing.
Not a sausage, mate. I didn't get a [ __ ] all.
No, I definitely didn't. I remember. I
definitely definitely remember last summer.
Well, that's England for you, is it? It
would always be the same here. And you
know the thing that annoys me about it,
Bquest, is the [ __ ] that they come
out with. You're too old for me. You're
too young for me. You're not a Muslim.
It's all toxic. Do you not understand
how toxic it is? I had a friend who was
Muslim. Yeah. And I spent like 5 hours
with her at Bquest and we was walking
talking went to Nando and she's like,
"Oh yeah, um I can't go on a date with
you because uh it wasn't a date because
you're not Muslim." Oh, so I'm not a
Muslim. So I turn around and said, "Oh,
I can I can I can change I can convert
myself to Muslim to see what the next
excuse would be. Oh, I'm not looking for
anyone." Like they lie when we know
they're full of [ __ ]
and then they seem to think that we
don't know that they're full of [ __ ]
Like when we know that they're
bullshitting. Like it's like that
45year-old on Instagram Bar Quest two
weeks ago. She was like, "Oh yeah, I'd
get with you, but we live too far away."
She was 100 She was 100 miles away. Um I
said, and I was thinking to myself,
"Mate, it's Friday night. if I went out
right now, they'd have another excuse
and another excuse and another excuse
and another excuse. And I told her that
and when I told her about that, she
blocked me. They're full of excuses. And
it is that is a trait of narcissism what
they're doing. You do realize that when
they're making these excuses, it's it is
a trait of narcissism. And if you're
smart enough, you'll understand it as
well because what they're doing is
they're trying to lie and blame anything
else but themselves.
that it's hard to explain it, but it is
narcissism. It is narcissism. It's a
trait of narcissism. It is. It is.
They're They're so full of [ __ ] Like I
had one that said, "Oh yeah, you don't
know um enough about Palestine." When
the Palestine [ __ ] was going on. It's all narcissism.
Narcissistic traits if you think about it.
So that's what you get basically. It is
narcissistic because they're trying to
blame something else other than their unrealistic
standards basically because you're not
fat, you're not ugly, there's nothing
wrong with you. So what? You're not
disabled. You haven't not tried. So what
the [ __ ] bro? So yeah, they just um
they are all the same. How people say
they're not all the same. Bar quest, I
shall never know. They are all the same.
They literally are all the same, bro.
Like even when I watch other people
approach, they get the same [ __ ]
they say the same stuff. They act
They're just NPCs. They're non-playing characters.
Nope. Not one person. So yeah.
And then she lied to me as well at Bar
Quest. She said, "Oh yeah, I blocked you
cuz I'm changing my number. Why not just
say that you blocked me? I wouldn't give a fuck."
So it's it is not it is it is narcissistic
and that's how you know that most of
them are narcissists
narcissistic traits anyways we can say
they've got narcissistic traits at the
very least. So
you're too old, you're too young. Um,
the last time I went out,
oh, the last time I went out was
actually with my sister, but the last time was
Yeah. And then they just give their
numbers and then they just lead you on.
They just lead you on, Barress. That's
literally all that ever happens is you
just get led on.
Depressing as [ __ ] bro.
Like when will this [ __ ] ever change?
Bar quest. When will this [ __ ] ever change?
You're going bedroom. Yeah.
Will it ever change barrest? You reckon
I felt better today when I woke up, but
not thinking it was going to ch uh not
change change. Sorry.
>> Nah, it will never change. It will never
People on Reddit say that you can get
dates whenever you want. Why do they say
this stuff on Reddit? Do you think Barquest?
Hey, what have I told you about calling
yourself a virgin? That ain't nice, bro.
It's a new year. It should be new year,
new you. Don't put yourself down, bro.
Don't call yourself a virgin.
It's not nice talking about yourself. Yeah.
Yeah. They must be trolling, bro. It must be.
Do you not think that's [ __ ] up, Bar
Quest? That like straight people can't
get sex when they want. Do you not think
that's kind of like mad?
No, I don't watch that, Virgin.
Um, did you not um
do you not think it's kind of [ __ ] up?
I was in this cinema box cuz I'm
thinking I'm 28 years of age. I
shouldn't have to try again. And that's
what made do you know what? That's what
made me give up.
That's what made me give up. Yeah.
The thing that made me give up is I was
thinking like, "Oh [ __ ] I'm 28. This
shouldn't still be happening. I
shouldn't have to keep trying.
I shouldn't have to keep trying, bro.
That's the way I saw it. So, yeah.
And I just lost the desire to ever try again. Yeah.
I don't know, bro.
It is bad. It is bad. It is really bad.
But I'm I'm thinking of joining the porn
industry. Um, bar quest. I told everyone
on YouTube I'm going to try and join the porn industry.
No joking, bro. No trolling. I'm being
deadly serious. I'm thinking, what else
are you supposed to do?
What else are you really supposed to do, bro?
Go out drinking every week, getting the
same old [ __ ] What the [ __ ] bro? Like, no way.
It's hard to get around. It's hard to
get your um head around how [ __ ] up it is. Yeah.
Bad ain't it, bro?
What would have you done if you had to
deal with women? Barqu quest.
Imagine you had to imagine you was bisexual.
Oh, I lost 100 pound on the FBI. Steven
Howard, I didn't go out yesterday.
I was in my nesticles.
You'd kill yourself.
No, not kill yourself, bro. [ __ ]
Yeah, someone owes me money. One sec. I
lost £100 on the FBI on I lost um money
on the Frankie and the roulette.
Yep. Earlier, bro, I went for spoons breakfast. Don't judge. [sighs]
What a life, eh?
Yeah, I lost 40 on Frankie and 40 on the
route. I got I got the 40 to 140 and
then [ __ ] lost it. I spat all over the machine. Yeah.
I don't know, bro.
You'd actually kill yourself.
Yeah. [snorts] There's no reason I've
not found someone that 28 years of age.
Brother, I don't gamble all the time
and I haven't drunk for ages.
Oh, is that Timmy? Yeah, that's Timmy. That's Timmy.
Oh, hey, Timmy. You are the virgin. I
thought that was that [ __ ] Irish guy
from the other day that join my
hangouts. Oh, Timmy, you are a virgin.
Timmy, you are the virgin.
You are the virgin, lad. The only virgin
is you. So, I don't know why in 2026
you are still calling other people a
virgin when you're a virgin yourself.
You're just like nonslegs. You and
nonslegs have so many similarities.
You both call people virgin when you're
virgins yourself. You both call people
skint when you skint yourselves.
>> Why are you calling people a virgin in 2026,
Timmy? When you're a virgin yourself,
you don't bother anyone. You don't you
don't wind anyone up.
You don't wind anyone up.
You don't wind me up. You just embarrass yourself.
You You You really don't wind me up.
You're just talking about yourself. And
we're addressing why you're talking
about yourself. Timmy, you are the
virgin. You do not wind me up. You are a
virgin. You are legitimately a virgin.
Like I have been seen with multiple
women in women's beds chagging women.
You are an actual virgin.
You are an actual virgin. Like it's not
even about a reaction or reacting. You
actually are a virgin.
That's that's that's the thing. You
You're just like legs. You you you're both virgins.
You and Nonss needs need to get a
part-time job. That's what I think. Mr.
B. Mr. B. I think Nons legs and Timmy
need to get a part-time job.
What do you think?
Just a little part-time job.
Just a little part-time job. I think it
will do him the world of good. Part-time job. text somebody, you know. Yeah.
But yeah, I lost 100 pound on the FB to um
the Steven Hour, bro. I thought it was
going to pay because obviously first of
January, they took enough people's money
in December, but nah, not a sausage. Not
a sausage, mate.
Rig does it all. always be always and forever.
It's bad, bro. It really is bad. Yep. Yeah.
A little part-time job.
Why Chibby? Why did you never call
nonslegs a virgin? I thought you didn't like nonslegs.
How come you never call nonslegs a virgin?
You're not biased, are you? Cuz you call
Monty a virgin. You call me a virgin.
Just wondering to be fair.
I'm just wondering, lad.
Yeah, you can't win money gambling now,
Steven Howard, unless you bet on the
football. There's no other way, bro.
There's no other way.
100 to 140. I spat all over the machine
as well, Steven Howard. I spat all over
it and then just walked out.
Yeah. Bad news. Like bad news.
Yeah, I just walked out, bro.
Dirty. All right, Timmy, join.
All right, Timmy, join. I put a link out.
No, you did not lose 250 yesterday. No,
you did not.
No, you didn't, Timmy. You didn't lose £250.
Oh, yeah. Nons is a virgin.
Nons is definitely a virgin.
He's a virgin and he's got a [ __ ]
one. He's gonna die one.
That's what he's going to do.
He's going to die a virgin.
What do you mean? 250
pennies. That's a lot of money to lose,
isn't it, Bar Quest? £250.
It's a lot of money to lose, isn't it, Barest? Yeah.
Yeah. That's a lot of money to lose. Yeah,
I think so. Yeah.
What? You don't think 250? Okay. What
about 500 bar quest? It's 500.
The most I've ever lost was two grand.
I've lost two grand barest before online.
Yeah, I've lost 2K me.
Yeah, two grand on Roulette online.
Two grand's not a lot of money to lose.
Yeah, it is.
Two grand is a lot of money to lose.
What? Two grand? Losing two grand? Yes,
it [ __ ] is. What the [ __ ] bro?
That's a lot of money to lose, bro.
Oh, you Oh, you haven't lost a lot, you
said. Yeah. No, 2K is 2K is a lot to lose.
What about 600? Is that a lot to lose? Bar quest.
600 is a lot to lose, isn't it? Yeah.
If 2K is nothing, I'll send you my bank
details and you can give me two grand. I was flame.
If two grand is nothing, I'll send you
my [ __ ] bank details right now.
Send it through.
I didn't go out New Year's. It's
overrated and overpriced.
Irish, give me two grand
if it's nothing.
I don't know how these people come on
here and talk like they're millionaires.
You never get anyone in the real world
talk like this. You know that. Uh Bar Quest,
you never get anyone say that. Like two
grand's nothing. No one says that in
real life. Only on this community. You
do realize that
they're all millionaires on this community.
They're all millionaires.
Yeah, they're all millionaires on this community.
You don't have 378 grand, you silly goose.
You don't have that amount of money.
You don't have 378 grand. It's like L.
He's skint. He pretends he's got money,
but really he's skint. Did you see his
fake watch? Steven Howard.
I don't get these pretenders on here.
Like L saying, "Oh, I own six
properties." And the guy is absolutely skint.
And he and he pretends that he's got
money. He's absolutely skint. I don't
know why he acts like he's got money
when he doesn't.
Same with nons legs. They're absolutely skint.
Like they really are skint.
And that's what you call [ __ ] scenes, bro.
Grezy, I'm going to get some D. I'm
going to get some digestive biscuits. Grezy,
I found you some digestive biscuits. Grezy.
[sighs and gasps]
What do you think about that?
I've got no confidence. I've got more
confidence than you would ever have.
Not one of this per not anyone of this community, right?
Not one person in this community can
approach women sober but me. Not one person.
No. No. No. No. No. No. That's
definitely definitely you.
Okay. Greasy. Grievy.
Okay. I I like Okay, Grezy. I like Shville Cole.
I like Shevil Cole. Grezy.
Yeah, I like Shrezy.
How's about that?
I've got approaching videos on my other
channel. I've got them on my other
channel, Bar Quest. I don't put them on this channel
cuz I don't want these people seeing it.
What do you think of that, Grezy?
What do you think I am, Grezy?
What do you think of me?
A big stinking coffee. [laughter] Oh wow.
So what do you think of Fruit King,
Grezy? Because he was talking about
Chevel Cole the other day. What do you
think of Fruit King? He said that Shel
Cole was fit we
so what's your opinion on Fruit King? He
was talking about Sher Cole the other
day. We caught him. [laughter]
So what's your opinion on him? [laughter]
[clears throat and laughter]
I love Grezy. It's good to have you back, Grezy. [laughter]
O Grey, do you remember um Ben Fury's comment?
Same people, same story. See you next year. [laughter]
Do you remember that, Grezy? Same
people, same story.
Oh, look. He says that she's hot.
Grievy, have you got anything to say about that?
Have you got anything to say about that?
I admit I think Shelar was hot Grezy.
Blah. Yeah, you said that she's hot. Grezy,
you got any opinion on that?
Literally, money and sex is everything.
Money and sex is everything
in my opinion.
Yeah, but you didn't Yeah, but you
didn't say anything after he had said
that. Fruit King, he commented after you
had said that. He said, "I admit I think
Chevulo was hot." Yeah, but you didn't
say anything after he had said that.
He just said that now.
So, yeah. [snorts] Uh, money and sex is
everything. Rezy, if you think about it. [laughter]
Yeah, he's a copycat. Fruit King is a [laughter]
He's a little copycat.
He's copying. He's copying. [laughter]
Yeah. That trend's been going [ __ ]
donkeys. Yeah, they mention it on the
inbetweeners as well.
O bar quest. Sex and money is everything.
Same people, same story.
Yeah, I'm I'm not I'm not going to be
live after this, Grezy. I'm going to not
be live for a while. I Do you know what?
After this, I probably won't be live
until next year, to be honest.
What's the point if it's just the same people,
you know? What's the point of being on a
community when it's just the same people every day?
It's pointless. It's just the same [ __ ] people,
you know? Yeah, but what's the point if
it's just the same people, Grezy?
[clears throat] Huh? Yeah.
True King's talking about Cole again, Grezy.
He's talking about She car again.
That Sher Co was [ __ ] ugly. And I I
can say she's ugly. And I can say to
non-legs, I've had more women than you.
I've had sex more times than you would
ever have. You skinton. And I'm telling
you, she's [ __ ] ugly. A gay. A gay. A
gay. You don't like shovel. You're gay.
Hi man. Homo Mike. Gay homo.
Yeah. What you say? Homo. Grezy.
A new copycat statement has been made.
It was actually made last week, but you
hadn't come on YouTube. But yeah,
there's a new copycat statement that's been made. >> [laughter]
>> A new copycat statement. [laughter]
Oh, that's nice for him. I don't go on
his channel. I don't go on Skinn Virgin's channels.
[gasps] I don't entertain skin virgins.
Yeah, I don't entertain skinned virgins
has never had their leg over. Sorry,
mate. Sorry mate. I already went to the
bookies earlier. I lost £100, Mr. B. I
spat all over the machine. Oh, I lost
£100 earlier, Greavvesy, in the bookies
machine and I spat on the machine and walked out. Yeah,
I made a scene.
Yeah, I made a scene. >> [snorts]
>> You're laughing, but uh who who's
better, Dusty, USA, Izzy, or Sarah?
I thought I thought um Greavvesy that
you know because the machines have took
a lot of money over Christmas,
right? I thought that I would have won
today cuz you know December they're on
the take because of Christmas and that, you know, um
uh because of Christmas and stuff, isn't it?
So I thought, you know, obviously being
the first, you know, day of the new year
that it would have paid something. It
was logical thinking, wasn't it? I
thought anyways, but no, it weren't
having it for toffee, mate. Weren't
having it for nothing. You weren't
having it at all, mate. You might as
well just gave thatund£100.
You might as well just gave that 100 to
a [ __ ] homeless person.
Yeah. Do you remember when he was
messaging USA? Is he
do you remember when he was messaging
USA is he um barrist knowing that he was
going to get an answer that he wanted
the [ __ ] skint virgin anything to
make himself feel better about the fact
he got rejected by Britney and she
didn't want him. You literally messaged
them knowing that you was going to get
the answer that you want cuz I had an
argument with them. You creepy skinned
virgin. He was trying to get wack
material. He was trying to get work
material cuz he don't have a sex life
because he's a skin virgin.
[ __ ] hell. You know, because he's a
skin [ __ ] He's never put his dick up
nothing. The ugly [ __ ]
Yeah, man. The worst mistake of my life
was meeting that [ __ ]
Seriously, he used to call me a virgin
when he's the [ __ ] biggest one going.
He's the biggest virgin himself.
call to be a virgin when you're
literally a virgin yourself, you skint
lanky [ __ ] Oh, I wish you would meet me
now, bro. I'd say that you're nothing
but a skint lanky virgin. And I put the
video up and show your f and I say, "I
don't care about a disabled girl. You're
a [ __ ] skint virgin that's never been
inside her because the police would have
been [ __ ] called if you [ __ ] did,
son. You're not allowed nowhere near
disabled women sexually. You and I know
that, man. [ __ ] hell.
Yeah, you got a big nose. I didn't know that, lad.
I didn't know that you got a big nose.
It's [snorts] not nice to to to say that
about yourself. You got a big nose. Yeah, [snorts] that's repeating, isn't it,
B? That's repeating, lad. um
mom they are jealous of me.
No, my mom says that you people are
jealous of me. No, no, no. She actually
says that you are jealous. You people
Um, yeah. She actually says that you are
jealous, but she's just sick of
repeating it. No, no, no, no, no. Even
my friend says that you people in here
were jealous. My friend, when I went out
last drinking, he said, "These are fat,
ugly people. They are jealous of you.
You go out drinking in Liverpool Street.
These people are fat, ugly people sat on
the internet." That's what he actually
told me. That's what my friend told me.
No, no, no. Laney has definitely said
that you people are jealous. She's just
sick of repeating the same [ __ ] to be honest.
See, and other people have definitely
said that you uh you haters are jealous.
Yeah. Okay. Okay. Okay. Let let me give
you this example, right? Look at Jamie
Thompson and then look at me.
Okay. Okay. Okay. Jamie Thompson and then me.
Look at him and then look at me.
Yeah. Just just just compare the two.
You know, fat Peter Griffin, double
chin, no family, no life, sat on the
internet stalking every day. Look at him
and then look at me.
You know, just look look at Nod's legs
and then look at me. No teeth, still a
virgin, you know. Would die a virgin,
could only date disabled, you know. Look
at these people and then look at me.
Look at me, mate.
>> Okay, I need to go in a bit.
got to go now. Yeah, because um I need
to um yeah, go and have this roast
there. So, I'll be back. Yeah, later.
But after today, I won't be live for
another year because it's the same
people. It's the same repeating people. [laughter]
It's the same repeating people. All
right, catch you later.