Oh,
this is my last live stream.
Look at that. a lot.
I don't feel that good. Lovely can.
Oh, did it?
Oh, bless you then if you're a bit lost.
But no, I'm This is my last live stream,
bro, cuz I don't want to be on YouTube this year.
I want to spend time with Laney and
stuff. And yeah, it's the same people.
There's no mix up. It's the
[clears throat] same people every day.
There's no point being on if it's just
the same people every day, you know,
the same people that be like
and fruit a little copycat.
All right, fruit king's a little copycat.
He's got no mind. [snorts]
I'm actually speaking to some guy in
Belgium. He's a cool guy
who says that the dating scene is much
easier in Belgium.
I showed him my experiences and he said
that's [ __ ] up. I told him I went to
Belgium before a few years ago, but I
didn't try to date in there. I only done
one cold approach. And he says that
you'd have more luck in uh in Belgium.
Yeah, probably would to be fair. Even if
it took a couple of months. Yeah.
I Belgium like three four No, not three.
Must be like four years ago.
I went to Belgium four years ago. [clears throat]
Yeah, man. He's a cool guy.
What do you prefer,
Belgium or Netherlands?
Yep. Four, four years ago I went
I was 20
maybe five years ago.
No, just having some crisps.
No, I went in March 2022.
Yeah. So basically four years ago.
And I went to [ __ ] Netherlands and
then a [ __ ] skint virgin copy my [ __ ] holiday.
I'm surprised you didn't go Belgium cuz
I went, you know,
[ __ ] copy of my [ __ ] holidays.
Obviously, it took him a couple of years
after because obviously he couldn't
afford it cuz he's [ __ ] skinned. But
you know, I [ __ ] who would have
thought that you could go on holiday, right?
and not have someone copy you.
Yeah, I went Belgium all by myself. I
went Netherlands by myself as well. Yeah,
I think I fit in better in Belgium than
multicultural people like me.
Oh, this is nice. These chicken
sensations, you can't beat them.
You ever had chicken sensations, [snorts]
mate? He's [ __ ] sk. He's skint
[ __ ] skint flint. That's his daddy's
life savings. I've told you this
already. It's his daddy's life savings, mate.
You also wouldn't be living in a bedset
if you had 13 grand. You would be
shopping in a charity shop. Well, weird.
You ever had chicken sensations?
Oh, that's lush. Nice hand coke. Don't
worry, I brush my teeth. Every time I
drink Coke and eat, I brush my teeth
so I don't get two fakes.
Um, I don't have any plans.
I'm coming off here 100%. I'm coming off here.
I'm not wasting another year on this [ __ ]
Maybe I'll come on to odd time to say hi.
Yeah, once once in a while, but I'm not
wasting my time on here.
[ __ ] that, bro. I don't need to be on
there. I'm not fat. I'm not disabled.
I'm not ugly like Jamie Thompson. I
don't need to be on here, bro. I'll come
and say hi time, but I'll still go live
now and then, but I'm not I'm not
wasting all day every day on it, you know? Yeah.
Feb the ver Mr. B the virgin is still
going at it. What a [ __ ] Yeah. Yeah.
Skimp boy punched a your skint yourself
virgin boy. You're the one showing
daddy's life savings. Punch the f
machine because it isn't a full grown
man who can punch back weak little man.
Perfect start to the year. What a
disabled economy spell. Ugly womenless
incel. What the [ __ ] bro?
Bro, this is 2026, brother.
Mr. B, this is 2026.
You do realize this is 2026. We're not
doing this again, bro. This whole year,
we're not doing this again.
We're not doing this again, bro. This is
2026, lad. We're not doing this again.
We've wasted enough years arguing with
these disabled, ugly, jealous people and
it is 2026 and we're not doing it
another year. You can get [ __ ]
I'm not even responding to that. Uh, no,
I didn't go out. Bro, it's 2026.
And I thought it was going to be different people.
Different people, different [ __ ]
These people told me they were smart.
Mr. Be. Yeah. So, I am leaving, but I
will be live like sometimes
cuz it's just it's just pointless. Yeah, bro.
I didn't go out yesterday, Bob. Bills,
why would I be going out?
You should learn to listen and listen to
learn. Why would I be going out?
For what reason, bro?
I don't need to go out.
Bad trainers, huh?
Who's got bad traders?
What the [ __ ] are you all about?
I don't give a [ __ ] if it's a new year, bro.
New Year's Eve is New Year's Eve is mud.
I'm speaking to a black guy from Belgium, Joe.
We're talking about the dating scene.
Yeah. He's got this life, yet he's
continuously stalking me every day.
Yeah. That Jamie Thompson's got this
perfect life. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. He's sat
there stalking me every day on Reddit.
Okay, bro. Make it make sense.
Yeah. Yeah. I'm sat here eating crisps.
I had a roast dinner earlier. Yeah.
Yeah. He's got this perfect life yet
he's sat here stalking every day. Make
it make sense. And that guy is an actual
stalker as well. That Jamie Thompson is
an actual jealous stalker. He No, he
actually is a stalker.
Yeah, jealous stalker with no life. And
we can actually say he's fat and ugly as
well cuz he's actually showing his face.
So yeah, he's actually brave showing his
face, you know, bro. My trainers are
bad. What? My 210 pound trainers?
Why am I bothered about what, bro? Huh?
I'm coming off of it, guys.
My trainers are 210. Bro, what you about?
My trainers are lovely.
That Jamie Thompson has got no life but
stalk him. That is that is an actual fact.
He's got no life but stalk him.
No life. No life outside of stalking.
I do hate women though.
Why are you talking about that?
No, I'm just talking to this guy in
Belgium. We're talking about the dating
game and that. He said he can't believe
it. He said I should come to Belgium and
try and I said I've been to Belgium before.
Have you ever Have you ever been to
Belgium, Joe? Have you ever been to
Belgium? Have you ever been to Amsterdam?
Oh, we were just talking about it.
Oh, I have given up. But we were just
talking about it.
Yeah, he's enjoying his life stalking
me. Yeah. Okay, man.
Yeah, I was wrong about the name cuz we
were talking about it.
Me and this guy in Belgium.
He's black. I I just called him a
Belgian LT. I don't know why I called
him a Belgian Belgian LT. Yeah.
I called him Belgian LT. I don't know
why. That's just his nickname
cuz he's back in it. So,
you haven't been to Amsterdam.
You haven't been to Amsterdam, buddy?
Nongs has been to Amsterdam, but he just
went cuz I went.
Yeah, he just went cuz I went.
Yeah, he's a copycat.
I don't know if you went, but yeah,
but I'm I'm actually coming off a video.
I'll just be live if and when. I will
actually be live um if and when.
Yeah. Do you know why it was crap? Yeah,
I can tell you why it was crap.
I can tell you why that was crap. I
mean, Amsterdam is overrated anyways,
but I can actually tell you why it was crap.
But yeah, Amsterdam is overrated. But I
can tell you why it was crap. It's
because you went with the school. It's
pointless go with the school. You can't
do your own thing. You have to stay with
them. It's crap. There's no there's no
point going on a trip with the school.
The the the school used to go I don't
know why you went to Amsterdam with a
school. Normally they're going to Paris.
They took you to Amsterdam with the school. Really?
What the [ __ ] I didn't know they they
they I know they take you to Paris. They
take you to Paris with the school. Um
I didn't know they they take kids to
Amsterdam. I've never heard of that. But
yeah, anyways, because you were with the school,
>> I don't have any I don't have interest
in weed, but I still smoked and [ __ ]
prostitutes when I was there. >> Yeah.
That's why I'm surprised the skin virgin
went. If he really wasn't Yeah, I did. I smoked. Yeah.
Wow. That's interesting because I've
never heard a school taking kids to a
trip to Amsterdam.
I was all up. No, I wasn't. I've never
liked Autumn. I think I said, "Oh, can
you be my mama?" as a joke. No,
definitely. That definitely was not me.
No, that definitely definitely wasn't
me. I've never sed over any woman,
especially on this community.
Definitely definitely definitely not me.
You've got me mixed up with LT and Money
Mike. They were the only ones sing over
her. That's definitely definitely not me, mate.
Definitely definitely definitely not me.
See you later. Anyways, so basically
Amsterdam is more than is Amsterdam more
more than prostitutes and weed. Well,
actually it's if you wanted more than
prostitutes and weed, there's actually
better places in the Netherlands that's
not Amsterdam. Like Rotterdam, I mean,
if you don't want to do prostitutes and
weed, there's better places in the
Netherlands than Amsterdam. Rotam is
better than Amsterdam.
Rotam is better than Amsterdam.
So, I mean, yeah, but I mean, if you're
not doing any of them two things,
there's an an actual better place to go
to, which is called Rotterdam.
You do realize that nonslegs went to
Amsterdam because I went to Amsterdam.
He's a copycat
because there's other places in the
Netherlands that's not Amsterdam. So,
uh, it's nice. It's nicer than
Amsterdam. It is nicer than Amsterdam.
See, people only think of Amsterdam
because it's the capital and that's
where people go. Netherlands is a nice
country and Amsterdam is not the is not
the um is not the best place to go, but
obviously it's it's the it's the
capital. So that's why people go there
obviously, but but yeah, I mean it's not
prostitutes and weed, but that is mainly
people that go in there mainly do one of them things, you know.
as in like why would you go to Amsterdam
if you don't do any of them two things?
Why would you go there? You never went.
You didn't. You went with the school.
You didn't choose to go. You'd go somewhere else.
I'm better than Amsterdam.
Um when I went to Amsterdam, why did I?
Because I smoked weed and [ __ ] prostitutes. [laughter]
When I went, I [ __ ] prostitutes and I smoked weed.
That's why I went there. Oh, Rotterdam.
Oh, because I was going through it.
Oh, Ram. I was going through it. That's
why I was going through it. So, I went
through it. That's how That's how I know
what it's like. Yeah. No,
I smoked weed when I was in Amsterdam
and I [ __ ] prostitutes.
I [ __ ] two prostitutes and I smoked weed.
It was a good experience, you know.
Amsterdam was a good experience.
It was staying in a hostel was a good experience.
I still talk to this guy to this day who
I met at a hostel. Yeah. So
why would you go Amsterdam if you don't
smoke weed and [ __ ] prostitutes?
No. But it's nicer. It's nicer. It's
nicer. Rotten is nicer than Amsterdam.
Nons went because I went. Joseph, he
went to Amsterdam because I went. He
wanted to copy me cuz he's a little copycat.
I have never ever known anyone else to
go to Amsterdam the first time they went
abroad. Never. Never ever ever ever in my life. So yeah.
Yeah, it was a good experience. Me
[ __ ] the escort was a good
experience. Me smoking weed was a good
experience. Me going me going on the
ferry was a good experience. Me going to
the steakhouse was was a good
experience. I went to a steakhouse when
I was there.
That was a good experience.
The weed. Yeah, that was a very good experience. No.
Well, you're bad. Bye-bye, idiots. Uh
yeah, it was good. It was good. And I
went all by myself
because I don't need to go back. That's why
I don't know why they would take kids to
Amsterdam on a school trip. That is weird.
I didn't even know they done that.
Never been a s in my life.
Never ever have I been a s in my life.
Never have. Never will. S have got low
IQ. Ss have got low IQ. Yeah.
A lot of simps I think have got autism personally. Yeah.
Yeah. The the the school went um to
Paris, but I don't know.
I've never been Paris. Okay. Put it this
way, Joe. Right. If not if Nons wasn't
copying me, you would pick somewhere
like Paris. You know, the city of love.
the city of love. You would go somewhere
like Paris, you wouldn't go to
Amsterdam. That is copying. I'm not
trolling by saying it. That is that is
being a little copycat.
All I'm saying is that's being a little copycat.
No, I don't care players. I literally do
not give a [ __ ] Yeah. Oh yeah,
you would go somewhere like Paris,
surely Joseph Ferrar, you'd go Paris.
I didn't go with the school. I went to
museums with the school and I went um
I think it was like camping. I went
camping with the school and I went to museums
Yeah, they do trips abroad, but I didn't
go. They went, but I didn't go. I can't
remember why I didn't go, but I didn't go. Nope.
I'm not going that approaching. I give up.
I can't remember the reason. I can't actually remember.
There was a reason. I can't remember.
I can't remember to be fair what the
reason was, but I know they did go to Paris. Um,
but they they went to Paris by coach.
They used to go to Paris by coach, which
never made sense to me why they didn't
they didn't just get the Euro store.
They get enough [ __ ] money. The
schools get enough money. So why why put
a kid on a on a coach before all of them
hours when you can just go buy a Euro
store? Never made sense to me. But yeah,
I can't remember the reason. [snorts]
So they get a coach to go to France for
the day and then come back. What's the
point of that to me? That that just
doesn't make any sense to be honest cuz
the Euro store is like 2 hours.
[ __ ] They could even fly the kids there. Really? Yeah.
That doesn't make sense. I think it's
like four or five hours on the coach in it.
I'm such an idiot. Thank you. [snorts]
I get really bad travel sickness.
Really bad travel sickness. I do in
cars. It only happens in cars. It don't
happen on trains. It doesn't happen.
Well, it happens in on coaches as well.
But that's not the reason I didn't go.
Um I can't remember the reason. This was
when I was like 12.
Hey bro, I get proper travel sickness
and cars and coaches. Not trains.
I don't get them on trains
or obviously the plane, but I get them
on um in cars, coaches.
It's weird as [ __ ] bro. It's like my
stomach just goes.
I've always had it. I don't know why.
Yeah, bro. When you get a full-time job,
you can start telling other people to
get a full-time job.
Isn't that right, Joseph?
Yeah, bro. It is time for you to get a
full-time job and get off of YouTube.
Right back at you, bro. Right back at
you. But yeah, um
I don't know why I didn't go off. Yeah.
Oh, I gambled today. Joseph, did you
hear? I lost £100.
Spat all over the machine.
But you probably heard anyways.
Only you could continuously win, lad.
Only you can continuously keep winning,
mate. No one else.
No one else, mate.
I lost 100. I lost 60 on Frankie and 40
on the roulette. I got it to 140 and
then I just lost it. You know Timmy's
video of the global draw roulette when
he got £141 and lost it. That was
basically the same as me. It just wasn't
having it at all. Just missed
everything. Couldn't get a spin. When
you do get a [ __ ] spin, it misses.
It's [ __ ] bro.
I was only trying to win like 150.
It was basically the same as Timmy's
video. You It's just the same old [ __ ]
You can't get a bonus.
I would have been happy with £150. I
didn't even need I don't need £150, but
if I had won 150, I'd consider myself a
lucky [ __ ] bro. It's so hard to
win now. It's so hard to win any amount
of money now on on them [ __ ] machines
that I would be happy. But nah,
it wasn't having none of it, mate.
You don't need to know what it's from. I
lost 100. I put £100 in the machine.
I put £100 in the machine and I put 40
on I played it down to 40 on Frankie and
then I played the roulette with the rest
of the 40. You can't even get a [ __ ]
bonus on the [ __ ] thing.
He wasn't having none of it, mate.
Nope. It wasn't that at all, mate.
But you keep thinking that anyways, bro.
You don't know how much money I have
and I like it that way. So yeah,
but yeah. Anyways, the point is and I
got it to 140 Joe on the roulette. So 40
pound up. I lost it all. I lost most of
it trying to get the trying to get a
next spin and I just spat all over the
machine and walked out.
I punched it and then I spat on it. I
hurt my [ __ ] hand as well. It's not
good, bro. Can't even [ __ ] win on the bastards. Why?
You can't win.
I didn't even get a [ __ ] bonus.
That roulette is so annoying, bro. I
think if I continued on the slots, I
think I just would have walked out. It's
that [ __ ] roulette is annoying, bro.
I was playing the global draw roulette.
God, it is so [ __ ] annoying.
And the green was on 40% and it kept missing.
[ __ ] bro. [ __ ] Yeah.
So, would you continuously would you
continue to gamble online, Joe, if you
wasn't trying for a mortgage?
Would you continue trying to
Would you would you continue gambling online?
Nope. You don't know anything, bro.
You don't know anything.
You really don't know anything, bro.
But keep thinking you do, bro. I'm not
going to argue with you.
Bro, you keep telling yourself that, brother.
You keep telling yourself that. I know I
have money. I know I can do whatever I
want, but you keep telling yourself
that, bro. If that helps you sleep at
night, then that helps you sleep at night.
If you think I'm living in poverty,
that's on you, bro.
You don't know what side hustles I have.
You don't know how much money I got
yesterday. You don't know anything.
[snorts] So that's why I don't block
you. I let you think cuz you really
don't know anything.
You really don't know anything, bro. You
don't know how much money I have right
now. You don't know what side hustles I
have. You don't know what I'm getting my
hands into. You don't know nothing.
So that's why I just let you carry on,
you know. I just let you uh continue
saying what you're saying, bro, cuz you
don't know nothing. Yeah.
You don't know nothing and you never
will know nothing.
But yeah, I'll tell you now for the last time. £1,200.
is what is more than what most people
are left with after they pay their bills.
So, I mean, most people not even left
with £1,200 after they pay their bills,
after they work. So, that's not even poverty anyways.
So, you don't need to know anyways what
what I have.
Oh my god, this [ __ ] is so boring. How
many accounts have you made?
So yeah, man.
I'm not like L. That L, he doesn't even
get a grand a month. He was
He does not even get £1,000 a month.
That L J is [ __ ] skint, bro.
Oh, he actually is. He is actually skint
and non legs. They are absolutely [ __ ] skint.
They have not got a pot to piss him, bro.
L don't even have a grand to his name,
let alone get a grand a [ __ ] month. Yeah,
bro. If you don't know anything, you
don't know how much money I have.
You don't know how much money I have and
you will never know. That's for me to
know and you to never know. You
But your boyfriend L J is definitely
definitely definitely ski. Only a skimp
person would beg money online.
Beg for money online. He is he is definitely skinn.
He ain't got a pot to piss him, bro.
Believe you me, do not believe a word he
says. Oh, I own property. You want
benefits. You don't even get a grand a
month. You skint
just like nunchs. You are skint
skint and boring.
My wardrobe is worth more than a whole
year of his income. That's how sad it
is, you know. So, yeah. Yeah,
brother. Listen, listen. Nons doesn't
have independence. He lives in a shitty
bedsit with no bed and no money in it.
That's not independence. That's sponging
off the system. Does he go to work and
pay rent? Okay. Okay. Okay. Independent.
Does he go to work and pay rent? You know,
does he does he does he go to work and
pay rent? No, he doesn't. So, he's not independent.
And LJ is absolutely [ __ ] skint. It's
not even a joke.
I'm not independent.
Has he ever worked?
Has he ever worked? I've worked.
It doesn't matter if he lives on on his
own. He got given a bed sick from the council.
Yeah, brother. That's not independence.
Independence is is literally going to
work and paying for your own [ __ ] You
live in a shitty bedsit. I would rather
live with my mom than live in a shitty
council bedsit that he lives in. And I
say this to him all the time. He says to
me, "You live with your mommy?" I said I
would rather live with my mommy than
live in that shitty council beds it. And
no matter how many that shitty cancel
trampy [ __ ] hole that you live in, you
know, at least when I was [ __ ] He
seems to think Yeah. living in a council
shitty bedsit is better than living with
your mom. I'd rather live with my mom,
you know, than living in that shitty
bedsit with no bed in it. that trampol.
I'd rather live with my mommy in a
house. I own it, bro. I own it. I would
rather live with my mom than live in
that shitty bedset. I've never ever ever
never I've never ever denied it. Ever. So, yeah.
I've never ever denied it. Never. I
don't know why he uses an insult. Yeah.
Well, you have now. You [ __ ] have now, mate.
You have now, [clears throat]
bro. Living in a council shitty bedsit
is is not independent.
Getting given a council bedsit, that's
not independence. When you work and you
make your own money, come back to me.
when he works and he makes his own
money. Come back to me about independence.
Yeah. I'll tell you what independence
is. When I used to go to the gym and I
used to work and I used to make my own
money. Yeah. Living in a shitty bedsit.
That's not independence. Go back when
you make your own money.
No, it isn't. Oh, no it isn't. Oh, no it
isn't. No, it is not. Living with one
parent. Living with one parent, right?
That is not better than living in a
shitty bedsit. Imagine taking a woman
back to a bedsit. Imagine meeting
someone, right? Well, while I am making
sense, imagine meeting a woman and
taking her back to a bedsit. A shitty
cancelled bedsit. They'd run a mile. I'd
rather take him back to my mom's.
Brother, it's not independent. Listen,
anybody can live in a cancel shitty
bedit, brother. Listen, when you work
and you pay your own bills for money
that you've earned, come back to me.
Yeah. Sponging off the system is not independent.
That is literally not independent.
Sponging off the system in a shitty
council beds it is not better than
someone living with their mom. And and
I'm saying that to you right now. I am
making absolute sense. sponging off the
system living in a shitty cancel bed is
not one up on someone living with their mother.
Literally, that is not some what if you
if you do that, that's fine. Like, you
can do what you want. Like, you can live
where you want. You can do what you
want, brother. But don't think you're
better than someone living with their
mom when you live in a shitty bedsit,
right? You're living off benefits and
you don't work. You are in no [ __ ]
right to try to [ __ ] talk about
anyone else. You know, nothing wrong
with living with your mom. There's
literally nothing wrong with living with your mom.
Cuz put it this way. Yeah, Dusty. Put it
this way. If the council If the council
Yeah. did not give him a bedit, where
would he be?
Where would he be, bro? He'd be with his daddy.
He literally would be with his daddy. If
the c okay let's just say that the
council didn't give him that bedset he
would be living with his daddy. Do you
not understand? He would be living with
his daddy. He would not be living by
himself. He would be living with his dad
not his mother because uh well he's his
mama hates him. But he would be living
with his daddy. Would he not? Where
would he be living? He'd be living with his daddy.
They would be living with his [ __ ] daddy. Yeah.
He'd be living with his dad. He wouldn't
be living by himself.
He be living with his daddy.
Yeah. It's I'm not having the same
argument anyways. Yeah. Bro, you make a good
Bob. Listen, this is why I'm coming off
of here, brother. This is why I'm not
going to be on it much because it's
always the same argument. It's always
the same [ __ ] with these little lowife people.
I'm done with them anyways, but I
already said I'm not going to be on here much.
Yeah. Why am I even arguing with biased
people? What the [ __ ] What sense does
that even make? You make a good point.
It is literally the same argument.
It's boring. It's childish. It's just
the same old repeating.
Like I said, I'll be on once in a while,
bro. I don't mind coming on once in a
while to see Grievy and that, bro. But
yeah, no one cares if he's got his own
place. I'm not having the same argument.
We've had the same argument before, like
what Bill just said. It's the same argument.
It's like what my mama said. Why are you
arguing with people on the internet that
you don't know?
Why are you arguing with people on the
internet that you don't know? Like, I
saw a few community posts today. I
didn't even respond to it because it's
just the same old repeating [ __ ] And to
think of it, bro, if these people
actually had a life, they would still be
doing this. This is 2026.
This is literally 2026 and they're still
doing this. So, they'll be doing it on
this. They'll be doing it by themselves.
And I had a long think about this as
well. I'm not having the same conversation. So,
if these people want to be low lives in
the year 2026 again, they can they can
do that. That's that's you know what I mean. Yeah.
And that's me here. All I got to say, bro. So yeah,
it's boring as [ __ ] is it, bro?
Boring as [ __ ]
And good for him if he's got his own
place. I'd rather live with my mom than
to live in a shitty bed suit. That's the
last I'm saying about it. Yeah,
that's the last I'm saying about that.
Same old repeating in it, bro. Yeah.
Joe's telling me that I live under
poverty even though I've got more money
than him, which I've stated multiple
times. I've got more money than him. And
he's still telling me that I live under
poverty when this guy has less money
than me. That's another same argument.
Same argument, same boring people. Yeah. Yeah.
Uh I'm not 27. you might want to get my
age right. And we're not having the same
argument anyways, bro. You're talking to yourself. And
you people are lower than me, bro. You
pe you, Do you know the funny thing
about this bill yet is all of these
people that are hating you are in a
worse position in life than you are?
That's the bit that makes it funny.
That's the bit that makes the whole
thing just laughable is that there these
people that are hating on you are worse
than you. And I mean in every way.
They're older than you. They're uglier.
They're uglier than you. They're skint.
They got no friends. Like all of these
people that are doing this are worse than you.
That's the thing that's so [ __ ] up about it.
Like I said, bro, earlier, I don't know
if you was on here, but you go on a L
day live stream and you're thinking, "Wait,
hold on. These people are saying that
I'm skinn. These people are saying that
I've got no life. These people saying
that I've got no friends, but they're
sat there talking to each other all day
on YouTube. These can't be the same
people that are judging me." No, no, no,
no, no. So, it's weird because they're
trying to judge you, but they're worse than you.
They are literally worse than you. and
they're trying to judge you.
So that's what makes it just just hilarious really.
They don't trigger me. I'm stating a
fact. They don't trigger me. I'm stating facts.
And it's not even like that. They don't
trigger me. I'm just stating facts. It's
not even like they're on here just doing
this like they're actually doing this.
They're worse than you and then they're
judging you. Like you you want to make
it make sense.
And you will see them, Bob, just type to
each other all day.
You will sit there. You you go on large
days and they will talk to each other
all day long
and you're thinking, "Wait, where's
their money? Where's their friends?
Where's their life?" You understand? It
doesn't make sense. You understand,
brother? You people laugh at yourselves.
You don't laugh at me, you laugh at
yourselves. That's what you people do.
You laugh at yourselves. You live a
worse life than anyone. So, at the end
of the day, bro, you pe Okay, the people
Okay, so you're saying to me that people
laugh at me from the L J channel, but
the people on the L J channel haven't
got any friends. The people on the L J
channel haven't got any money and
they've got no life. So, how could they
laugh at anyone when they're worse than everyone else?
Make it make sense cuz I know that's a
fake. That's the That's the thing. You
are living your worst lives. Your worst
lives. And you're saying that you laugh
at me. Make it make sense.
You really, really, really need to make
it make sense as it's your favorite
word. I've seen you on L I've seen
people on LJ's and they've been on there
all day. All day typing to each other.
Make it make sense. You know,
make it make sense. That's it.
You know, think of it, Joe. I'm younger
than you. I'm better looking than you. I
got more money than you. Nons legs. I'm
younger than him. Better looking than
him. I've got more money than him. We
can go on and on and on and on and on
and on and on and on and on. It's not
going to change anything. You know,
you show fake wins. You know, people
have clocked on to your [ __ ] I clocked
on ages ago what you was doing with them
fake wins. And before you try and say
that I'm jealous, again, I'm younger
than you. I'm better looking than you
and I got more money than you. So before
you want to try and say that I'm jealous
for calling you out on your [ __ ]
fake wins, um, just bear that in mind.
Please bear that in mind.
You are full of [ __ ]
You are absolutely full of [ __ ]
And that's what you are. You're just
you're just a lavy mold rubber. Really?
Come on now,
mate. Listen, I am done with these
people, Dusty. We're not doing this all year.
We're not We're not doing this, bro.
We're not doing this for another year of
this. I meant it. I meant what I said.
We're not doing this.
Well, I don't know about we, but I'm not
doing this. So, yeah. I'm not doing
this, bro. I'm not doing this back and
forth regurgitated [ __ ] You know, at
the end of the day, I should have
learned a long time ago. Look, Ant-Man's
not on here. He He knows what they're
like. Monty man's not even on here. So,
like I said, I'll come on occasionally
and that's it.
Cuz you know the maddest thing, Dusty?
Yeah. You could spend the whole You
could spend the whole of this year.
Yeah. going back and forth with these
people, uh, trying to meet these people,
showing them money, doing this, that,
this, that, and then you've just wasted
another year with nothing.
You are literally just waste, you've
just wasted another year arguing with
biased autistic spastics
and you would have just wasted another
year again, [snorts]
you know, and that's and that's
literally what happened. It will
literally be no different and that's it. Uh,
what about me? Well, I don't I don't
date disabled women. So, and he's not in
a happy relationship. That's why he
stalks all of my sloppy seconds and stalks me. So, yeah,
[snorts] he's not in a happy
relationship. That's why he stalks me
every day and stalks my sloppy seconds.
But anyways, yeah, you would have spent
you would just spend a whole year and
you would just get nowhere, you know? >> [snorts]
>> basically. Yeah.
And before you know it,
you're old like these losers. Huh? That's that.
Not doing this again, though. We're not
doing this again.
No one's going to meet. No one's going
to say anything to anyone's face. This
is never going to end. So that's that. Yep.
All of the women I've been with has
never been disabled and never looked like Sarah. Yeah.
But I'm the ugly one apparently. Yeah.
Stop asking stupid questions.
that you already know the answer to. But yeah,
Joseph, you need to stop pumping
machines with money and pretending that
you've won, bro. You're really you're
really not a good troll. Like, it's to
the point now where I'm actually feeling
sorry for you.
Nope, that never happened. I've never
been with any disabled women. Never have
and never will. Let's forget she's
disabled and put aside
Let's forget she's disabled and put
aside hatred of him.
No, I wouldn't. I hate women.
Uh, no, I wouldn't, bro. I hate women.
But yeah, you need to stop putting money
in machines, bro, and um acting as if
you won. It's getting really silly now.
Getting really, really silly.
And before you're jealous,
bro. Come on. It's pathetic now. Yeah.
Well, Joe, well, I don't want people
I've never wanted sympathy. I don't want
sympathy from anyone. All I All I found
was strange is that when women complain
about men, everyone feels sorry for
them. Um but yet when you when you say
your struggles, um people dismiss them.
I just thought it was a bit unfair and
[ __ ] up. I don't want anyone's
sympathy. Never have, never will.
I just think it's very strange how yeah,
a woman will moan about like a man even
though they can get dates and they can
get sex. So they would never really know
the struggle. And then you got all of
these people feeling sorry for them. But
yet if you're a man that's been
struggling for ages or had to just put
up with [ __ ] generally people just
dismiss it. I just think it's unfair and
[ __ ] up. That's what I said cuz it is
it is generally [ __ ] up. It is. It is.
It is weird. It's [ __ ] up.
Yeah. I said that it's sexist.
It's biased and it's double standards.
That's what I think is [ __ ]
And the double standard is just [ __ ] up.
No, I really don't want people to What?
What views? Wait, hold on. Hold on, bro.
What What views are we talking about? I
mean, I've got approaching videos. I've
got messages. I mean, I've got evidence.
The evidence is there. The evidence is
literally there. So, I mean,
the evidence is literally
in front of your eyes.
So, I don't know why you're talking about views. Um,
and again, why is it always everyone
else's fault, mate? Again, I'll repeat
myself one more time. If you do not
listen to it, uh, that's on you. Uh,
I've shown approaches and I've seen and
I've shown messages.
So, again, that'll be the last time I
say that. If that doesn't process in
your mind, then that's on you. [snorts] Simple.
Yeah. And all I thought was it's really
[ __ ] up how everyone feels sorry for
women um that can get dates, that can
get sex, that can be with men because
the man has broken up with them after 3
weeks. Yeah. If a man struggles,
everyone dismisses it. I do find that
[ __ ] up. Yeah. I find it [ __ ] up,
unbiased, and I find it [ __ ] up,
biased, and sexist. Yeah, it is. That is
[ __ ] up. That literally is [ __ ] up.
It is [ __ ] up. Yeah, I admit it. It is So,
yeah. Well, yeah. I mean, no one is
going to agree with me. I mean, most of
the people, they're brainwashed. Most of
the people in this society are
brainwashed into thinking women are good
when they're not. There's nothing good
about them. I mean, most people I mean,
think about it, bro. No one likes a simp
and a white knight, but most people are
white knights. It's just because um it's
just because that's how they're brought
up. That they're brainwashed.
And it's not the right way either. It's
not the right way what what they're
doing. They're brainwashed
because I don't want to I don't want to
go along with society. I'm not a
copycat. I've got a mind of my own, you know.
I'm uh I'm trying to uh Yeah, I'm
uneducated, mate. I'm uneducated. Your
boyfriend Lord Jacod even spell
and you're saying that I'm uneducated.
Look who's talking, bro.
I don't I don't go along with society. I
hate women. I hate white knights. I hate simps.
So, I don't I don't want to go along
with society. I'm not a copycat.
I don't agree with society. Societyy's
[ __ ] up. I wish I was born in the 80s.
I hate white knights. I hate simps. I hate women.
I reckon you I reckon you were bullied
in school. Oh, dear. That's nice of you.
Um, so yeah, I hate women. I hate white
knights. I hate simps. Bob, if if if a
white knight or simp tries to get
involved with anything again, I reckon
I'll just glass them in their neck.
I'm that fed up with it, bro. That's why
I don't go out. I reckon I would just
glass someone in their face at this point. >> Sorry.
Up in before I know what you're going to
say and then we'll go over it all over again.
I generally would, bro. I generally
generally would at this point.
Wait for it. Wait for it. Wait for it, Bob. You know,
wait for it.
I never said a girl. I said a white
knight. I said a simp.
And I can say that if I wanted to say
that, I can say what I want, mate. And
that's not what I said if you actually
listen properly to what I said. And I
can say I hate them.
You know, the way they talk to people,
bro. That guy in Manchester, that poor
innocent black guy that approached this woman.
Oh. Uh, no, I don't need to prove anyone
wrong. I'm not here to prove people
He was on the phone. He was on the
So, he he he approached this woman. She
was on the phone and um
uh Right. You're bad. Self projector.
Um, and she and she's like, "I'm on the
phone. Move away from me, brother." What the [ __ ]
What the [ __ ] bro? She was on the
phone. She said, "Oh, I'm on the phone.
Get away from me."
What the actual [ __ ] That was pissing
me off, bro. Just watching it. Who the
[ __ ] do they think they are?
You know, that poor innocent guy. This
guy in Belgium was I showed him my
screenshots and he said, "Oh, it pisses
me off just what um just looking at it."
I said, "Yeah, imagine how I feel having
to actually put up with it for all of
them years. I did.
Why? How am I going around in circles?
I've given up. You're the one that's
brought it up, bro. Why? How am I going
around in circles when I've given up?
Can you please explain that?
I've given up. You're the one that's
bringing it. You're the one that's
bringing it up.
I'm not going around in circles.
I ain't going around in circles at all.
And I tell you how what else I'm not
going in circles with this shitty
community with these shitty low life
people in 2026.
That's another thing I'm not going
around in circles with. [ __ ] that.
And lady doesn't even want me on YouTube either.
So that's another thing.
I need to stop respecting people's
wishes and get off this [ __ ] shitty
community. Same shitty people that have
clearly got no life that they're doing
this in 2026. 2026. and they're still
[ __ ] doing this. You know, I was
thinking about this on um my way back. I
said, "Oh yeah, Laney doesn't really
want me on YouTube, but she's just tired
of telling me." And it's like, "You
might as well just listen to Laney." You
know, these people ain't got no life.
There's nothing that's going to come of
this. None of these people are ever
going to meet you. They're never going
to say anything to your face. And it's
just going to keep going around in circles
and they're all biased and it's just
boring. It's just generally boring. This
is why Monty's not on here anymore.
This is why Monty's not on here anymore.
I can see it. I can see why.
We're 20 We're in 2026.
Yeah, I've got [ __ ] better things to
be doing than arguing with some [ __ ]
skin lanky virgin in the shitty bedsit,
you know, for another [ __ ] 10 years.
A life loser that would ever meet
anyone. What the [ __ ] bro? What am I
getting out of this? You know,
uh I mean, yeah, I gamble very rarely.
Your point is
Yeah, I gamble like every couple of
months. Okay. And
Yeah. What's your point, bro?
Yeah. On this community. Yeah. Yeah.
If ask yourself this yet if these people
are better than you. Yeah, cuz obviously
they're judging you. Why are they on YouTube 24/7?
That's what I want to know. [ __ ] the
jealousy. I don't care about people
being jealous or not being jealous. I
couldn't give a [ __ ] if they are or
they're not. I'm saying why are these
people on YouTube 24/7 if they're better
than you? They got more money than you.
They got better life than you. So why
are they on YouTube 24/7 speaking to each other?
from the time they wake up to the time
they go bed. I would love the I would
love the answer to that question. I really would.
So yeah, and I want to listen to Laney
as well, you know? I don't want to, you know,
you know what I mean? It is Laney's
house and that and I could stay on it if
I want to, but do I really want to do
that, bro? Like, nah. Yeah.
Yeah. I gambled £100 um earlier today.
Yeah. Yeah. You want the link?
But yeah, I am off here after this um
live stream. I'll come on occasionally.
Like I said,
yeah, I spat on the machine. Yeah, I
spat on it. I lost 100 pound in lads. Yeah.
Yeah. [ __ ] it.
And then you got [ __ ] Joe F saying
that people are living under poverty. He
doesn't have a clue, mate. He doesn't
have a clue what money people get, what
money people don't get. And he will
never know. He will never know. That's the thing.
It's just weird. It's just a weird
community. That's what it is. And the
reason I stayed on in December cuz I
thought, "Oh, I might as well just stay
on now." But I ain't doing this another year.
So, there's no point you, you know, even um
wasting your time to be fair.
like doing community post and [ __ ]
Yeah, it was annoying. I lost 100 pound on it.
No, I'll be live like once in a while if
and when, you know, to talk to Greasy,
but very rarely. I can't be bothered
with it, bro. I really can't.
It really is just a loser place.
Um, I'm not saying you're a loser. I'm
not saying everyone is, but I'm just
saying the haters and [ __ ]
Joe F is a loser. Lord J's a loser. Nons
is a loser. They're all losers, bro.
They're just dead beats. They ain't got
nothing in life. Think about it.
Just want to argue about [ __ ] all day long. Yeah,
I've got another channel where I put my
approaches on, Bob. I've got approaching
channel. I got approached on my other channel,
but no one knows about it cuz I don't
want these people following me about
what the [ __ ]
Can't tell you that, bro. Top secret.
Yeah, that Jo he's a [ __ ] but trust me
that channel that Jo channel he is not
winning like that bro
he is not winning like that believe you
me so he probably lost today he might
have gambled today and lost today I'm
telling you bro you are not winning that
kind of money on them machines
And that channel was definitely
definitely dedicated to me. He's so bad
at trolling that it's actually embarrassing.
Anyone that's got half an intelligence
would know what he's doing on that channel.
And it is bad, bad trolling, bro. Really bad.
And then he's trying to make it so if
you call him out on his [ __ ] you'll
be considered jealous. He's a sad
bastard. He really is a sad bastard,
bro. This this Jo is another one, you know,
only showing [ __ ] wins. That is
embarrassing, bro. Really embarrassing.
Nothing to be jealous of, mate. I'm
younger than you. I've got more money
than you. I don't need to be jealous.
>> [clears throat]
>> And I kind of feel sorry for Laney as well,
you know, over the YouTube [ __ ] and that
people at that age just want peace in
their life. You know what I mean? They
don't need this [ __ ] bro.
But saying that even if I moved, I still
wouldn't be. So, and this lady in his
house and that, you know, so like
she doesn't want me on YouTube. The only
reason she doesn't tell me to get off it
is because she's just sick of saying,
"Get off of it. Get off of it. Get off
of it." You know what I'm saying, bro? Like,
so I'm just I'm just going to come off
of it, I think. Bro,
same people doing the same [ __ ]
in 2026. [ __ ] madness. Bad by bad. Yeah.
You would have thought these people
would have grown up.
Yeah. You got you got the join.
Why do these people do this? PJ's
evidence pack. They need to [ __ ] grow up, lad.
But yeah, you could spend, like I said,
you can spend all year trying to meet
these people, showing them money, and
you'll just literally just
become brain damaged.
You would literally just become you just
become brain damaged. The more you
engage with these people, bro, the more
you'll become like one of them eventually.
Like whenever I go on L's channel, I
come out with brain damage.
I literally come out with brain damage.
Every time I actually develop brain
damage, bro. I'm not even joking.
You know what I mean, bro? Idiot. Who's this?
Hello. You going to talk? Yeah.
Um, have you seen how biased they are in
here as well? PJ's evidence about Have
you seen how biased they are?
Look how many people I've gone and tried
meeting and no one said anything and
that. It's actually embarrassing, bro.
It's really really embarrassing if you
think about it. This community is proper proper embarrassing.
Really is. You know, the more you think
about it, it's actually embarrassing, bro.
So, yeah, I'm just going to spend time
with Laney and stuff. Um, yeah.
Yeah, that's that. No.
Yeah, that L channel is proper proper disabled, bro.
And then you're arguing and then you're
actually annoying yourself because you
don't understand that the people that
you're arguing with are disabled.
You're actually arguing with disabled people. Yeah.
What do you think about 2027, Bob Bills?
You reckon it will be the same people
next year or
maybe I'll just come up for a year. Come
back in a year's time.
See if it's the same people.
What do you think?
If I just come back in a year,
you reckon it'll be different people or maybe
always same people every day. Yeah.
Yeah. That Jo is a he's a he's a Lavry
Mong. That's what we call people like
him. We call him a Lavry Mong.
You can't troll a guy like me, bro. I'm
too intelligent. You can't troll someone like me.
You know, like I said, his whole channel
was dedicated to me showing fake wins to
try to get me [ __ ] gambling. It's not
going to work. He's very, very low IQ.
He thinks he's intelligent, but he's
very low IQ.
I go out the house every day.
I went out today. I go out the house
every day, bro. Just cuz I don't
approach and deal with stuck up [ __ ]
doesn't mean I don't leave the house. I
leave the house every day, bro. Yeah,
just cuz I don't deal with stuck up [ __ ]
and drink anymore.
I had breakfast earlier, then I went
out, went down and went out again. Yeah. [clears throat] No.
Why don't Okay, I'll do that on one condition.
If Red Star shows me what he's doing every day
and All Night Spaz and and them people,
if you if they show me what they're
doing, I'll show them what I'm doing.
I think that's a fair deal.
You know what? I'm going to retitle this
video um this live stream. Same people,
same story. See you next year.
Yeah, I think that's what I'm going to
tell it. Yeah. And I'm gone.
Same people, same story. Hey, I bomb.
You know, you know, yeah,
he thinks £1,200 a month after bills is poverty.
He's an idiot, bro.
He's got no life experience.
He thinks having £1,200 after paying
[ __ ] bills is poverty.
He's a [ __ ] He is an absolute [ __ ]
bro. These people are retards.
They really are stupid. I am.
No, I'm actually done
until next year
cuz I thought it was going to be different people.
Bro, it's not What do you mean make it
last? It's not even a small amount of
money for the month.
You know, bro, you could go out drinking
every week with that if you wanted to.
See you later.
But you could go out drinking every week
if you wanted to. It's not a small
amount of money. Even in London for a
month to last a month.
That's not a small amount of money, bro.
For a month. Not really. But go drinking, bro.
I went out three weeks in a row.
That's not poverty, bro.
£1,200 after bills is definitely not poverty.
Well, I'm off of it, bro. Anyways,
I'm going to have another kind of talk
with me. Thanks.
Same people, same story. >> Yeah.
Same people, same story. See you next year.
>> I love that.
>> Yeah, I love that.
Who the [ __ ] is that?
Oh, you can [ __ ] off.
There's so many bombs on this community,
isn't there, Bob?
There's so many [ __ ] Mongs of this community, bro.
[ __ ] big is it?
I like sh.
You what? Ah sh go. story. Hello. I like
If you don't like Sher Gold, you're gay.
I can't get over that, bro.
What a stinking copycat.
>> Oh, for God's sake, man.
If you don't like
copy, [clears throat]
you big fat stinking copycat.
You big fat stinking copy.
Why did nonsle say that to me? Bob bills.
If I don't like cold, that must mean I'm
gay. I'm not gay.
I'm not gay at all, bro.
No, I'm not gay, bro.
Have you done Have you done your uh Have
you done your money in B bills?
Have you done your money in uh Bob Bills?
This guy's not talking.
Oh, some um celebrity that was that's
been put on the pedestal for many years.
Isn't that right, Dusty? >> [snorts]
>> Isn't that right? Oh yeah.
Yeah. Just some celebrity that was put
on a pedestal for many years.
She's one of many. Yeah.
That is ridiculous why someone would say that though.
That is that is actually ridiculous. Yeah.
How much money have you got left? Bob bills.
You've got a grand left. How long is
that going to last you?
Yeah, man. How long is that going to last you?
Yeah. Yeah. It should last you two
weeks, shouldn't it?
Yeah. That's all right. You got a grand
Yeah, it's good.
I just try and save some money, bro.
It's so hard.
I haven't drunk in ages, too. Well, I
drunk on Christmas, but yeah, I haven't
to be fair.
You'll be wasting your time going out in January.
No one's out January here. No.
Oh, yeah. Then then you
Um, do you want his channel?
There you go, bro. That's the new one.
That's the virgin one. Dusty. >> [snorts] >> Yeah.
Why do these people on YouTube call me skin
or bills? Is it because they're skin?
Oh, that's mad, bro. Anyways,
I'm going to jump off in a minute.
Yeah, bro. For real. They're proper low
lives on here. I like
Do you ever get depressed, Bob Bills? Do
you ever get depressed? Uh,
I've always been depressed living in
this house, but when I was back in the
old house, I never really got depressed,
to be fair.
I feel like I'm isolated living here. I
feel very isolated.
I can't explain it. I don't have um any company,
but Laney, I don't really have anyone here.
You feel isolated.
No, I don't want a bird. I hate women, bro.
I hate women.
Women are evil.
No, not women. I mean generally, bro.
When I was in the old house, I had
people living there, so it was good.
No, not women, bro. Women are evil.
No, I mean the Gemini Yeah.
No, I hate women, bro. I really hate women.
I actually do hate them.
No, my life's not bad, bro. My life's
all right. I don't starve. I can do what
I want when I want. Nah,
my life's not bad, bro.
I mean, look at the people on here.
Their lives are [ __ ] at the pits.
They've got to come on here every day
hating on people they don't know. Bro, I
mean, look at the people in this community.
I don't know if you're trolling me. I
think you're trolling me, bro. Yeah.
Does money make you happy, Bob? Bills,
money doesn't make me happy.
Nah, not really, bro. Nah.
Winning money is nice, but not Nah, not really, bro.
Winning gambling's good, but that's about it.
It doesn't make me happy.
It actually doesn't.
It really doesn't me, bro. Ah,
no. I'm too far gone, I think,
in regards to like the women and stuff.
Like, I am too far gone with it, bro.
There's no getting out of this. No.
No. Money doesn't make me happy, bro.
It's not suddenly going to change my
mood having more money.
I'm just bitter all the time. I'm bitter.
I like to be around people that think
the whole world is against them. I like
people like that, bro. I'm I'm done with it. So, no.
Yeah, I got plenty of nice shirts.
Nothing, bro. I'm just chilling.
That Lavy Mong Joe was on there, Steven
Howard. He keeps telling me that I'm
living under poverty when I'm not.
January is dead, bro. January is dead to
go out. No one goes out. January.
Yeah, he's a Ly Mong that JF Steven
Howard. He's a Ly Mong proper.
a Ly Mong.
How do you know that he's a Ly Mong, Steven Howard?
But what gave you the impression that
that Joy Mong?
I knew it when he was sticking up for a
notch legs not being a virgin when he is a virgin.
Um, and the fake wins
it's really bad.
It's really bad. >> [snorts]
>> Why does this Jo keep saying that £1,200
off the bills is poverty?
Man, it literally isn't.
That guy's a [ __ ] bro. He is an
actual [ __ ] [ __ ] isn't it? Yeah.
Yeah. His autism is proper bad, bro.
Nah, we're we're sad because of our bad
experiences with women. [ __ ] them. Yeah,
I'm good, bro. I'm just bas I was
basically saying Cory yeah I'm not doing
this um after today I'll go live the odd
time like very rarely bro I'm not doing
this in 2026
going back and forth with these losers
bro I'm not doing it no way am I doing
I'm not doing it there's no way I'm
I ain't do going another year this [ __ ]
[ __ ] that same people same story [ __ ] that bro.
Definitely definitely definitely not.
Same people, same story, bro.
Same people, same story.
No, that's a madness.
Same people, same story. See you next year.
I might just come back next year to be
fair. I might just come off for a year
cuz it's the same people, you know, like
Chloe, it's the same people, bro.
No, I Um, Yeah.
Yeah. I might come off by here, Cory, lad.
And then we'll try again in 2027 and
then still see if it's the same people in 2027.
And then if it's the same people in 2027,
come back in 2028.
Yeah, but it's the same people every day. Cory. Oh, Cory.
Cory. It's the same people every day,
It's the same people every day.
Same people every day. [laughter]
Oh, I know. I know. I know, Cory. Same
people every day, [laughter]
bro. Every time I go on Lord J's, I I I
develop brain damage.
I develop brain damage. Yeah.
What do you think of that Jo account, Steven Howard? Huh? Yep.
Why does Jo keep saying I live under poverty?
Why does Jo say that I live under
poverty? Steven Howard, I don't live under poverty.
Why does he say that?
I don't live on the poverty me matey. Yeah. Yeah, bro.
Why didn't we come on here for Steven
Howard and Greavesy and Cory?
And Laney doesn't like me on YouTube either.
And I feel like I'm like violating
I feel like I'm disrespecting Laney by
coming on here. She doesn't say
anything. But I know she doesn't like me on YouTube.
I don't know.
It's just it's just the same pe same repeating people. Yeah,
bro. It's so depressing living in this
house, you know.
It's depressing living in this house, bro.
It's like if I lived alone, you'd
actually get depressed.
Even if you lived alone, I think you'd
be really depressed.
I get depressed when I live by myself or with
one other person and that.
See, I wish King was here, man. He's good company.
That's why people get a dog, you know,
just for the company. Yeah,
I feel sorry for ladies. had to put up
with a lot of [ __ ] cuz of this YouTube.
You know it's the Gov Cory that started
all of this [ __ ]
You know it's the Gov cuz he's the one
that put people's addresses out there.
He put people's addresses out there.
So, it's actually him that started all
of this [ __ ] bro.
I don't know. Hopefully, he's dead.
Yeah, RJ is a [ __ ] [ __ ] bro. Yeah.
I feel sorry for Laney.
Must be scary getting your windows put
through when you're sat on a couch,
isn't it? That must be scary. Bless lady.
Yeah, that's actually scary, bro.
Uh, I like Sher Co.
Sorry. I like Sher C. like sh
I like call
you like co I like
I hate Oh,
devil call is [ __ ] ugly. Yeah,
my toothies have been better.
Yeah, my uh
my toothies have been better, Steven,
since using the electric toothbrush.
Every time I drink Coke and I eat, I
just brush my teeth.
It helped with the uh cavity.
I can't I can't stay off the sugar, bro.
But every I reduce the sugar and every
time I have sugar, I brush my teeth
after with the electric toothbrush.
No, I don't need a good night out, mate.
If you don't like Cole, you're gay.
No, I only have two I only have two cans
of Coke a day, Stephen Howard. I don't
buy bottles anymore. I don't buy bottles
of Coke cuz I just end up drinking it. I
only have two cans a day and I brush my
teeth like after I drink and eat. So,
it's got a lot better to be fair. It was
bad. It was bad, bro. Really bad.
I know it does, but it's so tasty.
If you don't like shovel cole, you're gay. Cory, really?
Why do people say that stupid [ __ ]
I'm I'm I I I um gole my mouth with salt water. Yeah.
No, they're not damaged, bro.
They're not damaged.
Bro, we don't have sauners in every gym
here. You know, you've got to go to certain places.
There's no You can't just go to any gym, lad.
No, I'm not going out and socializing,
bro. I'm chilling.
No, not every gym has it, bro.
Obviously, there are gyms that do, but
not everyone do. You need to go into
like the city to to get that like a sauna. Good job.
Do you like grievy? Um,
Tory Grezy called me a big fat stinking copycat.
He says you're a big fat stinking
copycat. I like Greavesy.
You big fat stinking copycat. [laughter]
What do you like the Do you like the Orington version?
I was on I was on um USA Izzy's sister's
Facebook and USA Izzy was on there.
USA Izzy's got a receding hairline. >> [snorts] >> Yeah. Um,
no, I'm not putting it up, bro.
I can send it to you. Yeah,
but the skin virgin might get obsessed. Yeah, bro.
She deserves it. Oi,
look at that cat. I'm on USA Izzy's sister's
Facebook. Look at that cap, bro. It
looks like the virgin [ __ ] Sorry.
That looks like the virgin [ __ ]
Looks like the virgin [ __ ]
I'll never forget that comment, bro. I I
swear I'll never forget that comment.
It looks like the virgin [ __ ] I can't.
It looks like the greeneyed monster. [laughter]
Somebody said that I can't you I can't leave YouTube.
I can't leave YouTube because that's
starving that's starving Grevy of
content. Paw [ __ ]
said I can't starve Greavesy off
content. Poor [ __ ]
Doesn't that cat look like the virgin
[ __ ] One second. I'm going to put up
that looks like the virgin [ __ ]
>> [clears throat]
>> Well, bless you. Look,
looks like the virgin [ __ ]
Oh, that looks like the virgin [ __ ]
Is it? It does a little bit, doesn't it? Little copycat.
He didn't want to feel left out. That's him. Copycat.
Oh, looks lovely.
That looks like a virgin. [ __ ]
Is he Steven Howard?
Yeah. I hate cats.
I hate cats. They copy.
Yeah, it's the one in the white.
USA is is the one in the white.
She still looks better than Sarah.
Still looks better than Sarah, believe
it or not.
[ __ ] hate cats.
He hates cats. Yeah,
she's a [ __ ]
I hope she rot to hell.
I hope she'll rot in hell. That scumbag.
Yeah, I hope she rot in hell.
She's a scumbag. Yeah. Heat.
You like USA is he now Steven Howard H.
Tell me more.
Looks like the virgin [ __ ]
You're not more loony than to me.
I'm more loony.
We miss Monty Man, don't we, Steven
Howard? We miss Monty Man.
should have never come on this community here. Yep.
Why Why do you think she thinks she was
a nine? because of her attitude, isn't it?
It feels weird Monty man not being on here.
He shouldn't have been on He He should
never come back. He should have left a
long time ago to be honest. Monty should
have left a long time ago
cuz all the [ __ ] that happened.
But it feels weird without him. Yeah.
She's scum of the earth, bro. Just like
most women are scum of the earth. Who's trip?
>> Yeah. Yeah.
He should have got off YouTube a long time ago.
I got him on here, bro. I didn't know
what these people was going to do, you
know? I didn't know what they were going
to do, mate. Cuz then they done all that
[ __ ] to him before they done it to me, you know? Yeah.
You lose his family, bro.
No, I wouldn't. I've had chances to, but
No, I didn't know what they were going
to do. Otherwise, I wouldn't have
brought him on it. How did he lose his family though?
How did he lose his family?
That doesn't make sense. Steven Howard [snorts] Yeah. All right.
He's going water. Oh, good for him. I
don't live anywhere near there.
I don't I'm not playing these stupid
games with people.
I'm not talking to you,
Laney. Yeah, I'm not playing them silly names.
I'm not going on that [ __ ] virgin channel.
I like cow. Nope.
Brother, what is what is all of this
[ __ ] in 2026? Steven Howard,
Waterloo. Meet me here, brother. We've
all seen the real him when I've been to
his area three times.
Why are we still doing this?
We've all seen the real Virgin when I
was in his area three times.
We We We've seen the real him. Not once,
not twice, but three times.
We've we've seen the real him, brother.
Maybe you've got selective memory or
something, but we have literally seen
the real him. Ah, what's it?
See, I'm on this live stream, bro. And
you know, the accounts would trigger me,
but do you know why they can't trigger
me, Stephen Howard? because it's just
the same repeating [ __ ] that we've heard
a million times before.
Yeah, I'm scared of nons legs. Yeah, you
keep telling yourself that, bro.
Yeah. Yeah. I mean, it could trigger me,
but it's just the same repeating [ __ ]
so therefore it can't trigger me.
Yeah. Yeah. I'm scared of Netflix. Yeah,
bro. You keep telling yourself that.
Anyways, uh back on to Monty. Yeah. Um
yeah, it feels weird. What? My
Don't let him get a win, brother. I've
already gone to his area three times and
made him go to the police.
We're not play I'm not playing these
silly games. This is 2026,
bro. This is 2026, bro. And I'm not
playing these stupid games with these
stupid lowife people. So, I'm just going
to change the subject now. Anyways, so
yeah, back on to Monty. Um, yeah.
I hope Monty man uh stays off YouTube. Yeah. Yeah, bro. What?
You think money man's going to come back on YouTube? No, [ __ ] hell.
I'm just chilling, bro. About to go sleep.
The skin virgins live
that Provident loans is another keyboard warrior.
Oh, it's the same repeating people.
Oh, I know. I know.
Bro, this guy, all I'm saying is he's
he's definitely definitely jealous of
me, bro. That's all I can say.
definitely jealous of me.
Look at his hairline. He is definitely
bored and he is definitely ugly.
Everything he says is self projection, bro.
All right, Steven Howard. This is self-p projection, man.
Let's Let's face facts. He's balding
and he is literally ugly.
Yep. Just another self projector.
So, uh, when is Monty gonna come back, bro? Yeah.
Oh my god, it's 2026.
[ __ ] hell, bro. Jesus Christ.
Stay repeating people. Yeah, I'm
definitely definitely off after this, bro.
Yeah, I'm definitely definitely off
after this. Probably until next year, lad.
Oh, man. I thought it was going to be
different in 2026.
I thought it was going to be different. Same people.
Yeah, I've seen that Clint account, bro,
a lot. That Clint account. I've seen
that Clint account a lot.
Oh, man. Same repeating people.
Oh man, I thought it was going to be different people. Same repeaters.
All idiots on this community, lad. >> [groaning]
>> What is it with that number 14, bro?
What is that? I like the show. [snorts]
What is that all about, bro? Yeah. You need
No, you're not independent. You're a
skin virgin and you've never had a job. Yeah.
Yeah. You're a skin virgin and you've
never had a job.
Yeah. You lived in your bedsit for 12
years. Yeah. That you don't pay for.
You're a skin virgin.
Yeah. And you're balding massively as
well. You are [ __ ] balding massively.
Oh my god. Look at Look at that hairline, bro.
And this skin one wants to talk about my
bloody hairline. What the [ __ ] bro?
Look at them temples.
Yeah, you're not independent. You're a skin virgin.
Never worked a day in your life,
bro. Look at that [ __ ] hairline.
Look at that [ __ ] hairline, bro. From
the skint one. Jesus Christ,
bro. Just go back on there and look at
that [ __ ] hairline. And he tries to
tell me that I'm [ __ ] balding.
You You're trying to tell me I'm balding.
You're You're You're trying to tell me
I'm [ __ ] balding with that [ __ ] hairline.
You skin bastard.
What the [ __ ]
Yo, I just wanted to say that, bro. That is funny.
[ __ ] hell, she looks like a [ __ ] pig.
Oh, you know what? She loves me. Really?
You know that, Steven Howard? She loves me. Really?
Nah, she loves me. Really, mate.
Oh, these comments are so self-p
projection, bro. What you have is what
he will never have a woman to spend time
with. And I love it. That's self-p
projection from Bomb. He's still a virgin.
That's Bomb. And he's still a virgin.
Same repeating pathetic people. This is
why I'm coming off of here, bro. I
thought it was going to be different in 2026.
Same same self-p projecting repeating people.
She She's calling me horrible and nasty.
She's calling me horrible and nasty,
mate. Have you looked at your virgin [ __ ] boyfriend?
Have you looked at that virgin [ __ ] you fat pig? [laughter]
She She's talking about me.
She's talking about me being horrible, mate.
What the [ __ ]
When she's with the When she's with that virgin [ __ ]
making fun out of people's dead relatives
and and I'm the nasty one.
Do do I have to message her? I I will
message her if I have to, mate. Cuz I
can actually message her.
That's if she's not blocked me. I'll
actually message this Sarah if if I
[ __ ] have to, mate.
Now you going to call me [ __ ] nasty.
where when you're with that virgin skin [ __ ]
[snorts] Don't know, bro.
Yeah, she's another one obsessed with
me. I think she fancies me. You know, Steven Howard,
he fancies me deep down. You know, just Sarah. Yeah,
I think she fancies me deep down.
They don't bring me down to their level,
bro. Not at all. I'm off after this
anyways, bro. I'm off after this.
I'm talking about this Sarah, bro.
Sarah loves me, you know. [snorts] Yeah.
Yeah. Sarah loves me. Do you know that, Dusty?
Yeah. Sarah loves me, bro.
Yeah. S was a fatty fatty, mate.
Yeah. For for a year, bro. And hopefully
2027 will be different.
Yeah, I'll be coming back in 2027
to see if it's different people, Dusty. [clears throat]
Let's see if it's different people.
Hopefully. Fingers crossed.
What do you think, Dusty? Fingers crossed. 2027. [snorts]
Every time I come on it, it's the same people.
No, it's boring. The same people, right?
It needs to be different people. There
needs to be a little little mixup, you know.
No, they need to mix it up, bro. Different people.
Do you agree with me, Dusty? There needs
to be different people. Otherwise, it's just boring.
What do you think, Dusty?
The same people. That's boring, bro.
Same people. That's boring. Dusty.
No, that is boring, bro.
Tragic. That's another repeating word.
Rattled. Who's rattled, bro? We're
having a normal conversation.
We're having a normal conversation. No
one's rattled, bro.
We're just saying that it's the same
repeating people every day.
No, it's just the same people.
No one's crying delay.
It is the same people.
Same repeating people. That's what Monty
used to say. Steven Howard. It's just
the same people doing the same [ __ ]
Is that true? Steven Howard.
Yeah, DNY. He's an addict.
He's an addict, fella.
I'm not giving him my time. I'm off
after after this live stream. I'm off, bro. I'm off.
I played Fishing Frenzy earlier, Timmy.
I lost £100.
Yeah, they are disabled.
disabled with no life.
Yeah, they are.
I'm sleepy, bro.
Aren't I disabled? No. No. Timmy.
All Timmy does is gamble, isn't it?
I don't know, bro. I don't make plans.
I don't make plans. You lad. Um,
I'm not sure.
I'm in my little dressing gown right
now. I had a shower, Dusty.
It's my birthday soon. Steven Howard.
I'm not sure what I'm going to do on my birthday.
I'm not sure what I'm doing on my birthday.
Oh, virgin boy.
Virgin boy ain't got money.
What are you buying me for my birthday? Steven Howard.
No, bro. I don't really got more much anymore. Yeah,
dusty. I like shovel car.
Come again. You can't deny she's attractive.
Can't deny it.
You can't deny she's attract you. Does
She not ugly. Little copycat. No.
Oh gosh, I'm so tired. All right.
I'm a little copycat.
I'm a little copycat. I'm a little virgin.
All right, sh
I'm doing nothing. I'm chilling.
Chilling at home. Yeah,
I'm gone. See you.