I just thought I'd go live for a little
bit cuz I'm bored and free today. Just
waiting on the
football. Just pop my neck up
there. I bet that does. Yep.
No, no, no, no.
Yeah, not back on YouTube. Just thought
I'd go live cuz yeah, like I said, I'm
bored. So, got no plans today. Just
chilling. All the detox all that there detox. So
yeah. Yeah. I don't need to come on here
anymore to be fair. Just made this
account yesterday. Thought [ __ ] it. I
might go live Saturday which is
today. Yeah, bro. Yeah.
See if any normal people join eh
Yeah, man. I got a banging football bet
on. I only put 20 pound on it. Hopefully.
Yeah. Yeah, man. No drinking today. Just straight up
chilling. Probably the last time I
chilled out on a Saturday to be [Music]
fair, a long time ago,
eh? So, we've been stressed out about money. Is everyone?
Hey. Yeah. Anyone that's like [ __ ]
projecting or anything, I'm just going
to block you. No projectors on this
channel, man. We just want like decent
talking, decent [ __ ] people, you
know? Went to get breakfast earlier. The
[ __ ] pub was too busy. I don't like
it when it's too busy, you
know. Don't like it when it's too busy.
Can't even [ __ ] hear yourself.
Think your [ __ ] eat your [ __ ]
breakfast and you hear [ __ ] people talking. [Music]
sent to the wrong [ __ ]
person. I went out was Tuesday. I got
two numbers for Tuesday. Yay me. That's
quite good on a Tuesday. Is
it [ __ ] hard? It was. It was [ __ ]
hard. Now I'm just on a detox. Won't be
out next week either because I got the
cinema to go to. Counting down the days,
buddy. Counting down the days until that
horror film comes out. Literally.
Yeah, I got a 20 pound treble. Both both
score no draw, which is a
banger. He's got a decent chance
though. Done a bit of study, you
know. That's all I do now
is 20 pound a week on the football.
That's all I do now.
do. It's too [ __ ]
stressful. I got some approaching videos
um up on my main channel, but they're
just unlisted. I went out
Tuesday. Oh, yeah. went out Tuesday, didn't
I? You sure
did. I don't know. The weather was nice Tuesday, but
then it turned cold again and I had shorts on.
Son. Yeah, that looks
[ __ ] Why is no one typing? Oh [ __ ] people are typing. [ __ ]
mate. Yeah, I done stuff. So So I didn't
even see the comments there. [ __ ] me.
I've just been living life, man. I can't
be bothered with this community anymore,
buddy. It's boring as [ __ ] I didn't go
out saying Patties. No, I went out on
Tuesday. Bro, I swear to God, I got that
American. Yeah, I done stuff with her
and then she just we just went our
separate ways. But bro, I swear down.
Yeah, I swear to God, bro. I went out on
Tuesday and I don't know what made me go
or the weather made me go out on Tuesday
like I said and bro trust me it was [ __ ]
mad like I think I got I got a boyfriend
about 10 times in a row. I swear to God
I got videos as well but I've just not
put them as um public yet. It was bad
bro. It was bad. Tuesday the weather was
I got like two numbers but yeah it was
bad bro. Not as in like there weren't
many people out, but it it's just been
it was just it was bad,
bro. Like I was I was predicting it. I'm
not going to tell you what I done with her,
but yeah, seen each other now anyway.
So, she's only here for two months, so
[ __ ] her in
it. I'm not going to go into details,
but yeah, I Tuesday was mad, bro. But
I'm not bothered anymore. I'm leaving
this country, bro.
I've just been, like I said, I'm doing
20 pound on the football every week now
and that's it. I'm leaving this country
very soon. So, yeah, cuz I'll go out
every Saturday, mate. Well, I'm not
going out for a few weeks cuz I want to
detox, but when I get back into it, no,
bro. I went mad. Like, I need to take a
[ __ ] break from this alcohol, bro.
When last time, do you know what I done?
Yeah. When I drunk Yeah. Last time I
drunk, which was Tuesday, do you know
what I done? I went back. Yeah. And I
smashed a mug and I pissed all over the
floor like in my own kitchen. It was
pissing me off, bro. I was like, "No, I
need to take a break from drinking and
and just just approaching shit." It was
It was white. It was pissing me off,
bro. I was drink I was only drinking
Guinness as well. I smashed the mug and
pissed all over the
floor. All over the [ __ ] floor, bro.
Now I've had to order a new Spider-Man
mug. Cuz when I went back to the [ __ ]
spider when I went back to the pound then
Monday. Why? Because I don't like Mondays. But
yeah. Yeah. And then I had to order a
new Spider-Man mug which was
£20. Bye-bye. You can [ __ ]
off. I know exactly who you are. But
yeah, I'm pretty much I got this person
to meet, but now I need to travel to see
her. I'm pretty much stunned as far as
this country goes, man. I'm thinking I'm
I'm at that point now, bro. I'm pretty
much at that point. Tuesday, yeah, was a wakeup
call. I've got like five
approaches on my channel was unlisted. I
recorded on Tuesday. It was bad, bro. It
was proper proper proper bad. Really
really bad. Like it was really bad. Like
that's why I'm just staying sober for a bit
cuz like you got to think about it
realistically, bro. Like you've had
people in this country, but honestly
nothing will ever change in this
country. Like it will never like
Tuesday. Yeah. Okay. There might have
not been as many people out as a Friday,
Saturday, but bro, I did send it. Trust
me, I [ __ ] did. And even though two
numbers is good for Tuesday, it's like
what the [ __ ] Why would Friday,
Saturday be any different? So why can't
be asked with it,
bro? It was It was constant. It was
constant. It was constant,
bro. That's why I'm just going to
[ __ ] just [ __ ] off. I need to get
myself an ebike as well. I'll be out of
here soon, bro. Ah, this country.
Miserable country, man. Miserable
weather. Miserable people.
And I had a haircut Tuesday as
well. So pointless pointless trying in
this country. I'm on a 3 week detox
minimum. So yeah, got this football
bet. You're rough. Why you rough? Did
you go out yesterday or
something? But yeah, it sucks, man.
Like how many times are you really going
to go out in this country and expect it
to change? Like let's think about it
realistically. Yeah. Okay. We'll go out
every every week, once a week, cuz we're
drinking anyways and we'll do a football
bet. Yeah. But
how long are you going to keep doing
this until you realize what these what
is going to happen? Like, you know what
I'm saying? You you have to like at some
point [ __ ] call it quits, you know?
Like Ant-Man was [ __ ]
32. I'm [ __ ] 2 [ __ ] seven. Some
people will be like 40. Like, how many
times are you going to keep doing
this? But I've got one person now after that American
anyways. But [ __ ] how many times, bro?
It's [ __ ] up.
Why do I just [ __ ] leave, bro? One
second. Someone Someone's messaging me. Hold on.
Yeah, man. And you feel good when you're
sober in it. Can't believe I done that.
Went to the kitchen, smashed the [ __ ]
mug, and pissed all over the
floor. [ __ ] hell, man. I was a
[ __ ] I'm a mad bastard, bro. I don't
even know what prompted me to do that.
It's the Guinness, Triple H. It's the
Guinness. There was lots of people out
today having Guinness. I went to the pub
in the morning to get some breakfast. I
was like, "Oh, I wish I I wish I could have a
Guinness, but no, I want to
detox before my [ __ ] liver goes
[ __ ] completely [ __ ] rotten, you know?
Yeah, I've got I videoed it actually.
I've actually videoed
it. I could I've actually videoed it."
No, I literally got the mug and I
smashed it into [ __ ]
bits and then my friend was [ __ ]
staying over and [ __ ] they've went they went
[ __ ] they obviously they went in the
kitchen and then there was piss
everywhere cuz I pissed all over the
floor, pissed all over the floor. The
cup was shattered in pieces. And the
worst thing about it, Greavves, is when
I went to the pound shop the next day,
there was no Spider-Man mugs left cuz
they had sold out cuz I had it for like
three months. So, I've had to order it
online. I've had to all literally order
it online. [ __ ] £20 it cost me cuz I
can't have a cup of [ __ ] unless it's in
a Spider-Man mug. It doesn't taste the
same unless it's in a Spider-Man mug.
Yeah. Doesn't taste doesn't quite taste the
same, you know. Greasy. It doesn't quite
It doesn't quite taste the same unless
it's in a Spider-Man mug. It has to be a
Spider-Man mug. I like
Spider-Man, Peter Parker, you know. But
yeah, I'm off the drink for a little bit
anyways cuz yeah, I went out Tuesday sending it.
Yeah, I didn't
really same old boyfriend. Same old they
got boyfriends. So that's why I just
take a break from it. But I got this
banging football bet, bro. It should
come in. Hoping it comes in.
E looks a good bet to be fair. Worth a wall.
Anyways, only 20 pound. Worth a
wall. Yeah, I smashed it to bit.
Greavvesy. Greasy. Do you remember
Ant-Man? Yeah. I said to Ant-Man, "How's
it going? How's the approaching going?"
And he's like, "They've all got
boyfriends." Obviously pissed
up. They've all got
boyfriends. I've actually caught myself
[ __ ] saying that. Yeah, that's just
standard in England, don't it? That's
what they say. They always say that.
That's not That's not any different,
bro. That's They always say
that. But yeah, Greavves. It was
non-stop. It was nonstop on Tuesday. It
nonstop. Nonfucking stop. It was
boyfriend, boyfriend, boyfriend. Like,
you hear it every time you go out, but never It's
never one after the other. It's like you
get it like three times. But yeah, it
was constant. It was
constant. No, I couldn't believe it. And
the person I was with, he couldn't believe it
either. The guy's like, "Oh, you should
go to Miami." He's like, "Everyone's
stuck up here in London. You should go
to Miami." One of the security guards,
he knows me. He's like, "You should go
to Miami." You know, it's be different
there. Still western eyes, isn't it? We'll see.
E had a KFC yesterday. Grievous. I was
thinking of you, buddy.
Yeah. Greasy loves
me. Greasy loves me. Don't you
greasy. I tried to um follow uh Morgan's
dad on Instagram,
Grezy. Yeah. And he blocked me. Yeah. I
remember I was think I was like pissed
up, bro, like a few weeks ago. And I was
just saying like not like even being
disrespectful. I was like, "Listen, like
you're one to call me a keyboard
warrior." Yeah. Yet you're the one who
has to make group chats on people, but
you will never say anything to anyone's
face. So what do you do? You you lower
yourself to a child. When you have to
make group chats on people, a whole
group chat dedicated to someone, but you
won't even say anything directly to them
or to their face. What does that say
about you? It's the truth though,
really. Is it? Like imagine that. That's
what kids do. Like that that's honestly,
bro, what what children do. I've never
done that to, bro. We don't like, you
know, we don't like someone. We sort of
just like block them. We don't have a
whole group chat. Someone else done it
before these silly little group
chats. But I just basically said, Grezy,
that you know, as long as you know that
that's all you can do is is make group
chats of people, you'll never say
anything to anyone's face, that's fine
by me. You
know, got the cunt's email as well.
Yesterday I [ __ ] emailed him, bro.
Yeah. Like Greavvesy, man. Who makes group who
makes who makes group chats to people
though, Greavvesy? I mean, would you
agree that's very
immature? Yeah, I just had a fling with
her and she [ __ ] [ __ ] off.
But like you're making group chats to
people like please man, you are the
keyboard warrior. No one else is the
warrior. Yeah, that's that's it. You
know, group chats. Imagine that. Actual
chats. Group chats. Wow. You're over it.
Yeah. No worry, we'll find another one,
lad. Yeah, I found an email. I just
basically said that as long as you know
you can only do stuff. You can only do
stuff behind the keyboard and you can
never say anything to anyone's face and
you can only do your little group chats,
that's fine by me. And I was like, you
don't own anyone in anyone's country.
Believe you me, you came here scared and
you started all of your [ __ ] when you
went back home. Yeah. come to England
and let me know when you or anyone you
know is in England and I'm telling you
you're not going back home. Simple. And
that will be the real indicator and the
real test. [ __ ] me. You you you made it
so awkward where people can't even
contact you when they're in your
country. You don't owe no one. You don't
bully no one, bro. Yeah. Believe you me, you are anyone.
Simple. Yeah. It was pissing me off,
bro. The other day it was annoying me,
bro. And I found their
email. I found their email and then I
just emailed them in it
straight. And your dad, stop talking
about yourself, buddy. I'm not even
reading that. I just saw no this, no
that. Same account, same projector
that's been doing it for three, four
years. Get yourself gone,
buddy. Go self-reflect on another
channel. We're on here talking to decent
people that actually want to come on, you know?
and actually have a chat and just chill
on this nice Sunday afternoon. We're not interested in
self-reflectors that have been doing the
same [ __ ] for years and it's
boring. So, yeah. Bye-bye
now. Bye-bye, buddy. But anyways, that's my point,
Gary. Yeah. [ __ ] hell. That G
account's been going for [ __ ] donkeys
years. This is how you know. Yeah. These
people on here, they don't have a life.
I just clocked that. That G account
literally does not have absolutely no
life. Nothing. That's the same one that
used to pretend that he used to go to
London and he's from up north. This is
Bro, this is this is how you know with
this community what these people are
like. Fat, ugly, nothing going for
themselves cuz they've been they've been
doing it years. Like absolutely years.
You come back, bro, and you you know you
see the same people. Literally, they
have been doing it for years. Absolutely
years, mate. Not even like during the
COVID when they were bored or during a
[ __ ] winter when they're [ __ ]
bored. That's how you know they got
nothing going for
themselves cuz they're sat on YouTube
every day trying to get a reaction out
of people to make their [ __ ] lives seem
not as [ __ ] It's [ __ ]
crazy. Sorry, bro. I just I didn't
realize there was that
time. [ __ ] losers. These people are
losers, man. I was gone for a little bit
just living life. I just thought [ __ ]
I'll come because it's Saturday. Just chilling
it. [ __ ] sad losers on this community, lad. Sad
losers. But yeah, that's what I
basically said, bro. Is it to um I said
it to the mom and I actually said it to
the dad. Like, no one's being a keyboard
warrior. No one's saying, "Oh, this that
and the other. I'll say everything to
your face. Now it's to a point now where
it's like I'm not even gonna [ __ ]
start being all disrespectful because
I'd rather just say it to your
face. Do you know what I'm
saying? Like you're doing your little
group chats because that's all you can
do is your little group
chats. Just understand Scotty. Like the
problem is it's not me. The pro the
thing is buddy. Yeah. It's not me and
it's not you. your daughter simply met
her match. That's what happens. You
know, it will happen to me one day if I
continue if I continued purposely going
around [ __ ] with people over and over
and over and over again. Eventually, I'm
going to meet my match and it just
happened to be somebody from another
country. That's all it is, bro. You
don't need to get all all high rate
about it. You
know, he told me if I come at your door,
you're going to [ __ ] get me nicked.
No, he said he was going to arrest me.
Who is the keyboard warrior,
man? Who is the keyboard warrior? That's
why whenever I message them now, I'm not
saying, "Fuck you. You're this." I'm not
saying no disrespectful stuff cuz I
don't want to be seen as a as a keyboard
warrior like them, you know?
It's proper [ __ ] up, man. It was
pissing me off. I was thinking about it the other
day. Yeah, it's [ __ ] up, Dad. in the
air. That's how it is, bro. Is it?
Yeah. Yep. Bye-bye. No self, no
self-reflecting on this channel. I told
you this. You're wasting your time.
You're not going to get a reaction from
me. I'm not reacting to these idiots, these
self-reflectors, these little nobodyies
in their 40s. I'm not I'm not reacting
to these people, bro. We actually need
to build a decent [ __ ] channel, you
know? And that's why you can't
even like really do it with these
people, bro. Like it's mad. I I'm not
even going to say like I'm not even
going to explain it anymore, bro. Just
let them keep
self-reflective. I'm not responding to these idiots
anymore. You know, that's what they
want. Cuz we all know that everything
that they call other people is
themselves. That's why they're on here
every day trying to get reaction because
they have nobody and nothing in their
life. So that's why they come on here
and talk about people that they don't
even know. You know the funniest thing
with this community as well, like with
these haters on here, they talk about
people that they don't even know. They
don't know what's in your bank account.
They don't know anything about you, but
yet they think they know everything about
you. [ __ ] Which obviously goes to show
that it's themselves they're talking
about cuz they only know their own skin, run their
lives. Self- affection, of course.
repeaters. Oh, why don't they anymore?
Watch kill a bit of time before the
football. Yeah, delay. [Music]
shot street [ __ ] hell. Who Who even
thinks of these account names?
Like [ __ ] madness.
I'm going to have a nice Chinese tonight. I
reckon any movie? No. I'm going to go
watch The Woman in the Yard next week.
Man, I'm on a detox. So, I'm not
drinking. I didn't drink since Tuesday.
I'm not drinking this week and I'm not
drinking next week cuz I need to go to
cinema and watch the horror film called
Woman in the
Yard. That's the one I'm going to see as
soon as it comes out. I'm watching the first
one called Woman in the Yard. If you're
into horrors, I don't know what you're
into, man. Horrors, whatever. But it's a horror
film. Go look up the trailer, man. You
might not be into horrors. I was going
to watch this Danny Dier one, but I
don't want to see it that much where I
actually want to pay money to see
it if that makes sense. Like, and I've
been like round malls and [ __ ] and I
just ain't got around to seeing it. I
just can't be
bothered. No, I just going to go by
myself. I don't take people to the horror film with
me cuz I actually want to watch the film
and not be sat next to someone. Just
going to go by myself.
Yeah. Never been on a date to a cinema.
Don't interest me. I want to actually go
and watch the film, man. I don't want
I'm going to go so I'm the only one in that
cinema. So, when it first comes out or
maybe I'll go What day is it come out?
You can't go by myself. Oh, here we go
again. and the [ __ ] trolling
attempts. Oh boy, here we go. Nothing
ever ever changes with this shitty community, does
it? Literally nothing ever changes with this
shitty [ __ ] Downey community, does
it? Literally nothing, does it?
No. Don't usually do. It's a nice day
outside today. It's quite quite warm.
Why don't you get off of YouTube and go
get yourself some
Guinness? Make some
friends. Why don't Why don't you go and
do that, man? Just Just go to the pub,
drink some Guinness, and get the [ __ ] off of
YouTube. No, no, no, no, no, no. I'm I'm
not trolling either. Why don't you go to
your local boozer, have a cup of
Guinnesses, and get off of YouTube? I'm
I'm not trolling either. I'm being serious.
No, no, I'm actually being serious.
Like, I'm not doing it cuz I'm on a
detox. I need to chill for a little bit.
Why Why don't you go and do it,
man? No, I'm I'm not trolling either.
I'm I'm saying, bro, and just get off of
YouTube. I'm going to get some cream
capes. Some cream cakes.
Yeah, I'm getting really into Chinese, you know,
bro. Yeah, I'm not doing nothing today.
I'm just straight up chilling, man. I
went out on a [ __ ] last week.
Yeah, I love Guinness though. I'm scared
it will turn I'm scared it would
actually turn me into an alcoholic, bro.
Guinness is it's addicting because it's
like even when you go to the even when
you go to the Weather Spoons, right, or
any pub and you have breakfast. Oh, let
me have a Guinness. And then it just
goes from there, you see? Cuz it's just [ __ ]
addicting. People always say to me, "Oh,
you ain't got a beer belly. How come you
ain't got a beer belly, man?" Because of
um I do a lot of walking, so I want to have beer
belly. I should invite my friends to see
that movie. Uh, here we
go. I know what you're trying to do,
bro. I've been on this community long
enough that I know what you're trying to
do. And just stop it because I'm not
Money Man or
Timmy. Yeah. Nothing wrong with going to
the cinema by yourself. You travel by
yourself. You people need to get a
hobby. You need to go off of YouTube.
Honestly, like when are you going to
like call it a day and think, "Fuck
this. I'm sick of projecting my life on
YouTube every day and just [ __ ] go
and get a life. It's the truth though,
is it, Griezy? I'm sure Grezy will agree
on me on this. You never think to
yourself, "Fuck this. I can't be doing
this my whole life, bro. Let me just get
off of YouTube and get a life instead of
coming on YouTube projecting." But they
don't see that, bro. They don't see that. It's
crazy. [ __ ] weird. Imagine having
nothing better to do in your life than
sitting on YouTube trying to wind people
up for a living. Imagine that, bro.
Like, imagine that for one second. Your
life being so empty that you have to
come on the internet every day trying to
wind people up because your life's [ __ ]
No. Can't imagine it. Can't imagine it.
I literally can't actually imagine
it. Greg, can you imagine it? I from
where I'm sat here, I literally can't
imagine it, bro. I'd leave the internet forever. I
actually these people are very bitter,
very twisted, very very hateful as well. I've noticed
that. You know what I'm
saying? Yeah. I'd say most of these people were
bullied or maybe neglected as a child
maybe. Yeah. You're again, you're just
talking about yourself and you're so
predictable because I just told you what
you're going to do. No friends, no
misses, no job. You're talking about
yourself. No one's getting annoyed.
We're just saying what you people do
because you've got nothing better to do. You're just
self-projecting. It's the same three
people that's been doing it for years. It's
boring. Anyways, like I said to you,
man, get off of YouTube. Go to the local
boozer and get a life because you're in
desperate need of one instead of coming
on YouTube telling people that they
haven't got things that you don't have
and you'll never have. Literally go and
actually get a life. Like at least Grezy
comes on here, you know, and and and has
like normal chats with people. Don't you
Greavvesy? You have normal chats with people
and you agree with some things, you
disagree with others. You know, that's
the that's the point of chatting.
But yeah, these self-p
projectors, they prove every day,
Greasy, when they're on here and they
can't take a day off of YouTube, it goes
to show that they're talking about
themselves. They're talking about their
own lives. You know, they don't
psychologically [ __ ] with anyone's head.
They don't ruin anyone's life. They
don't affect them in the slightest. They
just come on YouTube just embarrassing
themselves. They just come on YouTube
just embarrassing themselves every day
for a living. That's that's their job. They're
pathetic. Well, somebody was just here,
man. And they're so predictable as well. Boring.
Yeah. Do you want So, do you want to see
the video then,
Beezy? Nah, I can't show it to you, bro,
cuz it will docks where I live. I don't
want to dock where I live.
E. Yeah, I saw that. Yeah. These people
can't get me like that anymore, though,
Grezy. These people can't get me like
that because they're just
repeaters. Like, so they can't actually
get me mad because all they do is
repeat. Yeah. Bully me off YouTube.
Yeah. Yeah. Good
one. Yeah. Like these people, the thing
is, Grezy, they can't get me mad. They
can't get me raging because it's just
the same old repeating with them.
So, how can something right that these
people have done and said a million
times get you mad when it's just the same old
repeated by the same old low lives? It's
It can't get me mad, bro. That's what
I'm saying. And it's predictable as well.
Like saying about how, oh, I'm
guaranteed you're going to be bullied.
You're going to be bullied off of
YouTube, bro. So why? So you come on
YouTube every day trying to bully
someone. What does that say about your
life? You're coming on YouTube every day
trying to bully people. Okay. So let's
let's just use that as an example. Yeah.
If you had money, if you had friends,
you wouldn't be on here trying to bully
people. Even though you've never bullied
me and you will never bully me, but as
an example. So, you come on YouTube
every day trying to bully people, but
somehow you're the one that's got this
money. Somehow you're the one that's
that's got all these friends. No. Like,
I hate to say it to you. I hate to break
it to you, buddy, but I don't like using
this word. These people are bully
victims. They've been bullied their
whole life. That's why they're on here.
They can't leave the house cuz they're
agrophobic. Look, the weather's nice
today, bro. If it wasn't for me being on
a de um on a detox, I would be out. They're on
YouTube. Remember, Grezy, no life but your
job. See, you know how I took over a
week off YouTube? These people can't
take a day off of YouTube. What did that
say about their
life? You need to go by the evidence,
bro, not by what someone says. You know what I
mean? And that's the truth, lad.
It's right though what I'm saying
though, isn't it Grezy? It is right what
I'm saying. Is it not right what I'm
saying? Am I
lying? Am I lying, Grezy? Like, come and
tell me I'm lying,
bro. Do you think I'm
lying? I don't think I
am. There we go. Oh [ __ ] the football
start in 20
minutes. I'll be watching that off.
Yeah. Uh baby other
channel. You're not going to get a
reaction, buddy. Take it on Timmy's
channel. Take it on Monty's
channel. You're not going to get a
reaction out of
me. So yeah, you stop reacting to these
idiots. They just want a reaction
because they have no
life. They they scribe of it. Sad.
Too Fancy a nice Guinness though. It's
getting that time where quite warm outside, man. [ __ ] [Music]
me. I'm [ __ ] tired now.
Okay. Where's this guy?
This is how You basically been bullied
your entire life. Bull in school.
Bully. Yeah, I know. It's crazy, isn't
it? Yeah. Very crazy.
Yeah. You know what I find so crazy? How
you people hate your life so much that
you have to come on YouTube every day
projecting. That's what I find so crazy.
Like I find it so crazy that you can't
even take one day off of YouTube without
projecting your [ __ ] lives onto other
people. That's what I find. Like you're
just you people are just people in your
40s that never made it. You got no
money. You got no you got no friends.
You you laugh at yourselves. You laugh
at yourselves every day when you look in
the mirror. You don't laugh at me. You
don't laugh at me one little bit. You're
on YouTube every day because you have
nothing. Imagine that. Like, you can say
whatever you want behind your little
accounts, but all you're doing is
talking about yourselves because we all
know that you people are in your 30s,
late 30s, late 40s. You all look like
mters. You all got no money. You ain't
got nothing. And that's why you're on
here every single day, cuz it's all you
have. Like, you people have been bullied
your whole entire life. like you don't
you don't it's so bad that you don't
even fit into society. You don't even
fit into the public eyes. So what you've
all done was you you found a community
where you can all talk to each other on and
self-reflect. Like your lives are [ __ ]
You're boring. Like you've been bullied your whole
lives. That's why you're on here doing
what you do every day cuz your lives are
empty. You need a little bit of uh No,
I'm not describing myself. I'm describing you.
Okay. I'm describing myself. Okay. So,
who showed six grand? Was it me or you?
Who showed me having sex? Was it me or
you? Who showed Who showed them
traveling all over the country? Was it
me or you? Who's proven to be better
looking than anybody on here? Me or you?
Me. So, no. I'm describing you. So, when
you actually can come on here and prove
me otherwise, I've got your lives to a
tea. Literally, I was off of YouTube
over a week. You people can't even take
one day off of YouTube cuz it's all you
have. And as the saying goes, you're
only as good as what you can show. From
where I'm lying, actually, you've never
shown six grand. You've never shown any
women. You've never shown any any
friends. So, you're talking literally
about your own
lives. Like, that's you. Like, I'm I
should be a psych I should I should be a
psychologist because I know what why you
people do what you do. You're sat at
home. You're on universal credit. You're
all old. You've all got anxiety. You got
nothing. That's why you're on here every
day. Now, in the winter, right, there's
sort of an excuse. It's cold. We're
coming up to spring now. Spring. And the
weather is actually booming outside. You
know, it's too hot to wear a coat. Guess
what though, Daz? It's the same people
on YouTube every single day that claims
they've got money, claims they've got
friends, yet they're sat on
YouTube. Literally doesn't add up.
Nothing they say adds up to anything.
It's It's crazy. It's actually crazy.
It's actually crazy. Like, I have more
money than anyone on this community.
I've had more women than anyone on this
community. Yet, they still self-rect
their [ __ ] lives onto other people. It's
a [ __ ] madness, bro. But, Daz, you
know, it's not that slug skin. All of
these people are skin on here, bro. All
of these Well, except you and Mr. B cuz
I mean, you show money. Apart from you
two, bro. Everyone's skin on here. Well,
and me obviously. We're the only ones on
here that are not
skin. Think about it, bro. Yeah. Let me
ask you this
question. These people claim they've got
all of this money. Why they sat on
YouTube every day? Why are they not
traveling the world with their friends
or their wife or, you know, why they sat
on YouTube every
day? Because they've got nothing. It's
not like what people You are the manta.
Stop calling yourself a ma. It's not
good for your mental health, man. You
know, you people are the monsters. You
people are the bully victims. You people
are the skinn ones because you're on
YouTube every day and you can't get off
it. It says a lot about your own life.
Look, I can I can prove it right now.
I'll put a link up. Why don't you come
in and show us your
face? Why don't you come in and I'll
show everybody who the mtor is. Come in,
put your camera on, show us all your
money, show us your beautiful face, but
you can't do that because you are the
skin manta. And I can say it literally
better than anybody on here. Come
in. All jokes aside, I've never seen
Yeah. Yeah. You've said it before.
You're boring now. Anyways, come in the
hangouts. Show us all your money. Show
us your face. Come on. What are you
waiting for? I've got all day. The
football starts in 10
minutes, you know. Come on, show us your
money. Show us your friends. Show us
your good-looking face. What are you
waiting for? You claim that I'm talking
about myself. I'm talking about you and
I've just shown you everything that I've
shown. Why can't you come in the
hangouts? Because you ain't got a pot to
piss in, you little m. Now get yourself gone,
buddy. Get yourself gone, buddy.
Get yourself gone out of
here. Hello, you tragic insult. Run on a
Saturday. Go away, man. You ran away
from Pat Mustard, man. Shut up. You ran
away. I am. Guess what? Pat Mustard
didn't run the life,
PJ, byebye now. I'm not arguing with you, idiots.
[ __ ] out of here with your [ __ ]
annoying Northern Irish accent, bro. I'm
[ __ ] too tired to be hearing that.
I'm all of these things. Yeah, whatever,
bro. But guess what? Pat must didn't run
me off the YouTube for you. Take that L,
buddy. Take that [ __ ] L. Imagine
that. Imagine the biggest coward of all
time running you off of YouTube for a
[ __ ] year. That is insane, man.
What's this car?
Yeah, bro. Imagine that. It's
crazy. I feel sorry for these people.
Yeah, I'm skin. Yeah. Yeah. Okay. You
need to come out with different insults,
bro. It's getting boring now,
man. It's getting really, really,
boring. You need to stop repeating
yourself and self-projecting. And it's
getting super boring now. And this is
part, do you know this is part of the
reason why the community Oh [ __ ] Know
this is part of the reason why the community is
dead because you get the same repeating
self-reflectors and then they just kill
the whole they kill the whole community. You
understand? It's like their lives are to
sit there wait for people on
YouTube and then project. That's
literally what they do. They literally
sit on YouTube all
day. Yeah, you've said that about a
million times. You're boring out. Anyways,
um what these people do is they sit on
YouTube. These people, I'm telling you,
bro, these these little basement
dwellers. And that's actually like a
word I come out with. They literally sit
on YouTube all day long. All day
longing. Yeah. waiting for somebody to
go live just to
self-reflect. Your skin, you're this,
you're that. Imagine what kind of Bro,
just imagine what these people look
like. Just imagine the lives that they
live. I feel sorry for them. I actually
feel sorry for them, bro. Like, they're
the ones that are trying to sit here
bullying me. Yeah, but I'm actually
feeling sorry for them. Crazy.
It's [ __ ] madness, bro. It's And I'm
actually starting to feel sorry for
them. Yeah, I made
another Yeah. Well, actually, no, I
didn't. I I come on here to speak to a
couple of genuine people. And I got the
self-reflecting skin [ __ ] from your
channel come on my channel. So, I was
just telling people what they do. And
that's literally what they do. And they
never stop cuz they ain't got a life.
Think of it. It's March. It's warm
outside. These people are sat on
YouTube. No life. It says everything
about them and nothing about
you. Yeah. Had a had a nice breakfast
this morning. LJ had a nice breakfast.
It was absolutely
lovely. Sausages, some bacon to go with
it. You don't troll people. No. No. No.
No, no, no, no. You don't troll. None of
you people have got the brain cells to
troll. Listen, there was a there was a
guy in here 15 minutes ago. I already
knew what he was doing. You're not
trolls. Trolls are people that come out
with different things. Trolls are like actually
funny. Like, you know what I'm saying?
You people don't troll. You just
self-reflect. That's what you do. You
don't. No, no, no, no, no, no, no. But
what what I'm saying is you don't troll. You literally
self-reflect. You you're not intelligent
enough to be a troll. See, people on
Reddit, they are actually good trolls
because they can actually [ __ ] with your
head and make you believe things. The
people on here are just
self-reflectors, self- projecting little
basement dwellers. So there's there's a big difference.
You know, you just self-reflect. Like
when you call people's skin alone,
you're just talking about
yourselves. It's not even trolling. It's
not trolling if you're talking about
yourself. It's called self projection.
Projection, which is what you people do here.
So, oh [ __ ]
man. It's funny, man. You have to laugh
at these people. The kind of lives that they live.
Yeah, it's it's [ __ ] up,
man. Oh, it starts in 4 minutes. Let's
win a bet today. Eh, only put 20 on
it. Nice little 400 return there if it comes in,
bro. Bye-bye, Fantasy Stories. Go make a new account, buddy.
Bye-bye. There we
go. No, I can't take to talk to the
genuine people off here because I'm on a
detox and I'm chilling and I've got no
plans today. So, I'm just staying
in. No, cuz I'm just staying in today.
Yeah, I followed up Morgan's dad on uh Instagram.
RJ and I said, "Yeah, that's all you can
do is make group chats of people, but
you'll never say anything to anyone's
face. You're a bit like people on here.
You'll never say anything to anyone's
face." So, it's all good, man. You can
make your little group chats, but we all
know when [ __ ] gets real, you're nowhere
to be seen. And I was just saying that I
don't I don't curse them anymore. I
don't disrespect them because if I do
that, that's me being a keyboard warrior
like them. You see, you
know, that's me um being a keyboard
warrior like them. And I'm not a
keyboard warrior like them, you
know. [ __ ] you hell,
bro. It is insane. E [Music]
Uh yeah, detox. In other words, you have
no money. I've got more money than you
would ever have. Yeah, he laughs at me,
bro. Of course he does. That's why he's
gone to the police about me. That's why
that's Bro, he has to make it seem like he's laughing.
Yeah, I don't really think going to the
police about somebody and changing your
number is a laughing
matter. Like, think of it. I had people
call me the other day. They sure made me
change my number. That's no laughing
matter, mate. That's no And I didn't lie
about going to Boston. And we're not
getting into that anyways. And I just
basically said, "Let me know whenever
you're back here. Let me know whenever
you are back here." That's what I said.
Uh, yes, they did go to the police. They
did go to the [ __ ] police. And also,
when I said I was going to go in his
[ __ ] door, he said that he was going
to handcuff me. He said he was going to
handcuff me. That's literally what he
said. That family is not about nothing,
mate. It literally is not about
anything because a real someone that's
really about it. Yeah. Would actually be [ __ ]
would be guarding people,
bro. They're [ __ ] They're just keyboard
warriors. That's what they are. Keyboard
warriors. But now I just said like it's
coming that time, April. So, you should
be back April, right? Let me know when
you are, where you are.
talking. Yeah, that's not going to
trigger me. Nice try though. Successful
with a confident partner with a job.
Nice try, buddy. It's not going to work.
Anyways, but listen listen. What what
I'm saying to you is, bro, I'm not here
to start cursing them. I'm not here to
start saying you're a slag, you're this,
because I'm not a keyboard warrior like
them. I'm not going to make group chats
right on them about them because that's
childish. All I said is it's April soon.
Yeah, you should be coming back to
Europe. Tell me where you are in Europe
and I will be there. It's simple. Where
you are when you
are. And if you don't do that, you're a
[ __ ] house. Simple. It's there. There's
no there's no there's no there's no
nothing, you know? It's you have to make
group chats about people cuz you get
owned. Simple. That's it. I'm not
[ __ ] you know what I'm saying. And
when he said that he's going to put
handcuffs on me, bro, he wouldn't even
have the strength to restrain me to be
able to even put handcuffs on
me. That family is is is [ __ ] bro.
And he blames me as well. That's the
maddest thing. Her dad is so [ __ ] up.
No, your daughter met her match, [ __ ]
That's it. Simple. Your daughter met her
match. That's all it is. Happens to
everyone eventually in this life,
unfortunately. You know, you met
somebody that will give it back to you,
bro. So, yeah, that's it. Like, yeah.
I might go back there in a couple of
months, bro. I'm thinking, really
thinking of going back there in a couple
of months, bro. I'm not even
joking. This time go the [ __ ]
door. I'm considering it,
bro. Like, you might laugh and take the
piss on that, but I'm not I'm not laughing,
bro. I didn't make a I didn't make Bro,
they made me fake a holiday, bro. They
didn't make me fake a holiday. I went
and guess what? Even if they did, guess
what? I made her change her number. I
made her go to the police on me. So,
bro, do you think that's anything to
like, we know that you change your
number? Do you know how many times Jamie
Thompson tried getting me to change my
[ __ ] number? I'm not [ __ ] changing
my [ __ ] number. [ __ ] that. I'll just
put on do not disturb.
You know what I'm
saying? That family annoys me, bro. I'm
going to go on that door. I think this
time, bro. I swear to God. I think this
time I'm going I'm going to go on their [ __ ] door,
bro. I actually am, bro. I'm not even
joking. Yep. Self-reflectors get
blocked. Bye-bye now. Self reflector.
Oh, look. Football star side now.
Yes. But yeah, like you're the one that
has to make group chats about people.
So, you are the keyboard warrior. But
like come and do it to my face. This is
what I'm saying. Like you say you you
should go you go to Europe every year,
right? April, whatever. Or whatever.
Whenever you go. Yeah. Come and say it
to my face. If you're not a keyboard
warrior, come on, man. like get the whole family
here. You know what I'm
saying? I mean, you change your number,
people can't get in contact with you
now. Even if they go back, you're a [ __ ] house.
Simple. I'd laugh too, to be honest.
Man, it's embarrassing,
bro. It's embarrassing. It [ __ ]
annoys me, bro.
Yeah. And who's the one that But you're
you're saying all of this [ __ ] but they
they're using the word stalking. So, I
mean, they're playing
victim, you know? They're playing
they're playing victim. So, I mean,
who's really who really lost, brother,
when you're the one who has to play victim, man?
Yeah, good for him, bro. No one
cares. Yeah, he owns me. I know, man.
That's why the whole family went to the
police about me and changed their number
because they owned me so hard in it. And
then he said that if I went on his door,
he was going to he was going to arrest
me. Yeah, bro. He owns me so hard, man.
And I I can't take it. I might have to
change my number.
I might have to change my [ __ ]
number. Do you know what, mate? If he
owns me anymore, I might have to change
my [ __ ] number, son. I might have to
change my number, mate. I can't take the
ownage. Yeah, I might have to change my [ __ ]
number. You think anyone could ever make
me change my number? Nah, bro. Nah, I
can put it on
DND. Yeah. Yeah. What's your question, man?
H Yeah, you can if you want. That's
nice. No one cares what that virgin
says. I got this woman messaging me.
Um, do I have a friend group? No, I've
got no friends, mate. No, I got no
friends. No, I'm a loner. I got no
money. I got no friends. Nah, I'm
starving, bro. I got nothing.
Yeah, I got nothing,
bro. Yeah, I got no friends, man. I'm
like I'm like you people on YouTube. I
got no friends. I got no money. I'm the
same as all of you people. Oh, they
got Yeah, I'm the same as you people
lad. I'm like
you. Yeah, man. I got a 20 pound
football bet on. I only do 20 pound a
week now on the football. Um,
treble. Treble both score, no draw. Yeah.
Yeah. Anyways, you're gone. And this
Jason, this is why I don't really come
on here anymore, Gary. Because it's the
same atmosphere, the same
repeating, the same spastics that I've
been seeing for years. It's just boring,
bro. Why don't you come on here anymore,
buddy? It's just the same. It's just the
same It's just the same [ __ ] Cuz you'll
notice when you're not on here, it's
it's normal. You see normal people, you
meet normal people. And then as soon as
you come back on here again, bro. Yeah.
I don't care if it loses. It's only 20
pound. I don't give a [ __ ] if it
loses. It's the same
people. Same people every day.
Oh, he's our good old friend. Yeah.
Yeah. Stop calling yourself a manta. And
do you really think that I wanna And you
know the thing is Gary. Yeah. Do you
really think I want to be on this
community with with these little
[ __ ] Yeah, mate. It is for these
people. Yeah. Because they've got no
life. They're Bro, these people on here,
I'm telling you. Yeah. They are in their
30s, 40s. They've got nothing. No money,
no nothing. All fat and ugly. That's why
they come on here and project. That's
the reason why they come on here to
project their fat, ugly [ __ ] lives onto other
people. They are mters. They are skin.
They are virgins. They literally are
everything that they call other people.
It's their own lives they're talking
about. Um, nothing, man. I'm on a detox.
I just wish there was genuine people
that actually come on
here. Yeah. Not on this community,
though. I'm just chilling, bro. I'm not
doing I'm on a detox. So,
yeah. Yeah. Bye-bye
now. These people are so boring.
Hi, man. How are we doing? You good?
Yeah. No, I only do 20 pound a week
because what's the point of gambling
anymore, bro? It's
[ __ ] You never [ __ ] It's just pointless.
unnecessary stress and that I don't
really do it anymore. I don't play the
machines or nothing. I just do the 20
pound on the football.
Yeah, I don't care if it loses. It's
only 20 quid, man. I don't give a [ __ ]
Yeah, I don't play Frankie
anymore. The only time I get tempted to
play that is when I'm in the pubs.
Yeah, man. It's nice not
[ __ ] hearing these [ __ ] [ __ ]
projectors every day,
lad. Yeah, bro. It was
good. I'm coming off again tomorrow,
bro. Cuz it's
just this is a point in this community,
bro. Come on. Like once a week, pop my
nose in and then [ __ ] off again.
But it's always the same people, same projectors, same losers. Yeah,
man. Yeah, buddy.
Yeah, I got Swindon
versus Aington, Fleetwood versus Tremau,
and Chingham versus MK
Dons. Treble. Both teams to score no
draw. Both score no draw.
Yeah, hopefully it
wins. Nah, but I'm on her every day
though. Yeah, I'm on a detox for like a few weeks,
man. Cuz I need to go cinema next week,
so I won't be drinking next week either, man.
Yeah, is good. Is
good. Am I even a fan of football? No, I hate
it. That's the funniest thing about it.
I just don't want to I just don't play
them rigged machines
anymore. Yeah, I just don't want to play
them rigged ass machines anymore. And
I'm going on holiday again this year.
So, want to save as much as I
can. [ __ ] might give Morgan's dad a
little fright. I might give her dad a
little fright. That family annoys me,
bro. I swear down that family [ __ ] annoys me.
Literally [ __ ] annoys me. That
family, bro. I promise
you. Maybe Thailand, maybe
America, [ __ ] baby Germany. Haven't decided
yet. Got that fresh passport. No. So, yeah. Don't know.
Yeah, Germany maybe. Yeah, sugar
Germany. [ __ ] give it a whirl, you know? Why
not? Why not go to Africa, man? But
yeah, like I just said to Morgan's dad
that that's all you could do is make
group chat to people, but in real life,
you will never say anything to anyone's
face, just like your
daughter. And you will never let me know
when you're in my country either. You
will never let me know when you're in my
country ever. And you know it as well,
cuz you should be here next month.
You should be here next
month cuz you know it's uh you
know my attitude towards women is let me
let me let me ask you this question. Um
because when was the last time you went
out and you spoke to a woman? See when
you people come on here and you say oh
your attitude towards women bro you
don't know what women are like. You
people rarely leave your [ __ ] house.
You don't even know what women are like
in these westernized countries. It's
they're the ones with the attitude here
in London. But I just don't say anything
about it anymore because I don't really
care. I'm leaving soon anyways, bro.
There's more to life than it. That's why
I don't complain about it. But no,
they're the ones with their disgusting
attitude. And that's been proven many,
many, many times, you know? So, I don't
know why you just you just defend them.
It's to me it's crazy how you defend
them and you know what they're like
because anyone that goes out and
socializes with women would know what
exactly are they are like but you defend
them for some reason. Strange man, but
each to their own,
eh? Can I speak German?
Nope. Yeah. Bye-bye, self-reflector.
Yeah. Yeah. Anyways, we're not talking about
women. But like I said, when you go out
and you actually speak to women, then
come back to me. when you actually go
out and you approach women or you speak
to women, wherever it is, pub, street,
club, then come back to me because
there's no point me sat here explaining
it to people that don't even leave the
house that have got no life experience.
It's ridiculous. I mean, it's a waste of
my time and it's a waste of well, your
time listening to me
really because what would a bunch of
people that don't even leave the house know about
women? You know, just because you're
older than me, it doesn't mean you got
more experience than
me. You know, that that's not the way it works,
bro. Nope. We were going to, but we never did.
No, we was going
here. Yeah. Yeah.
Yeah. Yeah. Okay, bro. Whatever you say, white
knight. Whatever you say, white
knight. Yeah. They don't like you
either. If they don't like me, they
certainly don't like
you. Yeah, man. H They're warn snakes on
here, bro. The
[ __ ] They're all snakes on
here. They're all like that, man. It's
what it is,
eh? Nothing new. [ __ ]
Nothing new at
all. But yeah, if women don't like the
old Peter Belly, they definitely don't
like you. I've got one I've got one
woman that wants to meet me. I've done
stuff for this American. But the thing
is it means me traveling near [ __ ]
Birmingham. Yeah, I heard I heard about it.
Yeah, but it means traveling [ __ ] up
by near [ __ ] Birmingham, man.
[ __ ] which you ain't. I
mean, yeah, women are evil, bro. They're
evil [ __ ] They're scum of the earth.
But that's it's always going to be that
way, man. It's why you go Thailand. It's
why you go to third world
countries. They are evil. Even the ones
that you're in actual relationships
with, they've always been like
that. Women have always been evil, bro.
The [ __ ] It's nothing new. But yeah, evil.
Rude. I think any woman can get sex
anytime she wants and get into a
relationship anytime she wants.
That's what I
think. But yeah, that means me traveling
near Birmingham. Skip. It's not going to
say the exact location, but I mean
that's not really anything to complain
about really. I mean, most people have
to go to [ __ ]
Thailand, you know?
So, but no, the problem the problem in
this country is definitely it is it is women
because if it wasn't women, most people
starting off now wouldn't struggle. The
fact that 80 to 90% of men struggle, it
proves that it is women. Because I've
I've had this and the fact that more
younger people are going to Thailand now
and more younger people are bringing
Thai women back to England now. It does
suggest that it it is women cuz I I went
out on Tuesday. I sent it I got some
approaching videos on my channel that
I've not put public yet and it is it is
them but it's it's never going to
change. So there's no point complaining
about it. Of course it's
them. Tik Tok [ __ ] everything up. Only
fans [ __ ] everything up. Instagram
up. You know, I was having a
conversation with, you know, we we say
the same thing with like new people that
I meet as well. It is them. It is
them. But that's the way it
is. No, I just don't really care about them.
him. The only person I really hate is that
Morgan. If she was in front of me now, I
would [ __ ] whip her ass, bro. I'm not
even [ __ ] joking. Like, that's the
only one. Like, I walk past Izzy, I
wouldn't care. Walked past Izzy's
boyfriend, wouldn't care.
walk past that one in Manchester.
Literally wouldn't give a [ __ ] bro. But
if I was in front of that CL, I would
whip her ass,
bro. And give her some some
um daddy treatment that she never
got, you know? Cuz I don't like cowards
and I don't like people that are [ __ ]
and people that think that they're [ __ ]
bullies. And I would do it, bro. I would
[ __ ] do it. Trust me, I
would. And I wouldn't care, bro. And
that's only one person. And no one else I
would. And you know what I do? I'd
record it and I put it all over the
internet. I'll be like, "How's that for
your [ __ ] group chat?" That's what I
would do. So I would put I'll basically
publicly humiliate them. Yeah. and then
make a group chat sending it to everyone
she knows all over the university.
That's that's probably what I would do to be
fair. Publicly humiliate
them. They're making groups out of them.
Send it to all the
exes. You know what I'm saying?
Yeah, bro. It's [ __ ] up, is
it? I got a [ __ ] up I don't have a
[ __ ] up mind, but you
know I don't. But you don't
Yeah. No, but bro, with the USA, I
actually did email. I've actually found
an email on the university
site. Yeah. I said, "Listen, your only
big behind the key will be with your
little group chats. Why don't you let us
know when you're back in England?"
That's why I said, "Why don't you let us
[ __ ] group chats. Like I [ __ ] had
the [ __ ] I've had her body, bro. It's
not even that. I don't give a [ __ ] about
that. I was like, "You're going to make
group chats, but you're the same one
that change your number. You're the same
one that ran to police. You're the same
one that's using the stalking
card. [ __ ] madness,
bro. I swear sometimes,
bro, I could whoop that club.
I swear to God sometimes I can just whip that cont as
well. They're all like that. Look at
Kaye, bro. Look at the Monty and Katie
thing. And And he was calling me a woman
abuser. Imagine that. Like remember a
few months ago? Yeah. Monty was calling
me a woman abuser. Now look, I was
listening to him. He's like, "Oh, why do
women always get away with things?" Bro,
I was saying it all along. Yeah. It's
just the white knights didn't like
hearing it, you
know? You know, like now look what's
happened to you, bro. Don't come running
back to me. And that's what's going to
happen. I don't want them to ever come
running back to me now. You made your
bed. You lying it.
Simple. But don't ever think you're
going to come running back to me, buddy,
cuz it ain't
happening. You know, it's not happening,
buddy. is not
abnormate. Yeah, they are e they are
evil. They are
evil. They're [ __ ] evil. It's the way
they're made, bro. It's the way they're
uh it's the way their brains are, you know. Sucks.
E M and that American I went with I got
her but now she's she's only here for
two months anyways. But
you're a bit of a [ __ ] in it.
Yeah, but you need a detox as well, bro,
from like the drinking and the
approaching because it does it does get boring.
Bro, he sounds like a lovely guy. Why
does he sound like a lovely guy? He his
daughter met her match. That's all it
was. And then he's trying to make it
seem like, oh, I'm the one in the wrong.
And then you're making [ __ ] group
chats. What the [ __ ]
man? Yeah, it's [ __ ] up,
bro. No, he's a [ __ ] idiot, bro.
Yeah, she was a [ __ ] as well. But no, I
need a detox because like I went out
approaching on uh Do you want me to send
you one of my approaches from Tuesday?
I'll do it. [ __ ] it. I don't care. Give
it a whirl. I'll do it,
bro. I'll send you. I'll send you if you
want. [ __ ] it. I don't care, bro. We've
all seen a million of these before.
you an approach,
lad. Give it a whirl. I
would I would give it a little while.
You need a detox, bro. You can't hear
him. I've got a [ __ ] boyfriend. It gets boring. Yeah,
that's one from
Tuesday. Completely sober,
obviously. Yeah, man. I'm just making some content, bro. Oh, [Laughter] no. [Music] Ow. Who's
that? Looking a bit
shot. Looking a bit [ __ ]
So much [ __ ] evil wall
there. No, I just couldn't be bothered
to come back on it, bro. I don't really
come on it
anymore. Same mode, is it?
Oh my god. Will you stop [ __ ]
scoring? You're the [ __ ] the
better. I love getting your channel
banned. Yeah, that's nice, man. That
just goes to show that I own you if you
have to get my channel
banned. Yep, I saw it,
man. Yep, I saw it.
No, my football bet's not looking
good. We're not Chinese today.
Well, a nice Chinese. [Music] I don't
know. They don't accept God. It just
makes everything so
awkward. So awkward. It is
Yeah, I done a football bet.
Yeah. So, what you going out drinking
today, Triple H? You're going to give it a little
Well, what are you going to do? Give it
whirl? I would if I was you, mate. I
know we're on a [ __ ]
detox. Yeah, I done a football bet.
Treble both score no draw,
but it's not looking
great. Yeah. I can't deal with a hangover's me. Yeah.
Some madness, mate. How comes every time
I go to Newcastle, I get women? Triple
H, but whenever I come to London, they
just act [ __ ]
again. Yeah, I know, bro. I got another one here.
Look, I'll send it to you, buddy. Yeah,
I would give it a whirl. Every time I go
to Newcastle, I get something, but I
don't get [ __ ] nothing in London, mate. Come
on. Score, boy. [ __ ] damn you.
Score. Yeah, that's another one, bro.
You laugh at that
one. There you go, buddy. That's another
Look, she was asking me questions as
well. She was asking me questions,
too. Don't know. No one cares about that
little virgin, mate. Don't bring him up on this
channel. No one cares about that irrelevant little
virgin. We don't talk about that virgin on this
channel. That's another one, bro. Go watch
it. I think I've sent you the right one. Oh [ __ ]
N this football ain't looking greatly luck knows man over.
Yeah, [ __ ] me. I'm starving,
man. Had breakfast this morning as well.
I'm still starving. [Music]
Let me lick you
up to you say
stop rage. Let me lick you up and down
till you say
stop. How to order a new Spider-Man mug.
Triple H. Do you remember the little
voices? You used to love the little
voice, didn't you?
Oh, you used to love the little voice,
isn't it? Hello, mister. Get out of the
bathtub. Oh, you like that little voice, isn't
it? Yeah. People pay good money to hear
that voice. That's an old school
one. What are you doing? That's not nice.
Yeah, I used to love it,
man. Why are you not scoring?
Yeah, I think I picked the wrong teams
today, bro. [ __ ]
me. Think I picked the [ __ ] wrong
team. It's going [ __ ]
[ __ ] Yeah, it's going [ __ ] [ __ ] bro. [Music]
Ski. Yeah, it's only 20 pound anyways. Who cares,
man? Yeah, it's not going good, man.
You know, like the football can even
[ __ ] with your head as well because with
the football you can be like, "Oh, I wish
um I wish I picked that team instead and
that team." So, you know, even the
football can actually like [ __ ] with
your head if you put enough money on it.
You do realize that? Yeah. [Music] Yeah, bro.
If you put enough body started,
some guy, bro, I met in the [ __ ] um
some guy I met in the
pub. Yeah, mate. We It was all night
long. I swear to God, mate. I don't know
what the [ __ ] it was, bro. Tuesday. But
it was all night
long. Money doesn't work. Money doesn't
work, buddy. And you know why money
don't work? I was having this
conversation with Ant-Man two days ago.
I have offered I have offered money.
You've seen me offer money. Money does
not work. And let me I explain to you
why money does not
work. Why money worked back in the day
and why money doesn't work now. It's not
oh because they've got selfrespect
tink it bro. All a woman has to do is go
on Instagram. She's got loads of simps
giving her money. Yeah. Giving her
money, right? Um given her money to
basically um given her money
um to send nudes or just to chat to
them. It would never work in this day
and age because a woman can get money
from simps without having to [ __ ] Think
about it. Right. Yeah. Say you, this is
the the the the the example that I gave
Ant-Man. Say you've got gay men fancying
you, right? And they want to give you money,
right? Would you [ __ ] one for
£300,3400? Or would you rather show them
your feet and get
30,430? You'd rather show your feet.
Why? Because you don't want to degrade
yourself by [ __ ] someone when you can
make money other ways. And that's why it don't
work. Yeah, they love money and they get
money without having to [ __ ] people. Did
you not just listen to what I just said?
They can get money from Only Fans, nude
pictures. They don't have to have sex
with somebody to get money. They can get
money from simps on Instagram. There's
this woman in America. She's got about
600,000 followers. Yeah. Just for having
big tits and a big ass. Think of how
many simps are in her inbox every day.
They love money. Yeah. And they get
money without having to actually have
sex with you. They get money from Tik
Tok. They get money from [ __ ] Only
Fans, Instagram. They don't need They
don't need to [ __ ] you for money.
They'll get money from simps. That's
what That's the point I'm trying to
make. And I've also tried the money
thing. It don't
work. Trust me, it don't work, brother.
It don't work. I think I went out one
Thursday. Yeah, there'll be some women
that are up for it, but very very far
and few between. I'm I went out I think
it was a month ago on Thursday. It was a
Thursday and they weren't having it
for mate. Trust me, I was trying. You've
seen the videos. So, yeah,
man. It doesn't work. You've seen it
doesn't work. You've seen me going off
of money. It doesn't
work. It doesn't work, bro. Trust me. If
it didn't work two times, you've done
it. It's not going to work [ __ ] now,
is it? It would work on someone. Yeah.
That has no money and it's not
attractive. Maybe, but for the vast
majority, it don't work. Like, I done in
a club and they just gave me a dirty
look. Like, I'm not even joking. ages
ago, but it doesn't work, bro. Nothing
works. And the only thing that works is Thailand. Simple. Asia. [ __ ]
Asia. Nothing else works in this
country. Nothing else works. You have to
leave the country. That's That's the
end. Okay. Swindon scored now. Come on.
I think they've scored. Come on, man. So
yeah, we need
[ __ ] Fleetwood and try to score. Yeah,
bro. I said they score. They got a
penalty. I'm hoping they
score. I mean, normally when they get
penalties, they score. They miss a penalty.
Yeah, probably missed. Probably missed
wrong. No, they missed it. What the
[ __ ] Yeah, this bet's not looking too good, D
lad. They missed it. I assume they would
have scored cuz they got penalty.
norally when they get penalties they
score. Yeah, it's not looking good,
buddy. It's not looking
good. So, yeah. Uh, back to the money
thing. It doesn't work,
bro. They're not up to They're not up for
it. They're not up for it, man. Yeah.
So, mate, we need like four. We need
goals. No, we need more than that. We need about
[ __ ] We need like seven goals. I
don't think it's going to happen,
buddy. Not going to happen,
bro. I got a [ __ ] I just want to
have some nice food today and
chill. So, what would happen if I go if
I go out today and do some approaches in the club,
Gary? If I do some approaches in the
club, that'll be worth a while, wouldn't
it? Nah, this country is dead, man. And
man's out today as well.
How's it going,
Antman? They've all got
boyfriends. I'll never forget that,
mate. I'll never I'll never forget
that. It's not both. I've got a treble
both teams to score, no draw. It's not
going to happen. I've got a a treble
both teams to score, no draw. It's not going to
happen. It's not going to happen, buddy.
Because one's one nil and the other's
nil nil. It's not going to happen.
Unfortunately, it's a it's a both teams
to score, no
draw. So, they need to all be like 2-1
or 3-1. It's not going to happen, buddy.
So, how's it going, Antman? How's the night out
going? They all got boyfriends.
Boyfriend. I'll never forget that, man.
I will never I remember it as if it was yesterday,
bro. [ __ ] funny, isn't
it? [ __ ] this. I'm off to Thailand, man.
I'm off to Thailand, Gary.
I'll show you another approach as well
if you want,
bud. Yeah. And he said, "You [ __ ]
what?" You know what? Yeah. He heard it.
Yeah. He heard it once. He's like, "You
[ __ ] what?" He couldn't believe it.
Yeah. He's been three times. That's the
first time he said it. He said, "You
[ __ ] what?" He said, "Don't you think
you're [ __ ] better than me? Cuz you
[ __ ] ain't." That's what he said.
"Because you [ __ ]
ain't." Yeah. He said, "Gee [ __ ]
what?" He said, "You'd never get guess
what I just
got. The only place you're not going to
get a boyfriend is Philippines and
Vietnam. That's the only That's the only
place you're not going to get
it." Like, get them like get them saying
That's the only place you're not going
to get them saying it,
bro. Like Vietnam or Philip Philippines.
And it's like, who do you actually
believe? Because so many of them are
such [ __ ] liars that how can you tell
the genuine ones? Because most of them
don't have boyfriends. Most of them are
single. So, the ones who are actually
genuine. How can you How can you
tell? Is that the same one I posted? No, it
ain't. Oh, it is, isn't it? Oh, [ __ ]
Yeah, it might be. No, it can't
be. Oh, yeah. Wrong one. Sorry, buddy.
Yeah. So, who who do you actually believe?
Yeah, there you go. You got
boyfriend. I'm just going to go on the
[ __ ] table, bro. I swear. Yeah.
B. Bye-bye, Virgin.
But yeah, sorry, bro. I clicked the wrong
one. Yeah. Bye-bye, Virgin. Did any of them score? No. Damn you. Damn
you. Yeah, man.
Anyways, you'll be putting content up.
I'm gone tomorrow, man, for another two
weeks. So, you'll be wasting your time.
Yeah, you need to lose your virginity,
Sean, man. You're [ __ ] 30 years of
age and you're still a [ __ ] virgin.
You know, at the best of time, some of
the times I used to think my life was
[ __ ] tragic. But [ __ ] it could be
worse. I could be a 30-y old virgin. But
Sean, that's got to be worse than
anything being a 30y old virgin. They
made a [ __ ] video on the 40y old
virgin. They should make one of you, the
30y old virgin. The little virgin that
can't get his dick
up. Still a
virgin, but just 10 years [ __ ] just
10 years lower. You know what I mean?
Yeah, interesting in this YouTube
keyboard warrior [ __ ] I'm past it now,
bro. But you do seriously need to go get laid
though. You need to go lose your
virginity, mate. You're going to [ __ ]
die a [ __ ] virgin. Like, you're going
to [ __ ] die [ __ ] virgin. Don't
want to [ __ ] die a virgin,
mate. You know, I might just I might
just get a curry today instead. I'll be saving
money. Nah, bro. Not even not even
nothing, bro. That's the way this
country is, lad. It will never
change. Do you know what you're best? Do
you know honestly, Gary? You know what
you're best off just doing? Yeah. You're
best off just going out once a week and
then just [ __ ] off to
Thailand. Like go every th like pick a
day of week you go Thursday, Saturday,
then just [ __ ] off. Like that's what
you're best off because if you think
about it realistically. Yeah. If you
send it on a Saturday, it's no different
than you sending it three days in a row
because you've done enough approaches.
Like that's what you're best off just
doing is doing it one just one day a
week. I used to do it three days a week
and it's it's [ __ ] exhausting, man.
Doing it sober. It is, you know, and
it's no different than like if you was
to go out three days because I mean they
say the same [ __ ] anyways. So, if you're
going to get lucky, you'll get lucky on the Saturday,
right? I mean, that's my logic anyways.
But I'm probably going to go for a nice
curry today, actually. [ __ ]
it. So, all in all, I spent about 40
with the football bets. It's better than
[ __ ] going on the pier.
[ __ ] got another approach. I think I
might have another one. Send you
No, but yeah, bro. It's the same same
thing, is it,
lad? Yeah. So, just go out every
Saturday. I got my haircut on Tuesday as
well. It cost me a bomb, bro. A [ __ ]
bomb. Cost me a bomb, lad.
Imagine that. I was thinking of doing it. No.
No. Well, Ant-Man is going to live there
permanent, but no. Realistically, no.
But what I'm trying to say is that
realistically the only thing you have to
do now is leave this
country. You have to you have to give up
and leave this
country. Like that's the only thing you
you actually can
do, you know? You have to I mean
Antman's living in Thailand permanently
when he goes back. He is. He [ __ ] is. So, you
know, that's it,
bro. Yeah, I've just I've not given up.
I've just I'm just taking a break. I've
not given up. I'm just taking a break,
lad. To be
fair. Just taking a break. And I'm just
going to go out like once a week. But I
used to do it three times a week. And it's [ __ ]
long. And it's always the same thing
that happens as
well. It's always the same thing that
happens in the same way as
well. I think the longest I went without
trying was about 6
weeks. And it was good. It was It was a
good six weeks, man. It was a good [ __ ] six
weeks. It was good six weeks, lad.
But the reason I tried is cuz I didn't
really have much else to do. If there
was new horror films coming out in the
cinema every week, I'd probably give up
to be honest with you, man.
It's Yeah, Tuesday was bad. It was
bad. Got two numbers, I think, on
Tuesday. Both of them was from the
street. Who was
it? I think I got three, but one of them
gave me a fake number. I'm
thinking that's the thing. Who was
it? Oh, yeah. Yeah, maybe it was that.
Yeah, I think I was out for about Nah, maybe
nine. Yeah, man. Imaginary
boyfriends. That's what you hear about
in this country. Imaginary boyfriends.
That's why you have to take a break from it,
bro. Cuz when they say like a lot of
women have boyfriends, but they they
really really don't. Most of them don't
have boyfriends. Because if you go on
Facebook, right, you'll see so many
single women. So many single women. So
there's no way
um they have
boyfriends. There's no
way. But like it's like even if I met
somebody from another country, I'd just
move to that country. Like if I knew I
could go to America, right, and I could
meet someone and stay with them or even
France, I would move. I generally would
move. So when you go into central
London, you meet loads of tourists from
all of these other
places. Yeah, I know. That's what I'm
saying. You don't you you can't tell
because they're all lie. They're all
liars. They've got imaginary boyfriends.
But if it was a case of like you met
someone in France, Belgium, the
Netherlands, America, and they would
stay with you forever, I'd move. I would
generally generally generally generally would
move. Yeah. Bye-bye. Go self-reflect on another channel. Yeah. So,
yeah, these people in here are such
bully victim narcissists. They're they
they they're such narcissists on this
community. They really are mongos. This
is why you don't see me on here much,
bro. This is generally, bro, on on on a
level, bro. I'm telling you straight.
This is why you don't see me on here
because it's just the same spastics
every [ __ ] day. Every day it's the
same projecting comments. Why you have
to take breaks from these things, man?
It's very um imperative, you know.
Same mongos, the same
spastics, the same failed roast
attempts. So boring.
No, not on my lap. We done
stuff. But yeah, I bet Virgin Sha wasn't
too happy about
that. I bet Virgin Sha wasn't um happy
about that, was
he? But that little virgin
wasn't. And this is what I mean by like
just because someone's older than you,
it doesn't mean they've got more life
experience than you. I mean, look at
Sean. He's [ __ ] 30, still a
virgin, [ __ ] never been
abroad, never traveled, never even been
to Scotland. I've got more life more
life experience than that virgin. And I
and I have lived by myself and I do live
by myself. So, he literally has like no
life experience whatsoever. Never
worked. I've worked. I've worked a few
times. So, this is what I mean by like
when you find when you see people on
here and then when they're like 30s,
40s, what life experience do they have
that I don't when they don't even leave their
house? You understand? It's not about
age. I mean, unless they're like [ __ ]
80 years of [ __ ] age, then obviously.
Yeah. But look at him. He's a virgin.
He's never been abroad. Never been on a
plane. Never been as much as Scotland.
never worked. I've done all of these things, you know.
So, and I have basically been in a
relationship as well cuz I met that
19year-old about [ __ ] 11 12 times.
So, you can't say that he's been in a
relationship either. But even still, you
know, he's never worked. He's never been
abroad. Still a [ __ ]
virgin. You know, it's a madness, bro.
It's a [ __ ] madness.
Yeah. Never worked a day in his [ __ ]
life. Even I tried that [ __ ] deliver
roofing. I made4 on
it cuz who else was going to pay for the
Stone Island baby bros and [ __ ] Yeah. Yeah,
man. Somebody said, yeah, on Reddit, I
think they're right. They said they
don't know what the problem is. They
said that maybe too many stuck up
[ __ ] in your country. I think that's
what it is, Gabby. Huh? Well, clearly.
Yeah. They said maybe too many stuck up
[ __ ] in whatever weird country you're
in. And to be honest with you, I think
they're pretty right, right? I mean,
going by the approaches, I mean, they
seem stuck up
now. There's so many. Even in Australia,
bro, like the people that go to Bali,
they're stuck up,
man. Like, our parents had it on easy
mode. Our parents had it on [ __ ] easy mode, mate.
Literally easy my
brother. What if there was stuck up
[ __ ] back then as there is now?
Probably not. But I think that is what
it is, Gary. Is
it? It wasn't a year and a half. It was
like 3 4
months. But she was flatchested anyway.
So I don't give a [ __ ] about her. Flatchested.
I think honestly yeah your best bet
around this year is just go out once a
week save your money do a football bet
leave this country come back just go out
every week I think that's the only way
around this problem
bro like literally just pick a day one
Thursday one Saturday mix it up a bit go
out send it [ __ ] off travel done what
else there's literally nothing else you
can do. Like literally, there's nothing
else you really can [ __ ]
do until you can leave the country.
There's there's not much else you
actually can do, bro. Like, think being
realistic realistic about it, you know?
And it's not worth worth doing any more than one
day because you're going to get the same
[ __ ] whether you do it in a one day, two
days, or three days. It doesn't matter,
bro. I've met people on Thursdays. I've
met people on Saturdays.
So, it doesn't really matter, you
know. But what do you think the problem
is, Gary? I think too many stuck up
[ __ ] in this
country. I think it is. Clearly, it
obviously is. If 80% of people are
struggling, it obviously is, you
know, cuz you go on PUA videos. Yeah.
There's this black guy that goes around
approaching. There's so many people in
London that go around approaching and
they get exactly the same [ __ ] Now, if
they weren't getting exactly the same
[ __ ] I'd be thinking, "No, there's
something not right here. It's got to be
me." But when you see so many other
people getting the same thing, it has to
be them. Because if if there's a problem
with one person, right, why the [ __ ] do
all of these people go to Thailand? I've
already done that before. They won't
give you an answer. The answer is is
because they're stuck up and they think
they're better than you. That's why they
can't answer you. They're stuck up and
they think that they're better than you.
That's that's why they do it. They're
not going to tell you that, but that's
why it is. I've asked them before. They
whatever. They'll say, "Oh, they're not
looking for anything or whatever." Bro,
it's because they're stuck up and they
think that they're better than you.
That's what it is for me. You
know, that's the reason, but they're not
going to tell you that, obviously. know.
So, and a lot of them are just evil as
well, so they just do it to be [ __ ]
So, yeah, man.
I'm going to take a few weeks off, stack
some money, probably book a holiday in
next week or two
weeks. Yeah. Get the [ __ ] out of here, bro.
Yeah. Do you know what? In England, you
know, it's not even just the women. It's
loads of different things. The women,
the weather, the government, gamblings
everywhere. It's just a backwards
country. It's just a
backwards depressing country. all
around. Same with America as
well. Yeah, I was hanging around with
that guy cuz he told me his dad died in
it. So, I was like, uh, I gave him my
number. I said, "If you ever need to
talk, I'm here." You know, whatever. I
didn't get his number. I just gave him
mine. I said, "If you ever need to talk,
you got my number. Hit me up, bro." You
know what I'm saying? I felt
bad. We was even doing some approaches
in the Weber Spoons as
well. Yeah, we was doing approaches in
the Weber Spoons. Well, I was He wasn't was Oh,
yeah. This football bet's looking [ __ ]
I'm going to go for a [ __ ] lovely
Indian, mate. Help
me. What's going on? You're not scaring any girls.
I got a model's number as well. One
second. Nah, the football's [ __ ] lad.
The football is
[ __ ] Hey, at least I don't play them
machines anymore, is it? At least I
don't play them bastard machines anymore.
No. Yeah. I can't sign a pub when it's
too busy, man. You can't hear yourself [ __ ]
think. Horrible, man. When you're trying
to eat. It's horrible when you're trying
to eat. It is horrible, lad.
Yeah. No, they weren't looking. They
were just talking. It was annoying. But
was just an annoying
atmosphere. No, it was just an annoying atmosphere, man.
No, I couldn't imagine being 30 and
still virgin. [ __ ]
that. Imagine that, Gary.
Do you know what Ant-Man said? He said
though, but Ant-Man said that they're
just not interested in this country. I
think he's right, in it. Well, it's a
westernized country, isn't it?
So, he said that they're just not
interested in this
country. I said, do you know how mad
that actually sounds when you're saying
that? But it's true, isn't
it? in this country, right? Laws are in
this country. You know, you got laws in
a in a country and they're not
interested in this country. So,
yeah. Sounds mad that actually does
sound mad when someone says
that. Obviously, he's right, isn't it?
Because of course he's right. Yeah.
Yeah. Yeah. I think I picked the wrong
teams today, lad.
Yeah, obviously that woman wants to
[ __ ] beat but means going near Birmingham
it [ __ ] going near Birmingham [ __ ] wrong
Huh? But be worth the travel though. It
g be worth the travel lad.
Gary, who do you think would wipe me or Morgan's
dad? Good old Peter Belly, of course.
I think it's
wood. I think I would, man. Boring. Boring. Same.
Repeating repeating repeating repeating.
Yeah, I'm going to come back live later
and then I'm going to be gone again for two
weeks. God, man. Boy, it's same
repeaters, isn't it? Same repeaters,
man. I'm off in a minute. [Music]
Yeah, I know. It's just
a same [ __ ] repeating bastards every day, bro.
I wouldn't mind if it was just different
roast, but it's just repeating. It's
boring. It's just they just b they
actually just bore people off of
YouTube. They just make people just not
want to come on YouTube with a
repeating. That's why people don't come
on here anymore cuz the repeating they
kill it, bro. I'm telling
you, they actually kill it. It's the
same spastics every [ __ ] day alive
honestly. But yeah, I want to go cinema
on 28th and then maybe I'll go out
drinking the week after that maybe.
Yeah. Hey, you got boyfriend, do you?
You got a boyfriend, do
you? Oh, was you looking forward to baby
Peter from America,
Gary? Yeah. Oh, baby Peter from America.
Oh, what a lovely
sight. Yeah, he was looking forward to
that, wasn't you?
You was looking forward to that. That
would have been a lovely
site. What would these first words be,
Gary? Well, this bear is looking [ __ ] bro.
[ __ ] man. Lots of nil nils
today. Lots of nil nils today, lad. Hot
dog. Why would these first words be hot dog?
Yeah, but it is funny that Morgan and
her dad happen to make group chats about
me. Yeah, it's
crazy. What did you think of Morgan's
dad? Did you like him, Gary? Did you
think he was a pretty good [ __ ]
Yeah. Do you remember your sick and twisted [Laughter]
[ __ ] We was all sat there in
the booze and laughing about it, bro.
Sat there in the booze and laughing about
it. You're sick and Justin, [ __ ]
Do you remember that? I'm sick and
twisted for you. I'm sick and twisted
you. I'm sick and twisted for
you. I'm sick and twisted for you, mate.
Yeah, that's what my friend said I
should say. So, I said it. I'm sick and
twisted for you.
Yeah, dude. I'm a mad c. I got I got the
lot. Hey, I got the lot involved. I got
the lot involved, mate. The absolute
lot. Yeah, I got them all involved.
Me? Yeah. [ __ ]
Yeah. And you know what, bro? Even to
this day, I don't
regret. I'm happy I done it,
bro. Teach you to be a [ __ ] all your
life. Hopefully, you're a bit more nicer
to people in the
future. I think it's you my lucky day
getting your stinky [ __ ] funny, mate.
[ __ ] off. [ __ ] off,
man. You just can't think she is, bro.
I think Scott's a a good [ __ ] He says,
"I just have the same energy towards me
as you have towards my daughter." Yeah.
Imagine that like a whole family knowing about you.
Like they'll be speaking to each other
saying, "Oh, did they message you? Oh,
did he message you? Oh, did he me?"
That's [ __ ] madness, bro. That
is like a whole family. Imagine a whole
family knowing about
someone. That's [ __ ] mad, isn't it? Yeah. Yeah. Bad boy.
Yeah. Remember everybody was saying that
Scottish guy owned me, Gary. He didn't
own me. I said, "I'll put my feet where
I want." How the [ __ ] did he own me? He
was just being a moody
[ __ ] And he was like, "Oh, well, yeah.
Well, you're putting your I said, "Yeah,
I'll put my feet where I
want." I will put my feet wherever I see
fit. And I will go wherever I see
fit. You know what I'm saying, Gabby?
Wherever I see fit. All I was doing is
putting my feet up and having a
Guinness. That's what life's all about.
[ __ ] guy being all grumpy and
that [ __ ] Scottish
prick. What's going on? You're not any
You're not scoring any goals today? No. copy
in. If you don't find shovel co attractive, you're
gay. I'm gay apparently, bro.
Oh, I was
gay. I generally didn't know I was gay,
mate. Until the virgin confirmed it to
me. She don't find her attractive. No
ass, no tits. How can that actually be
attractive? No ass and no tits.
How the [ __ ] Just
copying. How can How can you be friends with a
copycat? Someone that has absolutely no [ __ ]
originality. Like no originality, bro. Imagine
that. Happen to copy
someone. You know, you base you base
your whole fashion on the
19 fucking7s, 1960s, but it's
copying. You know that Cole thing is
just him being a
copycat. The name, it's the [ __ ]
name. He's a
copycat. He's a He's literally a
copycat, you know. Copycat.
going to chase you all around. You copycat copying
people. You better like my [ __ ] problem. What's going
on, man? This football wet as [ __ ] bro.
I think it's going to
happen. Ain't happening today. [Music]
Joe, I've not had in ages. Nandos. I had
Nandos in Asges. Come
Uh, I'm laid back. I'm laid back. I am, bro.
I'm laid back,
Gary. You know, not a care in the
world. All right, I'm going to go get
some food anyways. I'm [ __ ] out of
it. I assume my bets lost cuz there's 20 minutes to
go. Yeah, that was fun. 20. Um, anyways,
I'm going to go get some food and I'll
be back late
later. Yeah, I'm gone for two weeks. I see you.