You're still doing this [ __ ] stupid
[ __ ] [ __ ] on YouTube. You [ __ ] low life.
You're still doing this, Poverty Joe.
The [ __ ] that's scared to talk. You're
still doing this in 2026. Seriously,
you're still [ __ ] doing this. Get a
[ __ ] life, man. Keep my name out of your mouth.
You poverty 200 phone rocking the 30
jeans. Keep my name out of your fat
[ __ ] mouth. Oh my [ __ ] god. How
many times have you got to tell these
people, bro? Give it a break. It's boring now.
Boring. The same boring disabled people.
Get a life. Get a grip. Oh my [ __ ]
god. Bro, it's a madness. Absolute
You're rocking the 200 pound phone
trying to tell people they're living
under poverty when you're the only one
living under poverty yourself.
Yeah, you are skin. Stop self projecting.
I lost a [ __ ] couple of brain cells
yesterday. Me, man. I can't lie. I lost
a couple of brain cells when I woke up
and I got him back. But I mean, you've
got no one really to blame but yourself.
Seriously. I mean, if you if you
marinade yourself with these disabled
low lives on here that ain't got no life
cuz they're skint, they got nothing
going for themselves. What do you
expect? You know, you know where the old
saying goes. So, I've got really no one
to blame but myself. These people are
the lowest of the low. They got nothing
going for themselves. That's why they're
on there 24/7. So, you marinate yourself
with these people. You become one of
them losers. And I'm saying as well,
like I was actually saying this earlier
when I woke up, you know, these people
have been doing this for 15 years. You
know, all of the evidence is out there
that they've got nothing. The evidence
is out there that they're nobodyies,
that have got no money, no life, no
friends. like the evidence is is fully
out there. Like there's there's no even
denying it anymore. You know, they've
got nothing new and they've got nothing
good to say about anyone. These people
in this community have got nothing new,
nothing good to say about no one.
They're just little disabled ugly people
that come online every day. And you know
what I'm saying is correct. You know
what I'm saying is the truth. That's why
you laugh at it because you know what
I'm saying is the truth. They're all
ugly fatsos that sit on YouTube all day.
Not a friend in the world, no money,
nothing going for themselves, and their
whole goal is to try to bring people
down to their level. It's so obvious,
isn't it? It's so obvious.
You've got an account showing fake wins
with a 200lb phone trying to go at me
when he's got a 200lb phone. A 200lb
[ __ ] phone. Seriously, bro. a 200lb
phone and a and30 jeans and you're
talking about poverty. And you're
talking about poverty, fat.
You're talking about poverty. Really?
With your £200 in your 30 jeans and
you're talking about poverty, bro?
You're talking about poverty to me.
[snorts] Sad, sad, sad, sad, bastards.
You would have thought 2026 would have
been the year, but [snorts] nope.
actually put the jeans on right now. But
I'd rather wear my tracksuit to be
honest with you, mate. It's the It would
always be the same old with these
people. It would always be the same old
with these people. They gave me a
headache uh yesterday. I had to take
some painkillers, bro. They They It will
always be the same [ __ ] with these low
lives. What do you expect? It's the
disabled community. What do you expect?
It's going to be different. It's always
going to be the same old with them.
They're lonely offkinned people. They've
got nothing but YouTube. What what what
do you expect's going to happen? What do
you think's going to happen? They're sat
at home, no money, no friends, sat on
YouTube 24/7. What what what do you
expect them to do?
I'm I'm going out in a minute as well. I
need to go out. I'll be out uh for a
couple of hours. So, yeah. I mean, what
do you expect?
What do you expect, bro?
Yeah. Skin, you've said that three times now.
Yeah, you've said that three times now,
mate. And that's just self-p projecting.
See, this is what I mean with them. It's
just the same repeating. If Let me ask
you this question, right? Let me I want
to ask you a question. If you're not
disabled and you're not skin, why have
you been on YouTube repeating yourself
for 15 years?
If you're not disabled and skinn, why
are you repeating yourself on YouTube
for 15 years? Do you not think that
maybe you're the disabled skin one? Like
obviously I know like you know you
people have got disabilities and
whatnot, but if you've got all of this
money and you're not disabled, why are
you on YouTube 24/7?
I'm just ask I'm just asking the
question. Like I'm not shouting over
anyone. I'm actually wanting to know the
answer. I'm not going to answer it for
you. If everyone else is skin and
everyone else is this and everyone else
is what you say people are. Yeah. Why
are you people on YouTube 24/7, 24 hours
a day lonely? I'm asking you. Um, I
think that's a good question to be
honest with you.
You know, sat indoors, lonely ass people
hating on people better than you. What?
Nah, not these people, bro.
Get a life, mate. Get a grip.
That's what these people need to do. Get
a life and get a grip.
That's what they need to do. Hating on
people that's [ __ ] better than them.
What the [ __ ]
It's madness, bro. Madness.
Oh, I just put my tracksuit on now. [clears throat] [snorts]
Oh god. Yeah, I am getting off this
YouTuber. I've only come on here to say
that people bully me. Oh, these people
don't bully me. These people bully
themselves. [snorts] These people have
always been bullied. They don't even
leave the house. They They ain't even
got a friend to their name, lad. They
don't bully me. They bully themselves.
If they bullied me, I wouldn't be on
here coming back for more. Nah, these
people have always been bullied. Sad,
fat, ugly, sadistic people. Oh, they
bully themselves. But they don't bully
me. They don't bully me, matey. Cuz I
wouldn't be on here. If they bullied me,
I would not be on there laughing at them
if they bullied me.
You know, these people don't bully me.
These people that's got no money and no
friends and no life, mate. They've been
bullied in real life, their whole life.
They don't bully a guy like me. That
could never happen.
They could never ever bully a guy like
me. At the end of the day, if none of
these people will meet you, if none of
these people will say anything to your
face, then they won't bully you. I know.
And that's what you people do. You sit
on YouTube and you project every day, man.
Do you know what Monty man? Do you know
why Monty man come off of YouTube? And
the same reason I'm coming off YouTube
is because it's just boring. You you
you're just all boring bastards. You
know, Monty man wasn't getting bullied.
I'm not getting bullied. They don't
Seaside Mark. I don't know about Seaside
Mark. He wasn't getting bullied. But the
thing is is it's just boring. That's why
people come off of it. It's just because
it's just the same repeating people.
It's just the same repeating [ __ ]
That's why people come off of it. And
it's not even that trip. It's not even
that. Yeah. Let me let me tell you
another reason why some people come off
like Ant-Man. You know, like Ant-Man. I
can tell you another reason. Yeah. cuz I
don't even think he was getting trolled
that bad. You know, these people on
here. Yeah. They have got nothing new.
They've got nothing good to say about
anyone. So, if anyone was trying to
improve themselves or get motivated or
be the best version of themselves, if
they're constantly seeing negative
repeating, self-projecting people every
day, what what's that going to do to
someone's mind, bro? Like, what is that
going to do to someone's mind if someone
actually if someone actually comes on
here? Do you understand what I'm saying?
You know, people wouldn't. They
literally people don't want to see it.
People ain't got time for it. It's
boring. They got nothing new. They've
got nothing good to say about anybody.
You know what I'm saying?
They just they're just fat wasters that
try to bring you down to their level.
And that's what they will always do
because these people haven't got a life.
It's been that way for years and it will
continuously be that way. They are fat,
ugly, lonely ass people. Like I can say
it like bro time and time and time
again, you know.
No, I don't think they bullied money man off.
They don't bully no one off. They just
bore people off. These are the true
bully victims. They don't bully no one
off. You can only bully someone when you
can meet them. And that's that. No.
Don't ask that. So yeah.
Yeah. And even then they won't stop. You
know what I'm saying?
[gasps and sighs]
Who's not moaning about women rejecting
them? I don't moan about women rejecting
me. I just say that women are [ __ ]
cuz I'm not a white knight. And I'm not
a s. I say my opinion.
But yeah, these people constantly
they've got nothing good or new to say
about anyone. They just they want to
bring people down to their level. That's
what they do on here because they're
losers. Because they're life's losers.
They want to bring other people down to
their level because they know that
they're the true bully victims. So if
they can like if they can uh if they can
if they can like bring other people down
for some reason it makes them feel
happy. Well, down to their level
basically as well. So that's basically
what they do.
People lose brain cells and [ __ ] as well. [snorts] >> [snorts]
>> Why? Because they're just like
Because they're just like him. That's why.
Yeah, [snorts] that's why they're just like him.
Or at least one second.
[snorts] You don't find this is just Yeah.
No, no, no. Um, no football bets today. No. Nope. Hey, bro.
No football bet today. Nothing. I'm not
doing nothing today, bro. It don't even
feel like a Saturday cuz it's January.
The vibe's gone. [snorts]
No, I'm not doing I'm just going out for
some food now.
Put my coat on. Nope. No footballs for me, lad.
I swear down. I just wake up bitter and
angry every day. Like, I literally wake
up bitter and angry every [ __ ] day.
It's so bad, isn't it, bro? I think it's
as you get older. I generally generally
think it's as you get older, you know? You know,
you just wake up bitter and angry every
day. That's what I do. Oh, sometimes I
wake up in a good mood and I become
bitter and angry.
Nope. I played it the day before. [sighs]
Yeah. I played 100 pound. Not yesterday.
The day before was the first I lost 100
pound. Yeah. [snorts]
Yeah. And then that's probably why I
react to these people to be honest. They
don't they don't bully me. These people
don't bully me, bro. I'm already angry
as [ __ ] [snorts]
You know, these people don't bully me.
That's probably why I react because I'm
already pissed off.
You know, this is what I'm saying to
Joseph Ferrar. He doesn't understand
that. Like, bro, I've got money. I
actually do have money. I'm not jealous
of anyone that's got more money than me.
I don't give a [ __ ] about money. I've
got money. So, again, I said to him
yesterday, why can't you go live and do
a gambling stream? And do you know what
his excuse was? Uh, Triple H. Oh, the
bookies are going to ban me. The bookies
are not going to ban you for live
streaming. You do videos in the bookies.
I've done live streams, videos. So is L.
So I just said to him, if you really
win, just go live. Go live and and
gamble. He won't do it. He literally
because he's only showing wins. And
that's not jealousy. That's facts. No
one needs to be jealous of a fat old
man. And that's not even being rude,
bro. That is the truth. know, you know,
when you're going to say that someone is
jealous, you need to elaborate.
You need to uh you need to elaborate
further what you mean by that. Because
when I say people jealous of me, I can
back it up. So, at the end of the day,
what? Because I'm saying that you're
only showing wins. That's not jealousy,
bro. For anyone that's got a an opinion,
that is not jealousy.
Um, and yeah, and I'm gone anyways now.
Yeah. So, that's that. So, see you later.