Oh [ __ ]
Sorry about that, man. I had to reset my phone.
Jesus Christ. You was [ __ ] quick,
bro. Jeez. Yeah. Sorry. I had to reset
my phone, man. I couldn't hear Timmy.
What the [ __ ] How quick was you, man? Yeah.
Yeah, I couldn't hear Timmy. I had to
reset my phone, man.
There you go. If you want to join to me
got like a real bad problem with uh
autism and money, bro. Proper
Yeah, I had to reset it, man, because
the the I couldn't hear him.
Yeah, they're going they're going on me.
They're going at me. Yeah. And Ly on
love is short. Yeah. Um Steven Howard
because they think everyone's like them.
Jealous of people that they don't know.
Like they think that everyone's like
them, bro. You see? That's why they
accuse people of like going to be
jealous of like people not being able to
sleep because they think everyone's like them.
You understand? That's that's what a lot
of these people in this community think.
They think everyone's the same as them.
>> Oh, PJ, have you had a good day?
>> I can't hear him, bro. Can anyone hear him?
>> Let me come back in. Let me come back
>> One sec. I can't hear the [ __ ]
Please don't tell me you can hear him
because I can't. [snorts]
They think that everyone is the same as them.
That's what they they think on this community, bro.
They think everyone's the same as them. Yeah.
I can't hear me.
I don't know why I can't hear him. I'm
not connected to my earpods, am I? One second.
Maybe I'm connected to my AirPods. I can
hear the [ __ ] One sec. Try again.
[snorts] Yeah. So, I don't know when I'm
going to be able to do some content, bro.
I really don't want to do anything
anymore, bro. So, I don't know when.
Hello. Is that better now?
>> One second. Recording audio.
No, I can't hear him.
>> I can hear that. I can hear myself.
>> Can anybody else hear me? Let me check the chats.
Uh PJ, um if you can't hear me, I you
just need to come back. Look, PJ, I'm
tired of giving you good advice,
brother. I really [ __ ] am. Stop
worrying about what these people do on
here. Who gives a [ __ ] about them? Like,
we all know they got autism. We all know
that they were PE.
>> No, I can't hear them, man.
>> And it's like they keep calling me slug.
It's laughable. That's why I call myself slug.
>> Why can't I hear anything new to say?
because their fake was this call me a
slug. They can call me a [ __ ]
dickfest comment what they like. I don't
care. You can even call me Tim. Nice but dim.
>> One second. I think my speaker's [ __ ] Hold on.
You're using an iPad with a [ __ ] Samsung