No, it's not my speaker. I don't know
what it is. [ __ ] knows.
Yeah. Autism and money. I think this community is
that's all they Yeah. Autistic definitely.
Oh, if only they knew.
Oh my god, bro. That's You really think
people care? Oh my god.
B is sadly mistaken. You really really
really think someone's gonna Bro, this
is what I mean. People are not like you.
You know, like I'm I'm just on this V
thing. Yeah. Imagine a throwaway 30 bet
PJ has given you bet has given you more
funds than the entire fake leanage. I
sent this to Charlene and put lanes in
for a rough night. You really really
think people care about someone winning
a small amount of money? You really
think everyone's like you people?
You honestly really think everybody is
like you people? That's another thing in
this community. You people um you get
mixed up. You think everyone's the same as you,
right? You must be talking from
experience, bro. When I've money when
I've won money in the past,
that is definitely definitely definitely self projection.
When I when I saw that win, bro, I just
literally ordered a takeaway and a it
doesn't bother me people winning money.
I don't care about money.
I've got more than 1,600 pound as well.
They really really think everyone is like them.
That's that's the vibe I'm getting with
with this autistic community is they
think everyone's the same as them
because that's probably what they do,
bro. every time. You know, I've won
money in the past.
They must be talking from experience,
bro. I mean, that's [ __ ] wild.
That is [ __ ] wild, bro.
That's all they talk about on here, Trip
H, is money. And that's another thing I
see on these live streams. Money, money,
money, money, money, money, money,
money, money. That seems to be all they talk about.
Must be part of their autism, isn't it?
Autism and money. I mean, someone
mentioned that before to that's that's
all they really talk about on it, isn't it?
You don't really see anything else.
Let me see.
>> Can you hear me now, PJ?
>> Yeah, I can hear you now. I couldn't
hear you. I don't know why I can hear
you now. Yeah,
>> mate. Well, I'm going to I'm sick of
giving you this good advice and I'm
going to give you it one more time. I
[ __ ] up today. Right. And hear me out
and I let you talk. All right. Cuz that
mass miller was making out I was the
[ __ ] Right. And I waited for him for
seven hours, PJ. Seven hours, right? I'm
going to get the full version off the
asylum. Yeah. And I'm going to upload
it. Right. That geser, right? I was at
his road. I went outside his house,
outside his drive, called him out. I
went to doxing it or trolling it little
rats. I went I've got Yeah. Get the [ __ ]
out of your house and he shat it. He
brought two cars of Pakistanis to his
[ __ ] door. Yeah. He shat it that
much. Right. So when when the when the
cars left, I went back as I because
obviously you do know if you go live on
someone's drive. Rock Banger did to you.
You could actually get him arrested
because you're not allowed to go live at
someone's front door. You're allowed to
go on the drive or on the roadside, but
if you be called their house, it's
actually classed as a criminal offense.
It's classed as a hate crime. >> Yeah.
>> So anyway, we'll get to the point. So
he's calling me a [ __ ] I've got round
up PJ. And now I want to go around
Birmingham around certain cold floors. I
know exactly where the [ __ ] drinks and
I'm going to [ __ ] film him live. I'm
going to say, "Look, mate, one and one
outside now. Money Mike's going to be
the referee." And I'm going to [ __ ]
floor the [ __ ] cloth ears [ __ ]
>> Why did you call him a cloth [ __ ]
>> Because he has got cloth ears, PJ. He
looks like [ __ ] Roger Smith out of
American Dad. Is an ugly look. He's an
ugly looking [ __ ] And that's why he
criticizes my looks cuz I'm gorgeous and he's ugly.
>> This is just the same [ __ ] on this
community. But this is PJ is I be
>> Oh, another thing. One second. One
second. Timmy, hold on. Chico, another
thing. I saw you being two-faced. Uh,
one second, bro. Yeah. Uh, no one's
jealous of your boyfriend's wins. We're
not all the same as you. People get
jealous of people that we don't know.
So, you might you must be talking from experience. But,
>> but PJ, the reason why I don't defend
you and that and you got to hear me out
here now. Some of the stuff you said
about children and women has been disgusting. Dude,
>> I'll say it again about women. I'll say
it again. But PJ PJ
women piss me off, right? That that girl
on the train, I shouldn't have done what
I done, right? But she pissed me off.
But what it is with women, hear me out.
And this is a constructive conversation.
>> Listen one second. Let me let me let me
let me ban Timmy. Hold on. Listen,
Chico. No one's jealous of your
boyfriend's wins, bro. Literally, I
don't care about money, so I don't even
know why you was writing that stuff.
Like, you know, you might be like that,
bro. Like when people win money, you
might like punch walls and get mad.
That's not a bit of me, mate. That might
be a bit of you, but it ain't a bit of
me. You know, no one's jealous of people
winning money. I don't care about money.
I'm not an autistic person
um obsessed with money. Do you understand?
Here we go. Will it Lord J,
>> I'm so happy you won. Now you're not
Skint, man. That's a good thing. Why are
you happy that I won?
>> I'm happy, man. >> Why?
>> Because you're not skin anymore. You can
buy yourself a decent watch. You can
actually go out. That's good.
>> Okay. So, you're saying my watch isn't decent.
>> But your watch is not decent. No, it's
not. Can you buy one?
>> And people are saying that it's not even real either.
>> Can you buy one?
>> Not my words. I'm not saying that.
That's what they said.
>> I said, "Can you buy one? Can you afford one?"
>> Yes, I can buy one.
>> I'll tell you what. Wait, why you
talking Why are you talking about
autistic voice? You know that win. You
know that win. I've got more money than
that. You do realize that.
>> You haven't paid.
>> Okay. Then I haven't. Okay then. You
haven't. How many times How many times
have you been shown money and been proven wrong?
>> What? The 10 that you show.
>> How many times you've been shown
thousands of pounds and you haven't been
able to show anything. Let's right now
millions of times.
>> You're not giving you You always say
that people overt talk you, but you ask
me a question and you're not you don't
answer. Okay. You showed what? That 6k.
You showed it once.
>> You've been shown £3,000, £4,000,
£5,000. The same money.
>> No, you've been shown.
>> You have been shown money multiple times.
>> It's the same money.
>> You have been shown multiple times. You
have been shown. But it's the same money you're showing.
>> No, it's not the same money. God.
>> Okay, let me ask you a question. You
asked me one.
>> So, how come you haven't brought any
clothing in a bread park at your answer
this. I bought clothes last month. I've
already answered this. I closed last
month. Okay, let me say this to you.
>> I have got more money than you. This is
the last time I'm saying this.
>> Okay. Well, then that's
Do you want to bet?
>> I have got more money than you.
>> You want to go to the bank?
>> You want to go to the bank and I'll go
to the bank at the same time?
>> Because I've got more money than you.
So, I don't give a [ __ ] Huh? What? You
keep You said you don't care about
money. It's ever since I came in here.
All you're talking about is money,
>> you know, like you're the one you are
the one that's pretending
you're buying all the other thing is you
don't get £1,000 a month.
>> You don't even get a grand a month.
>> Okay. Yeah.
>> You don't get a grand a month. You do
not get a grand a month.
>> Well, okay. Can I ask you a question?
Why didn't you pay your phone bill?
>> I've already answered that. I have paid
my phone bill. >> Okay.
>> I pay my phone bill every month. Your
phone your phone got blocked.
phone got 40. It's actually coming out
which is tomorrow.
>> Your phone got blocked. Let's
>> got blocked.
>> You do not get £1,000 a month.
>> Got blocked.
>> You do not get,000.
>> You put your credit file up and show all your money.
>> You do not get three grand a month. You
don't even get one.
>> Was that fake?
>> You showed the balance. Why don't you
people show your balance? Why don't you
show your money?
>> Same question to you.
>> Listen. Do you want to go to the bank
and I'll go to the bank at the same
time? Show our accounts.
>> Show your account. Yeah, you go show
your account first.
>> No, we'll both go to the bank. No, no,
no. You go show your account.
>> We'll both go at the same time.
>> I'll stay on your leg. We'll both go to the shop.
>> Show Show us the money. Go on.
>> Are you not going?
>> Show us the money.
>> No, you're not going. Of course you're
not. You don't have any money.
>> Oh, listen. I've got more money than you.
>> Yeah. Okay.
>> See if that was true. See, if you had
more money than me, I'd probably hang myself.
>> My 12-year-old
son has more money than you.
>> Lie about what you do,
>> Pete. My 13-year-old son has more money than you.
>> Okay. So, why do you lie about what you do then?
>> Why has my we lad been to more countries
than you've been to?
>> What? Why do you lie about getting money
when you don't get money? You're on benefit.
>> Why do you care about
>> You're on less than £1,000 a month.
>> Didn't you say that you don't care about
other people's money?
>> I don't. I'm just pointing out your life.
Listen, do you not understand by my
reaction? I don't care. You know when I
went on that asking me about money?
>> Listen. You know, you know when I went
on I joined the comments. I was laughing
about money. But you said you laughing
my ass off.
>> You know, you know when they were like,
you know when they said lany's in for a
rough night. I was laughing my ass off.
You know that.
>> I thought you didn't. You weren't sub to my channel.
>> Because you jealous people get jealous
of people's money. That's
>> why you keep talking about money.
>> You said you don't care about money. And
ever since I joined this panel, all
you've done is talk about money.
>> You know what I'm saying, PJ? Anyone
with a job even on minimum wage gets way
more than 1K a month. No, they don't.
And LJ don't have a job.
>> You don't have a job.
>> Yeah, they do. How much is minimum wage?
>> But you don't have a job.
>> How much is minimum wage? I'm asking you.
>> You don't have a job.
>> Yeah. You don't know cuz you never
listen. One second. One second. You
don't have a job.
>> I know. I don't need a job.
>> You mate, you're on benefits.
>> I don't need a job. Okay. What? Okay.
You think I'm on the board? One second.
One sec. One sec. You live off the benefits.
>> Why are you talking about money still?
You said you don't care about people's
money. No, I don't point out why you lie so much.
>> Here, all you've done is talking about
money, Pete. The reason I understand why
you lie so much jealousy.
>> Yeah, jealous of you.
>> To Joe's money is way
>> I've got more money than you and Joe. Try again.
>> I've got more money than both of you.
Try again. [clears throat]
>> What? Prove it.
>> Listen, you've got all of this money,
but you beg on the internet. Make it
make sense about money. Make it make
sense. You got about money.
>> He's got all of this money, but he begs
on the internet about money. Make it
from my joint about money.
>> One second. Make it make sense for one
>> You want to talk about something else?
>> Yeah. Yeah, we could talk about
something else. But in the future, if
you're going to lie about having money,
make it make sense. Make the story make
>> Like your story. Does your story make
the story make sense?
>> You get money.
>> If you're going to lie,
>> did you get money?
>> How many hustles?
>> The story makes sense.
>> You said the other day, okay, forget
about money, but you begged. Forget
about money. the other day that you had multiple hustles.
>> Literally make it makes sense. And you
know, right you buddy.
>> Listen, your I understand your autism is bad.
>> You keep banging on about money.
>> What is it? You sublet six properties
and you get free.
>> No, I don't sublet six properties.
>> You've never seen three grand and bump for your
>> I've never seen the lies.
>> I've never seen three grand
when he went to Vegas.
How do you think when you went to Vegas?
>> You bro, you went to Oh, about that. You
went to Vegas for five nights. >> Yeah.
>> [ __ ] hell. You went to Vegas for five
nights. Did you not,
>> Pete? I did indeed. That's all people.
>> You went to Vegas for five nights?
>> Yeah. For five nights. That's all people
shitty. You listen. Can I ask you a
question? One second. This is your life
experience. Why didn't you show us the hotel?
>> Why didn't you show us the hotel?
>> Why would I show the hotel for people to
try the [ __ ] hole that you were staying
at? It was a cheap hotel.
>> Did I not hotel, bro? Did I not put
pictures up by show the hotel?
>> Did I not put pictures up while I was
lying by the pool?
>> You didn't. No, I mean the hotel. You
didn't show cuz it was a shitty hotel.
How could you go and not show the hotel? >> Okay.
>> What? No. Why? Why? I'm asking you.
>> You You're saying there about five
nights in Vegas? You know, most people
only go, bro. Every most you [ __ ]
[ __ ] You know, you don't stay in
hotels. You've never been abroad and
stayed in a hotel. So, how would you
>> been abroad? Okay. Okay.
>> I said, wait, now think about what I'm
saying here. I said you've never been
abroad and stayed in a hotel.
>> Okay. I've never been abroad and stayed
in a hotel.
>> Yeah. You stayed in a host when you went
[clears throat] to Amsterdam
>> and you spent a whole day in washing the
one pair of pants that you had with you.
>> So, why didn't you show everyone your hotel then?
>> Cuz I didn't want to get thrown out.
>> Cuz it's a [ __ ] hole. kind of like the
same happened to you when you went to
Where was it? You were and you got
thrown out of the hotel. Newcastle.
>> Yeah, it was a nice hotel, wasn't it?
>> No. What was it? [ __ ]
>> It was a lovely hotel. It had a balcony.
I've showed all my hotels.
>> You've never showed your hotel cuz it's
a [ __ ] hole.
>> It had a balcony.
>> You know what I'm saying? You've never
shown M. You need to gamble so you can
go on a night out. That's your life, not mine.
>> Nope. That's literally your life, not a balcony. Barbadness. >> Yeah,
>> a hotel with a bar. Anyway, as I said,
you're going to be Can we see some
content next week?
>> When you've been abroad, Pete, all you
stayed in in Amsterdam was
>> we see some content next week.
>> So, it was a hostel.
>> Can we see some content next week?
>> Why are you repeating yourself?
>> Cuz you're not skinned anymore cuz you
won. I'm happy. Can we see some content?
>> Some drink. Wait, now you're talking
about people's money again. You said you
don't care about people's money.
>> I don't. I'm just saying that you're not
anymore. But this is now again this is
you circled back to it.
>> You said you don't care about people's money.
>> You are an absolute life's loser.
>> Oh my god.
>> You're living with your mom at 28. No
driving license, no girlfriend, no life,
no friends. What a life.
Not a single friend to your name.
>> Yep. That's it. Repeater. Repeat.
>> What are you doing, Pete? What What's
your plans for this year?
>> I seen somebody write a comment and you
said nothing. You lied.
>> What have you done in 2026?
>> What have you done in 20 years?
>> Absolutely nothing.
>> What the [ __ ] Absolutely nothing.
>> What have you done in 20 years?
>> In 20 years.
>> What the [ __ ] have you done? Nothing.
>> In 20 years,
>> you've done nothing.
You've done nothing. [laughter]
>> Pete has absolutely nothing planned for 2026.
>> You need to get yourself a little job.
You know what? I think you need to get
yourself a little job.
>> Here we go. Here's the repeating again
cuz his mom said that to him.
My mom told me to get a job.
>> Your mom said maybe you need to get a
little job and get another house.
>> My mom's never said that to me.
>> She told me she said it to me.
>> My mommy never said that to me.
>> Again, here comes the autism voice.
>> No, she's never said that to me.
>> Again, here comes the autism.
>> So, that's not good.
>> Listen, listen. How comes we've never
seen you with a friend?
>> All these lies. All these lies.
>> We never seen you with a friend in the
world. We've seen me with friends.
>> We've seen me with multiple friends.
random people on nature.
They weren't random people. You did
random people. I've been seen with the
same people multiple random people. >> Okay.
>> Okay. Right. Is everyone listening? So
army lads. If if PJ puts up army lads,
>> if PJ puts up two videos with the same
people in it, two different videos with
the same people in it. I'll give him the
money for my multiple times.
>> I'll give you the I'll go and claim
tomorrow and I'll give it to you. I
don't need what the [ __ ] are you going with
multiple times with multiple fans just
like you said you said that you double
money that you didn't double any money
have you mate listen you said the same
thing with the money you didn't double
>> you don't have no mates you talk to
people on the internet that will never
meet you due to fear and anxiety they
will never meet you will never meet you
>> have you met any social anxiety
They've got social anxiety.
>> Have you met any of the people you talk to?
>> Yeah, I have actually.
>> Who? Who?
>> I've met [clears throat] Charlie.
Unworthy clock. I've met Toasty. Yeah.
Who have you met?
>> And wait, how many times did they meet
you once and then they never want to
meet you again? It's kind of like
>> never met you once.
>> It's kind of like even worse then, isn't
it? Because women ain't got no meet you
once and then they never want to see you again.
>> Yeah. Yeah.
>> That's it.
>> You're just a self. You are
>> Frasier all
never wanted to see you again.
>> I mean I mean I doxed Fraser so
>> and then they never wanted to see you
again. That's mine.
>> You've never even had any friends. So
you're even worse.
>> You went to Newcastle. You went to
Newcastle to meet Triple H,
>> you know.
>> And yeah, but Trip didn't want to meet you.
>> Yeah, but Triple H has got to meet you.
>> Yeah, but he's got anxiety. So
>> who was it? Was it money? He met you as
well, didn't he? I never wanted to meet
Jig and after
>> Can I ask you why does why do people
join your panel?
>> That's crazy. Why would you know if
people join my panel or not? So you
don't watch my channelics.
>> You don't watch my channel. So how would
you know who joined my channelics on your channel? >> Oh my channel.
>> You said you never watch my channel.
>> You said you don't watch my channel. So
how would you know? Is it because
they're a bunch of spastics? How would
you know who joins and who doesn't?
>> Is that what it is? How would I know?
Because Do you want me to answer? I
cannot. How do I know when I don't go?
>> You watch my channel. That's how you know.
>> Do you know Do you know how I know?
Because my channel and you claim you don't.
>> Because it's been the same people.
>> You watch my channel and you claim you don't.
>> It's just been the same people for
years. So, one live stream is the same.
>> Can you give me your m number so I can
live stream is literally the same. It's
the same spastics every day
>> because I'm telling you since got your
money stopped your mental health is you
keep telling yourself that but I've got
more money than you've
got more money than me. Yeah.
>> I've got more money than you and Joe but
you keep telling yourself more money
than me telling yourself that.
>> But you had three boiled eggs for your
dinner. Couple more. What did I What did
you eat today?
>> I had a I had a 33 pound takeway today.
What did you have? did three boiled eggs
a couple of weeks before Christmas for
you when you got
>> takeway today.
>> I had a roast pork dinner.
>> So, you had a roast pork dinner? I had a
33 pound takeaway.
>> So, I'm beating you, aren't I? [laughter]
>> What does that prove?
>> So, you know they they do you know what
they call your watch? LT said what they
called your watch. You know that? A poor man's Rolex. What?
>> A poor man's Rolex. [laughter] This this
coming from the man who's never owned a watch.
>> A poor man's Rolex. Is that what he call it?
>> A man who has never owned a watch.
>> I don't like watches. No, I don't. I
don't I don't like watches.
>> You can't afford one, Pete. It's okay.
>> I can't afford a watch. Okay. I can't
afford the watch. I don't like watch.
>> Pete, listen. If you go out and buy the
watch that I have.
>> I don't like watches. I don't want a watch.
>> Listen, you go buy the watch I have,
I'll refund you the money, then return
the watch, and you're up.
>> Do you want to show us your under quick.
>> You want to show us your wardrobe? [laughter]
>> Hey, let's see your wardrobe. I'll show
you my wardrobe. Let's see who's got
more designer clothes.
>> See your wardrobe?
>> Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah. Let's see.
Let's see who's got more designer clothes.
>> Why could you have two years two uh
Stone Islands that are 2 years old?
>> No, no, no, no. I've got designer jeans,
trainers, designer tops. We should We
should show each other's wardrobes.
>> You've got that years old. You're still
wearing You're still wearing True
Religion. your skin. You're still
wearing true religion
>> wearing greens that are 2 years old.
That's a madness.
>> You know,
>> you haven't bought any new store liners,
have you? Since Red Star got your money stopped.
>> Well, Red Star never got my money stopped. [laughter]
>> You keep telling yourself that.
>> Listen, listen, listen. If you've got my
money, if he's got my money stopped, why
have I still got more money than you? It
doesn't make sense. So, why have I still
got more money than both of you? [ __ ]
got more money. Wait, why are you
talking about how much money people have
never got my money stopped? I already
told the story multiple times. He didn't
get my money stopped.
>> You said you don't talk about people's
money. You don't care about the story
multiple times talking about people's
money. I put a court letter up.
>> Why are you talking about people's money for?
>> He didn't get my money stop. Why do you
keep lying to yourself? It's not good
for your mental health.
>> You and him need to stop lying to
yourself. Not one person on this
community has ever got my money.
>> What happened there? Okay, let's change
the subject. Wait, wait, let's change
the subject. Why?
>> Even if you did, I still have more money
than you and him. So,
>> no. Okay. Yeah. I thought you weren't
coming on here all of 2026. >> Huh?
>> I thought you weren't coming on YouTube
all of 2026.
>> Yeah, cuz it's the same people, same story.
>> Yeah, but what I'm saying is you left
the other day and said, "Right, I'll see
you in 2027." And you've been
>> to own you
>> every single day, multiple times.
>> Yeah. Anyways, you're boring now. Bye-bye.
This guy is so boring, bro.
Oh, look, man. This gets all the viewers
in. What the [ __ ] 48 people watching. That's lovely. Yeah.
All right, Timmy, do you want to join?
Bro, this guy is boring.
This guy is boring as [ __ ] man. Timmy,
do you want to join?
[ __ ] hell, lad. Oh,
a poor man's Rolex, they call it, Mr. Bean.
A poor man's Rolex.
That is funny as [ __ ] it. A poor
man's [laughter] Rolex.
Is that what they called it this to be? >> [laughter]
>> Do you remember LT the other day, Mr. B?
What did you What did you call LT, Mr.
B? A [ __ ] in it. [laughter]
Oh, that's funny, bro. What do you call
him? A fug. [laughter]
Poor man Rolex.
They do. I heard they do call it a poor
man's Rolex. He knows that I'm right
about what I'm saying as well.
The guy's making fun out of £1,200 a
month. He doesn't even get £1,200.
He doesn't even get £1,200 a month.
[ __ ] me, lad. Good.
I almost was Let's [clears throat]
get some money out tomorrow and just
embarrass these people against even
Howard. But it's not worth it.
It's not worth it, lad. You know what I mean?
No. Where's Filthy Ben, man? I want
Filthy Ben on here. Ben. Filthy. Filthy
Ben. Same people, same story. See you
next year. Triple H. He actually went
off for a year as well, didn't he? Same
people, same story. He said it on Timmy's.
Same people, same story. Tim, see you
next year. [laughter]
Filthy Ben. Yeah,
same people, same story.
Oh, I love that, bro. That is class.
Not saying that's that's a classic.
That is funny as [ __ ] bro. Same people, same story. [laughter]
What does it mean by the same story?
Like arguments, isn't it?
Six years. It's been longer than six years, mate.
It's been longer than six years. The same people
needs to be different and it needs a mix
up, you know, like a mixture. Yeah, man.
Same people, same story. Yeah, he took a
year off it in it. I want to take a year
off it, but I think it's too late now.
You need to literally do it from the 1st of January.
Otherwise, it don't count.
You have to literally leave from the 1st of January.
So, now it's too late now to be able to
do that. You have to say on the 1st of January,
same people, same story. See you next year. Yeah,
that's mad. He actually took a year off
with it. That's mad. Yeah.
Yeah. He was from Sunderland.
That Ryan Hansen was from Sunderland.
Yep. And you're the biggest dread going.
You're the biggest one going.
Yeah, I do remember him. He's from Sunderland. Yep. Yeah.
Same people every day.
It's the same people every day.
That's five people in this community
without a family on Christmas.
That was Monty's last live stream,
wasn't it? I've just gone live. Yeah. To
see basically who's on here Christmas.
And if anyone's watching me now, that
shows that they've got no family in it.
I was dead, bro.
I was dead. Yeah. He says that they've
got no family life.
He says that's five people in this
community without a family.
That's what he said, Trip. Is it?
That's five people in this community
without a family. I was dead, bro.
Yeah, he got bullied off, didn't he?
up. What Mont want his live stream?
Well, he's deleted it.
Mom, did you have the ticker?
It's nice, isn't it? Really?
I gave Laney some chicken ticker.
Well, so man, what time you done it on Christmas?
Was that enough? Huh?
It's nice to tickle, man.
I like chicken ticker.
I've been defeated, haven't I, Grezy? I
just can't get motivated anymore, bro.
Grezy, I just can't get motivated, brother.
I just can't get motivated anymore, bro.
I wonder what changed in them years. Eh,
I think cuz I've got older in it. You
see the you see the world for what it is.
I'd rather just sit around all day and complain. Bro,
I still used to go out January last uh
last year. I was still doing stuff.
Maybe I stayed in for a while. I don't know.
It's very hard to get motivated, bro. You know,
it's so hard to let go of the resentment, bro.
The resentment and [ __ ] It's very hard
to let go of it this time.
These people in this community are so
autistic, bro. They just say the same
[ __ ] every day. Everyone's skin. It's
just the same repeated [ __ ] on here, isn't it?
Maybe that's why Ben come off of here
for a year.
Everyone's skin in it.
It's so so disabled, is it, bro?
Everyone is skinned to these skinn
people, isn't it? Is that what the Is
that what the saying should be?
It's literally the same thing, isn't it? Every day.
Everyone is skin now to [clears throat]
these people that sit on YouTube 24/7
but everyone else is skin not these people.
Isn't that a madness? Eh,
skin. Even though you've shown them
money multiple multiple times, they
still sit there and call you skin cuz
they're skint themselves.
So boring. And the only the only people
that are skin is them. And that's why
they're on here 24/7. Have you noticed
they weren't able to answer any of the
things I asked them? Because it's the
truth. If everyone else is skin, why are
they sat on YouTube every day hating?
They can't answer it. They can't answer
it cuz they know I'm correct. Triple H.
They know that I'm correct.
Everything they say is just about themselves.
Everyone else's skin, everyone else's
everything. Everyone else is being put
down by these people.
That's that's what they do. They've got
nothing new or good to say about anyone.
And I made I made that I made that
saying up, by the way. They literally
just slag people off their whole life
that they don't know what what bums are they, bro.
It doesn't matter. I don't know why they
keep calling people skin themselves. I
don't know why they keep calling people
skin. I don't know why they keep doing
it for 15 years. I don't know what they
get out of it.
Yeah, they're always slagging someone
off as well. You'll notice that, bro.
[snorts] They're always slagging someone off.
It's cuz where they failed at everything
in life, they have to come and hate on
the internet every day. So weird.
What the [ __ ] bro?
It is very boring. That's why a lot of
people left, I think. You know,
that's none of your business.
You went out last night. Nice. How much
did you spend?
You don't need to know how much I have.
All we hear about is money every day
with these people, Steven Howard. It's so autistic. Autistic community
that just talk about money every day.
No, it won't get them to stop talking
about money. They've been shown
thousands and thousands and they still talk [ __ ]
No, it won't. Even if you show them,
right, listen. Even if you show them
right now a million pound, they'd still
call you skint every day.
It's cuz they're skint themselves. So
what they're saying is they're not
really calling you it. They're calling
themselves it. They skint themselves. So
they're trying to project that onto you.
You could literally show them you could
show them a million pound in cash,
right? You could have the whole room
showed with money and they'd still be like, "Nah skin,
you can say whatever, bro. You don't
know how much money I have."
Why are they so obsessed with other people's life?
You don't know how much money I have, bro.
You spent £100.
That is it. Do you know what? Do you
know what? Yeah.
You know what's weird about this? Yeah.
All they do is talk about other people.
Well, they slag over other people. They
talk about other people. Do you know?
It's just that it's just people that are
just obsessed with other people's lives
cuz they ain't got a life of their own.
So weird, is it, bro? So weird.
You don't know how much money I have.
And I don't care about money, bro.
You really think I give a [ __ ] It's
like when people was on Lord J saying,
"Oh yeah, Laney's in for a rough night.
What? Because someone won money?" You
really think everyone's like you people? Seriously?
I don't care about money, bro.
I think if I saw someone with like a
good-looking woman, that would probably trigger me.
That kind of stuff would trigger me to
be fair, but not money.
That would probably trigger me more than
say what, bro?
Say, "I don't care."
Then just say, "What?" Yeah.
I like How hard can it be? He goes on
large, but he's actually a cool guy. See,
like I [snorts] said, you can tell the
ones on here that's actually got a life
and they don't have a life. Like people
like B, all night spas,
they like have nothing.
They don't need to know how much money I have.
have. They don't need to know anything
about my financial circumstances. They
need to worry about their own life
and their own content. Isn't that right,
Stephen Hour? They need to worry about
their own life and their own content if
they've got any, which they don't.
All they need to worry about is their
own life and their own bank account.
Yeah, he did come to my old house. He's
actually a cool guy. Like, how hard can it be?
People like Jo, All Night, Spaz, uh, Red
Star, they have got nothing in their
life, but do not let them try and tell you otherwise.
People like Ben, how hard can it be? Um,
who else? There's been a few other
people that they they've actually got a
life outside of YouTube. And that How
Hard Can It Be don't even like me
anymore, bro? Cuz But I can be real and
still say stuff, you know? But these
other people like Jo, they really have
got nothing but jealousy every day to
someone that they don't know. That's
that's that's really that's really them, bro, you know.
Oh, and Charlie as well. Yeah, Charlie's
cool as well. Yeah, I forgot about
Charlie. Yeah, so these people are the
ones that like have actually got a life
and but the others like V and they ain't
got no life, bro. You go on Timmy's, you
will see them doing what they do every day.
The time they they wake the time they
wake up to the time they go to bed.
And that's that, you know. Yeah, man.
Why do I need to tell these people how
much money I've got? Why do they tell me
how much they've got? Why do they show
what they look like?
I can't even brush my teeth. I brush I
brush my teeth three times a day. Have
you got anything new or anything good to
say about anyone
but just writing negative crap on the
internet all day every day?
This is what I don't understand yet.
They they they sit on the internet every
day writing negative crap about people
that they don't even know. They're
life's losers. They can't tell you
nothing. I'm telling you, bro. They
literally can't. That's why they don't
bother me no more. You know, even when
they stalk me on Reddit, you know, they
literally sit on the internet writing
negative crap about people that they
don't know every day. That's that's
their life, bro. They're not even saying
negative stuff about themselves.
That is mad.
No, I never said that. I brush my teeth
three times a day.
They've got nothing better than to just
write negative crap about people they
don't know every day. What have they
really got in their life? Ask yourself that question.
Nothing, bro. Nothing. >> [snorts]
>> I brush my I brush my um You're supposed
to be encouraging people, not demotivating them.
Isn't that right, Steven? They're
supposed to be uh encouraging people,
not demotivating them.
But it's like I said earlier, where
they're at a level in life, they want to
bring other people down to their level.
Do you not understand? Uh,
that's that, bro.
Does that make sense? I hope it makes
what I'm saying.
I brush my teeth three times a day, bro.
So, I don't actually think I'm
depressed. I think I'm just actually uh
when I'm I think I'm actually just
bitter cuz I brush my teeth three times
a day cuz obviously I don't want
toothach and [ __ ] So, I do brush my
teeth in that.
I think I'm just bitter and mad at the world, bro.
I think there's a bit there's a bit of
there's a big difference.
You people constantly tell lies like
pretending that you got a life yet
you're sat on YouTube 24/7. V.
That is V behind that account. I can
smell him a mile off again. Autism
V. Get stuffed. I know that's you.
You're too obvious. I know you're typing
pattern. Get a life. [gasps and sighs]
Stop it. He's another Ly Mong. Smell your Moff.
Yeah, they are self-projected losers.
Definitely. definitely self project to
losers. How hard can it be? He's all
right, though. He's actually a cool guy,
bro. He actually is all right.
Now, he come my door with a coke and a
football bet. And I've actually spoke to
him on the phone. He's all right, bro.
Right. And when I was off of here for
two, three weeks, you people still on here.
Right. You people was on here for two
Yeah. But when I was off here for 3
weeks, you people still on here.
I'm not reacting to it. I know that
that's me while behind that account. [snorts]
Yeah. Yeah. Charlie's all right. Um
Ben's all right. How hard can it be? Uh
I wonder what happened to that Hugh guy
that went on Monty's. Do you remember
him? Then he started talking [ __ ] behind
my back and I never saw him again since
he stopped going on Monty's. Remember that Hugh
was it Jansen cell or some [ __ ]
You remember him ain't it Greavvesy?
You know the real ones the run the ones
that have got a life they either don't
come back or they pop on or they pop or
they pop on every now and then. You can
tell the ones that have got a life. Go
that way. One here.
Do I go on with Joker? Yeah, he's all
right, but he's a bit of a troll. Yeah.
Uh, what was I saying? I forgot to say now.
Yeah, L2 is all right, but a lot of the
stuff he says doesn't make sense.
A lot of the stuff that he says doesn't
really make a lot of sense. But I mean, yeah.
Nope. I'm not going out this month and
I'm not going out next month.
I'm done with it all, bro. Very very
done with it all.
Very very done for it for a very very forever.
Trust me, I won't be going out nowhere.
You know, I'm already a loose cannon.
I'm already a loose cannon, bro. I don't
need any more bad experiences. Trust me.
Trust me, lad.
It ain't happening, man.
I ain't going out this month. I'm not
going I probably will just never go out
again to be honest with you, bro. Like,
so I might be letting you down, bro, but
I will not be going out again. I don't think
because if someone tries getting rude to
me again or a white night, I will not
take be taking no [ __ ] And I not that I
do anyways, like I tell them about
themsel anyways, but I mean I will take
it to the extreme
because I'm not in the mood as it is. I
mean, I don't take their [ __ ] anyways,
but they will I will seriously hurt one of them.
And it doesn't matter who it is. So,
there's no point me involving myself
with that toxic [ __ ] There's no point.
And I'll probably just end up telling a
woman about herself and drawing
attention. So, there's there's no point.
There generally generally generally is no point,
you know? And that's me, bro. There's no
starting again. There's no there's none
of that [ __ ] I shouldn't have to be
trying again. I'm 28 years of age. I
don't have energy like I used to. 24, 25.
I don't even have the energy or desire
to, you know, people have got different levels. Yeah.
Some people try for a month, they give
up. Some people never try. Some people
try for 6 months. Um, some people like
me try for years and give up. Everyone's
got different levels, you know.
And obviously I'm I'm where it's at
where I will just never try again.
Everyone's at like different stages in
it. So that's that.
And it's only down from now as well cuz
I'm 28. It's not even like I'm 24 25
anymore. So I mean it's only it's only
going to be get worse from now.
So if you think about it.
Yeah. Skin that's repeating, bro.
Yeah, they can miss me all they want. I
don't give a [ __ ]
Yeah, that's the that's that's that's um repeating, bro.
That skin thing is repeating.
I hate the double standards. I hate everything. So yeah,
waiting on the pit. That's self
projecting, bro. That's you talking
about yourself. You're not talking about
me. You don't know how much money I have.
You must be talking about yourself, bro,
cuz that's not my life.
These people think people need to be skint depressed.
That's how autistic they are and how
obsessed they are with money that they
think people need to be skinned to be uh
I don't know bro
nothing is it nothing you can do nothing
we can do Uh,
my lies are crazy. Yeah, you keep
telling yourself that and I'm not on Reddit 24/7.
You people on YouTube 24/7 from the time
you wake up to the time you go to bed.
If if you people right right listen if
you if you people right wasn't I would
be sat here talking to myself. I'm a
lion, Stephen Howard. If you people
didn't have a life, if if you people had
a life. Yeah. If you people actually had
a life, I'd be sat here talking to
myself. Think about it. You have been on
here with me. So, it says a lot about
you, doesn't it? It must say a lot about
you cuz you're also watching me. So, at
the end of the day, you're proving
yourselves as well. If you think about it,
you're sat on here watching me. You're
not doing any um productive.
You're sat on here with me. So, what
does that say about you?
Think about it. I should be talking to
myself. Theoretically, if all you had a
life, I should be sat here talking to
myself. But I'm not. You're on here with
me. And you've been on here with me the
past couple of days. So, what does that
say about you calling me? You're calling
me. I'm not calling you.
You, these people come on here, Stephen,
and they start insulting me first. I
don't come on here start insulting them
unless this Joe F has put a [ __ ]
community post about me. So they're
actually coming on here insulting other
people every day. I'm not insulting them
until they insult me.
Who starts with the skin comments? They do. Yeah. So
I should be talking to myself.
I said to this guy, "Not at all. Not at
all. You're just white knighting." Then
they turned around and said, "Okay,
incel." I said, "Do you call women that
complain about men an incel?" thought. So
that's the truth really, you know,
that's that's the way people need to
really think about this stuff. Yeah. Is
that we all know that if you had a
vagina between your legs, they would not
be calling you any kind of names. So
never kind of never change never ever um
take the stuff that these people say
personally because it's a gender thing.
They are sexist. They are biased. you
know, they are blaming you because
you're a man. Um, and when you realize
that, you can't even get mad at it.
It's a gender thing. It's not a personal
thing. If you had a [ __ ] in between your
legs, everyone would feel sorry for you.
And that is the way it is. So, you know,
that's like that's just that's just no
one really cares.
These people don't drag me down, bro.
They drag themselves down.
They don't They don't drag me down. They
drag themselves down
really on here. They don't drag me down.
I can only drag myself down. These
people don't drag me down. Why do you
think I'm not asked about these people?
Why do you think they're not triggering
me? Cuz I was in a bad mood the other day
as it was. That's why I'm not I'm not in
a Well, I am in a bad mood, but you
know, like bad for the mood.
So, this guy, can he can he I want him
to basically uh reply to me.
Do you call women that complain about
men in in the cell? Thought so. Cuz it's
the truth, isn't it?
That's the truth, bro. They're only
blaming you cuz you're a man.
And oh, do women owe you something?
Well, yeah, they do owe you something. Exactly.
I think society needs to change to be fair.
Yeah, women do owe you something.
Just like your boss would owe you
something. Just like your boss would owe
you something if you worked a whole
month and they decided not to pay you.
They do owe you something.
Mhm. Yeah, they do owe you something. So
whenever people ask me that, um, Steven
Howard, well, yeah, they do owe you something. So yeah. Yeah.
Well, it is. Well, they do owe you
something. If you put if you've put
effort into dating and you've done what
most people are scared of doing, etc.,
they do owe you something.
They do owe you something and I stand by
that. It's not a right or wrong thing.
It's just opinion and my opinion is that
they do. So that's that. It's like they
they think men owe them something.
And [snorts] you know when I was
thinking about it more and more and more
the double standards that's another
thing that made me give up like how unfair it