Sorry about that. My thing froze. Yeah.
Yeah, man. My [ __ ] Streamyards that's
freaking telling me something, bro. I
run out. Streamyards.
I was talking to myself like 10 minutes, bro. Jeez.
[ __ ] you now.
>> [clears throat]
>> Yeah, I think I want to come off this
thing for a little bit anyways after today. Bro,
my brain's a bit scrambled again.
These people need to create a different
atmosphere. It's just same old [ __ ]
same old repeat people.
This is mad.
These people saying to this guy, you
need to scrap this, you need to scrap that.
It's not the man, it's the women that
are the problem.
They are stuck up in this country.
Can't believe they're trying to blame
this poor guy. Anyways, bro.
Oh, they're just all stuck up NPCs. Why
does this keep coming up on my Instagram?
Why the [ __ ] does this keep coming up on
my [ __ ] these approaches and
[clears throat] these [ __ ] women just
being [ __ ] Why do I keep saying
this [ __ ] bro?
Still me and get a boyfriend.
[ __ ] hell, bro. It's annoying just
look at just watching that [ __ ]
Why does it Why is it coming up with my Instagram?
I can't remember the last time this guy
got a number.
Oh, here's another one.
Oh my god, they're so
Listen, bro. I am watching this guy and
they are saying exactly the same thing.
This woman is a M. I've just watched
this video. This M woman is saying she
got a boyfriend. She is a [ __ ] ma.
She has so much [ __ ] You know, the
thing is, right, you could just tell
they're lying by the way saying it as well.
They're not even like they talk so much [ __ ]
that you could actually tell like
genuine people that they are full of
[ __ ] they are so full of [ __ ] you know
I don't even like watching it bro I
don't even know why it comes out just
pisses me off watching it you Funk madness.
You could tell they're full of [ __ ] as
well because it's not even like they're
getting combo that, oh, I'm married.
Like, they're actually so full of [ __ ]
They ain't got no boyfriends at all,
bro. They talk so much [ __ ]
I hate seeing this on my channel, bro.
On my um Instagram.
Why does it come up, bro?
And this is not even me. This is happening to
they ain't got no boyfriend.
Most women are single. Most people are
Well, nah, 50/50 really.
I don't know the actual statistics. I
don't know, bro. To be fair, I just know
there's loads of single people out there.
Who's their boyfriend, bro? Casper the ghost.
That's another thing they do on Reddit.
They report you.
Well, there's a lot of single women out
there and there's a lot of single men
out there, mate.
There's no way every guy woman this guy
is approaching has got a boyfriend.
They're full of [ __ ] You know, you can
actually tell the genuine ones,
which is Terry, by the way. That's Terry
behind that account.
They're [ __ ] I watch. Why is this
even coming up on my [ __ ] thing, bro?
Pisses me off just watching it,
you know. They are so full of [ __ ] They
ain't got no boyfriend, bro. [ __ ]
annoying even watching it.
Surprised it never used to annoy you and
it used to happen to me to be fair. It
annoys me watching it happen to other
people. Pisses me off, bro.
I might have to [ __ ] unfollow that
guy on Instagram to be fair.
They all say the same thing.
How do people say that these women are
not the same? They literally say the
same thing. Well, one second, bro.
Good. They've got a boyfriend. They are
literally all the [ __ ] NPC. Same.
People are starting to think they're
[ __ ] AI now, bro. That's how much the
same they are.
I guess these people are still young.
That's why it it doesn't bother them to be fair.
Another stuck up bit. What's up? Oh
Yeah. If you say anything bad about
women on Reddit, they report you.
[ __ ] hell, bro. Peter Belly was wrong
and was born in the wrong era.
I think people that have kids nowadays
are evil, you know.
You know, I think they're evil people
that have kids nowadays,
knowing how hard it is, uh the cost of
living and the way society is,
you know. And then if the child's a boy,
then when the when the boy grows up,
he's going to have real struggles
dating. Unless he gets, you know, lucky
school or something, you know, it's
going to probably be even worse, you
know, in 20 years time. [clears throat]
>> Poor [ __ ] If that child's a boy, poor
That's what I can say. >> Yeah. Oh, [ __ ]
Is there anyone normal in these interactions?
Like once you've met one, you've met him more.
I had I had an Indian
Oh yeah, that's that that's that tenant.
I had to block her. She was being an ignorer.
Yeah, I remember that tenant. I had to
block her from a few years ago. Don't
[ __ ] ignore me, you [ __ ] I had to
block her before I ended up saying something.
So like the mature thing was just to block them.
Yeah, I had an Indian lad.
Yeah, I saw some more approaching videos
from this guy on Instagram.
These women are still pretending they
got boyfriends, bro. Never changes, does
it? Never change. [ __ ] pisses me off
just watching it, lad. And it ain't even me.
It pisses me off just watching it, lad.
I don't know how you think it's fun.
It's [ __ ] depressing, bro. I'm
watching this guy do it and it's so depressing.
I don't know how you can find it fun. I
think it's [ __ ] depressing.
It pisses me off, bro.
I'm tired now, bro. I'm going to make
myself a tea in a bit.
No, not really.
I never did.
And all women are the same scum anyways.
So you can't crave people that are scumbags. Dirty scumbags
to be fair. And that's what they are. Dirty scum. Dirty scumbags.
There's no new 24 hours in police
custody. That sucks.
Yeah, women are evil. They truly are
I don't Do you know what I don't
understand is how people say they're not
all the same when they evidently are.
Because if you watch these guys approach
like different people. Yeah. From what
I'm watching, they all act the same way.
They literally act exactly the same way.
They've got the same attitude, the same mannerisms.
You know, even if you watch any of these
videos that pop up, I don't know how
they say that they're not all the same.
They're literally lying when they're saying that.
I don't know how people can say that.
They're literally not all the same. I
I'd love to know that how they can how
they can they're lying, bro. They are
literally all the same.
There's not one that's good out there.
You know, you've seen from the messages
as well what they've done multiple times. Yeah,
they're not. They are literally all the same scumbags.
They are, bro.
I'm a full-on [ __ ] misogynist, bro.
And I can actually generalize as well. I can. Oh, yeah.
And that's why I've got my approaching
videos. That's why I've got my little evidence pack
to show to people that don't believe me, you know. So
that just disproves everything they say
when you show them like approaches and
messages and [ __ ] Yeah.
Get what I mean, bro?
When are you out drinking next?
I'm going to know you out drinking this, Bob.
You're such an alcoholic [ __ ] you are.
Yeah. And I don't care. [snorts]
Yeah, I have seen it. And I don't care.
I don't get jealous of other people and
I don't care about money.
So that just goes to show how they don't
know me than people on that um on that uh
on that LJ live stream. Sorry, that Lord
J channel. They all think that people
are the same as them.
That's why they say that because they
think that like I'm not jealous of
anyone. I can't get jealous of people
that I don't know. And I and I don't
care about money either.
Uh [snorts] I don't care about money
either, you see. So stuff like that
doesn't bother me.
Only the disabled people on here
are jealous of people that they don't
know. See, like in in in normal society,
yeah, outside of this community, it
doesn't happen where people are jealous
of people that they don't know. But on
here, it does. So they think that
everyone's like them,
if that makes sense, cuz they're [ __ ]
spastics basically. So yeah,
just no lives.
Nothing new or good to say about anyone.
That's my new slogan if you haven't
heard it. And that's that.
They just come on every day. Hate him.
What the [ __ ] life today? Have they mad?
Yeah, I done a football bet yesterday.
Yeah, I don't know if it will, but
yesterday I lost 20. Yeah. [snorts] Yeah, man.
Anyone got any plans for next week?
I've [snorts] never won big on a
football bet before, bro.
I've won big on roulette, but
No, no, no.
If I want a football, if I want a big
football, I'd literally do nothing, bro,
with the money.
I do nothing, bro. Yeah.
Do I miss the casino? Nah, not really. No, bro.
Yeah. No, no, not really, bro. No,
I don't really care about gambling, bro.
I just had an urge on the 1 of January.
I don't really do it like that, bro. No. No, lad.
No, no, no, no. Yeah, bro.
I won't be out next week either.
Won't be out the week after that. Week
I don't actually see what the point of
life is, man.
Live to get bad experiences then die. That sucks. Yeah, bro.
I need a T, bro, but it's too cold downstairs, man. Oh,
never been [clears throat] in mommy's
box room in my life.
Are you still a fat ugly old man on
YouTube hating on people you don't know every day?
You still a fat ugly old man on YouTube
hating every day, huh?
See you later. No.
These people are [ __ ] bro.
take me four months to save £1,600. How
do you work that one out, man?
When I've already got more than that,
that don't make sense.
That don't make no sense.
No, it doesn't make any sense. Yes. Yeah,
[ __ ] Oh, bro.
Red Star is my biggest stalker.
Wow. If there was a loser that showed
they truly had nothing in life,
he would be the one, bro. He would be the one.
Uh, just my biggest stalker, bro. Just
my biggest stalker. But yeah, anyways,
nothing's going on, bro.
Just the same old [ __ ]
Fed up board.
I don't know.
I don't watch the [ __ ]
Don't watch the [ __ ]
I only watch Timmy really, which I need
to unsub from Timmy cuz that's the same
[ __ ] as well.
Oh no, here we go again.
Yeah, here we go again.
Yeah. I don't I don't watch him, bro.
I have a lot of people obsessed with me
on this community, lad.
A lot of people.
I think a lot of these people want my ass.
Tell you the truth.
really. That's nice. Money doesn't bother me.
Money don't bother me, bro.
Really doesn't. I I I'm not jealous of money.
I don't care about money. I don't care.
I can't get jealous of people that I
don't know like these people on here.
No, that's not me, bro. That's that's
No, I'm good, bro.
No, I'm good.
Just sick of women and [ __ ]
Just thinking of getting revenge.
Yeah, not depressed. I brush my teeth
three times a day.
No, they're not blocked. They're not
I don't know why they're not typing.
They're not blocked.
just sick of women and [ __ ]
My bad experiences and [ __ ] bro.
All the bad experiences, the leading on,
the piss taking, the lies,
just revenge, you know.
Oh, just to show you that like Yeah.
I'm not depressed in it. Yeah.
this the [ __ ] they've done over the years
to be fair
what they've done over the years you know
I'm going to go watch Oreo man in a bit
I want some more negativity bro I love
this [ __ ] Done. I love this [ __ ]
Depressed people don't brush their teeth.
Nope. Don't know what you're talking about.
I have no idea what you're talking about, mate.
Must be on the wrong channel.
I really need to get revenge, bro. But
it's trying to get one of them to meet
her. That's the thing.
Uh, he does it for a reaction. He didn't
get any of my money stopped.
He does it to try to get a reaction, but
it doesn't work. He never got any of my money stopped.
just a random woman
because it helps him sleep at night
telling himself that. But he's he's
never got any of my money stopped and I
got more money than him.
That's all this autistic community goes
on about is money. Is it autism and
obsession? I've noticed that as well.
All they talk about is money on here
and calling other people's skin when
they're skin themselves.
It really is a disabled community in it. Okay. Whatever. Yeah.
No. If he had anything in his life, he
wouldn't be stalking me 24/7.
Yeah. Okay, bro.
Brother, you you are all on benefits yourselves.
You are literally all on benefits yourselves.
calling people skin every day.
Why do you go on about money every day,
bro? Can I ask you that? Is it part of your autism?
And you never got any of my money stopped.
And that's why you don't get a reaction.
You ain't got no money. And like I said,
Red Star, the more you do this, the more
it proves my point.
The more it shows you've got nothing.
And that's why I love it. That's why I
don't react to it. Because the more you
do this, the more it shows I'm right
about you people having no family, no
life, no money.
So I I don't mind this stuff, bro, cuz
it shows that you really hate
yourselves. You got nothing in your
lives. No money, no nothing.
So I don't mind, bro. You can keep doing
this all you want. You did not get any
of my money stopped. That's why you
don't get a reaction. Explain the story
multiple multiple multiple times.
And it shows that you have got nothing
by doing this. Simple.
And that's that. That's literally that.
And you're saying about people claiming
benefits. You people claim benefits yourselves.
You're on YouTube 24/7. None of you work. So,
but yeah, you need to stop saying you
got people's money stopped when you
never got any of my money stopped. You
would never be able to do that.
You have never got any of my money
stopped. Why did it take you four years?
Why did it take you four years when you
knew I was subleting for four years?
Stop telling yourself that.
It's not good to lie to yourself and say
these things. You know that
I've got more money than you. I think
I've said this about 14 million times
now. This is the point of it being an
autistic community. This is exactly what
I'm saying. You'll say something to them
and then you have to explain it again
and again and again cuz it's that's the
part of it being a disabled community.
They are literally disabled on here.
That's what I'm saying.
When have I said that I'm loaded? You
come on here every day trying to say
that I'm skin and I've told you that
I've got more money than you when which
is a fact. When have I said that I'm loaded?
Why are you so interested in how much
money I've got?
Why are you so interested in what people
have got? You people in this community
every single day. Yeah, you're coming on
here slagging people off.
Why are you so interested in other
people's lives? I'm I'm wondering this.
Why are you so interested in what other
people have got? You know,
you people on here don't have a job. You
people on here do not have a job. You
are on here 24/7. Why are you so
interested in what other people have
got? Can you answer that question? I've
been asking questions all day and you've
not answered it. Jesus Christ. >> Hello.
>> So interesting how you people have got
>> PJ. Stop. Yeah, I'm good. I'm trying to
like have a man-to-man conversation with
you. I'm doing this out of love. PJ,
>> don't kick me out when I say this. Why
are you so bothered what people have got
in life? Why are you so
>> Okay, I'm kicking you now. See you
later. Bye. We're not having this. I'm
not talking to a [ __ ]
You were poor. I have the emails back.
You literally did not get any of my
money stopped. You never got none of my
money stopped. See you later. You did
not get any of my money stopped. Yes,
Red Star. You are skint. That's why you
stalk Peter belly every single day. Yes.
That's why you stalk Peter Belly every
day cuz you are skint. And it kills you
that you are skint. We know you're
skint. Stop [snorts] talking about yourself.
If you people weren't skimp right, you
wouldn't be on here doing this every
day. I stand by what I say. I stand by
my point. If you had anything in life,
you wouldn't be making accounts hating
on a 28-year-old every day. It just does
not happen. No matter how many times you
want to try to justify it, it just does
not happen. And I know any person that I
idolize does not come on YouTube hating
strangers every day. That's not someone
with a better life than you. You need to
always bear that in mind. I know it.
Anyone that anyone knows, everyone knows this stuff.
You literally did not get anyone's money
stopped. We've had the same conversation
multiple multiple times. I put the court
letter up multiple multiple times. You
did not stop anyone's money. Stop
telling yourself that.
You need to stop telling yourself that
you got my money stopped. You need to
stop lying to yourself because if that's
the case, I wouldn't be sat here with
more money than you. If you got any money stopped,
stalking and harassing every day is your
life. It just shows you're you're a
nobody. It just shows you're a bully victim.
That's why I love you doing this. I
actually love you doing this because it
shows what you are. You're embarrassing
yourselves. Like that guy um earlier
that was making free accounts to get
banned. It's showing everyone what you
are. That's why I love it.
You know that red star. Nothing but a
fat skin slob. And here you are. You're
just a fat skin ugly slob. That is
stalks people on YouTube every day
because you got no one. No girlfriend,
no money, no life. It's the truth. And
you've never had that. And you've never
had that. It's not even that you don't
have that. that you never have that
because you're on you are on the
internet every day stalking another man.
You've got nothing. It's clear to see.
It literally is clear to see, bro. You know,
you you are a loser, mate. Listen, you
people in this community are losers.
You are the biggest losers. Like I said,
you people are on here 24/7.
Like you people are the biggest losers.
You're Bro, listen. Like I said, listen,
listen. You have been on this community
for 15 years hating your life away. You
are the biggest losers. You would know
all about losers, lad. You would know
all about losers. You're the biggest
ones going like, how old are you people
on this? Okay, let's let's let's let's
cut this right now. Yeah. You people are
in your 40s every day on YouTube hating
people you don't know. You're no
strangers to the word loser. Like you're
no stranger, bro. Like listen listen,
brother. Listen listen. You
You are no strangers to the word losers.
You are in your 40s and you have got nothing.
nobody. You was on YouTube Christmas. No
family, no misses. You You're no
stranger to the word losers. Like facts.
You people are literally the biggest
losers going. And if you're not and if
you're not right, why are you on here
with me talking to me? It's the same
thing as I asked you earlier. You
couldn't answer it cuz everything that I
say to you people, you know it's the
truth. If I'm the loser, why are you on
YouTube all day stalking me, talking to
me? Come on, bro. Come on.
Yeah, you ain't got no work, bro. Being
on YouTube 24/7 is not work. You ain't
got a life.
Go back on your account, you sad
bastard. Like, like I said, by rights, I
should be talking to myself. There
should be nobody on this live stream.
But you're all on my live stream, so it
says a lot about you as well. So, by me
doing this, I'm also showing you up as
well for what you are.
Sad, sad, bitter losers. That's what a
lot of these people are on here. Bitter, bitter losers.
Sat on YouTube stalking someone every
day. What a loser.
Only a disabled loser would be able to
justify that. [ __ ] losers. And I mean
it when I say it. You hate yourselves
that much that you need to stalk people
on the internet every day. Jeez.
That's madness, bro. Oh [ __ ]
But I just blame your autism to be
honest. I mean, like I said, man, you
you you even you even stalk me on you
even stalk me on Reddit.
You even stalk me on Reddit. What is
your life, bro? What is your life? Come
on. Stalking men on the internet that
you don't know. Come on. Tell us what
your life is, bro. Come on. I'm all it is. you know,
stalking men on the internet that you
don't know. [ __ ] mad.
To be honest, it's it's so pathetic. You
actually got to laugh at it. You're
stalking men on the internet that you
don't even know every day. What a loser.
But only you people would think that's
normal. Only Only autistic people would
think that's normal. Only you people
would actually think that's normal
though, isn't it?
Because you're disabled,
which is okay. You know, it's fine.
Yeah, that's self projection, bro. We
all know that nobody nobody likes you
people. That's why you're s And then
I'll ask you the same question then. Why
are you on YouTube 24/7?
You know, why are you on YouTube 24/7?
You can't answer it because you know I'm
correct. That's why you can't answer it
because you know what I'm saying about
you is our truth. It's the truth. Like
the wrestler, you are on it from the
time you wake up to the time you go to
bed hated. You ain't got nothing in your
life. That's why you can't even trigger
anyone. You people in here, you can't
trigger no one because we know what you
all are about.
We knows what we know what you people
are about. So that's why you can't
trigger no one on here. We know you're
jobless. We know your skin. We know you
got no girlfriend. We know you got no
friends. We know you was on YouTube Christmas.
So it doesn't bother us what you say.
You laugh at me. That's nice, bro. But
let me guess get let me tell you
something right now. I get more laughs
out of you than you will ever get out of me.
You know, I get more laughs out of you
fat, ugly old men, than you'll ever get
out of me.
Yeah, I went live on Christmas for five
minutes to see if you was on on YouTube.
And I was right. You was on YouTube.
Yeah, there was a reason I went live for
5 minutes and it proved my point that
you was on a Christmas day despite
telling people that they ain't got this,
they ain't got that, they ain't got
this, they ain't got that. You know what
I mean? We know, bro. You people have got nothing.
You listen listen we you people have got
nothing. I'll repeat myself again. You
have been on YouTube for 15 years right
hating on people. You have got nothing.
The we crew have got nothing but
repeating and projecting for 15 years.
You have got nothing. Let that sink in
your brain. Yeah. You are in your 30s,
40s. You're batty old men. Listen.
Listen. your fatty wrinkly old men
losers that sit online every day. Yeah.
Lying in your own [ __ ] I would be very
surprised if any of you haters leave the
house. I would be very very surprised if
if you have left your house in the in
the in the past 6 months.
We the loser crew is that. Yeah. People
that don't even leave the house, lie
about on YouTube, self-projecting every
day. We are the losers. And if your if
your brain actually work properly, you
actually understand what I'm saying to you.
Yeah, that's facts, bro. Literally. Literally facts.
Don't you are no one to take the mole
high ground. You are dead beats. You
ain't even got hope. You know the
maddest thing is? Yeah. You ain't even
got hope. That's how damn bad you are
that you ain't even got hope. And then
you're telling people that you laugh at
other people. Get real, kid. You laugh at yourself,
you know. Okay. Okay. I'm 30. I'm this.
I'm that. Brother, you are in your 40s
and you haven't got any of that. How
about that? You are You are in your 40s
and you've got none of that. No job, no
money. That's you people. Like I've
said, you are on YouTube 24/7.
That's you people. No job or no money.
That is literally you people.
And that's why you come out with the
most randomest things cuz it's about
your own lives. You bounce off your own
lives. That's why you come out with,
"Oh, this person's got no money. This
person's got that." Because you're
talking about yourselves, but you're so
disabled that you don't even realize
that you've actually been doing this for 15 years.
Yeah. I'm going to put the link out now.
So, they're so disabled that they don't even realize
that, you know, that they're talking
about their own selves. This is the this
is the maddest thing about it.
I've never known a 28-year-old brother,
you're 48 and you've never even had sex.
It's repeating now. You people don't
have a girlfriend. You people have never
even had sex. I would say a lot of the
people on here are even virgins. Bro,
most of you are virgins and you're
talking about a relationship. Please,
now, bro. Come on. It's embarrassing.
Everyone's bored of this now. We're
bored of you little self-reflecting
virgins. It's very, very boring.
Like, brother, most of you people are
[ __ ] virgins. You know, we've seen
how V acts around women. You know, simple.
It's so being 48 and never having sex is
pretty much impossible. Really?
Why would it be impossible, bro?
Why would it be impossible? I know
someone that lost their virginity when
they were 40.
I mean, bro, it's not impossible. It
really is not impossible. There are
people I mean, we're talking I mean,
this is a disabled community, lad.
No. No. That's what you people do. No,
bro. What? You, bro? Come on, man.
That's you people. You're sat on YouTube
every day calling people skint when you
skint yourselves. And no matter how many
times people say that to you, like
you're on YouTube 24/7. The only skint
ones are you. Like that has been proven
many, many times. But even when it's
been proven to you, you you you still talk [ __ ]
You know, you you people on YouTube
24/7. That's not projecting. I've got
evidence of this. I've got evidence that
you people can't get off of YouTube
because you're skin. I've literally got the evidence.
Simple. You are on YouTube 24/7 fat
slobs with nothing going for themselves
trying to bring other people down to
that level that you're on. Listen. Why?
Okay. Listen, listen. Okay. Why is it
right every time I go on a live stream,
you're always slagging off people?
It's cuz of how you feel about
yourselves. You're trying to bring other
people down to your level. Every single
live stream I've gone on is full of haters.
You never got any of my money stocked.
You did not get any of my money stocked.
This red star is so desperate. He's got
nothing. He's got no one in his life.
This is this this this this goes to
prove it. This just goes to prove it.
You know, he really really has. He's
really jealous of me. Like, he's really
proven this, bro. He's really really
proven it. And listen, bro, before you
sit there and say I'm 30 and I'm this,
brother, you people are fat, ugly old
men. You're below me. So, stop talking
about me being almost 30. Brother,
you're in your 40s and you're fat, ugly
old men before you even try to say
anything about me. Yeah,
simple. And when I'm on here, you people
are on here with me. So, what does that
say about you? Another thing you can't argue against.
Yeah, that's another thing that you
can't argue against. You people are fat,
ugly old men. Do not even try to talk
about me, bro. You You You are not You
are past my level. Simple. Yeah.
Okay. So, what do you people do every
day then? Okay. Okay. Yeah, that's fair
enough. That's that that's not fair.
Yeah, that's fair. You can't be jealous
of someone on Reddit all day moaning.
Yeah, that's true. That's true. So, what
do you people do every day? Call people
skin on YouTube from the time you wake
up to the time you go to bed.
Really? Yeah. Yeah.
I mean, you people come on here every
day calling people skin, bringing people
down, hating on people.
Yeah. Yeah. That's what you people do.
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
Yeah. My autism, mate. I don't have
autism like you people. I don't sit on
the internet for 15 years calling people
skin. That's what you people do.
Autistic rants, mate. I've got I ain't
got autism like you. So, you must be
looking in the mirror.
Yeah, I don't have autism. I don't I'm I
don't have autism like you. So, you must
be looking in that mirror cuz you're the
one with autism, not me. You are the
ones that sit on the internet all day
calling people skin. Talk about autism.
Do you even do you even know the traits
of autism, lad?
Brother, you are on benefit yourself.
Brother, you are on benefit yourselves.
Bro, you people have been on here for 15
years repeating the same [ __ ] You know
all about autism. Stop projecting.
Bro, listen. Okay, bro. Every live
stream that you go on on this community,
it is the same repeating people. The
same regurgitated comments. Why is that?
Cuz you're [ __ ] autistic. That's why.
Cuz you're autistic.
You're just [ __ ] autistic. Fat ugly
downies. That's what you are. I went on
Timmy's earlier uh when I was on the
couch and it was the same [ __ ]
repeating people and you want to judge
other people. Really? Get a life, man. Seriously.
Seriously, man. Why are you on here 24/7
repeating yourselves if you're not
autistic? Answer it. You like to You
like to ask questions, but you don't
like to answer them. I've noticed that.
What the [ __ ] bro?
coming on here every day hating on
strangers. You know that would never
ever happen outside of this community.
You do realize that
madness. You people have got serious serious issues.
You've been doing this for years. You
know that as well. You've actually been
doing this for years.
Slagging off people on the internet that
you don't know.
calling people skint when you don't know
how much money people have. It's just
pathetic, isn't it? Really, really, really pathetic. Yeah. [ __ ] me.
You need to stop. Why do you come on the
internet hating on people every day?
My whole life is not No, no, no. My
whole life is not on the internet. You
don't know how much money I have. You
really, really, really don't. You
I've never had friends in school.
Really? Really? You keep telling yourself that?
You would have thought in 2026 you
people would have stopped hating on the
internet. See, I don't even re I don't I
don't even like care if it's negativity,
but you just like you you're just trying
to bring people down every day. I never
go in someone's chat and there's
anything new or nice said.
You know, I never ever see anything new
or nice said about anyone.
Nothing new or nothing nice said about anyone
on any channel.
It's all about
trying to bring people down to your
level, isn't it?
All about trying to bring people down to
your fat disabled level.
Isn't that right? Jesus Christ.
Always slagging someone off, aren't you?
I don't care about me. I'm not talking
about me. I'm talking about jealousy.
You're always slagging someone off. Have
you looked at yourselves once in a
while? You know, you you you know you're
doing that. Slagging people off. Mark, Belly,
uh, Bonnie, me. Have you took a good
look in the mirror at yourselves?
Have you looked at Have you looked at yourselves
and what you do on here every day?
You know, I'm I'm just I'm just
wondering that, you know,
one second, bro.
One second, man. Someone's just Yeah.
Why is he entitled for approaching
someone? One second. Someone just
replied to my comment.
Yeah, there's a lot of them, bro.
Get used to it. They're never going to go away.
They're never going to go away, lad.
That's their life, is it?
Popping on YouTube every day being
obsessed with a 28-year-old. That's
their life, lad. They'll never stop.
That's just their life, laddy. Yeah.
Just screen recording everything.
Why can't he interact with people with
Oh, that's that's self projecting.
That's literally self- projecting, bro.
Now you're Now you're just self- projecting
cuz you people don't even leave your house.
Yeah, that's stiff. That is self
projecting. You people don't even leave
your house. That is self projecting there.
Some of the stuff they say is vile.
Yeah. Just don't take no notice of it,
bro. These people have been bullied
their whole life. Without YouTube, they
have nothing. Without YouTube and
hating, they got nothing. Just leave
them to it, bro. You know,
they're just fat, ugly. No one's
nobody's most of them. There's some
there's some good people on here. This community,
there's some good people.
But that's what they do, lad.
This bitter, ugly people that's been
bullied their whole life.
And you can tell that. Yeah. Because
it's what they actually do on here.
Like hating every day. And I'm not even
talking about on my live stream. It's
like it's what they do. Always bullied. One sec.
Yeah, you people are ugly. Yeah. No
woman No women No woman replies to me.
Yeah. Really, bro? That's nice. But I've
been with women. I've been seen with
women on YouTube. Have you? If you want
to go by that logic.
If you want to go by that logic. I've
been with women and I've shown it on
YouTube. You people haven't.
[snorts] So yeah, I'm saying that you're
ugly. Yeah. Yeah. I am saying you're
I've already explained how you're ugly
as well. Multiple I've already explained it.
Why do you want people to explain the
same stuff to you, man? Come on. [snorts]
Yeah. No one replies. But I've been with
women more multiple women.
Yeah. I just I just laugh at them, bro.
To be honest. I've laughed at them. I
just laugh at them, bro. Because I know
what they're about. That's why they
don't bother me. I know what these
people are about.
Uh, I've been seen with multiple
multiple multiple women. Multiple
multiple multiple multiple multiple
women. But like I said, you biased
people have got selective memory.
So you choose to forget things that you
want to forget. That's another reason
you're a waste of our time.
Uh, mute. You've never even had sex, let
alone a girlfriend.
Stop talking about yourself.
Like I just laugh. I actually just laugh
at these people. They actually they
bully themselves and they don't even
realize it because of their disabilities.
I just don't know how people of this age
can sit on the internet hating every
day. [sighs and gasps]
It blow. I don't know, bro. Like it's
just it's normal to them because they're
disabled, but it's not normal, you know?
sitting on the internet every day hating.
They really do hate themselves.
You have seen me with multiple women
multiple multiple times. Why have we
never seen you with a woman? Why have we
Why have we never seen you people with a woman?
Answer my question. Why have we never
seen you people with a [ __ ] woman?
Yeah. As soon as a woman comes on the
community, you're you're all begging her
off. And we've seen it on Les. Why have
we never seen you people with a woman?
Never. Never even once. Why have we
never once seen you with a woman?
Because you're too ugly. This is where
Peter Belly would always have one over
on you. You know, get a life, man.
Seriously, it's 2026. Have you got
nothing better to do than to sit on the
on YouTube hating your whole life, you know?
Do you not do you not have anything
better to do? It's 2026 and you're still
doing this. Really?
Madness. It really is a madness.
>> Hello PJ. Have you calmed down yet?
>> I'm completely calm.
>> Have you seen my avatar? >> Yeah,
>> that's the £500 what I in Nottingham.
>> Yeah, that's good. Yeah, I was about 200 in PJ.
>> What slot was it?
>> It's the one with the snow. I can never
pronounce it. I'll put it on the
communal post tomorrow. I ain't can't do
all the comments tonight. I've got
better things to do. >> Yeah.
>> Anyway, PJ, look, listen to me, mate.
Don't cut me out the house. Let's have a
conversation like white wings, not like
lefties. Right. Why do you let these
people affect you, mate? Because
>> they don't affect me.
>> They do cuz you go on about them.
>> They don't. They're the ones that are
going on about me every [ __ ] day.
>> But why can't you ignite that PJ? I loan
it, right? [laughter] I I I own it. The
reason why I reacted to Winchester this
girl cuz I hate being called a [ __ ] cuz
I do show and that lot. Right.
Regardless of the situation, if I do get
a bit of a boiled egg or I get a bit of
a [ __ ] thumping or whatever, right?
>> You know, do you know what I find
strange to me? Do you know what I find
very strange? Yeah. >> Yeah.
>> Is how these people listen to me? Yeah.
or in their 40s and they continuously
hate people they don't know every day
listen do not find it weird
>> PJ right this is called the [ __ ]
community right they want to be
something they're not right this is what
these people are like PJ listen to me
and don't cut me out right yeah
>> and you're the perfect person who gives
them a reaction right because you kick
off and PJ right life's not about money
hear me out right there's more to life than money.
>> You Timmy, you need to tell them that.
Don't tell me that. You need to tell
them that. They all They continuously go
on about money.
>> But PJ, right, don't kick me out. I used
to do this. So, I'll put this a bit
easier. I used to do my balls in PJ. I
used to get bitter when people won
money. I used to get angry and I used to
do what you used to do and make out that
I had all this money and lie and all
this and all that. The reason why I'm in
a good place in life now, PJ, is because
I'm 41 years old and I've calmed down,
right? But you know, you're you're
younger than me by 11, 12, 12 years.
Why? I don't
>> Yeah, you people are the monsters. You
people are the ugly muners. We've seen
what you people look like when you've been
>> PJ, you know, instead of being jealous,
why don't you just say fair play, Red
Star, you've got money. Congratulations.
>> Because Red Star doesn't have money. That's why.
>> How do you know? But how do you know
that, PJ? Honestly,
>> how do you know he does have money? Have
you Have you met him?
>> Yeah, cuz I
Red Star's loaded. I know who he is.
>> Listen, brother. He does. If he had
money, he wouldn't be stalking someone
on the internet every day. That's not
someone with money. That's not someone
with a life.
>> Listen, Timmy, I'm trying to explain
something to you. Yeah. And you keep
talking over me. Someone that's got a
life and got money don't do this.
>> I know that for a fact. At a very
minimum. I know that. Yeah,
>> PJ. They do. And hear me out. What they do?
>> Listen, brother. He doesn't have money.
He doesn't have no money.
>> Say Red Star's got no money. Can we have
a normal conversation? Yeah.
>> No, no, no. I'm asking you a question,
right? If he's got all of this money, if
he's got all of this money, why is he
sat on YouTube stalking a man every day?
>> Because that's what people do, PJ. This
is the 21st century.
>> I don't do it. I don't do it.
>> And that pays me boy [ __ ] going
around bullying Christians cuz he's
trying to get content. But if you met a
[ __ ] I don't
>> I don't stalk men on the internet every
day recording them, bro. Yes, but PJ,
can I just try PJ? He doesn't meet
>> He thinks I deserve it. But guess what,
bro? He will never meet me cuz he's a
coward like his boyfriend. So if you're
never going to meet anyone, you're just a [ __ ] >> PJ,
>> you're just a little [ __ ] boy.
>> PJ, do you know why?
>> And he deserves to be skinned on YouTube
every day wasting his life on me. He
deserves it and he will keep doing it as well.
>> But PJ, do you know why you're doing
these streams and you're going to kick
me out cuz you don't like the truth? Cuz you're
>> Well, if you don't look like Pat and
Bomb, why don't you join the hangouts
then? If you don't look like that. One
second, Timmy. One second. One sec. Hold on.
>> I'm I've come back and I'm cooking my chitas.
>> If you don't look like that. Yeah. If
you don't look like that, join the
hangouts and show us your face. What
have you got to hide?
I tell you what, Timmy is right about
here. It is a [ __ ] disabled community, brother.
It it the money. Stop trying to troll
you. A I'm not trying to troll. The
guy's got no money. Yeah, he is. Yeah.
Yeah. I'm not trying to troll. He
literally has got no money. £2.5,000 is
no money. Yeah. That is no money at all.
Yeah. 2.3 grand. He ain't got no money.
He's got no money. That's no money at
all. Show some actual money, bro. Show
some actual money and prove it's yours. Yeah. Simple.
Simple. And listen, the only M is you
people. Have you seen the state of you
people when you've been shown on camera?
Look at the state of you fat ugly people, bro.
Like you people are stinking fat ugly
people calling people a m every day.
Look in the mirror. Actually look in the
mirror and look at yourselves, your fat
ugly selves before trying to judge
someone better than you, [ __ ] retards. [snorts]
So anyways, Bob, why are you drinking on Monday, lad?
Why? Why the [ __ ] are you drinking on
Monday? He said tomorrow. Huh?
I'm just ignoring these self projectors now.
You self projecting low lives. [snorts]
You skid self- actors. So anyways, why
are you drinking on a Monday, bro? H. Yeah.
So what you drink every day?
>> So what you drink every day?
>> Right, PJ? Right. I'm just cooking my dinner.
>> Yeah. I'm not I'm not reacting to these people anymore. >> PJ
Let me hear me out. Right, brother. When
I reacted to Winchester earlier, I was
an idiot. I own it because we all know
Winchester's a bottle job. We all know
his face doesn't want to go out there.
And we all know that I was in the air.
>> I went on your I went on your live
stream yesterday and it was just the same people.
>> But PJ, the reason why they do what they
do is because it winds you up. And they
>> But they don't wind me up. It does wind you up.
>> They don't wind me up to me. They wind
themselves up because they're the ones at PJ.
>> They're the ones that are wasting their
life on me.
>> Yes. Because
>> they're winding themselves up. They
don't wind me up. These people do not
>> You're rattled about what these people
have got in life. Why does it bother you?
>> You know, Timmy, listen. Do you know
why? Do you know why these people don't
wind me up?
>> Why? Go on.
>> Because they're fat, ugly old men. They
don't wind me up. They could.
>> They don't w me up.
>> They do not w me up at all. Listen, they
they want Timmy, right? Listen. How tell
everyone how many years these people
have been doing this.
>> They've been doing it over. Why do you
think it's boring, PJ? Why do you think
they're laughing? It's the same constant
[ __ ] day in and day out, PJ. But you
still allow it to get to you.
>> They've been doing it for 15 years.
>> Because they've got nothing better to
do, PJ. What part of that don't you
understand? You know,
>> PJ, the more you go live, the more
you'll talk about it, the more you look
like a pratt
>> and the more they'll stalk me.
>> Yes, but PJ, you you it does let them
wind you up. Why don't you just go
silence and do some normal content like
normal [ __ ] people?
>> And they don't bully people. They bully
themselves, but they're so disabled,
they don't even realize that.
>> Been reacting to all through Christmas.
>> And they're reacting to me. So, what
does that say about them?
>> They're not reacting to you. They're taking
>> They are. Okay. So, Oh, one second. One
second. So you think people on YouTube [laughter]
One second to me. So you think people on
YouTube typing away all day is not them
reacting to me in what in what PJ?
>> Yes, that is that is them reacting to
me. So you think Red Star recording and
stalking me all day is not reacting and
giving me his time. Make it make sense.
>> Make it make sense, bro. It takes a lot
of energy and a lot of dedication to
hate someone for years every day.
>> Yeah. You don't understand that.
>> You give them the reaction. And they
give me the reaction.
>> I've given Mass the reaction today.
>> And they give me the reaction by going
on their channel. Their reaction,
>> you're the one who's constantly going on
about Bang. You're the one who's
constantly going about them. Why can't
>> Red Star never stopped my money. I've
got more money than Red Star as well.
And he never stopped my money.
>> Well, PJ, if you've got all this money,
why don't they just show it and then
wipe the smile off everyone's face?
>> Same to you. Why they can't they show me
money? It's the same argument.
>> But they Well, same
on his online win.
>> Red Star didn't show. Redstone didn't
stop my buddy and I've got more money than him.
>> And I've got more money.
>> You're never going to learn, are you?
>> And I've got more money than you. And
I've got more money than him.
>> Right, PJ? Right. Let's be honest about this, right? >> Yeah.
>> When are you going to I'm not being
nasty. When are you going to start to grow up?
>> When are you going to start to grow up?
>> I've already grown up, PJ. I Okay, I admit I
>> There's no There's no deals. You people
have been shown thousands of pounds and
you've all run away. Why are we still
having this conversation? You've been
shown thousands and you've run away. So
why are you still asking people to show your money?
>> PJ, just show everybody your bank
account and then you win.
>> You have been shown thousands and
thousands and you've run away. Why are
you still asking people to show your
money? Is it autism?
>> [ __ ] comedy gold. This is
>> No, I'm not talking about the past. I'm
No, no, no. You have been shown
thousands and thousands and thousands
and thousands and thousands.
>> God, this guy's very obsessed with
money. He never got any of my money
stopped. He literally got none of my
money stopped [laughter]
>> at all. No, he did not. No, he did not.
He never got any of my money stopped.
And I still get money. And I still get
money. So try again.
PJ, the trolls are winning because you're reacting.
>> They're not winning. They're fat, ugly
people that don't leave the house.
They've never won nothing. But PJ that
you're the one who's reacted to me by doing these
>> new people have never got any of our
buddies stopped. Keep telling yourself that
talking about garden talking about cars.
>> Anyways, we're banning you now. We're
banning the spastics. Anyways, we're
Right. See you later.
We're banning these spastics now. See you
sad, lonely, fat, ugly people.
And you're banned as well. See you.
We're not dealing with these plastics, bro.
Sad. Why have I got a bunch of
middle-aged ugly men obsessed with me,
Bob? I think they want my ass or
something, lad. They generally generally
want my ass. They want my ass or something.
They're so jealous of me. I've never
known anything like it.
Terry. Oh, another one obsessed with me.
Why have I got all of these people that
are obsessed with me?
Jesus Christ. The jealousy. [ __ ]
hell. The m You know, bro. You know when
you've got a bunch of people obsessed
with you, they're jealous of you, bro.
You know when you've got people lining
up, love, lad. Yeah. You just know that
they're jealous of you. So, you know
you're doing something right, bro. When
you've got all of these people Yeah.
stalking you on Reddit, stalking you on
all of these pages. Bro, you know you
got something they want. You just know
you're better than them. You know you
are, bro. You know that you've got
something these ugly people want. That's
what you need to think of. And that's
not reacting. That's the truth. That is
actually the truth. Okay, look at look
at Okay, look at uh listen look at this
guy right here, Red Star. Uh uh Terry,
shitty trainers, ugly as [ __ ] a [ __ ]
Look at that guy compared to me. He got
run out of his area by me. I bullied him
out of his area and he's still coming
back for more. Bro, the guy got bullied
in his own area and he's still coming
back for more. That's how that's how
[ __ ] they actually are. Bullied by
who, bro? You people don't bully no one.
You [ __ ] [ __ ] [ __ ] with shitty
trainers. Mate, I went to your area and
I bullied you out of it. The only one
that got bullied is you.
I literally went to your area and you
did not show up, brother. You got
bullied in your own area. Are you
disabled or something? Are you literally literally disabled?
I You called me out. I went to your area
and you didn't show up. Have you got brain damage,
Terry? The only one that's been bullied
is you. You didn't even beat me. I told
you to come around the corner the first
time and you didn't come. You you
stinking ma [ __ ] with your shitty
trainers. I've spoke about your kids.
I've spoke about your shitty trainers.
You still won't meet me. I went to your
area and you didn't come out. You're a
[ __ ] You're a little [ __ ] You done
all of this. You done all of that. I
went to your area and you didn't come
out. You're a little [ __ ] Stop lying to yourself.
You shitty trained skin ugly mun with
your ugly kids and I'm still doing it
and you're not gonna do nothing.
Like I'll bully your kids in front of
you next time, bro. Not just you.
Okay. So why didn't you show up the last
time I went to your area?
Bidget boy, why didn't you show up the
last time I went to your area? Big man.
Big man, why did you not show up so I
could smash your face in last time I
went to your area? Tell everybody on
YouTube why you didn't show up. Because
you knew you was going to get knocked
out. You're a keyboard warrior. Tell
everybody when I went to your area last
time why you would not come out that
front door. Tell everybody. Big man that
bullies people apparently. Why did you
get run out of your area? You still
haven't told anyone? Cuz you're a [ __ ] house.
You're a [ __ ] house. That's why you keep
changing the subject. I was going to
smack your teeth down your throat that
day. You know that. I was going to smack
your teeth down your throat if you come
down that train station. You know that.
And you knew what was good for you. You
knew what was good for you. So, you did
not come out. You [ __ ] ugly [ __ ]
shitty trader. Ugly kids. And bear in
mind, you know my address. I don't know
your address. [ __ ] ugly trained, ugly
[ __ ] ugly kids. You should never talk
about a man's kids. And you're not doing
nothing about it. Ugly man, ugly life,
ugly kids, and you're not going to do
nothing. You're not going to do nothing.
Listen, mate. Come right now and I will
wait for you. You're never going to meet
anyone. You're just an ugly [ __ ] with
shitty traders. You're just an ugly man,
ugly kid, ugly life, and you're never
going to meet no one. That's what I'm
saying. You're just an ugly man. Ugly
life, ugly kids. Cuz you know people
don't you don't like people talking
about kids. Well, I'll talk about your
kids. They're [ __ ] ugly and you know
where I live and you're not going to do
nothing about it.
Simple. I mean I mean listen you you
want to talk about LT LT tried to beat
you and you wouldn't even meet him. Like
he even said that if you actually listened.
[ __ ] ugly man, ugly life, ugly kids.
And he knows where I live. And he'll do
nothing. And he'll do nothing. I I tried
to meet this [ __ ] last time. Oh, I'm on
parole. Was it? Oh, I'm on like he's
never going to beat no one. This Terry
is another nod legs. They're just bully
victims that will never beat anyone.
They're just complete bully victims that
will never beat anyone. I went to this I
don't know how long you've been on this
YouTube, but I went to this cunt's area
and he would not come out. He would not
come out. These love nons. They've got
no shame. They're just bully victims
that think that they bully other people,
but they don't. They get bullied themselves. Bro,
listen. And I'm going to time you out
now anyways. You're boring. See you
later. Sad [ __ ]
Sad sad sad sad sad [ __ ]
Sad sad sad bastard.
Sad sad bastard.
You didn't get anyone's body stopped. Oh
yeah, I've just gone on that by the way.
Yeah, you reported me, but you didn't
get my body stopped at all.
This red star, bro, I'm telling you, he
is a bully victim. He's got nothing. I
don't know why Timmy keeps defending
this fat loser. He's got nothing
about He's got They've got nothing but
trying to harass a 28-year-old every
day. They've got nothing. They prove
what I'm saying is right about them. I
love it when they do this because it
shows that they're jealous of you. The
more they do it, the the more the more
they do this, the more they waste their
time, the more it shows jealousy. But
this is why I love it. This is why I
love when these people do it. It shows
that you've got something they want. And
it proves it. It proves it, bro. I love
it. This is why I love all of this [ __ ]
cuz it shows their jealousy. And that's
what I love, you know? I love it. I love
these people being jealous of me, love,
dedicating all their time to harassing
someone every day. I love the jealousy.
I love the jealousy towards me, love.
>> I love it, man. I love it.
They hate that you're younger and better
looking than them, which is what I've
always said, and I've stuck to my guns.
These people are fat, ugly, old people
before they try to [ __ ] say anything
about me again. You know that's that.
They're fat, ugly bull losers slobbing
away on YouTube every day cuz they got nothing.
That's the truth, bro. Literally.
Literally the truth. What life have they
got, bro? What life have these people
[clears throat] really got? Just sit on
the internet hating people they don't
know every day.
What life have they got, man? Come on.
[ __ ] nothing. They don't lie.
Just sad, jealous people every day on
YouTube. Nothing new, nothing good to
say about anyone. No good comments. Oh,
bro. I'm always these fat ugly people.
But to be honest with you, most of they
just own themselves
to be fair. Most of them they just own themselves
every day, bro. To be honest, it's not
even like hard to do.
Nah, bro. That's you people. That's self
projecting. That's you ugly [ __ ]
That's you ugly people and LJ's. You got
no life outside of YouTube. Don't copy
my words. Don't [ __ ] copy my words.
You people have got no social
interaction outside of YouTube. You all
type to each other because you ain't got
no one. You ain't got no friends. You
got nothing in life. People that have
got, you know, people that have that
have got stuff going for themselves. And
you people have literally got nothing
going for yourselves. And that's why you
you you hate it because what I'm saying
is the truth.
Sat on YouTube for 24 hours a day with
no social interaction.
No social interaction. But YouTube, you
want me to come off YouTube for two
weeks together and prove that it's you
people that's got no life. Dude, we've
done this millions and millions of times before, bro.
You're on YouTube sat on YouTube 24/7.
No friends, no girlfriends. I'm talking
about you people. I'm talking about you
[ __ ] I wouldn't mind it. Yeah, but
you're sat on YouTube hating people that
are better than you in life.
People that are better than you.
YouTube hating people that are better
than you. But you're so disabled you
don't even realize it.
All about trying to bring people down to
your disabled level.
Have you looked at yourselves? [ __ ]
hell. Have you actually looked at
yourselves when you're trying to call
other people all of these things? Have
you actually looked at yourselves?
Have you ever just looked in the mirror
and looked at yourselves?
[ __ ] ugly people sat on YouTube every day.
Peter Belly can say it better than
Monty. You know, Peter Benny can say it
better than Monty, like
Yeah. Really, did you? Yeah. Really? [clears throat]
This is self projection.
When are you people going to get life?
When are you people going to get alive? H.
So, okay. So, I I'll do this, right? So,
if I don't come on YouTube, right,
tomorrow, are you going to be on YouTube?
Are you going to be on YouTube if I'm
not on YouTube tomorrow? [clears throat] Simple question.
So, you're not going to be on Lord Jay's
or nothing? No.
Okay. Well, I'm going to come off
YouTube for a bit and then I'm going to
go on L Js when I come back. And I
better hope you people are not on YouTube.
So then if you're on YouTube, then it
shows that you are the ones that have
got no life.
Yeah. It shows that you are the ones
that have got no life.
Yeah, it shows that you are the ones
I've got no life.
Autism and money. I think this community
is Yeah. obsessed with money as well. Autism.
My brain. My brain. My [ __ ] brain, bro.
people every day.
What a life, eh? That's mad.
How lucky I am. What? Someone that's
younger and better looking than you.
Someone that's younger and better
looking than you. Again, bro, you're
getting yourself confused with me,
brother. How lucky? What? Being a fat,
ugly bog, that that means you're lucky.
What? someone that's younger and better
looking than you and not pass the cell
by date. Remember what I talked about
autism when I talked about it being a disabled community?
I'm literally younger and better looking
than you. How would that make you feel
lucky? You're a fat slob. [laughter]
You're [clears throat] a fat [ __ ]
slob with nothing in life. >> [snorts]
>> Yeah, for real, bro. Yeah. [clears throat] Yeah, bro.
I just made myself this cup of [ __ ]
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
Yeah. Yeah. Man, they've got nothing new
or nice to say about anyone, do they, Bob?
Nothing new or nice to say about anyone.
So you drink cuz of anxiety, you know?
probably staying in to be honest.
Yeah, I'm 28 now, bro. It's only down from now.
It's only down from now, bro.
It's all right when you're, like I said,
when you're 25, 26. I've got no reason
to try anything anymore in life.
See, normally I would get this mood and
then after a week I'd calm down. But
it's been this way for months now, bro.
Yeah, it's been this way for months.
And I meant it when I said I was never
going out again as well. I meant it. I
stuck to it this time.
Yeah. I was really dumb, wasn't I, bro? Really was.
Oh yeah, that
I've had that before.
I don't get anxiety me, bro, anymore. I
to be fair.
No, I can't get anxiety, bro. I've been
through the worst of the worst of the worst.
Like, I have had that when I was
younger. I have had it. It's not nice.
But I think it's probably why I don't
even give a [ __ ] if I die. So yeah,
maybe that's why. But I don't really get anxiety, bro.
Oh, it is bad, bro. I should be with
someone. I should have a sex life at 28.
It is bad. Not financially bad or like
homeless bad, but with the women [ __ ]
it's not normal.
Yeah, I given up with life. My but no,
my life's not bad like that.
Like obvious not obviously in that way,
but it's not normal.
Yeah, it's not normal, bro. It's not
normal that I should have to even go out
and try again. And that's what I keep
telling myself. And that's how I've been
this way for months because it is the
truth, you know.
Yeah. They'll never stop, Mike. It's all
day, every day with these clowns.
Yep. You know, ain't it?
Same people, same story, lad.
Nah, it is pretty bad, bro. It is pretty bad.
I think you're getting revenge every day.
No, no, no. I think you're getting
revenge every day on these women, bro.
That's why I don't put myself out there anymore.
I've got a really short temper now, bro. Yeah.
No, it's pretty bad, but just not in
that way, you know?
And I haven't found a desire to get motivated.
No, I haven't found any desire to get
motivated because it's just the same old
[ __ ] in my head, Mike. I have it how I
shouldn't ever I shouldn't have to try
again. That's how I've got it in my head.
That's how I've got it in my head, bro.
That I shouldn't have to try again.
and it's valid and it's the truth, you
know. So that's why I don't Yeah,
I with a few [ __ ] women lately as
well. So yeah.
Yeah, I am uh
bro. So, might as well just call it quits.
You can't find one. They're not
interested, Bob. Unfortunately, they're
not interested. They either say they've
got boyfriends, give you attitude, or
lead you on. The end. That's all they do, Mike.
No, you can't go out and find one.
They're not interested. They're just [ __ ]
You're too old for me. You're too young
You're not a Muslim. Oh, bro. If I hear
that one more time, I'm going on a watch
list. 100%. I'm going on the watch list. [gasps]
Yeah. 100%. Mr. B, I'll be on a watch
list, lad. Yeah.
No, you can't go out and find mom.
You could try a whole year the whole
time and you would still get the same bad experiences.
You would actually still get the same bad experiences.
Nothing would change. How mad is that? Eh,
you should have to go out and try again.
I've been out for years trying. I
shouldn't have to try again.
So, unless someone's really really
willing to prove that they're different
on some some kind of social media thing,
then that's that.
And even if I met somebody, I would just
[ __ ] them over, Bob. I'd probably rob
them to be honest. I probably just rob
would rob I would just rob someone.
Yeah, I would just rob someone. Even if
I did meet someone, I would royally [ __ ]
their life up, bro. It It wouldn't even
be worth it to be honest, you know?
And that's that. I would just rob him
and ruin him, bro. Like, I'm not even
joking. I would just do something nasty.
Trust me. Yeah.
I mean it, Mr. B. I mean it, bro. 100%.
I mean it.
I'm on my last nerve as it is, you know.
Yeah, I would. 100% I would.
The amount of [ __ ] Yeah. they've done
over the years, bro, is mad.
Come to think of it, is actually mad, bro.
getting revenge on a woman.
Honestly, that's the only thing that
would make me happy, bro. I don't care
about money. I don't give a [ __ ] about
any of that [ __ ] Probably getting
revenge on a woman. Like, badly bad bad revenge.
Then I would just move on with my life.
That would Yeah, 100%.
All the [ __ ] [ __ ] they done over the
years. That would really make me happy, bro.
Do you remember, Mr. B? I thought like
starting the American [ __ ] up again.
Like starting up the uh the whole
American [ __ ] again, bro. Oh yeah, bro.
You don't know me, bro. You don't know Trust me.
Trust me. Yeah.
Yeah. I'm mad, bro. Seriously, I've got
like I got nothing to lose, bro. Nothing
to lose. I got no responsibilities, nothing.
You know, you know, before I had like a
responsibility and [ __ ] so I had to be
careful. Now I'm a free man, bro. I can
do whatever I, you know, I can do
whatever, you know. So,
These women need to pay Mike Hunt. They
need to pay lad for all the [ __ ] that
they've done over the years. The
[ __ ] the lying, the leading on. You
know what I'm saying, lad?
[ __ ] go. I don't even drink anymore,
Mike. I drunk a couple of beers
Christmas. I don't even drink anymore.
I don't even drink anymore, lad.
The last couple of times I went out was
like Simpsons and [ __ ] white nights. I
got into some madness.
You're well, you would always die
lonely. Whether you try or you don't
die, whether you try or you don't try,
you're always going to be lonely.
You're always going to get bad experiences.
So why does it matter, bro? You might as
well just accept your fate. Yeah.
You always Yeah. I haven't had a date
since April, by the way, Mike.
Since April. I know you don't come on
here, but I haven't had a date since last April.
If that doesn't tell you that it is
impossible in this country, I don't know
what what possibly will. Yeah.
>> [snorts and clears throat] >> Yeah, [snorts] Mr. Be [clears throat]
Nope. I'm not showing you money. Oh my.
This this community makes my head hurt, bro.
This community makes my head hurt, lad.
It actually doesn't it?
Ah, my head
is so disabled. That's why I had it.
It makes my [ __ ]
makes my head hurt. It's so disabled.
It does though. Is it Mike?
Oh, you know, would you say that they're
biased on this community, Mike?
Would you say that they're biased?
Like, would you say that they've got
their own agenda?
They've got their own agenda, lad, on here.
I feel upset sometimes, you know,
like cuz when people call me a virgin,
no one sticks up for me. I feel upset.
Like they never bring up the porno.
Like when I go out nonslegs, yeah,
calling non legs a virgin. Everyone
sticks up and says, "Oh, well, he can't
be a virgin. He's got a girlfriend." But
then when they call me a virgin, when he
calls me a virgin, no one talks about um
the time I've proved I've had sex
and like been in women's beds and stuff.
It's very biased, you know. Very, very
biased. Don't know why they do it, but
they do. Yeah, I've met Timmy Aldridge.
Yeah, they're definitely biased, bro.
They're definitely biased. You can tell
by the virgin
by the virgin thing.
What do you think, Mike?
They say that I'm a virgin there.
I haven't got 200. Okay. I haven't got
£200, bro. Yeah,
there's no point showing these people
money because if you show them money,
they're just going to ask you to show
them money again 2 days later.
It's a It's a It's a disabled community, lad.
You show them. You show them.
Oh, yeah. They stalk me every day, bro.
They stalk me all day, every day. These people.
Yeah, they stalk me every day.
Yeah, Red Star stalks me every day, lad.
he records everything. They stalk me on Reddit.
You should say repeating people.
Same repeating people in it. All right. cuz
you know there's no hope for you. That's why
people I I I surround myself with
negative people now. People that's given
up with life. Mike, I like them kind of people.
I like them kind of people with a victim mentality. You know,
I like them kind of people, bro.
Those the people that I watch. I like them people. Yeah.
I like people that think the whole
world's against them.
Those are my kind of people, bro. Yeah.
go back in a minute.
You're still there, Bob?
Why do people on Reddit keep saying that
I'm going to find someone, Mike, and
that it's temporary? It's not temporary.
This has been going on for years.
Yeah, I remember that, bro. People on
Reddit say that stuff happens and things
change. I said, "No, it [ __ ] doesn't.
This never changes. It's been the same
[ __ ] for years.
It's been the same old for years.
It literally never changes. Nothing ever
gets better, bro. What the [ __ ] How do
I don't know how people can even say that
must be trolling um
in this country? One in a million.
Yeah. One in a million I reckon. Yeah.
Why would this year be any different?
Every other year has been the same.
Yeah, probably one in a in a million.
It's never happening. Uh
in this country anyways. Yeah.
What is it supposed to be all? Is it
going to be different suddenly? What's
changed this year than than last year
and the year before that and the year before that?
Nothing's changed. They will never
change. It will never happen.
And if you keep going out trying, you're
just going to make yourself worse and
you're just going to have more bad
experiences. That's all that's going to happen.
So, I'd rather not.
Yeah, it shouldn't be this way, Mike. It
shouldn't be this way.
Yeah, I'd say one in a one in a million.
My options are basically nothing.
No, my options are nothing.
Yeah, I'm glad he I'm glad he assaulted
a woman on a train. Women are evil.
Women are scum. Evil. And he never he
never [ __ ] assaulted a woman on the train.
What I done was worse in the Weather
Spoons. What I done was worse than him
that same week. And that's good. The
women are evil. So
yeah, I'm big up Timmy for that. Timmy
didn't even do anything wrong to be
fair. He should have smacked her one to
be fair. Like that woman on the train, I
should have knocked her the [ __ ] out.
Even though I called her an ugly
crackhead, I should have just knocked
her the [ __ ] out in front of everyone.
Yeah, I should have knocked the [ __ ] flying, bro.
Off that train.
It's toxic. Very, very toxic, bro.
That's why I don't put myself in these situations anymore.
I didn't like that energy. No.
Oh, Mike, do you remember nonsleg saying
that Cheryl Cole was attractive to fit
in? He said, "If you don't find Shervel
Cole attractive, you're gay." Do you
remember when he was saying that to fit
in with the crowd? Little copycat.
Where was that little copycat?
[snorts] He didn't want to feel left out.
He didn't want to feel left out. Bless
him. Bless him in life. >> [sighs]
>> Yeah, I own them.
Yeah, they weren't even that bad. But
that one on the train, I should have
knocked her out, bro. Even though I told
her she's an ugly crackhead
and I weren't scared. I did tell her
about, but I should have like I actually
should have knocked her out.
Thinking of it now, I should have
actually knocked the [ __ ] out, bro.
Yeah, to be honest, that's what I should
have done. I was half asleep. It's the
time when I cast out the bet in it.
Yeah, bro. I should have really knocked
her the [ __ ] out. Teach her a [ __ ] good lesson.
[sighs and gasps]
Yeah, that's why I don't bother no more, lad.
I like shovel cole. If you don't like
shovel co, you're gay. Get yourself down
to waxies, lad.
Get yourself down to wax to waxies, lad.
The waxies lad.
No, I don't want any more bad experiences. Dusty.
What? Go there with LT. What? To waxes. [gasps]
You could take nonslegs to waxies, but I
don't think the manager allows virgins.
It's a no virgin zone, Mike.
No virgins allowed. So, so he says
they don't allow virgins.
No skin virgins allowed, mate. I don't
make the rules.
I don't make the rules, mate.
Yeah, that's what I mean.
No virgins allowed in it.
No skin virgins.
He's a [ __ ] virgin. That one is it.
He's a skin virgin. Oh yeah.
Mr. Bean the 26th of August 1984.
Does that ring a bell?
The 26th of August.
Uh, nope. I'm not doing nothing this
year. I'll be chilling in bed.
I'll be chilling in bed depressed.
How about you? Yeah.
26th of August. [snorts]
No holidays. No, lad.
What about you? You going on holiday? Yeah, [snorts]
I'm so comfy. This bed is very cozy.
All right. These Reddit mods love power,
don't they, Dusty?
They're very, very power hungry, these Reddit moderators.
They've got their own agenda.
Sorry about that.
No, no, no, no, no.
He's just a [ __ ] virgin to me.
45y old virgin here. It never got better. Oh,
there's some guy that's a 45y old virgin.
It will never get better.
Are you going on a holiday? IVA.
Well, bless you then. If that's where you're going,
I'll be in bed. Yeah.
Yeah. I'm just watching this Oreo man.
I like Oreo man.
He thinks the whole world is against
him. I like people like that.
I do like a bit of Oreo, man.
Yeah, I like watching these incels.
Yeah, I like these incelss.
It wasn't my dog, bro. my sister's dog
and she took it back. We was only
looking after it,
but he doesn't come for sleepovers anymore.
Where do I go in Thailand?
Well, go to Thailand and meet Ant-Man.
Dusty, have you ever been to Southampton? What ball?
You know, Southampton people are cocky.
People from Southampton are cocky.
Oh yeah, it was funny. Yeah.
Yeah, Antman's funny.
Who do you know that's from Southampton? Dusty,
do you know anyone that's from Southampton?
What about Ali Law? Ali Law is from Southampton, Dusty.
I don't know if you know who Ali Law is.
He doesn't do He doesn't do social media anymore.
I used to like his videos.
Good old Ali.
Did you see the one when he climbed up
the O2? Oh,
[ __ ] hell, bro. You remember it?
Well, you you climbed on the O2.
I'm sure you know who it is. [snorts] Nope.
He don't know about back. I thought he
was going to go through the [ __ ]
thing, bro. The the O2 thing.
No, I'm not playing that.
no, dusty. Yeah.
Remember, Dusty, don't let them [ __ ] women win.
Don't let them [ __ ] women win.
Remember that account, poor [ __ ]
I ain't seen it for a while.
There was an account yet and I said,
"Oh, I'm not going to go out anymore
approaching." He says, "You can't let
them [ __ ] women win.
You have to go out and approach. Don't
let them [ __ ] women win. You can.
Yeah, I went Amsterdam years ago
and then [ __ ] nonslegs went there.
Little copycat. You copied my little holiday.
You little copycat. Little copycat.
Can't go anywhere without that [ __ ]
[ __ ] copying me. [ __ ] copycat. Yeah.
[snorts and laughter]
Yeah. Yeah. Nons is very insecure. Yeah.
He said if I don't find cheerful co
attractive, I'm gay. That's so ridiculous.
What the [ __ ] That is so That's what
people used to say to each other to fit in.
[ __ ] pathetic, bro.
That is pathetic.
Yeah, he did say that.
That was a copycat trend back in the
day. They always used to copy each other.
Yeah, he did say that when I met him. Yeah.
And if you go online, you will see that
people say to each other,
"Are you gay or not?" Yeah. They're just copy copycats.
He says, "Yeah, yeah, definitely gay. If
you don't find her attractive, you're gay." Yeah,
he said that. He did say that.
People used to say the same thing to
each other. They used to copy each other. Mike,
it used to be a big trend to put uh
celebrities on pedestals
back in the day.
It It was the trend.
There was a copycat statement, you know,
back in the day to do that. Beyonce,
Rihanna, Sher Cole, they done it with
silly really, you know.
silly to feel the need to copy another person.
You know, that's what some people like
to do in it. No.
Yeah, that Sydney Sweeny's all right.
That's only cuz I saw her naked.
But I wouldn't say if you don't find her
attractive, you're gay.
N is copy and n is copying the crowd. Yeah.
Oh, this account is so funny trying to
get my attention.
He is a very controlling person. He
tries to manipulate everything whether
it's the truth who can and can't speak
women his mother what other think what
others think of him must be why gambling
makes him so angry and he starts on
people randomly but backs down when they
mean business he's a complete narcissist
who can't stand that he's skinn and
alone because it's his fault.
Oh my god, bro. Do you not think Can
there be one day they don't say the word
skin on this community?
Oh my brain. My brain.
It's hurting. Mike, is there not one day
they can just stop using that word? It's so boring.
It's so boring, bro. Who started all of that [ __ ]
They're boring as [ __ ] bro.
Do you know it's not even an insult
saying that? You do realize that?
They've been saying that now for like
seven years. You know that? Your skin,
your skin, your skin, your skin, your
skin, your skin, your skin.
Is that why it hurts your brain, lad?
Oh, that word gives me brain damage, bro. Yeah.
David Campbell from Leeds. Greasy. David Campbell.
Greavvesy. David Campbell.
Big up David.
That's non legs his stepdad. David
Campbell of Leeds.
Your surname's Campbell.
That's quite a common surname, bro.
I'm so tired. Oh gosh.
What is it with people in this community
in the word skin?
in the word again.
You don't know my income,
Mr. Account that was made 18 years ago.
Your account was made more than half of my life. That's mad.
Your account is older than half my life.
You sad bastard. Old man.
18 years ago. Jesus Christ.
Your account was made 18 years ago. You old man.
That was when I was in my very first
house. I was 10 years old.
You don't know my income. You know what
I want you to know.
You know what I want you to know.
I tell you what I want you to know.
That's the joy of it.
Your account was made 18 years ago. What the [ __ ]
You're an old man. You know,
I'm 28. Yeah.
18 years old.
Yeah. What's my shoe size?
What color boxes are am I wearing?
When's my birthday?
There you go. Couple of questions for you. Oh [ __ ]
I like shuffle.
You little fubby cat.
Why Mike Nons said that to fit in,
didn't he? Didn't want to feel left out,
did he? Bless him. He just wanted the
bullying to stop in college.
He wanted it to stop.
He wanted to fit in.
You didn't want to feel left out.
[snorts and sighs] Oh, really? Nice. Yeah. No.
I like shovel girl. Meow.
I don't know why they used to talk about
that shovel girl.
She's not even hot. I don't even know
why people used to say that [ __ ]
Well, they said it to fit in obviously,
but why? I don't know. Copycat statement.
Yeah, they all used to copy each other. Mike,
absolutely no chance.
Never at them.
Obviously, I know how long YouTube's been going.
I know [snorts] the first YouTube video
as well. It was the guy at the zoo.
It was a guy at the zoo in it. 20 years.
Me at the zoo. Wow. 20 years ago. That
was It's still up there.
That's the first YouTube video 2005. [snorts] Wow.
So I was eight. Seven. No.
So he got famous from that then, didn't he?
cuz obviously that he he made the first YouTube video.
20 years ago. That is mad. Heat. Heat.
I like to walk out. Sydney Sweeney.
Yeah, you got to be gay, mate. [ __ ]
homo. Homo d
[ __ ] little copycat.
Little stinking copycat. [snorts]
Got to be gay, mate. Got to like dick.
You can't deny she's attractive, though,
Dusty. You can't deny it. You can't deny
it, mate. You got to be gay. No, you got No.
Got to be gay, mate.
to the guy that made the first YouTube video.
Is that who you're talking about?
Who that guy
I know where I'm going. Yeah.