[ __ ]
I'm sick of this [ __ ] Reddit. I am,
bro. I'm sick of this Reddit, man. They
just give such [ __ ] advice.
It's they give such [ __ ] advice, you know,
people don't owe you anything. Come up
with something new. Come up with something original,
something that we've not heard before.
Do you know what I'm saying? Bro, I'm
sick of that having to justify this
thing that they do owe you something.
They do owe you something.
It's like your boss owes you something.
If you was working for a whole month
before you get your paycheck, you are
owed something by women, by the gym, by
your boss, you are owed something.
Anyone that's putting effort into their
life is owed something. They are owed
Jesus [ __ ] Christ. I've gone on this
Reddit and they put me in a [ __ ] bad
mood again, bro. On this [ __ ] Reddit.
Just defending women again and
dismissing people's struggles. Why the
hell do these people do that? Why is
there so many people like this?
I don't understand why they keep
defending women. Women do owe people
something. Yes, they do owe people
something. When people are are literally
Yes, they do owe you something. If you
have put effort into your life and you
have approached, they do owe you something.
They literally do owe you something. And
stop trying to twist it to suit your
narrative, Grievy. Um, would I say yes
to a fat? Would I say yes to a fat lump
of lard? We're not talking about a fat
lump of l woman. Stop saying stuff to
suit your narrative. Um, that is
completely twisting things. I'm not a
fat lord. So why are you talking about a
fat lord? You're twisting things to suit your narrative.
You know, that's exactly what you're
doing. Why are you talking about a fat
lord? We're not talking about fat lord.
You mean if an averagel looking woman um
uh come to me? Yes, I would say yes.
Yes. So that's what the original that's
what the actual question would be, but
you're just saying something to suit your narrative.
So do you mean if an averagel looking
woman? Yeah. No one cares about that
self-reflecting repeating [ __ ] So
anyways, uh so what you mean is if a if
an average woman
uh would I say yes to an average woman?
Yes, I would say yes to an average
woman. Yes. Yes, I would. Yes. Yes. So
why are you saying something to suit your narrative,
Greavvesy? Why are you saying something
to suit your narrative? I mean, a fat
lump lord of woman would have to work on herself.
A fat large lump of woman would have to
work on herself.
She would have to work on herself.
I'm speaking to this woman on on
Instagram, right? And she's saying about
coming down to London from Scotland.
She's 45 and her husband don't give her
sex. And we was voice noting and stuff.
Maybe I'll try to ruin this person's
life. And I think they're I think
they're actual they're actually serious
as well cuz I spoke to them today. We
were speaking on Instagram.
Maybe I I'll try and ruin this person's life.
I told you the next person's getting it,
bro. The next person is definitely
definitely definitely definitely getting
it. And she says her husband doesn't
give her sex and that, so I'll ruin her life. Uh
I'll ruin her life. Any woman that I can
get my hands on to ruin, I will do it,
bro. Just give them a bit back. What
they've gave me over the years,
Greavvesy. Just a bit back.
I was uh I was making a tea earlier,
Greavves, and I was thinking about this
community and LT and stuff. And it was
it was hurting my brain a bit. I can't
be on here too long, bro. It hurts my
brain. It hurts my [ __ ] brain.
But why are you talking about a fat lord
woman? I'm not a fat lord man. So why
are you talking about a fat lord woman,
bro? [snorts] That didn't make any
sense. Why did you talk about a fat lord
woman, bro? I'm not a fat lord man. So
that's twisting things to suit your
narrative. That that is literally
twisting things to suit your narrative.
That is twisting things to suit your narrative.
What? Someone with glasses. I've been
with somebody with glasses.
So, I've been with someone with glasses.
And do I wear glasses?
Yes, I would. I already have. Yes, I
But I don't wear glasses. I don't have
red or blue hair. [laughter]
But I have, if that answers your question.
So, now you're just twisting things, ain't you? Um,
yeah. I was thinking about the whole uh
bias thing on this community when I woke
up, bro, when I was making a tea. The
whole like nonslegs thing and it's like
they they really really are like, oh,
they really are biased, isn't it, bro?
We've already been over it, Triple H,
brother. You know, my opinion on it, lad.
And my opinion stays the same. My
opinion stays the same, you know.
You know, my opinion stays the same, bro.
Yeah. Self projecting. Bye-bye. We don't
have self projectors on this channel.
So, yeah, with the Jo thing, bro. Um,
I've uh I've already told you my opinion,
lad. I told you what it is. He puts
money in and acts like he's won. We've
already been over this, bro.
What I find very strange, Greavves, is
when LT was on here the other day and I
was calling Nles a virgin and he says,
"Oh, how can he be a virgin? He's got a
girlfriend." But no one ever talked
about the pornos and the women that I've slept with. Strange.
I just don't think we'll ever know the
answer to that. Will, Grey, I just don't
think we'll ever know the answer, so I
probably won't mention it. I don't think
we'll ever know, to be honest. Strange,
isn't it? Very strange. Strange one, eh? >> [gasps]
>> Strange. Someone has actually put a
porno out there. Where's Kieran when you need him?
I don't think we'll ever know. So, it's
silly to assume that someone that's got
a girlfriend is a virgin, but it's not
silly to literally think someone that's
actually proved that they've had sex
with multiple women. I've been seen in
women's bed naked, but no one says
anything about that. Strange. I just
don't think we'll ever ever know.
Strange. I think we'll be waiting
forever to get that answer. strange.
There were the links there if you want
to join. I won't be on I won't be on long anyways.
I should be on there to be honest. Won't
be on there long.
This Reddit gives me mood swings, bro.
Reddit and gambling gives me mood
swings, but I don't really gamble, but
the women thing gives me mood swings as
well. I'm still stuck in the same loop,
Greasy. I still haven't calm down.
I think I'm in it too deep now, bro. I'm
really, really in it too deep.
Have you not noticed something, G? Oh,
well, I was saying this to Ant-Man and
someone else yesterday. I was saying
this. Have you noticed that this uh um
this aspect of your life never changes?
Like you know how like you can win money
or you can come into money or you can I
don't know something can happen
something randomly can happen. Yeah. But
with this it never changes. It never
ever ever changes. Have you noticed that
you don't meet anyone that's decent? You
don't stop getting your ass led on. You
don't stop hearing the same [ __ ] Like
this aspect of your life never ever ever
ever ever changes.
Like it never does. Like you might you
might as well just go back to [ __ ]
gambling. But I was actually thinking
this yet. If you really wanted to take
risk here, you might as well just go
back to gambling. You'd have better
odds. I'm not even say I'm not even
joking. I messaged a couple of people
about this yesterday.
There's lo, you know, if you've seen
throughout the whole six, seven years of
your life. Yeah. What's changed? Good,
bad, good, bad stuff has come up. Like
it's hard to explain, but this has
always been the same and it will always
be the same.
It's really bad, bro. Like Weezy, it
really really is bad.
You didn't believe me, Grey, did you
when I told you I was done done? When I
told you I was done done, you didn't
believe me, did you? I told you I was
done. You didn't believe me.
It's weird, you know. It's just such a weird thing
and the double standards as well. And no
one can help you either, Grezy. Because
if you if you say anything about it,
people would just keep blaming you.
Whereas, you know, with gambling, right?
Like say you went back to gambling.
Yeah. And you won sometimes and you
complained about gambling, people would
understand it. People would acknowledge
it. But in dating, right, no matter what
you do, what you try, what you say, what
you show, what you send, everyone will
just keep blaming you, no matter whoever
you are. And it will just continuously
keep going round and round and round and
round and round and round and round and
round in circles.
You understand what I'm saying, bro? Like,
so what I don't understand is why they
don't tell people to quit dating like
they tell people to quit gambling. It
makes sense, doesn't it, Greasy? Cuz
dating's got way worse odds. It's got
literally like you don't ever win.
Nothing ever changes. Nothing will ever
change. And that's that's me being
that's me being real. That's not be me
being negative. That is being [ __ ]
real right now. Nothing ever gets
better. Nothing ever changes. Society
does not change. You You'd be best off
just going back to gambling, you know?
You really would be just best off going
back to that, you know? Really?
It sounds I know it sounds mad, but you
should understand what I'm trying to
say, you know. >> Hello. >> Yo >> hello.
>> My phone is [ __ ] bro. I can't even
hear this [ __ ] What is wrong with this
[ __ ] [ __ ] phone? One second. I'll be back.
>> Can anyone hear me? >> [snorts]
>> Man, I can't hear this guy, bro. I
really can't hear him.
>> I'll jump back on
Well, I know we're not asking Grez. I
mean, we're saying
I'm just saying generally, bro. Like,
the whole thing is just [ __ ] up. And I
don't know how people are still feed.
Maybe it's the way your No, it's not the
way that I'm approaching. My approaching
is fine. Sorry, I didn't even see that.
Well, go away.
Um, yeah. My approaching is fine, bro.
No, no, no. My approaching is fine. My
messages are fine as well. Nope.
Uh-uh. My approaches are fine. See, this
is what I'm saying. They're always going
to find ways to blame you in every
single circumstances when it's just the
women that are just stuck up evil
[ __ ] you know?
No. One second. Let me try to go live on
this other one. No, I don't know why
it's not working. Hello. >> Yo. >> No.
>> Can you hear me?
>> No. I can't hear him, bro.
>> This is pissing me off now. I can't hear
him. What the [ __ ]
Let me reset my phone. One sec. Yeah.
>> Pit phone. What a Samsung Galaxy Fold 6
is a pit phone. Okay, bro. Yeah. Okay.
Yeah, let's try again. It should work now. Hello. >> Hello.
>> Yeah, I can hear you now. Yeah,
>> right. I I've got a B to pick with that Joseph Ferrar.
>> Yeah, go ahead.
>> He doesn't He doesn't lose on them for days.
>> No, he always wins, bro.
>> Yeah, it's what I I don't know. There's
something not right about that. I played them yesterday.
Oh, you played yesterday, did you?
>> I went on yesterday. Yeah. And I [ __ ]
Oh, yeah. What happened 30? And I got a
end up taking 50 to be honest cuz I was
I was up and down. Up and down all day on it.
>> It's just up and down. Up and down
[ __ ] Yeah, I know. That's right.
Yeah, I told you.
>> But it gets you up. It gets you up and
then you lose. It takes a It takes all
the winnings to get the next spin,
doesn't it? Have you noticed that?
>> Do you know where it does?
>> If you number I had number two
yesterday, 100 to one. I had on it. It
takes that win back trying to get It
takes the win back trying to get the
next spin. I know.
>> Yeah. It took 40 quid to get a a green
bar, but the green bar was only about 12
quid. Took over 40. >> Yeah.
>> That far. I don't know that far does it.
>> He seems to be pulling out thousands.
It's [ __ ] isn't it?
>> He doesn't need to work the way he's
going on doing stuff like that. There's
more to the story.
>> It's [ __ ] is it?
It's not right, Peter. Well, something
it's not adding up.
>> No, it's not adding up. There's no way
on this earth he if he if he has won
good on him. But I don't know. There's
more of the story. He doesn't lose. [laughter]
I seen him put a 500 ticket on yesterday
and I thought,
>> bro, he probably puts money in the
machine and takes it out. That's what I
think he does.
>> Yeah, that's what I could that's what
possibly could happen. Maybe. Yeah.
Yeah, I agree with that.
>> Cuz I said to him I said to him I said
to him, "Yeah, why don't you go live
right in the bookies?" And he says, "Oh,
you get banned, but I've gone live in
bookies. Lo J has g live in bookies." I
said, "Okay, then next time you're in
the city, like leads, go live in the
bookies, and if you get chucked out, you
get chuck, but he's he won't go live
doing it. Have you noticed?"
>> Yeah, that's it, lad. Um Oh, [ __ ]
Yeah, there's something to miss with
that, Joe. It's not right. Even L went
to collect his winnings yesterday and I
caught a a clip of LJ saying like he
lost 200. Like, how do these people win?
No one ever wins on them.
>> I know. And Smokeoky B as well. Smokey B
has said as well whenever he puts money
and he just lose lose lose lose lose.
Everyone's saying it, bro. You're saying
it. I'm saying it. Everyone's saying it.
>> But your but your but your wins every
time he plays and Nah. I'd love to.
>> [ __ ] is it? I noticed, you know,
when they you know when they updated the
terminals last December, do you remember
when they updated it? They upgraded
them. Do you remember? >> I
>> That's when they started getting worse.
Like you couldn't win on them. like last
December. It was I think
>> not last December, the December before that. November.
>> Yeah. Yeah.
>> November. December. And they and they
upgraded them and now you can't win
nothing. You can't even get a [ __ ]
bonus on it.
>> You know what [ __ ] me off on them F
days. I haven't played them for a long
time. Me and I ended up having a go
yesterday. What [ __ ] me off is you hit
your best number. It gives you 10 to one.
>> Yeah, it does. It does. It does. I was
shouting in there yesterday. I said it's
a [ __ ] jaw glad. Was people was
people was people looking at you?
>> There was a guy next to me on the
machine. He was watching me like he's on
he's on T I think it was. And I said
look I said look at that. I said are you
number are you
>> what was the what was the what what what
spins was you doing? Like how big was
the green and how big was
>> like a quart was like a 12 quid spin 12
quid spins I was doing but um
>> I I had like a [ __ ] a quid on 12
numbers me and hoping for get like a 75
100 to one.
>> Yeah. Yeah.
I can't even get a bonus, bro. I can't
even get a [ __ ] bonus
when I've played them.
What made you gamble? Did you put a
football bet on or something?
>> Did you put a Did you put a football bet
on or something? That's why you done it?
>> I don't I got a one in yesterday, lad.
I've got the snippet here. I've got you
had um 20 quid on um Leicester eight
West Brom Leicester scor 94th minute in
Nigeria to win by our I put I put three
I don't know three both score no draw
and I got two out of three bro the other day
>> gutting bro
[ __ ] win anything from them man especially
>> you can win on football you can win on
football but not them machines you can
win on you don't have to double both
both teams to score you could
>> but Not for
>> he's full of [ __ ] in it. He's full of
>> I need that Joseph Ferrar in the box and
we need to have this out cuz it's not
adding up to me any bad.
>> He's scared to talk. So how's that going to happen?
>> Or even in the chat he needs to come on
cuz it's not right man. Like I watch I
sat and played it yesterday for an hour
and I was up and down up and down like
and when you do it your best number you
never get the 100 to one or 75 to one or
50 to one or 10 to one or 20 to one all the time.
>> Yeah. I'll just tell him to put videos
up where he's winning in it. But then he
But he can't even do that. So
>> it is [ __ ] man. It's hard to win anything now.
>> It is. It is. Yeah. Yeah.
>> I'm going to drink.
>> I'm going to go get some breakfast in a
bit. Like um I went to McDonald's yesterday.
>> Nice, man. [snorts]
>> I had them wraps from McDonald's.
>> No, I went I went Greg's yesterday. I
got a steak bacon, a bacon and cheese
wrap. They just come out.
>> Yeah, the nice them
>> when they just come out. You know when
they just come out? >> Yeah.
>> My favorite's the bacon and cheese wrap
though still. I think I think that's my favorite.
>> I like them. I'll probably say my
favorite from Gregs is
>> sausage roll.
>> Nah, they are nice, but they're not my
go. I like the um I like I like I like
the chicken bakes, mate.
>> I've not had that one. I've only had a
steak bake. The steak bake's nice, but
you need to be careful because it can
burn you like it can scorch your mouth
in it when you're biting in it and it
just leaks. You know what I mean? The mint.
>> I like the bacon and cheese wrap. The
bacon and cheese wraps are so lovely
when they come out. Have you had one?
>> Yeah, I used to always get them. But
they're expensive out there.
>> They are. Yeah.
>> I don't really I don't really like
sausage roll, you know, man.
>> I don't mind it. I don't mind it. It's
not my favorite.
>> Yeah, that self.
>> Yeah, they're always hot as well. Do you
think he's just loading the machine up
with 500 and playing 20? Yeah,
>> Sean Boyce. Yeah, that's a high
possibility. Yeah, cuz there's no way
that he wins all the time. It's
there's no way on this earth he's
winning every [ __ ] single day. Every
time he plays on properties, he doesn't
lose it. It's not adding up at
>> and you're not winning like that either
anyway. It's like every other day he's
posting. How are you winning that kind
of money every other day?
>> If that's the case, he doesn't need to
work. Yeah, he says he works, but he's
on here a lot as well, isn't he? Think
if you think about it,
>> I think he does work. He does work, lad,
but he just There's no way he's running
on them properties every every time.
>> How come you're not How come you're not
back at work?
>> It's snowing in. [laughter]
>> So, what tomorrow then?
>> Um, I'll be back tomorrow. I was meant I
was back yesterday, but I was I'm
>> You know, you know it's snow. You know
it's snowing in Belgium.
>> I wouldn't know, mate. that I've got a
friend in Belgium.
That Irish flame, she's a gobler, [laughter]
>> you know.
>> Do you think Do you think Do you think
Belgium has a dentist?
>> Obviously. Yeah.
>> Well, it's like maybe not though, is it?
Cuz it's I don't know.
>> I was laughing yesterday when you said
that Sean's scared of the dentist.
>> Yeah, he is scared of the dentist. [snorts]
>> Yeah, lad.
>> I'm going to the dentist tomorrow.
I go every six months, man.
>> Yeah, that's good, man. That's good.
Yeah. [ __ ] what was I saying? Um, so
what do you think of these people st
What do you think of these people
stalking me on Reddit?
Alex B still think it's that red star.
>> Yeah, they're pretending to be a woman and that. [laughter]
>> I'm a I'm afraid of hairdressers. Yeah,
I go to the hairdressers all the time.
Oh, okay. That's nice, man. That's nice.
>> I don't know. I don't know why I'm going
to keep doing this.
>> It's cuz they got no life.
>> Yeah. Yeah.
>> It's got no life, mate. They got no
life. So, what else are they going to
do? That's why I don't react to these clowns, bro.
>> I was just in a bad mood the other day.
That's why they don't bother me. They're
They're just self projectors, bro. You
go on Lavy's channel.
>> I've seen him win that football bet
which was a nice little win. And I I
watched a little he done a little short
saying um he lost 200 quid on the fab
like he said I don't know I don't know
people win. He's right man. No one wins on them.
>> They don't they don't mate. When I put
Listen when I put £100 on the on on the
machine. I got it to 140 and I lost it
all in the bar roulette. Bro, it took
like 80 pound to get the next spin.
>> Yeah. It's [ __ ] scandalous. They
shouldn't even be allowed in the bookies
and fies. They've ruined the They've
ruined the bet shop and f
>> it's addicting though. You know that
global um you know the global draw
roulette bro it's the way it l like you
know how you can tell what number it's
going on it's addictive bro it is
>> yeah you know where about you know
whereabouts it's going that's what I was
playing in coral has to like
>> have you played the roulette with the
three uh zeros
>> no I wouldn't wouldn't wouldn't ever play that
I've won big on that before like a grand
from 60 a couple years ago
>> why would you play roulette what's got three zeros
>> I don't think it had three I think I had
two at that point it had two but now
they've put more on it Yeah, I've seen
I've seen that, Peter. They've got three
zeros and whoever plays that a fool.
>> I think it's four now, bro. One I think
it's four or five now.
>> They got four zeros. >> Yeah,
>> they'd be [ __ ] idiots who play that
roulette, though. That's how thick the
people are, man.
>> Because they know that if they didn't
have that, then people could still win,
you know, even though they've got the bar in. >> Yeah.
>> Have you seen it in a pub where where
they have that bar roulette, but you can
only win 100? Have you seen it? Um,
yeah, I've seen that. Tim Eldridge has
put a few videos on, but I haven't I
haven't remember the one. Do you
remember the one with the four wheels
like in the pub?
>> The the when I was playing with when I
was playing with little Isabelle.
>> Oh, the the fruit machine.
>> No, no, the four roulette wheels. It's
got four wheels. It lands.
>> Oh, yeah. Like red, blue, green, and
Yeah, I've seen that. Yeah, I've played
that before [laughter] [ __ ]
Yeah. You remember when I was playing
that with Lil Isabelle?
>> I kind of lad. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
>> What? You remember the video?
>> Hi. Hi.
>> Why Timmy Timmy doesn't take a day off
gambling, does he?
>> Tim is wild. >> Yeah,
>> I've seen Tim Eldridge upload the
barrels yesterday. King Blitzes. I think
he was Mikey and they had a little win,
didn't they? Got all the gold. >> Yeah.
>> Yeah. I like
>> you should you should go to Belgium.
>> No, lad.
>> Why? You might like it.
>> It's not for me. Belgium, babe.
>> Has your parents been? >> No.
>> You You know people that's been there in it?
>> Um I don't know anybody who's been to
Belgium personally, lad. [laughter]
>> Amsterdam. You Amsterdam. You know
people that's been in it.
>> Yeah, that's Yeah. Yeah. You haven't
been there, have you?
>> No, I don't smoke green and that me so
wouldn't be for me. [laughter]
>> I don't, but I did when I was there.
>> Nah, [ __ ] off for me that lad.
>> Oh, do you know who I've not seen? That
account that used to come keep mocking
me. Do you remember that account that
says poor [ __ ] you need to get back at
these [ __ ] women and that? You know
the one I'm talking about it.
>> I have seen it floating the vault lad.
>> I don't know who it is. I don't know who
it is though. I don't know who it is.
>> I thought it was Joker but I don't think
so. Mac. No, I won't be joking. Joking.
All right, man. McDonald's have gone on
your menu, you know.
>> Really? I might have to check that out.
>> Check it out.
>> Hey, what was your favorite burger from
McDonald's? Mom was Mom was a big ass on there.
>> The Philly steakhouse, I think.
>> Yeah, Philly cheese stack.
>> that was [ __ ] [clears throat] nice,
Peter. That was mate. Yeah, it was them.
>> They don't They don't do Let me Let me
see the menu. Hold on. Let me have a
little gander. You [clears throat] know
what that means? means have a little
look. Billy Chier Gravy used to that
used to be my favorite. The cheese sauce
used to be a messy burger like to be
fair, but it was probably my favorite that
>> So when I used to say to Monty, why do
these people call me skint? What did he
used to say?
>> Because they're skint themselves. [laughter]
>> True, though. They
>> Oh yeah, I'm looking. I'm looking. Oh
yeah, that big that big arch looks good.
>> That big arch as well, Pete. Chicken Big
Mac. That's what I I used to get a
chicken Big Mac. Surf and turf.
Chicken chicken cheeseburger. Oh wow.
>> Yeah, we [ __ ] love that. I know what
I used to do to get double cheeseburger
chicken meal and put the chicken me
inside the cheeseburger. That's exactly
what that is. Lush then.
>> Yeah, it looks
Where's your newest KFC?
about two mile away. >> What? >> Yeah.
>> Are you having a McDonald's today, Grezy?
>> Oh, I think I think Did you get told off, >> Sunny?
>> Did you get told off?
>> Mom's lad.
>> Ronny's been off here, but I think yeah,
there's something going on with like him
getting his kids back and stuff. It
makes sense. I think like why he's not
on here. It's got to be is it?
>> Um, yeah.
>> You get what I mean?
>> They got that Monty man off of you, but
he should have got off a long time ago
before all [laughter] the damage was done.
>> Yeah. Who got him on here though? >> You.
>> Yeah, that's it. Grevy lad. Yeah, you
should do another um another video
testing all the new menu.
>> No. Who actually got Did I actually get
Montlly on here? But I I tried to get
him off though, didn't I?
>> Yeah, but you got him on.
>> Yeah, but I did
>> I just said to him one I just said to
him one day. Yeah. I hadn't spoke to him
in ages and we met on PlayStation. I
said, "Oh, do you want to come and argue
like come in this community? There's a
guy called Timmy Elders, isn't it?"
>> Yeah. Yeah.
>> Then he [snorts] joined and then Yeah.
Um that's how it started. Yeah. And they
all started like making accounts with
his family and that. But
>> yeah, I've seen that about I I Yeah,
that pat must have used to make one of
his daughter and that man. He was a sick
hunt and like
>> Yeah. Yeah.
>> He was the worst person on
>> Oh, do you remember Filthy Ben?
>> Yeah, he was on the other day, Ben. He
was on Lester, I think.
>> So, what what did he say like two years
ago in January?
>> Yeah. I wonder what's happened with that
seaside Mark Grey. I think they finally
defeated him, haven't they? You were Peter.
>> What What did Ben say two years ago? >> January.
>> Same same [ __ ] Same people. See you
next year. And he had the air off.
>> That's funny, isn't it? You That was on
Timmy's as well, wasn't it? That was on Timmy's.
>> Yeah, it was on Timmy.
>> So you said it would always So you said
it would always be the same people.
>> Yeah. Never change. There might be a few.
>> They've got to be bots in it. They've
got to be robots in it. They've got to
be bots. There
>> is a few bots about Yeah. Yeah.
Because how can they do it every day for
five? That doesn't make sense, is it?
And what do they just write the same?
It's like you do remember what Monty man
said. He said you come in this community
and you can't even take a bite of your
cornflakes without seeing the word skin.
[laughter] He says you tried to you get
a spoon and you tried to put it in your
mouth and your skin. Yeah.
>> That's what he said there. Yeah.
>> Yeah. What did Monty say on Christmas Day
when he was live? Um,
>> he says, "Oh, I've just gone live."
Yeah. To see who's watching me. So,
anyone watching me has got no family
life up. That's five people watching me
now. That's five people without family
on Christmas. That's what you said in it. Yeah.
>> Yeah. He was all right. Bond, man. Like,
>> so what you're saying, he got run off.
>> They done him, didn't they? Got got him
off. H these people.
>> But would would have would have they
ever left him alone if he stayed?
>> No, they did. They've just done this
just continue to [ __ ] to comment on that.
I'm full of cold me.
>> It's cold to be fair. It's probably cold
where you are as well.
>> I'm going go Greg's me.
>> Oh, to to get something to warm Do you
know what I like in this weather? Like a
nice hot curry, bro. You know, to warm you up.
>> Yeah. Yeah.
>> Like a nice bindaloo. Warms you up nicely, man.
Yeah, I'm under I'm I was under the
electric blankie the other day. I had
three covers on me and I was under the
electric blankie. That's how cold it is.
>> I seen [ __ ] Lavy saying um that you
can't apart to put the heat on or
something. That's why you're under the electric blanket.
>> Oh, did they? That's nice for them, bro.
They they like to talk a lot of [ __ ] in it.
>> They think Why did they do this, man?
>> Cuz they ain't got a life.
>> Yeah, but I've seen
13 years ago. I think what happened with
Yeah, I saw one that's 18 years ago.
>> What's this?
>> I think what happened with Monty was
karma for what he done to girls on PlayStation.
>> Yeah. So why don't you people go nons?
Why don't you go for nons legs? He's a
>> because Shing you more than Sean. So
they have to
>> Yeah. Yeah. But yeah, but even when I
was arguing with Monty though, they they
still they still went for him.
>> I know. Because the what these people do?
>> They're retards, isn't it?
>> It's when it suits, isn't it?
>> Yeah, pretty much. Yeah.
And don't want to be Yeah, that nonsleg
just tells the same stories, isn't it?
Is it the same stories?
>> Yeah. Just just I um I commented on his
thing yesterday actually wrong on
Central's account. I said, "What's all
this Dr. Pepper thing about?" I said, "I
don't understand it." He said, "I'm
going to go live." But he never went
live. Yeah, he did.
>> Did you go live? I was out then. Me, I had
>> Yeah, I saw it. It's just the same [ __ ] in it.
>> Yeah, I didn't see it actually.
>> So, what what stories is it the same?
>> Just virgin and all that [ __ ] in it. And [laughter]
>> it's boring, isn't it? It's so boring, you know.
>> No, this community will be all right if
we Brock add some better crack.
>> Yeah. Stop repeating and different
people as well in it. Mix up. Yeah. And
PJ tells the same stories about Jericho
call for past six months. That could be
>> I couldn't because I couldn't believe
how like it's just mad how he used to
copy. I couldn't get over it, bro. But
you know, he's been telling the same
stories for [ __ ] years.
>> Yeah. Yeah.
>> The Chinatown story. That's years, bro. That is it.
>> They've got no else to do, have they? [laughter]
>> Monty's funny, is it?
>> Monty was all right, actually. Yeah, he
was. They just called him the [ __ ] ns
and all that. And they made his life.
>> Hopefully hopefully when Lord Hopefully
when Lord Jes live today, it'll be
different people, is it?
>> No, the same [ __ ] cheek or
>> Didn't you hear saying, "Oh, what's his
name?" Uh, that Daz B. He was like, "Oh,
it's the same faces, lad."
>> Who said that far?
>> No, the Scouse. No, no, the Scala one.
>> Oh, yeah. Yeah.
>> You know the one that goes at Timmy?
Well, used to go at Timmy. out.
>> He said, "It's the same faces, isn't it?" [laughter]
>> Tiger used to say, "It doesn't matter
what time, what place, whatever. It's
the same. It's the same faces."
>> Oh, dear Tiger. >> Yeah,
it's the same people every day. Oh,
same people. Same people. I would have
thought cuz it was a new year, it would
have been different.
No, never been the same. It's the same [ __ ]
>> But what makes me laugh is how they can
call people disabled when they repeat
the same [ __ ] for [ __ ] seven years.
Six, seven years to be fair, every day
like commenting that in it.
>> You know what I think of it now? These
people actually like 40 year olds, 45
year old people, right? like they should
be going on all day with the families
that instead of just wanting to be on this YouTube mental [laughter]
>> it's bad is it and they do it in the
summer as well when they should be out
yeah enjoying the nice weather they're
sat sat indoors have you notic that
>> it's like it's summer coming it's the
world cup in our morning be I'll be out
[ __ ] for every England game but these
people still be on here
>> cuz they've got no friends and they've
got no life
>> but that's why though yeah That's fine.
But then it's they tried to call other
people. That's what makes me laugh. They
tried to call other people.
>> Calling the pop black.
>> Yeah, basically. Yeah, you should have a
go in them f today.
>> I need to go collect it a bit like lad. But $28. Yeah. 20.
>> Yeah, put it in the fy, lad. [laughter]
>> Put it in the [clears throat] fy and do
a little video.
>> I know. I might do a little video and
upload to be honest. Like if if I go on
If you do it, if you do a video, if you
do a video, I I'll go and do a video
>> on the property.
>> Yeah. Yeah. Well, do you know what?
There's a ch I was in a pissed-off mood
yesterday. Yeah. And there's a small
chance I can get back deep into the
gambling again, but I always like don't
do it. I always choose not to, but
there's a chance it could happen in it.
>> What? Because of the mood swings. >> Yeah.
>> Yeah. But even when you play these, even
if you lose a tenny, it's still if
you're right with yourself.
>> Yeah. I I want to like I I want to try
and win, you know.
>> I was just pissed off in on the FB
yesterday, man. It was me numbers and it
was giving us 10 to one, 20 to one. It's
a symbol, man.
>> Bless you in life. Then
you should come to London. We could go
for a nice Indian meal.
>> How much do you pay for an Indian there? E
>> expensive, bro.
>> So if you sit down places I go, well, it
depends. The places I go is expensive
cuz it's in the city is it?
Probably like 40 50.
Anyways, I'm gone. Yeah. [ __ ] They are