Oh, that was yummy. That filled me right up.
That was yummy. [Music]
Lovely. [ __ ] bored today,
man. Bored. Bored. Bored. Bored. stream your
link. But yeah, after I'm gone for a
couple of weeks,
man, it's cuz I bought nothing to do. Come on
here. It's the same idiot, same repeat as well. [ __ ] Come on.
Yeah, I'm [ __ ] nice.
Oh yeah, the football back didn't win.
[ __ ] Only got one
go. That's [ __ ] [ __ ] Alex.
Strange. It's strange. [Music]
Yes, I heard you're putting content up
on your channel. That's nice for you.
I'm going off I'm gone after stay after two
weeks. Nothing changes, bro. You come
off this for two days, three days, a week, two
weeks, [ __ ] two years, 20 years. Nothing ever
changes. These people will never stop
repeating. It's mad, is it? They've been
doing it for
[ __ ] They've been doing it for about
[ __ ] 13 years. cuz these people been
on here since 2012. I haven't, but I've
heard about it. Imagine that. And
they're still using the
same same uh sayings. It's madness, isn't
it? Ask yourself this question. What
have these people done in 15
years? Nothing, bro.
I really fancy a Guinness man, but I'm on a
[ __ ] Yeah, a nice cherry as
well. I ain't doing that.
[ __ ] busy down the [ __ ]
streets. You are busy busy busy.
Listen to my friend. You want to go out?
Give it a whirl.
Nah. [ __ ] that. I'm
chilling. Good to have these little
um you know
chills. So when did that come out
then? Got to be next Friday that comes out. Yeah, it
is. Why is it so late? [Music]
Listen to a fair. I wish you was here,
lad. Give it a
while. He's a b at the
moment. Yeah, it' be good if he was there,
man. Not anymore. I haven't done for ages. I used
to, but I don't really care about sex
that much anymore like I used
to. So, don't really care about it,
bro. Yeah, I used to all the time. One
month I spent like £400 on
it. I spent £400 in the [ __ ] escorts
before. It was like a few months ago.
Yeah, it was
mad. What do you reckon would happen if
I went out today approaching the sausage
rolls? What do you think the woman would
say? The women would say if I go out
approaching today sausage
rolls. I know. I already know, bro.
I think I know the
answer. I'm not going to say it, mate.
it. My friend's out, but I'm out.
Yeah. And you know what?
Yeah. That's another reason to have this
little detox as well is that if you
notice right, they are literally all the
same. Like bear with me. Like women, men, you
see the same people with the same
attitude. Like whenever you go out, you
see the same women, right? with the same
attitude, the same look that they they
they walk around like their [ __ ] don't
stink. Same [ __ ] men with attitude
and same [ __ ] men that women go for.
That's another thing. It's like you see
the same people everywhere. They're like
NPCs. They're literally like NPCs,
lad. Yeah, they are all the same, bro.
Why is it that they all say the same
[ __ ] They've got a boyfriend. Why don't
they say they're not interested and why
they're not interested or like just walk
away or just say they're not looking for
something? Why do they all say they've
got They're all the
same. Yeah, I'm out of this country soon
anyways, bro. I am out this country soon
anyways. I'll be out soon anyways.
This is the same memory. We'll book a
holiday in a couple of weeks. Yeah.
Yeah. Don't know where I'm going yet,
mate. Don't know where I'm going. And
then obviously I'll just save and I'll
just go out once a week here.
Yeah, I just go out once a week here and that's
it. Every Saturday or Yeah, something like
that. Or maybe Saturday, then Thursday
and next Saturday.
Yeah. I do like drinking Guinness, man.
But I think I'm getting kind of fat, you
know? I don't think so.
Yeah. A little bit. probably just
eight. But yeah, they're all the same,
but everyone has the same attitude in this
country. Obviously, I've got this woman
from near Birmingham. She said she'll
meet me. I don't mind traveling,
man. I don't mind traveling.
Plenty of hot girls in the
gym. I'm not even going to answer that
question. Have you not seen my approaching
videos? Have you not seen my This is
what makes me think a lot of you people
on this community have got brain
damage. I think a lot of you on here
have got brain damage. You're telling
me, have I thought of going to the gym
to get plenty of hot girls, right? Have
you not seen my approaching
videos? So, if you've seen my
approaching videos, why would you then tell
me? Oh, um, I'll show you an approach
video from last week. Oh, that's fair
enough. Let me jog your memory a little
bit. I'll be out here soon, mate. I'll soon. Trust
Oh, this is an approach I done on
Tuesday. Yeah, this was Tuesday. I done this approach
Tuesday. That's the last time I dr up. Yeah. Fair
play. Fair play for what, bro?
What? Wanted to leave this [ __ ] whole
country. Yeah, you don't say
[ __ ] Um I don't know yet. I've not
decided. But then I'll just go out once a week
here until I go over it because got
drinking anyways. might as [Music]
well. That's a good shout,
man. Yeah. So, so
G, I just done an appro I done an
approach on Tuesday. I just sent you it,
bro. I think it was quite a
banger. Well, they've all got imaginary boyfriends.
Boss need to go on a few different detoxes, man.
Damn. Yeah. I don't know what country I
haven't decided yet. Put my passport back. Yeah. There we go. Not human.
Bye-bye. You love it. What? The YouTube
losers love it. The losers that ain't
got no life that start on YouTube every
day. Yeah, good for
you. What do you mean? English girls
don't do it, bro. But I just sent you a
[ __ ] approach video. What do you mean,
man? Just sent you a [ __ ] old
approach video. It's funny how you say
we. Because when you say we, you're
talking about you little YouTube losers
from Lord J's channel. You ain't got a
life. That's why you're sat on YouTube
every day because you ain't got nothing
in your lives. That's why you come on
here projecting every day for a reaction
because your lives are that empty.
Imagine that, bro. These people have
been on here since 2012. Absolute sad
acts. That's what this community is.
Yeah, I just come back from a
restaurant, bro. This community is just
full of sad acts. Like absolute failures
in life. I swear to God, lad. They're
absolute losers, man.
No, I'm not talking about you. I'm
talking about this guy. They're absolute
sad act losers. I swear to God, bro. My
whole life. Yeah. I've come across so
many different communities. Yeah. And
I've never come across such a disabled
loser community than this one. I swear
to God, bro, they're all [ __ ] losers.
Um had a curry and some chicken picker. the death
chair. Don't know what you're all about.
Bye-bye. Yeah, they're absolute losers,
mate. These people in this community are
absolute lo. They're like the dregs of
society. You don't even see these people
out in public. You know, you know these
people on YouTube, these spastics,
right? You don't even see them in
public. You don't even see these kind of
people in public. The
madness. Uh, depends where you
go. I got chicken ta curry coke rice. It
cost me 22 quid, so it weren't bad. Yeah.
It wasn't bad to be fair. It was nice.
I'm not doing anything late. I'm just
chilling. Chilling in bed. That's [ __ ]
all to do, man. I'm just going out. Yeah.
Well, rough would have been rough,
buddy. Rough in what
way? Uh, I met Lord and I was in public.
Well, actually, it wasn't in public. It
was outside my front doorstep. So,
actually, it wasn't in public.
Yeah, they're [ __ ] bro. They hate most
men. Welcome to England, bro.
Yeah, welcome to the
westyland. It's very hard in these westernized
countries. But it's not even just that.
It's like I was saying a minute ago,
it's like whenever you go out, you see
the same people with the same attitude, like
NPCs. Like you get you'll see women
walking around all stuck up like their
[ __ ] don't stink. You see the same
[ __ ] men. Like you see literally the
same people everywhere you
go. [ __ ] It bors me, man. It actually
me. It It's actually It actually bors me,
bro. You experience that as well. It
[ __ ] bors me, man.
Same [ __ ] men as well you see
around. They got attitude as well,
lad. Yeah, it is a dump, mate.
Hopefully making use of that passport this year, mate.
Yeah. And these people don't know anyone
they're talking about on here. But I'll
give you an example. They just call me
Skimp. How am I able to get food if I'm
skinned? Nope. You know what I'm saying, bro?
Madness. These people call themselves every day,
lad. It would have been a good day to go
out drinking today cuz the weather's
nice and that,
but I'm not doing it, bro. I'm not doing
it. I've got enough numbers anyways.
So, but at least I'm 27 learning this.
At least I'm not 32 like Ant-Man when he
finally left. You know, at least you
know, at least you know now that
like, you know, you're 27, this country's
dead. You know, people are not really
interested in this country. Quite a
young age to start knowing this now, you
know. Well, maybe you didn't know. I don't know.
Yeah, it's a mad city there.
Yeah, they've all got
boyfriends. They've all got invisible
boyfriends. They've all got boyfriends,
but most men are single and they hate
men, but they got boyfriends. But you
know, a lot of these people don't even
like, you know, a lot of them. Yeah.
They don't even like friends. A lot of
them are just like celibate. You know
that a lot of these
women they're celibate and you know are
or they just most men you'll see most
men are single bro trust me. So how the
[ __ ] can they how the [ __ ] can they all
have boyfriends when most men are single
and they hate most men because they've
got the same minds? Just
doesn't add up. Hey grievy. Did you like
the curry lad? It was
nice. Did you like it? Do you remember
my parents left me? They flew away. They
left me in the old nestic was by
myself. Oh, it's uh almost April. Uh
Grezy, it's almost a grievy. A
Zippy, you have to go on them uh dating
apps, don't you, boss? You said in April
you was going to go on them dating apps.
Okay with you, boss.
Yeah, I love Greavvesy, man. He can be a
white knight at times, but I still love
him. Isn't that right, Grezy? You can be
a bit of a white knight sometimes, but I
still [ __ ] love you, bro. You know
this. You know this,
lad. No, no, no.
No, you said before. You said before you
was going to Okay, well then don't use dating apps
then. That's up to you. But you said you
was going, dude.
But so well don't
then. Up to you, buddy.
Yeah. What's the best way to pick up? Leave
England. Uh, leave
England and go to Asia. Sorry,
man. Cuz they're not interested in this country.
Well, unless you're a drug dealer or a
[ __ ] big YouTuber with millions of followers.
Yeah, they're NPCs. It's like if I went
out today, bro, I'd get the same result.
If I was to go out today, I'd get, oh,
I've got a boyfriend.
Yeah, they've got the same They've got
the same minds. They're the
same. You know what I'm
saying? Why would you make mistakes,
Greasy? You still housebound, Grezy?
that? What should we call you? Daniel,
huh? Yeah. Just chilling
today. I bullied you. Yeah. You bullied
me so much that when I come to your
country, you kept your mouth shut. Yeah.
You've bullied me so much that you let
me come to your country two times and
you shhat your pants. Yeah, I'm bullied
so senseless. I'm like shaking right
now. You let me come to your country and
you done nothing about it two times. And
another thing is you're calling me skin,
mate. You can't even afford an iPad. You
silly little kilwearing [ __ ] sausage.
Shut the [ __ ] up, mate. I come to your
country and you done nothing about it.
Everyone saw it. Literally everybody saw
it. Bro, your anxiety is so bad you
can't even talk. You are the ma. You're
the alltime skin m. You can't afford an
iPad. You can't talk because you sound
like a spaz. You let me come to your
country and you don't do anything about
it. You are the bully victim.
You literally are the bully victim and
and everybody knows it, buddy. You know,
but guess what, Mike? I came to your
country and you done nothing and
everyone saw it. Where was you bullying
me when I was in your country and you
went quiet? Do you remember when I was
in your [ __ ] [ __ ] hole country? And I
can and I can say that as well. I've
been to your country and you done nothing. Stop deflecting. Stop
deflecting and you're banned. Bye-bye.
See the This is the same [ __ ] right,
I've been dealing with for [ __ ] years
with this spast with these spastics.
This is why I don't come on here. It's a
waste of life. It's a waste of time,
bro. They're all idiots. They're all
repeaters. They're all little people
with [ __ ] up lives. He lives in
Scotland. This why I don't bother
anymore, bro. This is why you don't see me
much. He lives in
Scotland and I've been there two times
and he kept quiet. This is why I don't
bother. [ __ ] So, he has to go. Yeah,
man. This is why I don't really bother
with this anymore, bro. Same spastics,
same people, same
comments. No one really has a normal chat anymore.
So, yeah. I didn't pretend to go USA,
bro. I went to USA. The [ __ ] shut her
mouth. I might be going back there as
well to be
fair. Yeah, bro. I'll get myself [ __ ] mad trouble,
bro. I'd love to give her a hide and
greasy. That USA is You won't even believe it,
lad. Uh because I want to. Bye-bye.
I'd love to uh groovy
dad. Yeah, I said to I said to her ma I
messaged her mom on Instagram. I said
that's all you can do is make group
chats to people but in real life you
know you're about nothing and you would
ever be about
nothing. That's why I said I said it to
her mom. I said it to her mom and her
dad cuz it's the truth, bro. That behind
a keyboard you can be what you want but
we all know the real you. The real you
in real life ain't about [ __ ]
So pathetic, man. Pathetic, eh?
Yeah. I pretty much hate women to be
honest. If I'm honest with you,
bro. No good comes from
them. All the same as
well, you know.
All the same as well, bro. It's partly
why I'm just chilling today,
man. Yeah. So many keyboard warriors on
this community, bro. It's boring. Uh
yeah, years ago. But now I just spit on
it. Yeah, I've got a video of me
spitting on the machine, but I'm not
going to put it up. I've actually got two. Yeah, man.
man. It's [ __ ] humid, bro. I like it.
So, the film comes out on
Friday. Yeah, it comes out next Friday. Oh,
[ __ ] Do you want to see the video of me
spitting on it,
Grezy? Yeah, they are retards, man. They
are [ __ ] retards.
You want to see it,
Grezy? Those some mad videos, bro.
Yeah, I'll show you, bro, if you
want. Yeah, I'll show you if you want.
Yeah, I'll show you,
bro. I'm uploading it now.
Yeah, I sp it. But you actually see my [ __ ]
flame. They called the police. I think police were called. Uh
Yeah, I think police were
called. Police were cold. Yeah.
That was a bad boy.
Lovely. Was a lovely site, mate. Was a
site. No wonder you're single. You are
single. You are single and alone. Stop talking about
yourself. Stop talking about yourself.
You look white.
Oh, bro. I think Do you know what it
was? It was that they lost 40 quid. It
was weeks ago. I don't play them no
more. I don't play them no more. But it
was when I was in the mall going to go
to the cinema.
Bro, you are single decked and you're a
white knight. How's that? Yeah.
That man's out there giving it a whirl,
lad. Yeah. Story of your life, King of
Belf. Story of your life. All alone. But
the thing is, you do something that I
don't. You You
uh lost it. I lost 20 pound. You have to
simp over women. You're pathetic. You
have to simp. Imagine having to simp
over women on YouTube. That's how you
know you're down bad, man. When you have
to simp over women on YouTube. Your life is
[ __ ] Nope. Not yet. Not yet,
mate. I don't know where I'm going yet.
I never said I booked anything. I said I'm going
to man's just come back. He's on the
pool tonight. I'm sat here with
[ __ ] I'm sat here in front of a
fan. But it beats getting I've got a
boyfriend. So why do you simp anyways?
RJ, why do you
simp? Why do you simp
man? Yeah, he's owning a monster.
when you're when you start roofing
course never in your mind. This is why I
don't even bother coming on here anymore,
man. This is why I don't
bother. Cuz you're just repeating little no lives. Idiots. Absolute
idiots. You call yourselves m every day.
You call yourself skint every day. It's [ __ ] mad.
Like you are the ones that have to sit
on YouTube every day jealous of someone,
bro. You know what? What could you just
think about this, right? What could
these people on here possibly have in
their life when they have to sit on here every day
self-projecting? What do these people
really have in their life? Nothing. They
have nothing in their life. You know, they're
old, miserable, skimp people that come
on YouTube and take out on other people
what these people are themselves. You
know, that's what they
do. I'm live for the second time today,
brother. I was off YouTube for over a
week. Over a
week because of you people, man. You're just
boring. That's all you do. Like, honest
to God. Like, you just bore people.
You just literally bore people off here.
Boring. You don't psychologically [ __ ]
with anyone. You don't bully no one. You
bully yourselves. Really, you just
embarrass yourselves every day, man.
Really, if I'm honest with you,
man. Sad, man. You have nothing else to
do than to come on here and do do what
you do every day. It's
sad. And you don't stop as well. Like
some of you have been doing this since [ __ ]
2012, but um 2012 some of you been doing
this since and you call me like Yeah,
madness. People are
disabled. And that's another thing when
when you say us, yeah, the YouTube
spastics that ain't got a life. Us is
the YouTube spastics that ain't got a
life. You people are in desperate need
of a life, lad.
when you're down to who's sitting in a bed sit,
bro. What are you talking about? Who's
Who's in a bedsit? I didn't know I was
bedsit. Yeah, I'm I'm in a bedsit. I'm
in a bedsit. I'm in a bedsit and I've
got no money. Yeah. Okay, bro. Again,
self self- projection gets you
nowhere. Self-p projection gets you
nowhere in life. You know, you should
know this by now. Self-p
projection gets you nowhere in life.
Where has it got you so far in these
years that you've been doing it? I'm
down to my last
penny. We all know why you people go on
about money. It's cuz you ain't got none
yourself. That's why you go on about
money every day. cuz you ain't got none.
It's why you're sat on YouTube every
day, stinking your beds out, calling
people what you are, yourselves, your own
life. You know what I'm saying? And
that's it. That's it. You people, it
goes to show, look, I was off of YouTube
for over a week. These people can't take
one day off of YouTube cuz it's their
whole life. They got no friends. They've
never had a woman. They got no money.
That's why they're on here. No life. No
life but YouTube.
That's why the real ones actually come
off and never come back. [ __ ] these people are
idiots. I work you on
pip. You're boring me. Boring.
Boring. Get blocked. Get blocked. Get
blocked. This is why I don't come on
here, Mr. B anymore,
bro. This is why I literally don't come
on here anymore. Because of these
people. because of these repeaters. Same
atmosphere every day. Same repeating
every day. You feel it as soon as you're
on here as well. So, this is why I don't
bother, bro. This is why you don't see
me for days at a time, weeks at a time,
because it's so boring. It is actually
boring. It's like It's like literally Yeah.
Someone you you you you're with someone.
Yeah. In real life, just keep repeating
the same story over and over and over again.
or like someone's keep making noise over
and over again. Oh, give it a break. You
know what I'm saying? As in like you're
boring. That's what they are. They don't
psychologically [ __ ] with anyone's head.
They don't bully no one. They just
embarrass themselves and bore people in
the process of doing it. And that's why
I don't even bother no more,
lad. Be off here now for a couple of
weeks after today, lad. It's boring as hell.
boring as [ __ ] Disabled community
finished moving my mouth
up. Yeah, that was a couple weeks ago
just spitting on the machine. It was
funny, but it's
only I only lost 40 I only lost 40 pound as well.
But yeah, it was annoying,
lad. Cuz I was supposed to go cinema, you
see. But I never cuz it ruined my mood.
Yeah. Yeah. These repeat these repeaters
ruin uh they ruin the um they ruin the
channel. Bro, this is what I was saying.
Yeah. This is why I made a new channel
because you don't get these spastics on
here. On my new channel that no one
knows about. You don't get these
spastics. These little repeating little
mongos. You don't get them on here. You
don't get them, bro. You don't get them
on that channel. That's what I mean,
bro. You know, that's why,
like talking about Shorty, I don't talk
about that [ __ ] virgin. The [ __ ] Why
would I be talking about that little
virgin? And no one's crying about the
American. I just state the facts to her
father and her mother that they're all
keyboard warriors and they can only talk
[ __ ] behind the
keyboard. That's what I said.
How is that me crying over them, bro?
I'm just I'm just telling them what they
are. Only big buying a
keyboard because they're a keyboard warrior. That's it.
Yep. Never wanted him, mate. Never [ __ ] wanted
him. That's why he's still a [ __ ] virgin.
Yeah, I seem to attract a lot of [ __ ]
spastics for some reason.
Yeah. And it's been the same spastics
for years as
well. Nah, I'm good, man. I'm on a
detox. I'm on a detox and I will never
talk to him again. He's a snake. I said
when I was live earlier, he better not
[ __ ] ever come back talking to me again.
You better not
[ __ ] ever come back and talk to me
again, bro. [ __ ]
him. [ __ ] [ __ ]
man. It's so mad how he used to give me
[ __ ] for talking [ __ ] about women, but
all he was doing the other day was
talking [ __ ] about women. Madness, is
it? It's crazy, bro.
Chase didn't do the worst as well. Chase
didn't do the worst. He just snaked me a
little bit. Mom.
Um because he wouldn't let me in his
hangouts. And he's blaming me as to what
happened to his
kids. And he and he was prepared to
throw me under the bus by going in these
Discord groups until people snaked him.
No, he done the worst. [ __ ] Chase. Chase
is a [ __ ] I said if I ever see you,
I'll slap you up and you're banned from
London. You are banned from London. You
will never let me know where you are in
London. And he knows it. He's a [ __ ]
Simple. Like they they know what they are, bro.
Yeah. Yeah. Nons will die a virgin. But
yeah, anyways, this decked um this
decked Mark has been on YouTube for
about six, seven years because I
remember him when I was like 22,
21 when I met up with Pepe. See, it's
the same spastics every day. They don't
know when to call it call it a um call
it a day. You know what I'm saying,
lad? This bad is madness. out there. Oh [ __ ] Yeah. die a
virgin. He will die a [Music]
virgin. That's why he's obsessed with
virgins cuz he's one himself. [Music]
Are we gone for a couple of weeks today though, buddy?
No, no, Welcome to football. All right.
I'm watching these approach Yes.
One second there. about that,
bro. I just watch these riz rezes. Um
um I done an approach on Tuesday. I
don't know if you recorded
one mate. I'm
good. I'm off to Thailand,
mate. I'm off to Thailand
and [ __ ] sending it, man. Send
it. No, it's the same in England, man.
They've all got imaginary boyfriends. I
just sent you an approach. I'm sure
that's an approach. Yeah, better
be. No, I said you an approach. I think
it's an approach.
No, sorry. That's the approach. God,
this is the approach on Tuesday,
lad. Let's not mad. So
there I tried was
Thursday. Go watch that video I sent you, man.
I have fun drinking by myself sending it,
man. I have fun drinking by myself and sending
it. But not today. I'm not doing that.
I'm not doing it
today. Just on a detox.
They make you
uncomfortable. Why is
that? You know, [ __ ] me,
bro. Why not? Why
that? Oh [ __ ] [ __ ] naked
eye. I'm actually tired, bro. It must be
curry. Why does my approaches make you
feel uncomfortable, dear, lad?
So, what do you reckon would have
happened today if I went out approaching the
cult? If I went out approaching today,
what do you think would have happened?
Do you think any good would have come from it? No.
Yeah, she rejected his ugly ass. It's
why he's still a virgin.
Yeah, you [ __ ] rejected his [ __ ] ugly
ass, didn't you? C, didn't you,
lad? You [ __ ] rejected his ugly
ass. Yeah. No, some of them reply,
"Well, there's this woman that wants to
meet me, but she lives kind of near
Birmingham, which obviously is a bit of
a [ __ ] but I'll travel. I don't give a
man. I don't mind traveling, bro. It ain't that
deep. It's not that deep,
bro. That's never going to happen
because of cop blocking friends.
That's not a chance cuz they're friends cop.
So it would never work because even if
they did like you or they're a drunk or
a slag like you say. Yeah. It's not
going to work because their friends will cop
block. So it would never happen. Yeah. Obviously.
Well, I'm telling you, mate, it doesn't
happen. I'm telling you, it doesn't
happen. And trust me, my word means a
lot because I've been out there. I know
what it's like out there, bro. I know
what happens. I'm telling you, 99% of
the time it doesn't happen.
Yeah. Yeah. Not in London, mate. Doesn't
work like that in London.
Maybe up north. Doesn't work like that
in London, mate. Trust me, it doesn't
work like that in London.
How do you know they would say they've
got a boyfriend? How do you know about
that boyfriend thing?
Cult that boyfriend thing gets old real far,
bro. I've been to
Nottingham. Yeah. Last time I went to
Nottingham, I got a
[ __ ] Couldn't [ __ ] her cuz she was on her period. Uh
uh. Well, it used to happen to you as
well. What did it used to happen to you
when you used to
approach in London, mostly
Nottingham? What is that they used to
say to you as well? Yeah,
surprised to four times. I think I've
been there four times.
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. But you know the thing
is London is the worst place for it. So
these people these people here
that defend women that white knight
women they're all virgins
virgins. Yeah. They're all they're
virgin. Like the people that defend them
or like people that don't even leave the
house because they would know that when
you go and you speak to a woman, you
would know exactly what they're like.
But these people defend them. So it just
goes to show that they don't really
have much experience in life.
No, I don't play that [ __ ] no
more. Nah, I don't play that bollocks no
more, mate. I stay I'm out of this
country. I'm I'm I'm going on
holiday. Yeah, you're right. It's the
same all over. Yeah,
but when you go to New Well, went to
Newcastle. I had I had women approach
me every everywhere's listen everywhere
is the same but
Asia you know the only place that's that
that that works is
Asia or like Brazil everywhere is the
same America and yeah it doesn't
matter but yeah so it's a lot worse in
London because do you know what it is in
London the thing is with London yet.
I'll tell you what it is with London. It's very westernized.
Yeah. And the thing is, you know, you
know, the thing with London is that when
you go to central London, it's not even
people from London really there anymore
because they're all skin. They can't
even afford to go out. It's people from
[ __ ] Paris, America, Australia. It's
all the people with money and that's why
they think that they're better than you.
It's not even like the time it's not
even English people anymore because
they're too skinned to go out. It's
dead. It's a dying country. It's
finished, bro. UK
finished. People from other countries coming here
because they go
out and go out out up
there. It's the same everywhere, man.
They're entitled. Same attitude. Everywhere but
Asia. Everywhere but Asia,
lad. That'll be like it in 10 years.
Let me lick you up and
down. No, I'm never using dating apps [Music]
again. [ __ ] hell. Yeah, the
monster think she's better than people.
Imagine that, bro. Imagine that M
thinking she's better than me.
No more Frankie ever Gendy.