Just check it to see if it's the same
people. You know what? I'm like Oh yeah. We are.
Uh, it's hurting a little bit. Yeah,
Yeah. I'm speaking to this woman on um
Snapchat and she's she's 39, so she's
almost 40 and they're still [ __ ] Even
at that age, they're still [ __ ]
I got bad vibes from it earlier before I
went to the dentist. You can always pick
up on vibes from people.
Yeah, you I can pick up on bad vibes
from people, bro. Very quickly.
She's a proper proper [ __ ] Like you can
you can tell by the way they type and
what they're saying.
I just said yeah.
Uh she's saying about um
I'm just getting bad vibes. She's saying like she's saying
we was talking earlier yesterday and it
was no problem. And now she's saying,
"Uh, to be honest, you are too young for
me. I feel like a pedo, but I'm 28 years
of age, a grown ass man." Then they've
turned around and said, "To be honest,
if you want to talk, awesome. Anything
more than that is will be a no for me."
I said, basically,
you're really acting stuck up and
stubbing. I I can't be dealing with
that. Had enough of way too many
people's attitude. Take care. Nice
talking to you. Um yeah, just just bad
vibes. You know, when people are giving
bad vibes and acting
like it's it's a vibe that they give, bro.
Like I just thought earlier before I
went dentist, they're just like, "But
no, don't act like you're better than
me, mate." I won't speak to someone that
thinks they're better than me.
Especially at that age, like you expect
it from younger people
because that's that. Like don't think
you're better than me. I won't talk to
someone that think they're better than
me. I don't think I'm better than
anyone. So, don't think you're better
than me. Basically,
it's anything more. I said, "No, who do
you think you are?" I just said, "Yeah,
take care and yeah, nice talking to
you." Simple. I'm not dealing with an
attitude like that, bro.
From a 39y old woman so they can get [ __ ]
It's no surprise really though, is it?
The day and age we live in, but I won't
be tolerating that.
Yeah. Don't think you're better than me.
Uh, typical American. That is typical
American. I would say they're worse, you
know, bro. I actually think these
Americans are worse. I actually think
they're worse, bro, than than than English.
Oh, just Reddit.
Yeah, I just read it, bro.
Yeah, you expect it from the younger generation,
but you don't expect it from the older generation.
Yeah, I went to the arcade today. I
spent £50. I want a Stitch toy. I've
been out all day, bro.
Uh, just talking to this American woman
who thinks she's better than me. And I
had my tooth pulled out as well.
It was even that bad to be honest.
And I won a stitch toy earlier. Why?
I don't understand this, bro.
Well, of course it's another one. You're
talking to a woman. What do you mean not
another one? They're never going to be
different, bro. Like, is does that
surprise you? I actually woke up in an
all right mood today. I didn't have any
mood swings today. Just woke up. I had
some good food yesterday. I mean, bro,
what do you expect a woman to be different?
Come on, bro. They're never going to be
different. I didn't I didn't take the twofy.
Come on, bro.
And this and this is a 39y old. Like,
you know the game, bro. Come on.
I said to her, she said, "Use humor with
women. You will get very far or pick on them."
Then I turned around and said, "I showed
you my approaches and message. Stop dismissing them."
You know what I find very strange? UK
asylum. Yeah. So, you know when I done
that roulette video, uh, was it yesterday?
You see how many people say that, "Oh,
gambling [ __ ] You should stop gambling.
Gambling shit." And they're
acknowledging it and they know that it's
it's rigged in it. So, they're they're
saying they're agreeing with you.
They're saying that it's rigged. Oh,
it's rigged. Don't play this [ __ ] But
anything that you show women do, they
dismiss it. It's It's like they act
stupid. It's like they act stupid when
when they're not. Um
like by that I mean they either like
defend them um or come up with some
nonsense. Like you've not just shown
them a load of [ __ ]
um evidence. It's It is strange. I was
telling this Belgian guy about this
earlier. It's very very strange um how
much stuff they they dismiss and I don't
know if it's like autism or whatever it is.
Why is she still talking to me? I told
you I don't want to talk to you anymore.
Why are you still messaging me?
I don't play roulette often.
Oh, one second. Someone's calling me.
calling me. Uh, I don't play roulette off them.
No, it doesn't really matter about that,
bro. I'm just saying that it's like, why
are you typing that? I don't even know
why this person is still typing m to me.
Yeah, stop talking to me anyways. I
don't like I don't want to speak to
someone that thinks they're better than me.
I can't be having that. [ __ ] that. So, yeah.
Yeah. One second. Somebody just typed me
a code, lad.
Sorry, bro. I'm trying to multitask
here. I'm talking to someone. Yeah,
I went bowling today. I done a lot of stuff today.
Yeah, I was all right. I was in an all
right mood today,
but I'm kind of starting to think
I need to use an escort again.
Maybe every two months.
But I was in a good mood. I didn't get
any mood swings. It's just my mouth
hurts from this tooth being pulled the
[ __ ] out. Yeah.
Oh, it's just some woman on Reddit.
It was just someone on Reddit. I gave
the Stitch toy to Laney. I'll show
Greavves here if he comes in.
I was trying to risk a Yeah,
I had Indian yesterday. I had Chinese
today. Well, I had savloid chips and
ribs. I can't really hear that well cuz
my my mouth tooth's been pulled out in it.
Yeah, they don't they don't they don't
bother me that much. Laney came with me
just for company, but I am not scared of
the dentist anyways. I just said if you
want to come, you can come
cuz Laney hates them.
Yeah, I'm only live for a little bit to
see Greavvesy, man.
I probably won't be live tomorrow. I've
been out all day, so yeah,
keep me company. Yeah.
Not because I needed it. I'm not scared
of the dentist, but Yeah.
They stuck a needle right through my
mouth, bro. Oh my god.
Like right in my gum.
Uh so yeah.
Yeah, she was being a bit of a [ __ ] Uh
this woman on Snapchat about it's a no
from me. You're not talking to me like
that with your full stops at the end of
your uh thing. You're not talking to me like that.
I mean, well, it is normal because I was
going out with my mom anyways.
I mean, why why is it not normal? See,
this is what you retards think. You're
you're so immature on here. You need to
grow up. Like, you're older than me.
You're literally older than me.
My mom didn't want to stay in. She was
bored. So I said, "Oh, you come dentist
with me." Why is that not normal? Only
in your only in in this bastic community
would you think that's not normal with
the way that your brains work, your
sick, twisted brains work, only you
would think that's not normal.
Only you would think that's not normal.
Only this bastard community.
Well, I don't know. I don't care. I
don't compare myself to any other 20
year olds, so I would know. I don't care.
I I don't know. I don't compare myself
to other people.
Waste of time.
Is my head swollen? No.
No, it's not.
Yeah. Lies just said come off. I just
said, "Oh, I had to I had to I had to
talk to Greasy and wait for Greasy to come on."
But yeah, only only this only this
community could twist something like
that. Only this community could twist
something like that. Say,
man, what's going on here?
So yeah, basically um they were acting
like a [ __ ] so I had to end the conversation.
Yeah, I've been out all day, mate.
Bowling, [ __ ] arcade. I went KFC as well. s.
Oh, bless him. Bless him.
I should have really said about that
thing with Now they're going to say I'm
scared of the dentist when I'm not.
Oh, Jesus Christ.
That's You know what they're like on
here, bro. Retards in it. You know what
they doing it? They're retards. So yeah.
So yeah, I've had to terminate that
conversation with that person basically.
Can't be speaking to someone like that
thinking that they're better than you.
No, I can't be talking like that. I
can't be talking to someone like that, mate. Um
yeah, I woke up still full from that
Indian, you know, it knocked me out
yesterday, that Indian, bro.
Um yeah, she was starting to be a bit dodge.
I was speaking to her earlier.
I just didn't like her attitude and she
was she was kind of all right earlier
and I just thought, oh, whatever. And
then she says, oh yeah, I can't get with
anyone your age. I'd feel like a pedo
even though I'm 28 years of age. Then
they started talking about [ __ ] um oh
yeah I'm trying to go over someone so if
you want to talk that's normal. Anything
else it's a no for me. Like don't talk
to me like that.
There's there's a word there's there's a
way of saying things. Don't talk like
you're better than me. I won't tolerate
in real life and I won't tolerate it on
the internet. I just terminated the conversation.
Would I? Probably. Yeah.
I probably would to be honest. Not date. Um 39.
You'd feel like a pedo getting with a
with a 28-year-old at 39.
Really, bro? I probably would to be
fair. An 80. I probably would.
So So how is 28 a pedo? How does that
make sense then?
So you'd feel like a pedo getting with a 28-year-old.
Really, bro? That makes a lot of sense,
doesn't it? No, it doesn't.
Nope. It wasn't for support. I'm not
scared of dentist. Laney wanted to come
along. I said, "If you want to come
along, you can come along. If you don't,
you don't." Laney was barred.
Uh, it's nothing to do with support. Not
scared of dentists. So, that's the only
time lany's ever come. So yeah. Yeah.
Yeah. I took Laney. Laney wanted to
come. We spent all all day out. Yeah. It
wouldn't be for support for the million
of time. I'm not scared of dentists. And
if I was scared of dentists, even with
Laney coming with me, it still would
have I still would have went.
It wasn't because of that, matey.
It was not because of that. So, yeah,
I just thought, you know, cuz she's so
scared of dentists,
why not see me, get surgery done?
Cuz if you're generally scared, you will
be scared even if you're with another person.
Like, you will be you'd still be [ __ ] scared. So,
and I got a feeling two months ago I was by myself.
Every time I've been I've been by myself.
>> Yeah. I've been by myself every single
time I've had surgery in my mouth. So,
but that's what these people do on here.
Triple H. You tell them one thing and
then they they twist [ __ ]
So, we already know what they do on
here. They twist things.
If I had if I had a chance to [ __ ] an
18y old and they were good enough, I
would do it.
I would do it. Yeah, 100% I would do it.
But I would date one. But would I [ __ ]
one? I probably would, bro. Yeah.
If they were offering it on a plate, I
probably would. 18, I probably would. Yeah.
So, if if that's the case, then 39 and
28 is not a pedo age. So, this is what
I'm trying to say, bro. You're you're
also dealing with attitude from people
that are past their sale by date.
Yeah. They did people that that that
couldn't even give you kids. You get me?
It's a madness.
I'm going dentist next week anyways. cuz
I need a I need one more filling
and I'll go by myself this time just
like I did the other day and two months
ago if you want to try and use that. But
that's what these people in this community do.
Yeah. I need one I've got one more
appointment and that's it. Yeah. Oh, yeah. Nope.
Yeah, I've only had one Coke today.
Anyways, I've only had one Coke. I've
cut down anyways
and I had no sugar in my tea. So
yeah, Peter Bellies. Yeah. So she was
being a [ __ ] wasn't she? Steven Hours.
She was being a [ __ ]
Yeah. And I won a stitch toy. Went bowling and Yeah.
Yeah, I went out all day. I spent like
60 [ __ ] town, bro. That's almost £300
in two days I've spent.
>> Yeah, madness.
But yeah, she was being a [ __ ] You can
admit she was being a [ __ ] UK signing
is it? You can admit she was being a [ __ ]
Not that it's a no for me. You ain't
talking to me like that, bro. The day a
39y old is talking like they're better
than me, bro, is the day we cut contact.
And I didn't abuse them. I just said,
"Oh, yeah. Let's just stop talking
because I'm not dealing with I ain't
dealing with that attitude, bro, in the
nicest way possible. You're not giving
me that attitude."
>> And that age thing boring.
Change it now. Change the excuse for
It's boring now, mate. And I'm not in
I'm not in a bad mood either. I'm not in
a bad mood. Dude, I'm actually all right
today, bro. But just stop it now. It's boring.
So, yeah, I'll probably go to a uh
thingy house soon, and that'll be me for
2 months, I reckon. Yeah.
You know what? I was saying this
earlier. Bowling would be a good place
to take somebody on a date.
bowling actually would be, you know,
but you can't get a date anyways.
>> Yeah, probably, bro. Yeah, pretty soon.
it's looking that way.
Bad, is it, Dad? Very bad. Yeah.
Yeah. She started getting very funny.
Oh, it's a no for me.
No, don't talk to me like that. That's
not what you were saying yesterday.
That's not what she was saying
yesterday, mate. And then saying that
you're going to act like a That's a
pedo. How the [ __ ] is 39 and 28 pedo?
I'm pretty sure once you're past a
certain age, it's all I think once
you're past 25, it's all whole bars, isn't it?
No whole bars. Once you're past the age
of 25, even 21, to be fair, you're
you're that's where you're at in it. Like,
it's mad. How are they saying that
stuff, bro? They're just [ __ ] in it.
But yeah, what I was saying, Triple H,
is when you show uh a roulette video,
people will be like, "Oh yeah,
gambling's rigged. This is rigged.
Gambling [ __ ] Oh, I understand why you
did this. Oh, I understand when you do
that. Oh, I understand why you did that.
Stay away from these gambling machines."
And then when when you when you show
like like bad experiences with women,
they just act stupid. They act like
they're stupid and they don't know anything.
They act like they that you haven't
shown them a load of [ __ ] They just all
act ignorant. Have you noticed that, Steven Howard?
Or if they don't, they just dismiss it.
So like you you'll show them stuff and
then they just carry on
um talking as if you've not just shown
them a load of [ __ ] basically.
So I mean it's strange, isn't it? It is.
It is strange. They they acknowledge the
gambling. They definitely definitely
acknowledge the gambling,
but anything to do with uh women [ __ ]
you over, they just act stupid like they
don't know anything.
Mad, is it? I was telling this Belgium
guy about it as well. He was agreeing with me
saying about humor. I was like, did I
just not show you a bunch of my
experiences of what what's happened?
Um, so they do dismiss it and if they
don't defend them, they still dismiss it,
which is concerning really.
But they don't dismiss the gambling
things. Why is that?
Why don't they dismiss the gambling stuff?
Yeah, she deleted me off. Uh, Snapchat.
Yeah, that's good, man. I can't talk to
an American that thinks they're better than everyone.
Americans are the worst. They're worse
than English. They're I would say
Americans are worse than English.
They think they're better than everyone
and they think their country is better
than every everyone else is as well.
No, I haven't.
I've been busy all day, bro. Then
I went to the arcades.
You know, I'm tired as [ __ ] I had to
take more painters. Oh [ __ ]
It's so mad. Yeah. That I was full up
until midday. You know, I had that
Indian at like 6:00 p.m. yesterday and
it filled me up the whole day and half of today.
There's just something about these
Indians whenever you eat them in, they
just seem to fill you up for like 10 times longer.
It just fills you up. It sends you It's
mad, bro. Like it's it's I think it's
because where it's not watery when you
eat it like the chicken and the curry
and that it's not watery and it's thick.
I don't know. Oh, I just I was felt I
was full up um filled up for a long
time, bro. I had a milkshake. I had a
Five Guys milkshake today as well. It
just seems to fill you up the whole day.
I can't explain it. It's mad.
Whereas, if you have a takeaway, it
doesn't hit you the It don't hit the same way.
You know what I mean, Dusty? It doesn't
hit the same way
as when you go to a restaurant. It just
It hits different, bro. It hits
different when you go to a restaurant.
It just hits different. And I walked as
well. I done a lot of walking and I was
still full up.
It just hits different.
I can't explain it.
Especially if you got a little flu.
So yeah, she went weird, didn't she? Uh, UK asylum,
but it's to be expected, is it?
That's to be expected. You wouldn't
expect anything less, would you? Really?
Come on now.
You wouldn't really expect anything less.
But yeah, they do dismiss people's struggles.
They definitely definitely definitely do
dismiss people's struggles. That's not
even me just saying that.
He doesn't matter if I met her on Reddit.
It doesn't matter if I met her on Reddit.
Yeah. Went to dentist and then I've been
I went to dentist. I've been out all day.
Yeah. I've been out all day, bro. Doing
stuff, bowling and that. Yeah. Yeah,
met someone on Reddit. They're a [ __ ] as well.
You're also a [ __ ] as well. Well, I'm
just going to have to keep I'm just
going to have to go and use [ __ ]
thingy again, aren't I?
I'm just going to start using escorts
again, I think.
Well, maybe once a month or something.
I'm not I don't need sex all the time.
Every week, bro. Maybe once a month. It's fine. Yeah.
Yeah. I wasn't in a pissed-off mood
today. I was too busy. But um Yeah.
Yeah, once every month.
No point being born with a dick if you
can't use it. That's what the pool
industry is for.
That's what the pool industry is for.
That's what the That's what escorts are for.
It's better than nothing. Think about
it. That's the way I see it. It's better than nothing.
Yeah, it's better than nothing, I think.
Oh, I want a toy, Grezy.
I want a Stitch toy today. And I got my
toothies out. Would you like to see the toy, Greavvesy?
I was going to send it to you with my
toothy as a little present.
Yeah, I won a stitch toy within free grabs.
Would you like to see it? I gave it to Laney.
I tried to win Caspandicut, but I couldn't.
I couldn't win the [ __ ]
He's too muscly. One second. I'll get
him for you.
Oh, we can't get something as well. Jeez.
Here we go.
There's a fishial as well. Yeah,
it's an official.
I just pop that right next back next to Laney.
Just pop that back next to you, Laney.
We'll do Laney. Okay, Laney.
Yeah, I put it next to Laney. I gave it
I got my toothy pulled out today. Laney
came with me. Just Yeah.
Not cuz I'm scared because uh Laney was
bored. So I said, "If you want to come
with me, you can come." Yeah.
I was speaking to some woman on Reddit, Greavvesy.
Um, and guess what happened? I was
speaking to her earlier when I woke up.
I woke up at 3:00 in the morning
looking ill. Am I
28 going online?
Oh, bro. She was being She was all right
earlier. Then she started being a [ __ ] We
he started being uh hunted with
attitude. No surprise there. Is it? Yeah.
Nope. Definitely sure. I don't want to
start approaching. Absolutely not.
Remember that one, Grezy? Absolutely no way.
Nuh-uh. And I was in a good mood today,
Greavvesy. I'm I'm in a good mood. I
didn't wake up pissed off or anything.
I was all right today, bro, from start to finish.
I'll be on uh
Yeah. Grieves you. So, what I was
talking to this uh woman on the on on a
on a on Reddit. Yeah. She's 39 and she
said, "Oh, she comes back to London, she
might hook up whether she's in a
relationship or not." And the next thing
she's saying, "Oh, I would feel like a
pedo if you if I got with you." When
she's 39 and I'm 28 and I'm thinking,
"I'm getting bad vibes." You know, when
you're getting bad vibes from someone
and then she's saying, "Oh, yeah. I'm
still not over someone. So, if you want
to talk normally, um, you can, but if
any if you want anything more, it's a no
for me." I said, "You are not talking to
me like that." And we are ending this
conversation and we are cutting content
contact. You don't talk to me like that.
Don't talk to me like you're better than me.
You know, I don't mind people just
talking and, you know, being normal, but
don't don't talk to me like you're
better than me. I will not have that.
And I weren't even rude either. So,
yeah, it's uh and this is a 40year-old
pretty much we
imagine someone my age.
Nope. She knows exactly how how old I was. 28.
stated it multiple times.
Yeah, I'm not dealing with that [ __ ]
You know what I'm saying? Greasy.
So, no. But I won't I'll probably just
go to I'll probably just use an escort
once a month to be honest.
Yeah. Better than nothing.
That's the way I see it.
That's literally all you have when
you're here. You you've only you really
only got that, you know,
Thailand or the porn industry. There's
nothing else you really have
to be fair.
So yeah, she was being a [ __ ] Greasy.
She was being a [ __ ]
Doesn't matter why. Look, mate.
Because they're just [ __ ] bro.
That's why they're just [ __ ] isn't it?
And so many people
you know what I was saying to this guy
in Belgium today um on Instagram I speak
to this guy in Belgium.
It was all right to be honest.
It was it was all right to be fair.
The only needle I felt was the second
one but I'm not scared of needles anyways.
It wasn't as bad as I thought it was
going to be. But yeah, but um
yeah, lady come. I said if you want to
come, you can come
cuz she had nothing better to do.
Yeah. And guess what? The only male
retention you're getting is from simps
on this community.
Yeah. That's the only attention you're
getting. So yeah. Uh, greasy. Um,
yeah, bro. I sure I need to go for a
fill in uh next week and I'm done.
I'm not wasting dentist appointments.
Free dentist appointments. That's a damn
shame wasting that. You know, you should
take advantage of that. That's why I
went. The truth was [ __ ] It stunk as
well when it come out, bro. It was horrible. Yeah.
Yeah. You should take it you should take
advantage of them uh appointments. Yeah. So yeah.
Yeah. Why do you keep telling me to go
out? Oh yeah. Do you want to know what I
was saying to this Belgium guy uh on Instagram? Greasy.
I said to him that um do cuz he's I
speak to him and stuff. I was like, "Do
you not find it weird how like when I
put gambling videos up, people say that
gambling [ __ ] Gambling is [ __ ] Um you
know, you just you should act that way.
You should act that way. Like you should
smash up machines." Like any anger
towards gambling I show. Have you
noticed how a lot of people love it and
agree to it, but then when you're
showing [ __ ] that women do, they all act
stupid and that they don't have a brain
and they can't see what they're doing.
Very worrying, isn't it? Very worrying.
That is they act like you haven't just
showed them a load of [ __ ] and even if
they don't defend them, they just they
just carry on as normal. Does that make
sense? So yeah, struggle dismisses. But
if it's anything to do with gambling or
anything else, their brains work again.
But then when it's to do with like
someone leading you on, uh you being
normal and someone saying straight away
they're not interested, anything where a
woman is wrong, they start acting stupid
like they don't know anything.
Weird as [ __ ] bro. Ain't it weird?
But they want equality. Yeah. Good luck with that.
How does that work then?
How How does that work?
How does that work, bro? It doesn't even make sense.
Um, and I'm not in a bad mood either.
I'm just saying it because it's true.
It's just stuff I'm thinking, bro.
They say that [ __ ] Yeah. Yeah man.
But how so how can it be equal then? How
can this world be equal when they they
defend be people based on gender and not
uh not individuals?
They don't judge people individually.
They judge people based on their gender.
You not agree?
It is strange. It is strange.
They seem to acknowledge everything else.
Maybe I get someone on the panel to come
on and talk about it, you know.
And I mean, even this Bob, he's he's a
struggle dismisser, you know, if you
want to get technical about it because
why would he be telling me to go back
and approach knowing all the bad things
that's already happened for years?
Why would you be telling me to approach?
It doesn't make sense.
It really doesn't make any sense.
You understand? Why would you tell
someone to approach when you know what
it causes? You know,
Yeah. Well, I don't like the content, bro.
I don't like it.
I don't like the content. It's [ __ ]
boring. That's why I gave up, lad.
If I was to ever try again, bro, you're
waiting like 6 months. You're waiting 6
months minimum. Trust me, bro. 6 months
It ain't happening, bro, for a very,
very long time, if ever. Yeah.
Sorry about that.
Sorry about that. Delayed, but it just
you get me.
So yeah, you just use escort every month
if you need.
Nah, it will never happen. I've not had
a date since April.
I'm not convinced.
Not even had a date since April.
No, it ain't that.
I know. You never know. But I know.
So, I won't be going out, lad.
You still there? Graves.
It's mad, isn't it? How
you have to be 28 with no sex life in it?
Mad, eh? When there's no reason for it.
Stand in it, bro. At least I ain't got
nothing to do tomorrow, so that's a good thing.
It's bad, isn't it? Really bad.
And it's also unhealthy as well because,
you know, when you see stuff, you think
the wrong things.
You know, if you don't have like a sex
life and that or intimacy for a very
long time, you start um it starts
changing the way that you think
negatively and that.
I wouldn't call her desperate. I've had
women approach me. No, I don't know what
I'm doing tomorrow. I mean, I can I
probably will stay in bed tomorrow just
healing from this tooth thing.
No, I wouldn't call that desperate. I've
had women approach me years ago. So,
yeah, when you're not getting sex or
like you don't get sex for ages, Dusty,
right, you start um
thinking things and [ __ ]
cuz it's not normal cuz obviously you're
supposed to have a sex life. You understand,
Greasy? You're supposed to have a sex
life. You see? So when you don't
you think of bitter things. I can't
explain it, bro. Like it's hard to
cuz it's not normal. You see, it's not
I just saw this woman's on a date. I
still haven't had a date for a very long time.
Yeah. No doubt I'll be depressed
tomorrow. I wasn't depressed today, but
I'll probably be depressed tomorrow
thinking about it.
Yeah, I've been watching this guy, bro,
uh doing these approaches today on
Instagram. He's put some new ones up. We
What do you reckon the women said to him?
That is so depressing, bro. Seeing that
even when it's not happening to me.
That's so depressing.
I have a boyfriend. Oh god, that's so
depressing, bro. Why does this guy's
videos keep popping up?
What would you do if you was me, Grey?
Let's ask for Greavves advice.
I'm trying to open this bastard lollipop.
I don't know what you're talking about.
I read it, but I don't know what you're talking about.
I think I heard about it. Was it some
killing in America?
Was it kidding in some Was it some American thing?
I think I heard about it on the news. Yeah,
I saw something about that. I don't know the story.
Well, that's what happens when you're
not getting sex, grievy.
That That's your only thing in your head
when you're not getting sex when you
should be getting it.
Yeah, I think escorts are literally the
only answer to be fair. I was thinking
the same thing to be honest. That's
literally the only thing on the porn
industry that you can move on with your
life to be honest
cuz in my head it's better than nothing.
And even if it wasn't even if it's not
the same thing, it's better than nothing. Yeah.
But yeah, once I see an escort, I should
be good for two months.
But at the same time, you should have to
use an escort. You you should have to be
you you should have to use escorts. You
should have a sex life. You should have
dates. You should be with people.
There's nothing wrong with you.
But that's just a sick sad world
that we live in. I mean, people
shouldn't have to be going to Thailand,
but they do. So
that's just the world we live in nowadays. Yeah.
You should be able to meet people and
go on dates and stuff.
Yeah. It shouldn't be that way though.
Slap maker. I should have someone.
I should be able to have someone already
with the amount of approaches I've done.
But should I have, would I have, could
have? It's a new year. I've not done any
approaches this year and I probably won't. So
yeah, escorts is is is a thing of it. Yeah.
It's depressing, bro. Very depressing.
I would still love for someone to uh
answer me another question I had greasy cuz
if uh if if one second, let me say. So,
you know what I was I keep saying that
woman that was saying, "Oh, yeah. I'm
feeling very very depressed because when
I go on dates, the guys ditch me." So
the guy's ditch her after two weeks she
gets stumped. And then my thinking if
that's causing you depress depression
and that's causing you to not out get
out of bed then how would you feel if
you never if you can't get dates and you
can't get sex you'd probably kill
yourself in it. That's the way that's
the way I'd see it. That's the way I see Um
men on uh men on um
how do I say this? This is it's like uh
if that's making you depressed then how
would you how would it make someone feel
they can't even get dates or sex
and they have to actually put effort in
as well. So it's like they don't um I
don't think they give sympathy to enough
men nowadays that actually try
you know I think men deserve sympathy to
be honest just like they give women. I
think if you've tried more, you try
you've tried or you've tried regularly,
then you should be you should be given sympathy.
I I generally think that, bro. I'm not
even joking. I I think you should.
No, I'm not going to kill myself. It's
not Is what I'm saying not true?
Bro, are you you not Is what I'm saying not true?
Come on, bro. Like, think about it, you know. Um,
I just think it's [ __ ] I think
societyy's [ __ ] bro.
And the struggle dismisses.
And the struggle dismisses, lad. It's mad.
No, I'm not gay, mate. I'll just use
escorts. I'll just get [ __ ] from
escorts, bro. Like I used to
ask an Indonesian
p [ __ ] Scared to approach. Yeah.
No, I'll just use escorts, bro. I'll
just get a [ __ ] from an escort.
Yeah, I told you I'm not scared of the dentist. Grey,
I'll go dentist next week and I won't
bring Laney. I've got another um I got a
fill in to be put in.
I'll go by myself this time if you want.
Just like I went uh yesterday yesterday
by myself. Today I didn't.
I'm not scared, brother.
You'll see that. You know that yourself.
I've been on this community. Yeah,
there is a lot of people that are really
bad with them though. Greavvesy. Really bad.
Grievesy. Really bad.
Bro, I had a fitting two months ago
and I went by myself. I went to the
dentist yesterday by myself.
I've been out all day, mate. And I'm not
going out on the pool either. I've been
out all day. I've been doing a lot of
stuff today and I will not be going out
on the pool either. So, that ain't
happening. Yeah. That's how Well, that's
how toxic it is, Bob. Then that tells
you how toxic the whole dating game
then, isn't it? Then that should tell
you how toxic it is. No.
Yeah. I I already told you why I took my
mom to the dentist.
I already told you why, bro.
Yeah. Appropriate adult up for a
dentist. Yeah. You keep telling yourself that, bro.
Yeah. Yeah. You Yeah. You keep telling
yourself that, man. If it makes you feel better. Yeah.
Yeah. You keep telling yourself that, bro.
You know you you know there's my
sister's friend um Greavvesy. He can't even go.
He literally won't go.
His whole teeth is [ __ ] He won't go.
He will not go unless they put him to sleep.
He will not go and he has to go to a
special dentist. They have to put him to
sleep otherwise he will not go.
Um his old teeth were rotted and he
won't go unless he put him to sleep.
Means I'm the other way around. I can't
be put to sleep. I've got a fear of
being put to sleep. So whenever they
say, "Oh, we're going to numb it." I
always have to make sure you're not
putting me to sleep, are you? I always
have to ask again cuz that's what I'm
scared of like being put to sleep.
Whereas he will only go and even then he
still doesn't go. So, he has to be put
to sleep, he has to go to a special
dentist that puts him to sleep.
Cuz obviously if someone's scared of
needles and they're scared of the
dentist, the [ __ ] is it? Because
Ant-Man Ant-Man don't like them. But he
when he's got fillings, he doesn't get
the needle. They don't numb it because
he's scared of needles.
So when he's had it, he's hadn't had needles.
Yeah. Ask her, man, if she's loving,
she'll come with you.
Yeah. So, he gets it done. I don't I
don't I don't uh I'm not scared of
needles. Me, they've never bothered me.
And you don't even feel them in the dentist.
Yeah. I tell you the needles are the
worst though. You know when you get an STD test,
Greavves? You know when you get an STD test?
You know when you get an STD test? Yeah.
Uh you they they it's a big ass needle
and you can actually see the blood
coming from your [ __ ] arm.
It's bro it's is bad. Trust me them
needles are bad. I remember I got an STD
test before I went.
I remember myself.
They say they're scared of needles, but
you don't feel the needles in the
dentist. I only felt the second one.
I only felt the second one, bro. I've
I've had needles cuz I've had ingrown
toenails in my So, I've had surgery on
my foot. You know the ingrown toenail surgery?
No, no, no. It's more than a blood test.
What they doing in a STI test? It's more
than a blood test. And it [ __ ] did hurt
cuz I remember getting it two years ago.
But I've had ingrown toenails. So I've
had I've had I've had surgery. I've had
surgery on um Have you ever had seen
ingrown toenail surgery? I used to get
infected toes, greasy. I used to bite my
toenails and they used to get infected.
So I had like Well, it's like a
procedure. It's not surgery surgery, but
So they have to stick a needle in your foot.
They stick a needle in your foot.
Three in your foot. And then they just
cut out. But they don't put you to sleep
or anything. It's just a minor procedure.
And I was trying to say, is that worse
than getting your teeth took out?
I don't know. Cuz them needles, you can
actually feel the needles in your foot.
Dentist, you can't feel the needles. Yeah.
I like shucking about that.
Yeah. Laney won't go. Laney stopped
going to the dentist for years and years
and years cuz she hated it. I said,
"Lane, you ready to go in the dentist chair?"
She says, "No."
Laney hates them. Bless her.
She used to shake on the chair.
Bless lady. Lady the legend.
I went to the arcades today.
I went to the I playing grabbing
machines. I want I want a toy and I went bowling.
You should have to use escorts.
I didn't go on the 2P pushes. You
shouldn't have to use escorts, but
that's the way it is. It's that or nothing.
No point having a dick if you can't use
it. Something's better than nothing, isn't it?
I do think of my experiences though. I
was thinking of a bit of them today and
the lies these women tell Dusty. Oh, the
lies and the narcissism from them. You
got to laugh in it, mate. You got to laugh.
Yeah, I was trying to
creepy. I was trying to I was trying to
win cash uh Crash Bandicut, but it
wasn't having it for toffee, mate. It
was an odd [ __ ] to try and win. You
can't win that toy, bro. It's It's the
way it's shaped. You can't grab it
unless it's on his back and then it just
slips again. You just can't win it. I
was trying to win Crash Bandicut for myself.
I like Crash Bandicoot. He's a lovely
little character. We bishop.
They're rigged as [ __ ] bro.
I was playing a Scooby I was playing a
Scooby-Doo thing as well. Greasy
[ __ ] going to run out of [ __ ]
money if I go every be [ __ ] day. me
like the skin virgin
in a shitty little bed.
If I went every day for weeks,
would you say that lack a lack of sex
life is unhealthy, Greavvesy? Yeah,
I would say a lack of sex life is unhealthy.
I don't think it's unhealthy me.
Yeah, I think it is.
I think it is me.
I don't know about you. I think it's unhealthy. Yeah.
No, it's impossible not to think about it.
Obviously, because of my experiences,
but also escorts can get addicting as well. So,
that can also be addicting.
I've already tried a fat bird. They're
all the same. This this 39year-old was
kind of fat.
They've all got the same attitude, so
you might as well just go for the best looking. >> Yeah.
>> Yeah. It's bad though, isn't it, Big? I
shouldn't have to get I shouldn't have
to get a hooker.
I should be able to have a sex life at
my age with all the approaches I've done and stuff.
You should have to,
but I'd much rather use an escort than
go out approaching again. [ __ ] that.
[ __ ] that, bro. It's too toxic.
I'd rather use an escort. I'm not going to lie.
Don't hear that [ __ ] again. Oh, you're
too old for me. Oh, you're too young for
me. I can't date you cuz I'm a Muslim.
All of this [ __ ] bro. All right. I'm
not I'm not dealing with that anymore.
You [ __ ] off.
I'm not dealing with that.
I would have just stayed with that 18y
old n. Well, she's 19. I think she's 20
now. She's 20. I would have just stayed
with her, but she started becoming westernized. So
yeah, do you remember that one, Stephen?
I can't date you cuz I'm a Muslim and
you're not. I said, oh, I'll convert.
Oh, I'm not looking for anyone. They're
such idiots, bro. You just laugh at it,
bro. You just got to laugh at them.
You do have to laugh at it. Some of it
is so funny, bro.
It's something to laugh at, isn't it?
Their excuses are laughable, bro.
You remember that one that was trying to
use religion as an excuse?
Do you remember that one, Steven, that
was using religion as an excuse?
Yeah. When they do stuff like that, you
know they've got narcissistic traits.
You know that they've got um narcissistic traits.
It's hard to explain it, but it's it's a
nar it's a trait of narcissism what
they're doing when they're doing that.
Cuz all you got to say is that you're
not looking for anyone. That's literally
all you got to say. Why are you using religion
when we all know that if someone's a
Muslim, you're still not going to get
with them. So why Yeah.
Like they're just going to [ __ ] with
you. And and the thing is, if you go and
if you go out approaching and stuff
trying to meet women, they're just going
to [ __ ] with you. You do realize that,
is it, Stephen Howard? They're just
going to [ __ ] with you royally. That's
what they're going to do.
That's what's going to happen. Not worth it.
They will [ __ ] with you royally, bro.
They trust me. Trust me, they will. Yeah.
[ __ ] idiots, bro. Oh,
have you ever met a good woman in your
life, Stephen Howard? I've never. It is
worse than gambling.
Yeah, trying to date women is definitely
definitely worse than gambling. But
people don't tell people to quit dating,
but they tell people to quit gambling,
which is strange really. It is. That is
cuz I could put £500 on roulette right
now and guess what? I could win.
I could actually win online maybe, you
know, but it is worse than gambling.
It is worse than gambling.
I need to have another coat, bro. I'm really dry.
Yeah, it's definitely worse than gambling.
And then with gambling,
with gambling, your struggles don't get
dismissed either. With gambling, your
struggles don't get dismissed. And um
there's obviously a chance of winning.
You know, you you've obviously got a
chance of winning.
With dating women, you never have a
chance. And even if you did, even if you
did meet someone, you would just get
[ __ ] over in the end. Anyways,
the best is winning money from gambling
and using escorts. That's literally the
way forward, bro.
That's literally it, bro.
No, no, no. But no, no, no. But, but the
experiences are not normal.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
But the experiences are not normal. The
experiences that come with dating is
definitely definitely definitely not
normal. That's definitely not natural.
Yeah. And dealing with women pretending
that they've got boyfriends and using
religion as an excuse and trolling you
and [ __ ] with you. That's not normal.
So yes, it can be compared cuz that's not normal.
That is not normal going through that.
That is [ __ ] depressing. and you'll
realize how depressing it is as well
because when you give up, you feel
better. Once you give up for a week or
two weeks, you feel better.
That is not normal, mate. Trying to date
in 2026 is not normal.
And I'm the only one that that says
about it. That's not natural. I wouldn't
call that natural. So,
yeah. No, I'd 100% rather go back to
gambling here. If I was to choose one,
I'd definitely go back to gambling.
You think getting trolled, people
pretending they've got boyfriends,
giving you attitude, ignoring, taking
the piss out of you is natural.
You think that's natural? Really? No, it
isn't. It's not normal. You know,
no, not everyone wants to have a partner.
No, not everyone wants to have a partner.
I mean, I've given up approaching. I'll
never approach again. So, you know,
I will never approach again. I haven't for ages.
So, it definitely is your experience. If
you've gone out approaching, it
definitely definitely is your experience
just like it is 90% of men's experiences.
I've seen it with my own eyes.
Yep. I've already explained why there's
couples in the world, bro. I'm not
explaining it again. We're not going
over the same thing. I've already
explained to you how people are in
relationships. If you didn't listen to
it, bro, that's your problem.
I've already explained it, bro. I'm not
going over it again.
Like I said, struggle dismisser. I've
explained the relationship thing.
It's not the truth. I've already
explained it a million times about why
there's people in relationships. There's
also millions of people that are single.
The truth don't hurt. I've just
explained it a million times. Um, I'm
not bitter. I'm not angry. I'm
completely calm. It doesn't hurt cuz
you're not talking the truth. You're
talking [ __ ] And I've already explained
it a million times how there's people in relationships.
So, and I've also explained that there's
loads of people that are not in
relationships, but that also didn't suit
your agenda. So, yeah,
that's that. you.
How do you know that? Greasy.
No, I I'd explain the partner thing, but
I'm not explaining it again. Steven
Howard, it's pointless.
It's pointless going over it.
you know, the dating stuff, why there's
people in relationships, why, you know,
it's point it's it's utterly utterly pointless
because you'll just be explaining the
same thing over and over and over again.
If you really think that because there's
other people in relationships that that
means you're going to be in a
relationship, you're sadly mistaken.
Sadly, that's not the way life works.
Sadly, Sadly, that is not the way that life works. Um
especially in 2026,
you know, 2022, 2023. Yeah, you know,
you could maybe but you can't say that nowadays
because there's a million reasons why
people met. There's a million there's a
million reasons why people are in
relationships. That is not going to be
you. So no matter how many times you
want to compare yourself and it's never
ever going to be you. I used to say I
used to say the same thing to Pat
Mustard. I mean, there's people that are
worse than me in life.
There's people that are virgins. There's
people that's never even had a date. I
mean, there's people that are out there,
and there's more than one. So, does that
mean because I've had sex and I've been
with women, that means they're going to
No, even if they tried. So,
so yeah. Well, could you blame somebody
for not wanting to have a partner in
this day and age, Greavesy?
Why would why would someone want a
partner in this day and age
after all the [ __ ] that we've been doing
that? Why would somebody actually want
to be with one of them other than sex?
As as bad as that sounds, could for what
reason? What can they give you other
than sex? Nothing.
They're they're [ __ ] people.
They they're just [ __ ] all around. I
mean, you've seen the ones I've spoke
to, you know, they're [ __ ] They can't
give you nothing like that. I can cook.
I can clean. You know, there's there's
nothing else they can give you
unless you want children. So, you know, that's that.
They've got stinking bad attitude.
What else can they actually give you
than than sex? I don't I don't honestly
know. Like, there there's nothing else
they can give you.
They're rude. They're stuck up. They
think they're better than you. Their attitude.
They Bro, I come out of Liverpool Street
yesterday, bro. And there there was so
many women vaping.
Ew. I mean, I I'll tell you a story
today, Grezy. When I was on the way to
the dentist with my mom, I said he said,
"What you up to?" I said, "Oh, I'm just
on my I'm just on my way to the
dentist." And he was like, and he said
to me, he said to me, "Grezy, um, where
are you off to, mate?" I said, "I'm not
your [ __ ] mate." Um, you remember
what I told you about how I don't like
being called mate? Yeah. And you get
these women using that word nowadays,
mate. Mate, and they're vaping. It's so
masculine. It doesn't look cool. It
doesn't think you're not cool vaping
outside of a [ __ ] bank. It's so
westernized and copycat-ish.
You know, that vaping trend is is for
copycats. Breezy like they're literally
vaping outside banks. These women
they literally are I saw about four
women in Liverpool Street vaping. What the [ __ ]
And when they call people mate as well
it's unbearable. Like it's bad enough
you know when a man calls you mate
grievy. Yeah. It sounds so common. It's
horrible. You know, if someone says like
buddy or pal or whatever,
um, pal or body, I'd rather someone have
a cigarette, bro, than vape. It's so
common vaping, mate. It's so masculine,
you know? I'd rather someone just have a
[ __ ] than a vape. I don't know about you,
it just seems so copycatish.
It just seems copycat-ish. It's just so
westernized. You don't You don't see it
in Thailand. You don't see people vape
in Thailand. It's a westernized thing,
Grezy. It is. You don't see anyone but
westernized people vape. I swear to God, you don't.
You don't. You seriously seriously
don't. It's a westernized thing.
Seriously, it is. Serious. No,
seriously, it is, bro.
It is. It generally generally generally
No, it is. No, it is. It is. It is. And
And them saying the word mate. Like, ew.
Could you imagine you on a date with a
woman, Greavves, and she called you
mate? That's just so offputting, isn't
it? That's what a 19year-old started
calling me. I was like, I'm not your
[ __ ] mate. I don't know how many
times I had to say it. I'm not your
mate. Not your mate. I will never be
You know, I don't like being called
mate, especially by a woman. It's
[ __ ] cringe. It's so common.
That is just so common, bro. So common.
You should use the word pal or buddy or something.
I hate it, bro. It's so westernized.
Tik Tok brains. Oh, I need to make
myself a coke.
>> What community did you say this is again? Greasy.
What community is this? A gambling
community or what?
What is it really?
So when you said so
what you was so so wait so wait what
what you were saying is that when you
used to be in school right um when you
was to go to class just before they open
the door like uh the the teacher opened
the door to teach they would they were
talking about she co and if you didn't
agree with them they'd look at you weird
they look at you weirdly
Is that what you're saying? So if you
didn't find her attractive, they'd give
you a dirty look. Really?
Wow. So what do you call So what do you
call them kind of people?
So what do you what do you call with
them kind of people So what
so what you saying that Laura J is a copycat
and I'm saying about sexy do you know
what I was saying about women
um only can give you necks and stuff. I
mean, I don't even think it's about that
nowadays. And it's about their body
body. As long as they've got a mouth to
put on Peter Belly's Willie, I mean,
that's all you need. So, if you can get
something like a sex tie with with the
sensation of a mouth, then I think we're
good to go really.
I was on the train yesterday coming back
from the Indian and I was looking at
this woman. She looked about 37 38 and I
was just seeing if you know I was I was
um summing up her mouth weighing up her
mouth rather to see if it would fit you know. Yeah. Really
okay with you captain Captain K. Yeah,
it's all about the mouth, isn't it, Grezy?
Yeah, it's about the mouth, Grevy, to
satisfy Peter Belly Billy's needs. But
yeah, they can't offer you anything
else. No, in all seriousness,
there's nothing else they can offer you.
It's like that 19year-old. I only used
her for her mouth, you know?
I only used her for that little mouth
around my PKA when I needed it.
Just someone to make me feel good. We
a copycat community.
I love that. I love that. That's so funny, bro.
A copycat community. That's funny.
I love it. Yeah, they'll copy each other. Yeah.
But yeah, I only used the user for her
mouth to be fair.
Yep. Nothing else they're good for.
They're not even good at cooking. I can
cook better than them. Poor [ __ ] Yep.
So, you mean like I'll do something and
then LJ copies me and stuff like that?
Yeah. Or when they like copy copy up
each other each other's football bets copycat community. Yeah. Little copycats.
No, I wouldn't put I don't care about
USA's face, bro. What the [ __ ]
All All a woman's good for is her boobs
and her mouth. Weezy, isn't that right?
Only boobs and their mouth. Nothing else.
Literally nothing else.
My toothy My tooth is hurting, bro. The
one I got pulled out. Ah,
there was three roots, you know. They
had to get They had to take out three roots.
It was mad.
They had to take out three roots after
the [ __ ] tooth. It was mad.
It was mad, bro. Yeah.
Yeah, they do copy.
Do you remember that, Grezy? When um
what do you do you remember that when
that 19year-old used to come around and
suck my willie? Greasy,
what did you think of that?
You could never get in a relationship
with a woman, bro. They would cheat on you.
They would actually cheat on you.
I think all women cheat on people, you know.
>> I don't trust them.
>> I think they cheat. They're little
cheaters. What do you think, Grezy?
I think they cheat. Would
you ever get back with someone that
cheated on you, Grezy?
I wouldn't on one condition.
Actually, I would on one condition.
Only if they never gave a [ __ ] If
they gave them a [ __ ] never again.
If someone gave someone a [ __ ]
they're done forever.
It's the worst thing you can do is give
someone a [ __ ]
cheating on them. You know, that's
that's the worst thing you can do. I
don't think I don't think there's a
worst thing you can do.
You would never know.
See, you would never know.
That's the thing. I mean, if you caught
her in it, you'd have to You'd have to catch her. Yeah. Yeah, man.
Yeah, it's hard to get a [ __ ] man.
Someone like stands you have, they don't
give it. Some do, some don't. I only had
one that never
I'm obsessed with [ __ ] man.
It's really bad,
Greasy. It's really, really bad, you know. Yeah,
Crash Bandicoot is a lovely character.
I miss when the 19year-old used to give
used to suck my dick grievy.
I used to feel so good.
Yeah, I used to feel good, man.
That's probably why I'm bad. I'm worse
now. Greasy. I don't have the only fans
one and a 19year-old.
So I Oh well, he's 20 now. I don't have any options.
So I have nothing.
Yeah, literally nothing
like in that in that way. So I think it's uh
I used to get mood swings in the old
house, but she used to come around and
stuff in it. Yeah,
that's what probably a lot of it is as
well, is it?
Yeah. Not anymore.
Not anymore, bro. She blocked me. I
tried I tried to get her back, but she Yeah,
I'm getting DVDs. Greasy.
What do you think of that?
Yeah. When she used to come out, I never
used to give her sex.
Like she just used to give me a [ __ ] That's it. Meow.
I like shovel cog wheels here.
I like Chevro car greasy.
Yeah, that 19year-old was good at
sucking dick, man.
She swallowed my [ __ ] once. Squeezy.
Yeah, she swallowed it once.
It was lovely, Grezy.
Someone swallowing your babies.
That's cute, ain't it, Grezy?
Yeah, that was cute. Griezy,
you gave me a [ __ ] once and had a
Chinese after. We had a Chinese after.
I think she gave me a [ __ ] like four times. Yeah.
I want to get some digestive biscuits.
Do you know what you are, Grezy?
You're [ __ ] Oh, what's that thing called again?
You're bag puss. The big fat stinking copycat.
You're a big fat stinking copycat.
You're just like bag. You big fat stinking copycat. Yeah.
Yeah, that was just her vitamins.
Greasy, when she used to give me a
[ __ ] Yeah. And I used to come. That
was just her getting vitamins.
You know how you get vitamins from like the resticles,
you know. That's the same way,
you know. It's just vitamins like
protein from the semen and stuff, you know.
So you basically give each other
vitamins and stuff. Sounds lovely
if you ask me. Greasy. Yeah.
One second. Someone's calling me.
I know I don't go down on women. No, I
don't believe in it. It's disgusting.
I just someone I have to listen to a voice. No.
Yeah. Grievously um Th Antman went to
Thailand cuz he was sick of it in his
country. He was just sick of it.
Yeah, it makes sense, isn't it?
He's done a he done a funny Snapchat
story the other day of him sucking
someone's boobs. See, I was going to
screen record it and put it on YouTube.
I was dead.
He's a wind up merchant, in it.
He's a wind up merchant.
Do you like the stitch green? I know
it's pink, but it's better than nothing.
Yeah, I need to cut down. I can't have
sugars in my tears.
It's a copycat community. All right. Do
you remember when Vinnie when Vinnie got nicked? Greasy.
Do you remember when Vinnie got nicked
on the live stream?
They took him away. That's funny.
How's your bipolar been, Graves?
How's your bipolar been, lad?
Oh, this woman, this woman said, um,
this woman was like, "Oh, yeah, she's
gone on a date, Greavvesy." And it
didn't go well.
Wow, you can actually get dates.
I haven't had a date since last April. Wow.
Do you believe in dating coaches? Greavvesy.
coach is an idiot.
No UK signing. I like Shevel Cow.
I like shovel cow.
I don't know about you.
So it says while exact realtime figures
may vary around 40 to 44% of London's
adult population identifies as single
translating to roughly 3.6 6 to 4
million single adults in the capital
with significant numbers living alone
and trends showing more people marrying
later remaining single longer even as a hold household compositions shift.
Told you there was a lot of people single.
So 40 to 44% that's almost half.
So I mean there's millions of people
that are single. That's my whole point as well.
It doesn't matter why they're single.
They're single, aren't they? So
I mean I don't think half the population
is choosing to be alone.
Do you get me?
So there's millions of people that are single.
I knew it. I already knew that before I
looked up. I already knew that.
Or maybe they haven't found the right one, Dustin.
You know, I've actually had chances to
be in relationships well as well. You do realize that
I've had chances to be in relationships
a few years ago. So when someone says to
you, "Oh, you've never been in a relationship."
You know, they can't even use that
against you because you've actually had
chances to be in relationships.
Not in the past year, but I have.
I have. I have, Grezy. You know, I have.
So when they say you've never had a
girlfriend, they they can't say to you,
they can't even use that because you
actually have had chances to be in relationships four times.
Yeah, Mike, I I went to dentist, got my
tooth pulled out, then I went to the
arcade. I've been out all day.
Yeah, I've been out all day, bro.
Yeah, I was I was talking to this woman
on Reddit. She's a [ __ ]
She's a [ __ ] bro.
She turned out to be a a funny [ __ ] bro. So,
yeah. Depressing. Yeah.
So, I've actually had chances to be in
relationships. They can't actually use
that. I haven't recently. Not recently,
but I have had
No, I don't use dating apps.
I'm just going to use escorts anyways
now. Um, Mike,
I only get [ __ ] anyways, so if it if
it gets that bad, I'll just use an escort.
Should I be paying for it? Not really,
but it's better than nothing. Um, it
beats going out approaching.
So, I'll just go with that option, bro.
If I do, so
wish I could get that 19y old back, bro. What? Yeah.
It's not happening, bro.
I went to the dentist today, Joseph.
Not really. Not really.
Cuz I could have been in a relationship
just not for years.
I could have been in a relationship for
2 or 3 months.
So I could technically have been in a
relationship if I wanted to. So you
can't use that.
You can't use that. I had a long day
today. Joseph for I went bowling.
Went to the dentist.
went to the arcade.
I won a Stitch toy.
I was out all day.
Uh cuz I couldn't get attached for 2 and 1/2 years.
Yeah. With one of my friends. Yeah.
I got my tooth pulled out.
I've only had one coat today, so I am cutting down. Yeah.
Oh, just one of my male friends.
Why would you say male or female? You
know, it wouldn't be a woman. Even
though it'd be a good date to go on.
No, I could have got it back if I could
have got it, but I didn't want to see
the tooth, bro. It's [ __ ] hanging. Disgusting, bro. No. Yeah,
a lot of it's to do with genetics as it
is diet, but a lot of it's to do with
genetics. You know that, Greasy.
There's people that can never drink
Coke, only drink water, brush their
teeth three times a day,
and still have um
still have um still have bad teeth.
Yeah, obviously there is obviously it is
diet, but I'm saying there is cases
where people can just have [ __ ] up teeth. Um,
like by [ __ ] up I mean have loads of
fillings and their diet's perfect. A lot
of it to do with genetics as well. I
mean, mine's not even that bad. I've
only had two fillings and one tooth
pulled out at [ __ ] 28. So,
yeah, it is the notice as well.
Yeah, I went with lady.
but um yeah, mine's just like medium, but yeah,
it's just genetics. It's like stretch.
It's like stretch marks as well.
I think my sister's had four pulled out
the back. Yeah, my sister's had four
pulled out the back, but she's never had a filling. Yeah.
What about you, Joseph? Have you ever
had any fillings?
That's what I should have done. I should
have done a six-year course and become a dentist. Jeez,
they make serious money them dentist squeezy.
Yeah, I think I've had three. I'm
getting one more done on um next week
and then I'm all done.
I'm complete. I don't think I'd have any
any more problems for years. So
yeah, they make some serious money. Them
dentist groups here.
Serious serious money, you know.
Yeah, bro. They do.
They probably make like£500 a day, bro.
Some of them
they probably make Yeah. probably5600
pound a day. Jesus
that [ __ ] then
what happened to [ __ ] the virgin's
teeth? He's got [ __ ] missing teeth
all on his front and that. No,
he's actually got missing teeth like in
in the front of that. Yeah.
[ __ ] hell, man.
I didn't wake up in a bad mood today. I
actually woke up in a good mood.
I didn't get any mood swings today.
Right. I didn't get any swings today.
Not today. I never
I was fine when I woke up.
Bro, you're talking [ __ ] I've been
having mood swings for [ __ ] years.
You do talk a lot of [ __ ] don't you, Joseph?
You're talking a lot of [ __ ] aren't you, man?
What a [ __ ] bro. What? Why would you
even come out with some uh uh
bro? I've been having mood swings for years
over women. My bad experiences. Yeah,
you've been winning any more money
today, Mr. Fur,
you've been winning any more money?
Oh, man. Oh, this Red Star's really got
nothing in life.
Oh, do you know what I was thinking
today, Steven Howard, for like one second?
Hey, do you know what I was thinking
today when I was out?
I was thinking today. Yeah.
I was thinking so, you know, when I was
in the arcades and going bowling and I
was out all day and I'm thinking, do you
know what's so mad is that none of these
people on YouTube today.
They're just sat there waiting for
content. How sad and pathetic is that? I
I only thought about it for like a
minute. I was like, cuz you obviously
anyone randomly I think you know the
likes of people like Red Star are just
sat on their ass just waiting for
content cuz they've got nothing in life
and then it went away. It's actually
bad, isn't it really?
And it's just a normal thing to go out
and do stuff.
Only lasted a minute or less than a
minute. That is strange, isn't it?
just sat indoors, no life, no
interacting with the outside world.
It's crazy, isn't it, bro? It really is mad.
It is mad.
Sat there with a little screen recorder ready. icon.
Nah, Greavves. I definitely definitely
I'm not describing you.
You've come off YouTube for a day before
and you're not on here constantly hating
and recording everything. No, I don't
think that's you.
I mean, and if that is you, I mean,
you've admitted that you don't leave the
house. You've actually admitted that you
ain't got a life.
So, okay. Well, if it's you, well,
you've admitted you haven't got a life, haven't you?
you you've actually admitted it and you
don't come on the internet hating. So
yeah, they're sat there with their
little screen recorder.
They're sat there with their little
screen recorder, bro, waiting for content.
You remember um Greavvesy Pat Mustard
used to do like eight videos a day.
Just sat there absolutely no life from
the time he woke up to the time he went to bed.
Hey bro, do you not remember the videos
he used to do of me and Monty?
Yeah, these people's on YouTube Christmas Day.
Monty man went live. Grey said, "I've
just gone live to see who's watching me.
Who's watching me on YouTube?"
Um, and if anyone's watching me, it proves
it proves that they've got no family
over Christmas. And he says that five
people in this community without a
family this Christmas. I was dead, bro. Yeah.
No, I wouldn't like I wouldn't like to I
wouldn't like to ride autumn. I don't
care about women on YouTube.
I can go out and approach if I wanted to.
I I would not ride someone that uses
filters that that's on YouTube. I don't
care. That what that's what separates me.
That's what separates me and these
clowns on this community
is that I don't care about no woman on
YouTube that uses filters. They do.
People like V do cuz he's a virgin and
he's never been with a woman. Hey bro,
that VR, have you seen him? He's
definitely definitely a virgin. that V.
Have you seen him? Proper proper virgin.
Have you seen him on Lo's
me? That's also how you know if they've
got no life. If they're biging up women on YouTube,
flirting with women on YouTube, or
putting them on a pedestal, Dusty,
they've also got no life.
They've got no life outside of YouTube
because you wouldn't if they did, they
wouldn't care about women on on YouTube.
You see, I don't I could go out and meet
someone and keep it all the way off
YouTube. I could go out and approach
someone tomorrow, get their number, and
keep it off of YouTube. Whether they
meet me or not is another story. But,
you know, I could keep it all off of
YouTube. So, why would you would you
flirt with a woman on YouTube? It don't
make sense because they don't leave
their house. People like V, they do not
leave their house. I'm telling you, bro.
Obviously, there's some decent people in
this community, bro. I'm not saying
there's not, but a lot of these people,
too many of these people, too many of
have have got no life outside of
YouTube. There's too many of them, bro. Yeah.
That's cuz they've got no life. See, on
Saturday, I could go to Waxies.
I could go to Waxies tomorrow and get
some numbers if I wanted to and just
talk to people that way.
And face it, even if they got with a
woman over YouTube, they'd get [ __ ]
over in the end. So why are they [ __ ]
with women on YouTube? Because they
don't leave the house.
I'm insulting I'm insulting Autumn.
I'm insulting the [ __ ] These people
are sing over her. What the [ __ ]
And it doesn't matter. Even if she was
good-looking, I still wouldn't I still
wouldn't do it. I still wouldn't um get
with her. I would never get with anyone
on this community, bro.
Never. Even if I I had chances to get
with Natalie G and I never.
And I'm glad I never
I could have got with [ __ ] Natalie G
before [ __ ] Monty. Yeah.
I'm not depressed, mate. I woke up in a
good mood today. Yeah.
Yeah. I could have got with that energy,
bro, but I never. Yeah.
Cuz look what happened with that USA.
Look at look at that USA. Yeah.
A lot of that that was caused cuz of
YouTube. Well, not caused, but it never
made Well, it wasn't caused over
YouTube, but when these people know who
she was, they made it 10 times worse.
So, if you got with a woman on YouTube,
you know, you know what's going to happen.
So, you know that you're you're involved
with YouTube. So, it just the whole
thing don't make sense.
I would never get with someone on um
Yeah, I've already seen it.
And I'm not depressed either. I'm not depressed today, you know.
What is this?
I'm not depressed, matey.
No, I can't. as if enlarge consoles.
What the [ __ ]
No, no, Joseph.
He's sat there 24/7, isn't he? That red
star waiting for content.
I honestly don't know how these people
can do this every day.
To miss out on life, to hate people on
YouTube they don't know.
There's no one on this community that
can say or do anything that would make
me waste their life on them. How was
about that one, Dusty?
Like, okay, put it this way. Yeah,
could come on here right now and says
that he wants to do this to kids. He has
done this to kids.
Do you think I'm going to be stalking
this guy from the time I wake up to the
time I go to bed? We'll use a different
analogy for you. So, does that mean then
I'm going to waste my whole my whole
life stalking someone like him
unless I have no life like Redstop? Do
you understand me, mate? You You understand?
You understand me, mate? Yeah.
And I tell you how they've got no life.
Do you want me to tell you how they've
got no life? Cuz I was happen to
multitask when I was in the arcades
earlier and it was very [ __ ] hard to
multitask. So, you're telling me someone
sat there having a life, but yet
stalking on YouTube 24/7 just doesn't
happen. I was multitasking slightly and
it was [ __ ] hard. You can't you can't
do it, you know. You can't, bro. You
can't. He is he is on YouTube
from the time he wakes up to the time he
go to bed. This is my first time on it
today. I haven't even checked YouTube.
You can't do it, bro. You really really can't.
Like, you you actually can't.
I would never do that, bro. I don't give
a [ __ ] what anyone says on YouTube.
I don't know, bro.
Basically. Yeah. Because just think
about it, bro. You're saying that it's
things people have said online. So if if
someone on the internet like this Ted
Valley or someone says some mad stuff,
am I going to waste my life going for
them every day?
No. It just doesn't happen. Do you
understand? It doesn't happen, bro.
It really doesn't happen.
It really, really, really, really does not happen.
for in order for people to do this every
day, they truly have nothing. Despite
what they're trying to say that they
have, there's no way, bro. There's no way.
Too much time on their hands.
Too much time on their hands. Some of
these people are Yeah.
very strange. Very, very, very strange.
Oh, I saw this video. Yeah,
they must be fat and disabled.
They must be. They must be. Bro,
why do you think you don't hear anything
in the background, Steven Howard, when
they're doing this? Like a shopping
center, people talking or whatever?
because they're sat at home. You know,
when they're doing this all of this like
screen recording and stuff, why do you
think you don't hear anything? Because
they're sat at home.
They're sat at home. They don't go out.
They don't leave the house, bro.
They You know, it's because they don't
they don't leave the house. People like
Red Star, they're housebound, bro.
[ __ ] disabled people. Strange.
I don't have bad or hygiene. My or
hygiene is perfect. I brush my teeth
three times a day. But yeah,
it is strange. It is strange. It is
You never hear anything in the background,
mate. I had one cavity and one tooth and
a bat took at 28 years of age. That's
nothing, bro. That's absolutely nothing.
I mean, you're 10 years older than me
and I've only had one more filling and a
tooth at the back. You're only 10 years
older than me.
I mean, there's only two things I've had
that you haven't, you know.
Yeah. And he is overweight. Joe is
overweight. He'll admit to you that he's
overweight. You can tell someone's
overweight by their hands as well. You
can tell by their hands.
Uh yeah, you work, do you? Highly, highly unlikely.
Yeah, you can actually tell if someone's
fat by their hands.
And Joseph Ferrar is a fat [ __ ]
Just one more. I'm going for one fill in
next week and I'm done.
So yeah, you've I've only had two more
things than what you've had.
I've only had two more things. Triple H
has had his teeth took out. A tooth took
And I'm sure Grevy has as well. A lot of people have.
So, I've only had No, I think I've had
Yeah, this will be my third one. So,
three fillings and one tooth took out.
So, that's only one more fill in than you. And
yeah, and and and Triple H has had it as well.
It could also happen when you're
pregnant as well. If you get pregnant,
um your teeth can start playing up.
Oh, well Trip Well, Triple H has had his
tooth out. He's had his back tooth out.
And another thing, Joe, you want to talk
about teeth? Yeah. Doesn't your
boyfriend have missing teeth all over
his mouth? Nunches.
Just pointing that out there.
Doesn't Doesn't your boyfriend have
missing teeth scattered all around his
mouth? Like his actual front teeth?
strange. I don't think you ever brought
it up, did you?
Cuz obviously you're all about old
hygiene and stuff. So I thought that was
a bit strange, is it?
He's actually got missing teeth
from the front.
I'm not comparing myself.
I'm saying, why haven't you said
anything about his teeth?
I thought you would have
I thought you would have had a I thought
you would have had a go at him as well.
What the hell,
bro? That's old. I know he doesn't, bro.
Bro, I know he doesn't. He talks [ __ ]
behind my back.
He's another Lavong. Yeah, we know that,
bro. He's biased. We know that.
Yeah, he's biased, lad.
Yeah. And he's biased as well.
Yeah, I know that, bro.
He's not the only one that's obsessed with me.
He's not the only one middle-aged man
that's obsessed with me, bro. There's
loads of them.
I already knew that, bro, from the
nonslegs thing when he was talking about
when he was defending nonslegs. I
already knew that.
But I just go along with it because why
not? They cry when they get blocked. So,
I already knew that, bro, with the biasness.
To be fair, LT is biased as well, to be fair.
I even said that LT was biased. So, I've
actually told other people that they're
biased as well. Not going to get into it
again because he's ridiculous, but he's also biased. Yeah,
he's biased as well.
There's loads of people like that on
here, bro. It is what it is. It
Howard's a bro. I like you, Steven Howard, man.
Thanks for bringing up the porno, bro.
Thanks for putting up the porno.
Thanks for putting up a porno. Thanks
for talking about the porno, bro. When
people's going at me at Timmy's,
that's what a real man should do. That's
what a real unbiased person um would do.
Thanks for that, buddy.
Yeah, I had a tooth out. Yeah.
Yeah. Steven Howard's not Yeah, Steven
Howard's um he's not biased. Thanks for
bringing up the porno, man.
Yeah, thank you, man. Thank you.
That's good, bro. That's good.
No one else but Kieran has Yeah.
What did you do today, Joe?
Tell everybody what you done.
Sat on YouTube
waiting for content like Red Star.
Sad, isn't it? Sad.
Better than what any of you or your
associates done today.
Yeah, I've heard myself. Yeah.
Oh, been at work. Yeah, really.
Yeah, really, man. You know what? It's
funny how you've got all this time.
It's funny how you've got all this time
on your hands for someone that works.
Someone like you don't need to work.
You're winning all these money on
properties. I wouldn't have thought you
would need to work.
I wouldn't thought you would have needed to work
for somebody that's that wins so much
money on these fobs.
You win a lot of money on fobies, man.
You could easy pack up work.
You win so much money, bro. like
so much money you win.
No, a few people do. A few people do
work on here, bro.
Ben works. How hard can it be?
No, there are a few people that do work,
man. But not Joe, not Red Star, not not
any of them people. There's a few people
that do work, bro.
There's a few people right on here, but
not not these people.
Not any of these like them kind of people, bro.
Red Star don't work.
Um, you know,
them kind of people, man. They just
they're just sat on YouTube 24/7.
They just they just they're just sat on YouTube 24/7
telling other people to get a job when
they ain't got a job themselves.
Think of it, Smash videos. You really
think that Red Star's got a life?
Sat on YouTube stalking every day with a screen recorder.
You really You actually think someone
like that's got a life, bro?
You really think someone's like that's
someone like that's got a life, bro?
Yeah, I'm a sad bastard. But you'll
never say that to my face, bro. So, I
don't care what a keyboard warrior like you says
cuz no one cares. Like, you can't even
talk. You're never going to say anything
to my face. So, no one cares. bias nonslower.
Isn't that right, Steven Howard?
No one cares, bro, cuz you will never
say that to my face. So, what what do
you want people to do? Get mad? You
can't even talk on a panel, bro. I had
my chance. No, no, no. I never had my
chance. You didn't even turn up to the pub yourself.
You didn't even You didn't even turn up
to the pub yourself.
I've tried meeting new people several
times before and it's always the same
story which is why I gave up
which is why I gave up. And it's
logical. I've tried meeting the bomb.
I've tried meeting non legs your
boyfriend. Um I've tried meeting a lot
of people on here and and it's always
the same thing. So why waste the time again, you know?
Why waste our [ __ ] time again? You know,
and that's that.
You know what?
Meet me halfway.
That's the only way I'm going to know
that you're not full of [ __ ] Meet me halfway tomorrow.
I'm actually uh I'm actually um
I'm actually free tomorrow.
I've got no point mentioning nothing.
I'll meet you halfway tomorrow
and we'll see. Right. And this is the
only way we're going to know that you're
not full of [ __ ] And you can say
whatever you want to my face.
Where is halfway?
Let me see. Halfway is like
bit more than Peter Burough, isn't it?
And if you're really not full of [ __ ]
you're really not full of [ __ ] then
we'll we'll see in a minute.
You'll see, [ __ ] cuz I know what
you were trying to do. Trying to get me
to go all the way over there. If you're
really on it, meet me halfway. Yeah.
So, yeah. See, you want to go all the
way to you. You're not about it. You're
not about it. You're not about it.
I'll call you a biased nonslegs lover to your face.
I'll call you a biased non-slegs lover
to your face.
I told LT he's biased as well with the
virgin thing and the girlfriend thing. I
told him he's biased as well.
Yeah, I also told him he's biased. So, I
don't I don't pick sides. Yeah.
Do you remember that?
Oh, that's funny, bro. Yes, she did.
Yeah. I'm not going to really be on it,
bro. Seriously, bro. Meet me halfway.
I'll meet you. I will meet you. Meet me halfway.
Mate, meet me halfway.
Meet me halfway. Show me tickets tomorrow. Yeah.
And meet me halfway.
I will I will actually meet you halfway.
No [ __ ] Actually, no [ __ ] No
[ __ ] I will meet you halfway.
That's like a bit more than Peter.
What's the stop after Peter? I can't
even remember. I haven't been to the
northeast in ages, but I'll look it up. It's like
It's like Okay. Okay.
What about like No, no. What's the one before Leicester?
Leicester's got to be halfway. So, meet
me in Leicester.
Yeah. And I've also got previews of
[ __ ] turning up, mate. And you can't
even talk. So, shut up,
you dirty, stinky little nonsle lover.
You dirty little nonslegs lover.
I think it's Leicester. It's got to be
Leicester or Love Bro. That's halfway.
So, let's meet in Leicester.
Yeah, it's got to be Leicester. It's got to be.
Well, I'm telling you, let's meet in in
Leicester or Luck.
No, it's not Nottingham.
Nottingham's 140 miles away, bro. That's
not But I'll meet you in Nottingham.
Yeah, I can meet you in Nottingham. Yeah.
No, it's not Sheffield. Sheffield's in
How can Sheffield be halfway, bro, when
it's in Yorkshire?
Use your brain, bro. How can Sheffield
be halfway when it's in Yorkshire? How
is that halfway to London? How is that
halfway from London?
That doesn't make any sense. How How How
do you work that one out, bro?
When it's 200 miles away from London.
How's that halfway?
How How is that halfway, bro? No.
Anyways, we'll do Nottingham. Yeah,
we'll do Nottingham anyways
cuz you don't want this guy having a
heart attack. We all know he's got We
all know he's got anxiety anyways. So, yeah, man.
Sheffield is a lot more than an hour
away from London, mate. I know. I've
been there three times.
Sheffield's nowhere near London.
So, anyways, we can meet in Nottingham
anyway. Yeah, we can meet in Nottingham.
Yeah, we can. Yeah, and I'll just have a
gamble on a roulette. I don't mind.
Yeah. And I'm telling you And I'm
telling you, Nottingham. Yeah.
Yeah. I'm telling you, Nottingham.
No. Sheffield's nowhere near London.
Sheffield's nowhere near London. No, I'm
not going to leads. Uhuh. I'm not going
to leads. You meet me halfway.
Oh, that's it. Because what he's going
to do Yeah. I'll tell you exactly what
this clown's going to do. Yeah. People
have done this before. He doesn't need
to travel to me. All he's got to do is go Nottingham.
He doesn't have to travel to me. All
he's got to do is go Nottingham.
The thing is, what's this? What this guy
is going to do. Yeah, I'm going to tell
you exactly what this guy's going to do.
He's going to have me go all the way
there and he's going to say, "Oh, I've
controlled you. I've made you come all
the way here and made you pay for hotels
and I know what he's going to do, bro. I
know what these people like on it.
They've done it before. So, I'm saying
let's meet halfway then. If that's not
the case, you'll have no problem coming halfway."
And if you're not willing to do that,
then [ __ ] yourself. Simple.
I know what you're going to do. You
mate, I know what you're going to do.
You know, there's not even any proof
that you live in Leeds, uh, live in
Yorkshire. There's not even any proof
that you live anywhere near there.
That's just your word.
So, if if you're really about it,
Nottingham or Lester,
I think that's fair to be honest. you know.
Yeah, that's what I thought. Yeah,
that's what that's what I was saying.
LRA or Nottingham, but I don't mind
going Nottingham either way.
Nottingham's a bit off, but I don't mind
going to Nottingham.
I was going to say LRA or Leicester. Yeah,
but he won't travel, bro.
Mate, just meet me halfway tomorrow.
Cuz if you're not going to do it,
there's no point you shit-talking
someone on Lav's channel when you're
never going to meet anyone. It's just
pointless. It just makes you look like a
fool. It makes you look like all of the
things that you accuse people on Reddit
of being a keyboard warrior. You say
that people on You say You say that
people on on Reddit are a keyboard
warrior, but you're doing the same
thing. You're doing the same thing as them.
You're actually doing the same thing as
them. You do realize that.
You know what I mean?
You're actually doing exactly the same
thing as them.
You are doing the same thing as them.
You're not meeting anyone, son. Yeah. If
you are, come to Leicester. Simple.
Leester or Nottingham or Derby, wherever
the [ __ ] East Midlands, I will come. Sorry.
I How did you know about this guy being
a Lav Mong Steven Howard?
What What What gave you the impression
that he was a Lavry Mong?
Cuz with me it was when he started
talking about nonslegs not being a
virgin because he's got some disabled girlfriend.
Red flag. Then you see him all over Lavies
[ __ ] talking [ __ ] behind people's backs. Yeah.
Yeah. When he started like sticking up
for his boyfriend launch legs when I was
having a go and red flag after red flag.
You are you are red flag after red flag. Yeah.
I mean LT is the same to be honest.
Even though LT is all right, he's
biased. He He is biased as well.
Yeah, he is as well, bro. He's also biased.
Yeah, he's also biased as well,
which is strange considering he's not
really on here, but he's also biased.
Yeah, they are biased, lad. They are biased.
which is strange because that guy is an
actual nons. That's the thing that
that's the mad thing is that that guy is
an actual pedophile.
That guy's an actual pedophile, mate.
That's mad at That's a [ __ ] madness, bro.
Well, mate, listen. I told you, meet me halfway. Simple.
Stop being like them people on Reddit.
Stop being a keyboard Yeah.
That's funny, bro.
This Josiah for all is an idiot, bro.
This guy's a [ __ ] idiot.
Guy's a [ __ ] clown, man.
You're an idiot, man. An absolute idiot.
Go show some more fake gambling wins.
I proved you wrong on a couple of things
the other day that a you don't win on
the fob tease and b you don't get banned
for live streaming.
I proved you wrong
and I was in a town as well.
You're just a bullshitter. That's what you are.
I'm starting to think you're in a
wheelchair myself to be honest. You're
just a bullshitter. Billy the
Yeah, bro. You're just a bullshitter.
That's what you are. You're a bullshitter.
We call you a lav mong.
Yeah, he's got No life. Trip R. I've
been out all day, lad.
Yeah, he's got no life, lad. Bless him.
He's another Joseph.
Sat sat in all day recording content
because he ain't got a life. I've been
out all day. Triple H. I don't have time
to sit and stalk people on the internet
that I don't know. Some of us have got a life, lad.
Yeah, some of us have actually got a
life. We don't have to sit on YouTube
stalking people we don't know every day
because they've said a couple of bad things online.
Ro how pathetic that sounds. Oh man.
Do you know what's so mad though um Trip
is that when Pat Mustard used to put
kids up, no one ever said anything.
Have you noticed that when he used to
put uh people's kids up? Yeah.
And talk about people's kids and [ __ ]
no one ever said anything.
You remember that?
When Pat used to be on there,
they used to make excuses for him. You
remember Candid Man? Yeah.
Yeah. So, it's not about stuff like
that, bro. Cuz look.
Yeah. He's very obsessed, bro. I was out
all day. I've been busy all day. I
wasn't on YouTube today, bro.
Yeah. It's sad, bro. It is sad, lad.
Have you noticed you never hear anything?
Pay pub. You'll never say anything to my face,
bro. You're just a little lavy [ __ ]
mong. Yeah, I've already proven your
lies to be [ __ ]
Even Triple H don't believe you. Um your
wins and stuff. Even Triple H don't believe you.
He was talking about this the other day
and I'm Yeah, I'm not going to be there
because I'm not going to Leeds. I told
you I'm not going to Leeds. I told you
I'll meet you in Nottingham or I'll meet
you in Leicester. So yeah, you're right.
I'm not going to be there, mate. You know,
I'm not going to be there because I know
what you're trying to do and it's not
going to work.
So that's that. Uh
yeah, I'm not meet I'm not going to leads.
I'll meet you in um Nottingham or Derby
or something like that. I'm not I'm not
meet I'm not meeting you unless you meet
me halfway. If you meet me halfway, I'm definitely coming.
I'm definitely 100% coming this time.
You little Ly Mong.
Oh, I can't go live. I can't go live.
in bookies. Well, I went I I done videos
in the bookies.
You're a [ __ ] bro. You You're a
[ __ ] bong. Just go back to Nons's
channel where you belong. Bro,
I'm not meeting you in leads. [ __ ] off.
I'll meet you halfway and that's it.
Yeah, take it or leave it. You're never
going to say anything to my face ever,
mate. Trust me, you're a fat old man.
Just keep posting fake wins on your you
you stupid page, you [ __ ] [ __ ] Yeah,
you little lathery mong. Oh,
well I Well, I can. UK signing. Can I
Can I Can I uh can I answer that?
Can I answer that? I can. I can. I can.
I can. I can. Do Do you want me Do you
want me to answer you how how how you
can, bro? Because
a uh Pat Mustard used to say stuff and
do stuff, but no one ever said anything
because they're all biased. That's what
a and b, bro, just because people have
said the most [ __ ] up things online,
that doesn't justify stalking every day.
You're you're you're wasting your life
away for that person. I just explained
this. I don't know if you was on here,
but I wouldn't I don't care what
someone's done online or said online.
I'm not wasting my life stalking them
every day. And if you are doing that,
then there's something wrong with you.
Really can [ __ ] go and [ __ ]
he can go and [ __ ] rape a child and I
wouldn't be stalking him every day for
10 years. If you want to use that as an
example, he can [ __ ] murder a police
officer. I wouldn't be stalking him from
the time I wake up to the time I go to
bed. So if someone's doing that, then
that's saying a lot about their life
really, isn't it?
I'm using them as examples, as extreme
examples. You get you get the point I'm
trying to make. Whatever the whatever
the [ __ ] it is they're doing. No one
that's got stuff going on does this,
bro. Do you not understand? No one.
No [ __ ] one, man. No one does it. You know,
how can you invest that much time on
someone you've never met that you don't know
that you will never meet? And to me,
it's just crazy, bro. It's crazy. It is
generally generally crazy. Really is.
They should leave the house once in a
while. We're doing the world of good. What's up?
I mean, I proved you wrong with facts. I
proved that you can record in the
bookies and not get banned.
I mean, I I I proved you wrong.
I mean, I proved I mean, I proved you wrong.
Yeah, I know it's double standards with
the Pat Mustard thing, with the nonslegs
thing. It's always been double standards, bro.
I I I pointed it out to LT
uh the other day.
I asked him why he was being biased.
They've got biasness and double
standards and they don't even realize
it. A lot some of these people I mean I
proved you wrong. I went in the bookies.
I'm recording and nothing happened. You
said that if you go in the bookies and
you record you get banned.
Yes, I have been in a small town. Where
I was was in a small town. That was a
That was Romford Town Center.
Yes, I have. That was a small town.
It will always be the same with these people. people, lads.
Yeah. I mean, Ronford Roford's a small
town and I and I recorded there.
You're talking out your ass, lad.
You are talking out your ass. You do not
get banned from recording. You're talking
out your ass and I'm not going to lead
for a millionth time. No one's going to leads.
No, it's not going on for me, bro. cuz
I'm not on here anymore. I was out all
day. This I'm not I'm not being on here
no more, bro. So, it's not going to go
out. It's not going to go on for me with me.
It's not going to go on with me, lad.
They'll be doing it to themselves.
They'll be doing it with themselves,
lad. They won't be doing it with me.
They'll be going around in circles for
12 months with themselves. They won't be
doing it with me.
Yeah, I'm going to come on here now and
then, bro. I'm just going to be on and off here
if and when, but I probably am going to
leave. And if I don't, I'm going to be
on here rarely. I won't be going back
and forth with these people, bro. Enough. >> Yeah.
What? Same people every day.
What? Same people every day. Yeah.
What was you doing today?
What was you doing all day, lad? >> Um,
nah, bro. It's not even 20 people, man.
It's like 10. It's not 20 people, man.
Yeah, I was out all day while she was on
YouTube hating on people that you don't
know. Class, it
Yeah, smoking smoking weed sat on YouTube.
Sounds about right, lad. Is it?
That red star is a [ __ ] joke. He's
such a joke loser.
I've never come across such a loser like
him in my life, bro. I'm not even joking.
You would have thought they would get
bored in it after like six months of
doing this. You would have thought like,
"Okay, we'll [ __ ] with someone or just
whatever." It's funny, isn't it? You
would have thought after like
six year, like 6 months, they would have
got bored of it, ain't it? Co or they
never seem to get bored, do they?
It's mad, isn't it, bro? It's funny as [ __ ]
That is funny, bro. They don't get bored. No. Yeah.
I think he's gay, bro. That's what I
think. I think he's a homosexual.
Yeah. They're always at work. They're
always doing stuff,
but they're on YouTube 24/7. I know.
It's mad, eh?
Yeah, it's a madness.
Same faces every day, ain't it? Yeah.
I generally think a lot of these people
on here are actually disabled, bro.
I'm not I'm not even joking. I think
they they must be.
Yeah. houses, families. Yeah, right.
How hard can it be? He's got a family.
Anyone? Hey, bro. You know that. How
hard can it be? He's actually a cool
guy, man. He goes on large. He's
actually a cool guy. His name is Simon.
He He actually He actually has got kids.
He doesn't hate on anyone though, man. He's cool.
He doesn't get involved or anything. Uh,
but yeah, I've actually met that guy,
bro. He's actually cool. Charlie's cool.
So, anyone that's got
uh stuff going on in their lives
wouldn't do this.
You know what I mean, man?
I wouldn't be doing this. Have you seen
that? How hard can it be, Steven Howard? Yeah.
Yeah. I'm going to brush my teeth
tomorrow. I brushed my teeth before I
went dentist, but obviously the thing's
hurting. So, yeah. Oh gosh,
I'm so tired, bro. Going to go to sleep
in a minute.
Some mouthwash. Yeah. Could do. Yeah,
looks like it. I won't be on YouTube tomorrow anyways. Yeah.
No, I won't be on to my Steven Howard.
That Jo is a [ __ ] mong.
You like LT? Anyone on here like LT?
What do you people think of LC?
That J is such a lovely mong.
You don't like him, do you, Steve? Bless you.
Yeah, it's kind of hurting my mouth, bro.
Mate, you're just a lavy bog.
When are you going to get off of YouTube
and get a life?
You sad bastard.
When are you going to get off YouTube?
Get a life. You sad bastard.
You sad sad sad bastard. You're sad
You are a sado.
You have no life.
You stalk people like Red Star cuz you got nothing.
You sad bastard.
Yeah, you need to tell yourself that,
mate. When you're defending nods when
I'm calling him a virgin.
You're the one with the agenda, Dad.
You're the one with the agenda.
You're the one that's biased, not me.
Where is Kevin anyways? I haven't seen
him for months.
Do you know what I think you Red Star
need to get a life?
That's what I think. I think you two
actually need to get a life.
No, you actually need to go live.
No, seriously. Joseph, you and M need to get alive.
Need to get alive this year.
Yeah. Go down to Waxies, lad. Yeah. Waxies.
Good old Waxies.
Waxies little sister. Do you know
there's a pub called Waxies Little
Sister? Triple H.
Yeah. Waxy's Little Sister.
That's the pub next to it.
Wax is Fiona Macdonald.
Triple H. Fiona Macdonald.
Mad name, is it Fiona Macdonald? Fiona McDonald's. Mad.
No, cuz he was licking ass.
When Bomie used to come on and Patty, he
used to lick ass, isn't it?
I need to go in a minute, lads.
There's no point playing a game of chess with Timmy.
Arguing with Timmy is like playing a
game of chess with a pigeon. Even if you
beat the pigeon, it's going to [ __ ] all
over it and strut around like it's one.
That's why I don't argue with Timmy.
It's like playing a game of chess with a pigeon. Yeah.
Pointless, lad. [ __ ] pointless.
But there's a few favorite sayings I
like on here.
My favorite is same people, same story.
See you next year.
Same people, same story. Bro, that one
never gets old. Never.
Ben just thought he'd come on in the new
year. See what what the crack was in it.
Bit of banter, you know.
Same people, same story.
No, I hate kids.
I want a dog though. I want I do want to
get my own dog. Um French here.
Look at Dusty's Look at Dusty's commentary.
O this guy here, this black guy that
approaches you uploaded Triple H. It's
the same old sad song. Oh, he's copying
my words. It's the same old sad song.
All that's funny, bro. This is a copycat
community, is it? Stephen Howard,
it's the same old sad song. All I'm
going to click on that video.
All Triple H. This is a copycat community.
It's a copycat community, lad.
Yeah, it's a copycat community.
They'd get whisked straight into the care system. J
You can't have kids. Yeah.
Yeah. Get whisked straight into the care system.
You shouldn't find that [ __ ] funny
though. Triple H. Like losing new Monty
lost everything over YouTube. It's not
funny. It's not
That shit's not funny. you know, losing
everything over YouTube.
That's madness, bro. Madness.
No, not really.
No, this YouTube was meant to be
innocent. Triple H something, you know,
kids could come on. Yeah,
I need to go anyways. Yeah. So, I'll see
you again when I see you.
Yeah, man. I'm tired as [ __ ] See you later. Yeah.