Yo, just a quick one. By the way, not
going to be on here long cuz some of us
have actually got a life
quickly. Uh cuz I just watched that uh
that thing. So, I'm only going to be on
here quick just just to say something.
Maybe someone can answer it. I doubt it
though because you don't really get many
answers from disabled people in this
community cuz I've just watched this video now. Yeah, [snorts]
one second. Let a few people join. Um,
it's not welcome back, mate. I'm only
going to be on here for 20 minutes
maximum. There's no welcome back. I've
got a life. Unlike you sad, spasticated
people that ain't got no life on YouTube
talking about other people. We'll get on
to talking about other people in a
minute. Uh, one second and then I'm only
going to be on here quick and then I'm off.
Still repeating. And that just clarifies
how disabled you are. You know, that's
another thing that we're going to also
be talking about. Um, a lot of these
lavry mongs. Um, also disabled. Um,
that's why they repeat themselves every day.
Um, but we'll wait. Anyways, let a few
more people join cuz I'm not going to be
on here long anyways. So,
yeah. Let let a few more people join.
Don't have to be repeating the same
[ __ ] you know. Can't be doing that now,
right? No, I just wanted to say
something, Grezy. Let a few more people
join. Still skin. You said that two
times now. And the only person that skin
is yourself. So, stop talking about
yourself. Anyways, we'll get on to that
cuz that's part of the disabled um thing
that we're going to get on to how you
people try to project your disabilities
onto other people. Uh there's not going
to be no shouting, Greavesy. There's not
going to be nothing. I'm just going to
point out some facts. Um,
from what I'm reading, um,
yeah, one second.
Uh, let a few more people join. No, I'm
chilling today. I'm resting.
One second, bro. Hold on. Let a few more
people join. Let a few more people join.
I was saying this to Laney. Um,
and to reply to this, Smokey Be agreed.
I'm finished bullying him. You never
bullied me to begin with. Um, so you
couldn't finish something that you never
done. Um, you're just sad, fat, ugly
people in here that ain't got no life.
You bully no one. But no matter how many
times people tell you these things, you
still think that you bully people. But
anyways, that's not what the point is anyways, right? Is one second
and then we're going to get on to
disabledness as well. Few more people
joining. One second. is um
what I don't understand, okay, we can
say it now is what I don't understand is
how these people in this community
talk about people being a loser when
they're the biggest losers going like
they are the ultimate ultimate losers.
They're sat on YouTube 24/7 in their
40s. They've got no money. They got no
life. They got no friends. They've got
nothing going for themselves. They're
just wasters that sit on YouTube talking
about other people that they don't know
that's better than them, that's younger
than them and better than them. These
people are the ultimate losers. Like
they can't even take one day off of
YouTube. Like they and I'm talking about
the Lavine Mreezy. Like they are
literally the losers of all losers.
They've literally got nothing in their
life and they're and they're trying to
talk about other people. That's the
thing that makes me what the [ __ ] Like
I'm looking I'm reading this bro and I'm
thinking a bunch of low-life losers that
are probably in wheelchairs talking about me
talking about me really mate and and and
and that's not reacting like have these
people looked at themselves you know
like on YouTube for 15 years repeating
the same [ __ ] self- projecting no life
no money and they're talking about other
people really bro
really really like it's it's mad and and
and then they're trying to call people
disabled group but bro these people are
the biggest disabled people you'll ever
come across in your life. You tell me
right anyone who's watching this that's
unbiased normal adults in their 30s in
their 40s that come on the internet for
15 years repeating the same [ __ ] and
hating people that they don't know. You
tell me what person that's not disable
You tell me one person that's not
disabled that does this.
No, I'm just I'm asking. No shouting.
Oh, [ __ ] all that [ __ ] I'm asking,
bro. So, like I said, it's time these
people really started investing in a
mirror. You know, they're not that. I'll
buy you a mirror if you want. You know,
obviously, you know, um they're not that
you really need to start investing in a
mirror because you can't spend another
bloody god knows how many years talking about yourselves.
You are disabled. You are losers. You
are wasters. You It's all about your own
lives. You've never had a woman. You
don't have a girlfriend. Like if you
understand what I'm saying, like stop
talking about people that are better
than you in life. It's it's it's
madness. That's the only thing I find strange.
Like I don't care about the skin talk
because these people are skin. I don't
give a [ __ ] about that. They they've
been self-projecting that for years. But
think about it, bro. They're
how they think they can talk about anyone else
that are better than them is beyond me.
I just I just I just don't get it. I
just don't understand it, you know?
hateful, bitter old men that ain't got
nothing in life that have to jump onto
YouTube every day. Look at your own
selves before judging other people.
Just just just think of yourselves. I
mean, look, I've gone live. I'm not
going to be on live. I'm not going to be
live long. You're straight onto YouTube again.
Hold on. Should you people have work?
Should you people have jobs? No, you
don't. No life. Just straight onto
YouTube, you know.
straight onto YouTube as usual. Madness.
It's actually mad how they think they
can talk about other people when they're
the life's they're not even life's
losers because they don't even fit into
society. These people, you know, they
they're such bums. They're such losers
that they don't even fit into society.
They're coming on here talking about
people that are better than them. Come
on. Seriously, man. It's it's it's it's
it's it's really it's really pathetic
now. You know, still repeating
yourselves in [ __ ] 2026 and you call
other people disabled. Come on now. It's
time you started investing in a mirror.
You really, really, really need to start
investing in a mirror, lads. Cuz this is
getting pathetic now.
At your age, not your shoe size. How is
a 28-year-old more uh more mature than you?
You aren't you people supposed to be
older than me?
You are the biggest losers. You and by
you I mean LJ's followers. The the
people that come from LJ's channel. You
are the ultimate losers, bro. Like the
biggest losers to ever exist. How you
think you can talk about other people is
[ __ ] beyond me. You got some nerve
trying to talk about other people. I
mean, it's so bad. Yeah. It's like,
okay, do you know what? [ __ ] [ __ ] women.
[ __ ] friends. [ __ ] [ __ ] all of that
stuff. [ __ ] you know, these people,
let's just say for argument sake that
they um I don't know, just stuff's
happened in their life. They were dealt
a bad card or whatever. So, put all of
that aside. They haven't even got a
life. Like, think about that. Think
think about that for one second, bro.
That the people in here legit don't even
have a life. Not even a life. I'd be
very very surprised if these people even
leave their [ __ ] house.
or their bedsits, whichever one they
live in. And they're trying to talk
about me. They're they're they're really
really trying to talk about me. That's
that's what you call projection at its
finest. You know, how many of these
people have a mom? None of them. How
many people of these How many of these
have got money in a family? None of
them. Just think, just read between the
lines with these people, you know? Just
read between the lines.
Very strange individuals. That's all
I've got to say. You know,
I only leave the house with mommy. Yeah,
of course I do. I mean, and what you're
saying, what I'm saying about you is
correct. That's why you're laughing
because you know I'm right. Because you
know I'm right what I'm saying, bro. You
can't trigger me. You're not going to
trigger me. The only reason I was pissed
off yesterday, uh, last week, bro, is
because I was in a bad mood. Anyways, I
don't understand Smash videos. Yeah,
they're calling me a loser when they're
worse than me. They got no family. They
got no money. They got no life. They're
just bums that just sit on the internet.
Wasters. Like absolute wasters trying to
talk about people better than them,
which I don't I don't understand that,
bro. I I generally generally generally
don't understand that. None of them have
got lives. None of them have got their
[ __ ] together. They they think about it,
bro. They have been on the internet now
for the past 15 years, obsessing over
people, repeating the same [ __ ]
obsessing over people that they don't
know. So, does that not tell you how
disabled these people really really are themselves?
Yeah, I'm a virgin. Stop talking about
yourself. You're not going to trigger me
anyways. So, just stop it. Everything
that you say is just about yourselves.
Everything you say is literally about
yourselves. Okay. Okay. Use this
analogy. Use this analogy. Autumn can't
put a picture up without using filters.
And you're trying to and you're trying
to talk to me. You're trying to cuss me
out. You look like an Oompa Loompa, bro.
Even when you're using filters. Look at
yourself. Like literally look at your
life and look at yourself. Like you're
trying to slag me off when you're using
filters. You look like Oompa Loompa. For
[ __ ] sake. Even with filters. So could
God only imagine, right?
When you don't use filters.
Come on. And listen, Autumn, the only
people, let me tell you something. The
only people that tell you that you look
good are these old men on here that are
virgins. Yeah. They're the only Have you
know, you know, do you know I'll tell
you a reason. You know why you get
attention on this community and why you
get these old men obsessing over you?
Because they're fat, ugly skin virgins.
They ain't got no life. They can't go to
the pub. They can't go to the bar. They
can't chat up a woman and get a number
because they're too skinn. They're too
fat. They're too ugly. They're too
scared. That's why you get all of this
tension. That's why you get all of this
unnecessary attention, you know? And and
that's the truth. And that is honestly
the truth. You know what's so bad is
that even if you offered to meet one of
these people, they're their anxiety is
so bad, bro. They literally wouldn't
even meet you. They literally would not
even meet you. I'm I'm not even lying.
I'm telling you facts. The truth hurts.
You have to be called to be kind. So,
you know, they're only old, ugly men
that ain't that that that that have
nothing. They're virgins. I've seen the
the way the people that type um you
know, uh you know, they're fat, ugly,
skinned virgins. You know, that's why
they give you all this attention. They
can't go out and meet a woman. They
can't go out and get a number.
Uh that's the thing.
And that's that. And that's that, man.
And that's that. Another day in bed,
depressed. No, I'm chilling today.
Recovering. Are you people going to be
sat on YouTube all day obsessing, hating
people that you don't know for another
[ __ ] 15 years?
But yeah, Smash. How these people think
they can judge other people is beyond me.
Literally everything that they say is
theirelves. Literally everything that
they say is theirelves. I just went on
to Lauria. I thought, "Oh, let me see
what this [ __ ] is saying." And the
comments, it's just it's just people
that just talk about themselves. You
would have thought they would have got a
brain and they would have stopped
calling themselves disabled losers in
2026, but apparently not. So,
yeah, more people. Yeah, they they
obsess over me more than anyone, bro.
Even more than Timmy. There's a lot of
people obsessed with Timmy. But that's
what happens. Smash videos. It's the
It's the perks of being younger and
better looking than these people.
I'm addicted to YouTube. No, I'm not
addicted to YouTube, mate. No, I'm not.
No, I'm not. I've took a day I've took
weeks off of YouTube. I YouTube is not my life.
So, no, you people are addicted to
YouTube. Ben Fury, man, you know what?
You're just the man I've been looking
for. I went on Lauria and
I actually saw your comment. What makes
me laugh, bro? Yeah. Is how these people
think they can call you losers when
they're worse than you. They're older
than you. They're uglier than you.
They're [ __ ] disabled. They got no
family. They got no money. And then they
think that they can talk about you. And
by you, I mean me. This is the This is
what I don't understand. It's not like
they're wasters that and they're just
doing what they're doing because they're
wasters. So, they're owning what they
are. No, no, no, no, no. They try to make you
feel like the situation that they're in.
They are wasters. They are losers. They
ain't got no life. Mate, I was out all
day yesterday, Ben. All day. I went to
the dentist. I went bowling. I went out.
And the only reason I'm not going out
today is cuz I'm chilling, you know? I'm
recovering from the dentist. And I just
want to chill, you know, have a day off.
And at the end of the day, and then
they're trying to talk about people that
are better than them. How does that make
any sense? It It literally does not make
any sense, bro. They're [ __ ] old men.
They're old men, bro.
They're They're old men, right?
Obsessing over people that they don't
know every day.
Come on, Ben. It's [ __ ] weird, isn't it?
It's [ __ ] weird, isn't it, mate?
You know. Yeah, I'm good, man. I'm just
chilling. I just went on Lavies. I just
went on Lavy's um Triple H and that's
what made me go live because I don't
understand how these people, these
wasters, these middle-aged wasters can
try to call anyone else losers when
they're literally life's losers. They
are the alltime Hall of Fame losers. No
money, no family. They ain't even got a
mom. That's why they go on about Laney,
you know, and they say, "Oh, you went to
the went to the dentist with Laney cuz
these people haven't got a mother. They
haven't got a mother. They haven't got
any friends. they haven't got a life.
And you know what? Even if they didn't
have a mother and they didn't have any
friends and they actually had a life,
then fair play. You know, some people
are dealt a a bad uh card in life. But
guess what, bro? They haven't even got a life. So,
and they try to talk about me. Someone
better than them. [ __ ] off, man. Seriously.
Yeah. Same people every day. Same
spastics every day as Monty would call it.
Same people, same story. them
and then they tried to talk about you.
This is one of the things I don't
understand how middleage bums life
losers that ain't even got hope and try
to call other people other people a
loser. These people
seriously these people out of all people
can try to judge your life.
Seriously, bro. Yeah. I went on Lavies,
man, and there was a silly comment. And
I thought, "Oh, we'll talk about this
again." You know, what is this?
And think about it, Ben. Yeah. When I
was when I was bowling yesterday, when I
was out, I was thinking, there's no way,
bro, there's no way that these people
can do this every day and have got a
life because I had to multitask doing
something yesterday and it was annoying
me. So, there's no way that these people
are sat on YouTube every day hating and
somehow I've got a perfect life. There's no way.
you know, they it's it must be horrible
to to to wake up every day and be
jealous of somebody that you don't know.
I couldn't do it. I generally generally
generally generally could not do it. Sat
on YouTube obsessing and jealous of
someone every day. I I just Yeah, that's
what it is, man. And have you noticed as
well, Ben? Another thing is you will
notice as well because all of these
people that are on loveies are all
similar. They're all similar age.
They're all fat. They're all ugly.
They've all got no friends, right? And
and like I've said, anyone that's
younger and better looking than these
people, they try to bring you down with
them. That's what it is. Yeah. They they
want you to be one of the levery Mongs.
Yeah. That's why Why do you think they
get on so well, bro? Why do you
literally think they get on so well?
Because they're all the same. All fat,
all old, all ugly. Why do you think,
bro, when you Bro, did you not see Yeah.
three years ago when I joined the gym,
how mad these people are getting because
they like, "No, no, we've got to bring
them down to they they try. They want to
bring people down to their level."
That's what it is with these people,
you know? They because they're fuckups,
because their skin because they ain't
got a life. That's what it is, bro. And
I'm right in it. And I'm saying it
better than Monty, man. I'm [ __ ]
right. Even little things like if you
went to the gym, bro, you know, because
they're in their 40s, they ain't got no
hope. They're [ __ ] You get what I'm
saying, bro? And that's what it is. It
is that. It is 100% that.
It is. I know these people better than
they know themselves.
And that's why all they can do is laugh
because it's the truth what I'm saying.
You know, it's the truth what I'm saying
with these people.
Cuz think about it, Ben. If it was
really about not being jealous and
people talking about kids, why did no
one have a problem with Pat Mustard? We
was talking about this yesterday. You
not find it mad how there's people that
are not saying stuff to non legs and Pat
Mustard and all of these people um you
know that's that said stuff about kids.
So we put their logic to rest basically
because they're just yeah they're just
fat ugly jealous people that ain't got a life. Um
and that's what it is that they want you
to be one of them.
It's like you what you basically said.
Yeah. They want you to be like one of
them. And I refuse, bro. I refuse. I
will never be like these people. Never.
Ever. Ever. Ever. Ever. And at the end
of the day, bro, even if I'm a loser
compared to uh society, you're no loser
compared to these people. You're no
loser compared to these people. Sat on
YouTube every day ain't got a [ __ ]
life. You know what I'm saying? [ __ ] no,
bro. [ __ ] no.
It's because they're biased, lad. They
used to do it with Pat Mustard. It's
because they're biased.
Yeah, it's because they're biased, brother. Um,
and you get like two, three people that
aren't biased. It's just, it's just They
used to do the same thing with Pat
Mustard, bro. They used to do the same
thing with Pat.
I wouldn't be live every day, brother.
Listen, I was out all day yesterday. I
was on YouTube once. Yeah. Why are you
on my live? And if you had a life, you
wouldn't be on my live stream right now.
And if you had a life, you wouldn't be
on my live stream right now, would you?
Cuz it takes two to tango. Isn't that
right, Grezy? Cuz why is it then? Why is
it, Ben? Yeah. All the times I'm on
YouTube, all the times I'm on YouTube,
all the times I'm on YouTube, these
people on here with me. So that must
mean that it's certified that they have
got no life.
That must mean that they've got no life
then, mustn't it? Also, I'm in uh I went
bowling with my mommy. What did you do yesterday?
Sit on YouTube. Didn't even leave your
house. I think I'd rather go bowling
with my mommy than sit on YouTube. And I
actually went with a couple of people
actually. I would rather go bowling with
my bubby than sit on [ __ ] YouTube and
waste like you obsessing over people
that you don't know every day. You can't
You can't skit someone that owns it. You
can't skit someone that owns it, bro.
I'm You really really really can't. Yeah,
it's crazy, isn't it, Ben? It's crazy,
isn't it, lad?
You know, it's It is crazy. These
people, what life have they got? Get
owned daily. None of you clowns own
anyone, mate. None of you clowns have
ever owned anyone. You own yourselves.
You are the ones that are sat on YouTube
every day hating people that you don't
know cuz you're all fat and ugly.
Brother, you people own yourselves. You
don't own a man like me. Trust me. I
don't know how many times I have to tell
you this. Listen, let me let me give you
people a reality check one more time.
You're fat. You're ugly. You're skint.
You don't own anybody. You own
yourselves daily when you wake up every
day. I hope that got through to you. I
had to raise my I had to raise my voice
a little bit more and that's the last
time I'm saying it. So that's that. Uh anyways,
I was going to go out today, Triple H,
but not today, sorry, yesterday. Uh not
yesterday, tomorrow. But it's January,
is it? No one's going to be out.
Yeah, I was going to go for a little
drink, lad. Oh,
but no one's out, are they? So,
I might have to leave it a couple weeks.
Yeah, I'm getting back to going out now,
Ben. Yeah, I'm going back to going out
now and doing stuff. You know what I
mean, bro? So, that's good.
To be honest, no one laughed at me
losing 100 pound to be honest, Ben. No
one actually said anything when I lost
100 pound on the roulette. No one said
nothing to be fair, man.
I don't think I would have drunk today
because of the mouth obviously. Probably
I would have went tomorrow, but there's
no point because no one's going to be
out, is there? So, it's pointless.
No one laughed. I lost 100 pound. No one
laughed. To be fair, I was just proving
that Joe F wrong, wasn't I? Um, Triple.
The fact that um the fact that um
the fact that uh you don't get banned
doing videos in the bookies and you
don't win on them [ __ ] things. No one
laughed at it because deep down they
know I'm right. They know I'm right,
bro. Why do you think no one laughed at
me losing that 100 pound? Because they they know.
Because they know, bro. It's the truth.
I prove that guy to be wrong. And I will
be going Nottingham soon anyways. I will
be going to Nottingham soon. And if that
guy wants to meet me, he can come to
Nottingham. I'm making it even more
easier for him.
So yeah, that's another thing.
I know, man. And he's an obsessed loser.
We know that.
You're And you're on YouTube all alone
hating on people that you don't know.
And you're on YouTube, Mr. Lonely every
day. Mr. Lonely on YouTube, a little
lavy mong. And you're all alone. Mr.
Lonely on YouTube in your 40s. A fat ugly prick.
Yeah, man. And you're a fat ugly prick
sat on YouTube every day.
Peter Belly's words is uh is a bit more, you know,
is a bit more um harsher than yours.
Sorry, lad. But it's the truth.
But yeah, you know, I find it strange
how many middleweight I think these
people want to bum me. Triple H. I
generally think they want to bum me.
These people, they want me to open my
ass for them. Strange.
I think they want they want to [ __ ] me or something.
I I just wanted to say I just I just
wanted to come on here and say is is
that how these people how these people
can sit on YouTube every day calling
other people a loser when they're the
biggest losers themselves.
That's all, bro. I'm I'm on and off
here, bro. I'm not on here every day.
All day, every day, lad.
I'm not on here all day. Every day. I've
just come on here to say this. Like I
went I watched Well, I didn't even watch
the video. I went I clicked on LJ's uh
channel, bro. on the video and I'm
reading the comments and I'm thinking
these people are calling me a loser.
These fat ugly waste of virgins are
calling me a loser. What?
What the [ __ ]
I I just I just can't believe these
people. That's one of the things I can't
what some I can't believe it on here,
bro. How these wasters that are worse
than you are judging you.
Come on now, bro. Come on.
It just doesn't make no sense. But I am
getting on with my life anyways. That boy, bro.
I'm just chilling now anyways, bro. I
don't get any mood swings or nothing.
I'm all right. I just was I just read
that, bro. And I just thought I'd come
and talk about it.
Yeah, I'm good, bro.
it is strange how many middle-aged
people I've got obsessed with me though,
isn't it? Uh, Triple H.
Yeah, it is strange. It is very, very Very strange.
It's madness, bro. It is really mad.
Bad a bro. Very bad.
Younger mxes. What the [ __ ] is that?
No, bro. I'm just going to rest his
mouth. I think you don't need to feel
sorry for me, bro. You people need to
feel sorry for yourselves.
Yo, you you are the ones that on on
YouTube every day happen to obsess
obsess over people that you don't know.
You really need to feel sorry for yourself.
And that boy, you already know the
answer to that question, lad.
You already know the answer. So, oh, I
thought that was what what it meant. You
know, it's never going to change.
You've you've accomplished everything I ever wanted.
So that's why you ain't got a life.
Oh, and that's why you haven't got a life. Oh, okay.
Yet you're on YouTube and you haven't
got a life because you've accomplished
everything that you wanted. Oh, okay.
Yeah. Okay. I don't know, bro. I don't know.
But yeah, that boy, you know, it's never
going to change, lad. So, uh,
in in this country anyways.
Yeah, maybe I'll go out. I can't even go
out in January, bro. It's dead. No one's
It's pointless unless it's the end of
January. Uh, I don't know, bro.
I don't know when I'm going to go out. Um,
I don't know.
I would have maybe went out tomorrow if
if Yeah, [snorts]
I don't know.
Get some food and that I'll probably go
to a steakhouse to be honest. Next time
Yeah. Oh, UK asylum. Why don't you join
the hangouts and put your camera on?
It'd explain a lot. That's why I always
say to these people, that boy, I say,
"Come on the hangouts and put your
camera on." They can never do it.
They can never ever do it. Never. They
can never do it, lad.
But yeah, you've I take it. You've
noticed the bias list then. Uh, Triple
H. You've noticed the biasless.
What? Did you just notice that, lad?
You just noticed that? Yeah. I'm
probably going to go to a steakhouse
maybe. Yeah. before I go out. When I go
out drinking again,
there's just no point drinking in
January. Even though I'd want to go out,
but I can still go to like a restaurant.
I'll just go to a restaurant. I've
already had a girlfriend, mate. You
haven't even had sex.
Nothing kills me, bro. I'm not bitter
about anything. I'm loving life. I'm not
sat on the internet hating people I
don't know every day like you people.
Nah, nothing kills me, bro. But it must
kill you being a virgin.
Nothing kills me. Definitely definitely
definitely definitely doesn't kill me.
Nothing kills me, mate. Cuz I've had
more women than most of you people on here.
I've had more women than most of you
people on here. To be fair,
fat, ugly bogs, haters. I've had more
women than most of you people on here.
Most A lot of these people in here are
still virgins. You know, Triple H. A lot
of them are actually still virgins.
They're just what they're trying to do
is they're trying to make you feel the
way that they do. Fat, ugly skinned
virgins. Why do you think that whenever
you go on J's is all hate towards people
that they don't know?
Do you not understand, lad? Do do you not understand?
But yeah, they've gave a couple of nons
a free pass, bro.
Yeah, that big nose thing is boring now,
mate. We all know that I'm younger and
better looking than [ __ ] 95% of
people on here. So, and I have had a
girlfriend. Stop trying to bring me down
to your fat ugly level. It's not going
to work, you waster.
You're wasting your time. You're not
going to bring me down to your level,
your little low life level. And if you
had a life, you wouldn't be [ __ ] even
doing this right now. You're not going
to bring me down to your level.
All the things that you do and say is
just self-p projecting. You're not going
to bring me to your level. You're
wasting your time.
You're literally wasting your time.
You're actually just wasting your time
projecting your bully victim life onto me.
Yeah. You stop calling yourself a manta.
Listen, bro. You're not going to trigger
me because we all know what you people
are that do this. Like it it's boring
out. It's very very very very very very
boring. We all know how the cookie
crumbles with you people. So just give
it a rest. You know, you know,
triggered. You need to think of some new
words, lad. This is getting boring now.
Think of some new sayings. Think of some
new words, mate. I'm supposed to be the
disabled one. Come on.
[ __ ] me, bro.
Yeah. Anyways, Triple H, they used to
give Pat Mustard a past a pass as well.
Yeah, they used to give him a pass as well.
Yeah, they done it with a couple of people.
Yeah. Okay, I'm disabled. Thank you,
bro. I'll put the link up. See if you join.
Yeah, I'll put the link up. See if you join, man.
Let's see if you join, lad. Come on.
Come in the box. As Monty says,
that's another thing. Why does mo Why
does most of you people um
Why do most of you people um
not join L J's hangouts? Have you
noticed that? Triple H. Most of them
won't join uh LJ J's hangouts. Red store
took your sublet money. You keep telling
yourself that. Um so why does no one
join LJ J's hangouts? Have you noticed that?
They don't join and talk. You know why?
It's cuz they're [ __ ] spastics.
I mean, more people join my hangouts
than then they join his hangouts. It's
because they're [ __ ] probably most of
them are in wheelchairs, lad. They're
they're [ __ ] fat, ugly. They probably
can't even talk properly, bro. Have you noticed that?
No one took my matey. Peter Benny makes money.
Peter Belly's got buddy. That's for me
to know and you to never find out. But
you keep telling yourself that.
Yeah, they did what Mustard said.
Yeah, that's what I'm saying. And that's
how you know with these people that it's
just jealousy. So when these people try
to say about how like it's stuff that
you said about kids and stuff. No, no,
no, no, no. They're just jealous. That's
what it is. They they do this because
they're jealous. I mean, look at um
Yeah. He said stuff about dead relatives
and he spoke about [ __ ] um thingies
kids as well. So they they do this
because they're just jealous low lives
deep down. They'll never admit it to
themselves, but they are. They are, bro.
They really really really are. I mean,
look at the evidence for [ __ ] sake.
Think about it, man. Think about it.
Well, I've already said what I've had to
say about her. She's ugly, fat, and she
uses filters, and she's still ugly with
the filters. And I said, "The only
attention you can get, the only She's
Bro, she's so Listen, bro. She is so
ugly." Yeah. That the only attention she
can get is from old pathetic virgins on
this community. Imagine that, bro.
Imagine that one.
Imagine that. Like, she's so stinking
Yeah. that she can't even get attention
in real life. She has to get it on a
loser community full of virgin old men
that have got nothing in life. Like she
can't even go on Instagram and just get
it from like people outside of this
community. That's how you know you're
down bad, bro. That's how you know
you're really, really, really, really
damn bad is when you're using filters
and you're still looking ugly in them
filters. And the only attention you can
get is from old men on the internet. Old
[ __ ] pathetic virgins like Bo.
It's a madness, bro. It actually is a
madness. You know that?
That's how you know you're [ __ ] bro.
Seriously, that's how you know you're down bad.
down bad. For real.
Anyways, I'm going to jump off in a minute. Anyways, yeah,
yeah. Why won't you join the panel
anyways? UK asylum.
Most of these people won't join the
panel because they're [ __ ] fat and
ugly stinking ass people. Not today,
bro. No, I'm chilling.
You won't be seeing me after five, mate.
Definitely definitely definitely
definitely not. I just basically come on
air smash to to tell these losers, stop
trying to talk about other people being losers
when they're losers themselves. You want
me to stay on? Join the hangouts then, bro.
Join the hangouts and let's talk about something
cuz these people are really boring, lad.
This is why I don't come on here much
anymore. Have you noticed I'm not really
on here much because it's just boring,
lad? It's just pathetic losers
that try to talk about other people.
Like, what the [ __ ] Losers try to call
other people losers. How does that even make sense?
Mad. Anyways, join the thing, bro. So,
like, if you want me to stay on longer,
just join because I can't be bothered
with this [ __ ] anymore, bro. I really can't.
Have you noticed now a lot of people are leaving? Monty Mark
him don't really come on here much
because it's just the same old [ __ ]
People are bored of it. It's just
pathetic and boring, bro.
That's why people don't really like
entertain it much anymore.
Yeah. No, not Fridays. It used to be Thursdays.
And it wasn't January anyways.
But yeah, then I just Yeah, I don't
drink much anymore
cuz of the dating game and that. It's
just It's just pathetic.
It's just a dating game. It's boring,
lad. It's just the same [ __ ] I used to
go out drinking to try to meet people,
but you know what happens. Hello.
>> Yo, lad.
Can you hear me?
>> Yeah, man.
>> You can hear me? Yeah.
>> Yeah. Yeah.
>> Yeah. Yeah. You You've gone quiet. My
phone's [ __ ] but I can hear you a little bit.
>> Yeah. [ __ ] I'm bad me, lad.
>> Yeah. These people on YouTube, is it?
>> No, it's the same [ __ ] is it?
>> What makes me laugh is how they can try
to call other people losers when they're losers themselves.
>> Yeah, but that's why these people like
you, cuz you react to them. They need to be
>> No, it's not reacting. It's giving, you
know, it's stating facts. That's not
reacting. That's an opinion.
>> Yeah. Okay.
>> Cuz they are literally No. No. They are
life's losers, bro. Why do you think
when that guy just said about Red Star
getting my sublet money stopped? I
didn't react because it's [ __ ] I'm
not reacting to these people. I'm I'm
just stating facts, bro. Is it like how
can these people try to judge anyone?
>> Yeah. You've been doing this a long time now.
>> I went on I went on I went on L J. Yeah.
One second, bro. I went on LA J's and
this guy was like, "Oh, you need to stop
giving him attention. He's a he's a
loser." And I'm thinking, "These people
calling me a loser." Really? These
people? Come on now.
>> The mental I don't hear the
>> It is mad. It's just It is mad. They are
really disabled, bro. Why do you think I
don't come on here much anymore?
>> You're always on, Peter.
>> I was on once yesterday. The whole day.
I didn't even look I didn't even look at
it yesterday until I come back.
>> What you need to do, you need to starve
these people of ox of um attention.
>> Yeah, bro. No, I am. I'm just saying. I
just don't understand how Mongs can try
to call you a loser. But yeah, doesn't matter. Anyways,
>> um that Autumn Rose has been going in on
you as well, lad.
>> Yeah, she's [ __ ] just some fat. She's
just irrelevant. All of these people are irrelevant, lad.
>> Yeah. Yeah,
>> they're just irrelevant ass people that
ain't got a life. Simple as that, isn't it?
>> Yeah. Living that to Elvin is not much
now. He's had enough.
>> Cuz it's boring. Why? Why do you think?
Because it's just boring. >> Yeah.
>> It's a copycat community, isn't it?
>> Just getting sick of it, isn't he? Just
a shame [ __ ]
>> Yeah, man. Every Yeah, they would do.
It's just Yeah.
>> Have you noticed how no one ever joins
Lord J's panels?
>> Oh, yeah. No one ever does ever. No one.
>> It's cuz they're [ __ ] all disabled. That's why.
>> Because say they can't they probably
can't even talk properly. Oh, and I said
to that Joe, bro, I said to that Joe,
yeah, I'm actually going to Nottingham
soon. Um, and that's more than halfway.
So, that's closer to him than it is to
me. I don't mind meeting halfway, bro.
I'm not going all that way cuz I know
what he's going to do.
>> But like I stated yesterday on the in
the chat, I said no one's meeting
anyone. You just need to let it go. No
one's not He's not meeting you and
you're not meeting him. Just a
>> Yeah, but I've actually got I've
actually tried to meet people on here
before though. So the meet's not going
to happen because of him. It's not going
to happen because of me.
>> If that really wanted to meet you, he'd
meet travel halfway. He said he needs to leave.
>> Yeah. Exactly. Yeah. Exactly. There you
go. So he needs to stop he needs to stop
saying about people are doing nothing.
He needs to stop the big man talk
>> cuz I'm not doing lyric now with that
joy. He'll never meet you. Then just move
>> and he needs and he needs to stop
putting fake. He needs to stop only
showing the wins as well.
>> Yeah, I agree with you. I'm going to catch you.
>> Why do you think no one lo you know when
I lost money the other day? Have you
noticed that not many people laughed at it?
>> Lier said it was a fake video I seen.
>> Yeah. How could it be a fake video?
>> Did you see that? What he cooked?
>> Yeah, but how could it be a fake video?
>> I know. I thought like you can't just do
a voice over on a video.
>> What the [ __ ] And another thing is, and
no one hating on it because they know
it's the truth. You're not pulling out
thousands from a [ __ ] machine, bro. Them machines.
>> You don't beat them machines. I've told
you this day one. No.
>> I I know you don't. I know. I know you don't, bro. >> Yeah.
>> You get 40 pound up and then you do you
get 40 pound up then you just lose.
>> Yeah. The lovely Gravesy, the really
nice um really [ __ ] nice fam. What
you saying? Sorry. Yeah. I said, "Yeah,
you win like 3040 and then you just
lose, don't you?" So,
>> well, you do get up on them a bit like
you do, but um
>> Yeah, like £40.
>> Not necessarily. It's just walking, >> huh? >> It's
>> I can't hear you properly. Say again.
>> It's not.
>> Yeah, true.
>> Get in there. Triple H cheeseburger lad.
Can you hear me?
>> He called you a cheeseburger, lad.
>> Yeah. Just as odd all I've got in it.
>> Yeah. Until they get in.
>> I don't mind.
>> Saying you think it's weird they don't
go for these non for nons.
>> That fruit king. Get in, lad.
>> So you wait. You think it's weird that
they don't go for that nonslegs then?
>> That fruit king's all right, actually.
Yeah, it is weird. The [ __ ] I don't
know. I'm not sure gets a pass to be
honest with you like but
>> and even and even if and even if I come
off of it there's only there'd only be
like two people that go for him
>> and that pat must he got away with
murder on here as well that [ __ ]
>> and and also another thing is look at
that Mark Samson thing bro how long did
it take for people to start calling him
out on what he is
>> who's that sorry
>> you remember that Mark Samson yeah when
I went to his area like 3 years ago
>> oh yeah yeah
>> yeah it took them three years to start
having a problem with him.
>> You know,
>> even though Even though he didn't show
up two times when he went to his area,
they started having a problem with him
when they had a problem with him. So,
they're not But you understand what I mean?
>> Yeah. Yeah.
>> So, he got away with doing this fake
calling out like 30 times before anyone
said anything. They're all idiots on here. They
>> are like smash videos where you from
like lad. Um they are just [ __ ] That's it.
They're just losers. They're like losers, lad.
>> And they're biased as well.
>> Course they are. It's when it suits these people
>> about it's it's ridic it's ridiculous me
calling non legs a virgin. Well, it's
more ridiculous him calling me a virgin, but okay.
>> They would never say that, is it?
They're idiots, bro. They're [ __ ]
They're just They're just spazzers.
That's what they are. Spazzers.
>> The reason the door in it.
>> The reason they don't go for Sean and go
for you is cuz they hate you more than
Sean. You do know that, don't you?
>> But [snorts] why would they hate me more than him?
>> Because what you said on this YouTube and things.
>> Yeah, but he's an Yeah, but he's an actual nons.
>> Not necessarily. You can't really say
stuff like that. There's no evidence on
>> Well, there is. He said that he would
get with a 15y old. So, I mean, there is evidence.
>> Well, I've not seen out like that. The
only way you can really he literally
said that he would get with a 15y old.
>> Well, I've never heard that. But all
I've got to say is you can't really
shout stuff like that. Ru and obviously
when you done that post
>> and another thing is when he used to
justify oh he'd get with a 16y old he'd
get with Do you remember when he you
never heard him admit that he'd get with
a 16y old?
>> No. No.
>> Yeah. Well, he used to admit that and he
used to try to justify it. Now, why
would somebody want to get with a 16y
old even though it's legal? Why would
they? Unless they were announce
realistically. Come on.
>> That's true, lad. Yeah.
>> Think about it. He would try to justify
in every way. Like me, would I would I
[ __ ] 18year-old if if she was like a
10 out of 10 and she put it on a plate.
Yeah, I would. Definitely. I would. I
think I would. But not a 16y old.
>> Hell no. Not a 16y old. No
[clears throat] way.
>> It's like Brew Kings just said there.
It's because you talk. You have talked
some about kids and that a lot. You know
that you have been sick.
>> Oh. Yeah. You know why I spoke about
LJ's kids, didn't you? It was because of
Timmy. I wanted to prove a point. You do realize that?
>> Yeah, but you shouldn't talk about kids,
>> you know. And that was to fend with
Timmy. You know,
>> Silver S, who the [ __ ] is
>> Okay. Okay. So, why did Okay. Okay. Let
me ask you this then, Fruit King, and
all you other people that are watching
this, why did none of you people ever go
for Pat Mustard? That's a good question
then, is it?
>> I told you why they didn't. Because they
were scared in case
them. That was what it was. Ros [ __ ]
scared of him. He's a [ __ ] nonsap
mustard. He's a wronger. What he said
about um Monty's kids was a disgrace as
well. And these people still defended
him for that.
>> You know what I'm saying? Yeah.
>> Then he got docked and he's nowhere to
be seen. He's [ __ ]
>> I don't I I think though No, no, no. But
I don't think that I think that if say
for example LJ woke up tomorrow Yeah.
and he started saying worse things and
done worse things than I did. I I think
they'd all let it pass though. I don't I
don't know about you.
>> No, probably not. Like I don't think they would.
>> I think a lot of them would.
>> Yeah, but yeah. Okay, I get that. Okay,
I get that then. Okay, Triple H. But
what I don't understand is Yeah. Say
that you say stuff about kids. Why would
you waste your life all your life hating
on someone that you don't know, wasting
your own life every day because of it?
That that doesn't make sense.
>> No, I agree. That doesn't make sense.
>> That doesn't make sense.
>> They're actually their life by hating
you every day if you think about it. [snorts]
>> So, I don't know, bro. It's just weird.
All of it's weird,
>> but they're weird.
>> Yeah, the sad people on here.
>> Um, I defend slug as well. Um, >> what
>> are you doing a football bet tomorrow?
>> I will be. Yeah. Yeah. >> Yeah.
>> I'm [ __ ] I need to go pharmacy. Me,
man. I need to get some gear for me for
this [ __ ] flu. I need some flu
tablets. I need one of them. It's normal
to It's normal to be ill in January, bro.
>> You have to wipe me out this way,
>> bro. You know, last January, bro. Yeah.
Even the other day, I woke up with a
[ __ ] bad ear ache, bro. You ever had
a ear ache? Oh,
>> no. I've never ever suffered with
earachche, to be honest. Like,
>> no, I just woke up with it and and it
feels like it's going to pop. It was
[ __ ] stinking, bro. >> Yeah.
>> Yeah. I had that tooth removed
yesterday, in it.
>> How did that go to act? Not really.
>> And I had the num all in your front mouth. >> Huh?
>> Did the numb all your mouth?
>> Yeah. And the only needle I felt was the second one.
>> Yeah. It's not too bad, lad. Is it?
>> No. It's not too bad, bro. It's not too
bad. But it hurt after though.
>> It does. Yes. Yeah. I couldn't park
after me. Like me [ __ ] mouth was out
killing me after when I got mine took out.
>> But I still don't think that, bro. I
don't think that pain was worse than the
foot pain I had, though. Nah, that's the
worst pain I ever had. The foot pain,
bro. I I even think even still and and
mouth pain is the worst pain. I think it isn't it
>> the what is sorry
>> mouth pain is the worst pain
>> yeah it's got yeah all day long I
>> but I don't think it was as bad as when
I had that foot thing when I was
limping. I don't think it was as bad as
that. That that foot thing was bad. Bro,
>> if you were to choose what you had to
have, what would it be? Would you rather
have toothache or earache? I'd rather
have [ __ ] ear ache. Me like
>> obviously an earachche. Yeah.
>> Yeah. Cuz I've had tooth fake once in my
life on that when I got me back to I got [ __ ] killed.
>> It really brought me to tears. It was
that [ __ ] painful I couldn't see.
>> It almost brought you to tears. [laughter]
>> The thing that almost brought me to
tears was that foot ache, bro. And I've
had a lot of aches, but that foot ache
was that foot thing was about was the worst.
>> Yeah. Yeah.
>> Her tentonitis it was called.
I seen that Lie upload a video about you
and your mom going to the dentist as well.
>> Yeah. Sad, isn't it? It's
>> mad, isn't it?
>> Why is that Rose on your back as well now? >> Huh?
>> Why is that Arton Rose on your back?
>> I don't know, bro. The only attention
she can get from is from people in this
community. That's how sad they are. Have
you seen that V how he acts around
there? You can tell that V is that he's
definitely a virgin. You know,
>> I don't mind that V. I think he's what
he to be honest like
>> cuz if and if they had a life they
wouldn't care about some random woman a
bit like you don't care about her
>> on YouTube that's how you know they got
no life as well
>> what silver surf said there that's true
yeah you wish rape and that and kids and
cancer that's rotten as well Peter
>> yeah and you people spoke about dead
people's relatives multiple times as well
nonslegs come on nonslegs come on my
panel bro uh when was it I think two
weeks ago and he was talking about dead relatives
So he was talking about red dead
relatives for no reason.
>> So yeah,
>> never going to end. There's only one way
it's going to end is when you're dead.
Like this future community is [ __ ] mental, lad.
>> Yeah, it's mad. And it shows how how
much their life sucks as well. Because
if they want people dead over stuff
they've said years ago that if they had
a life, they wouldn't care about any of
this. You understand?
>> Yeah. Exactly. I I wouldn't care about
hating people for what they've said
years ago. They could not like someone
like how hard can it be? I don't think
he likes me, but he doesn't ever talk about me.
>> He's all right in that how hard actually. >> Yeah,
>> he's done you a
>> So, if you don't like someone, can't you
just move on and just just not talk about them?
>> Yeah, but they've got nowhere else to do
on any of these people.
>> That's what I'm saying. That's that's
exactly what that's my point. >> Yeah.
>> So, yeah, man. When are you on the drink again?
>> I'm going out for dinner about 12 today,
man. I'm going have a I'm don't know
whether I have a pint or not. I'm a bit
rough. I'm bit [ __ ] What food is it?
>> Probably spoon. I think I'm going mate.
>> Weather spoons.
>> So spoon. Yeah.
>> What? Fish and chips.
>> Nah, probably a wrap or something or um
or maybe a nice do pie chips and gravy
from there as well.
>> Did you Did you like the look of the
Indian the other day I had?
>> Yeah, it did look nice. How much was that?
>> Uh, a lot, bro. A lot in it.
>> I just don't understand why you pay 50 B
60 quid for you get Well, I'll be here,
man. You get a [ __ ] You'll be They'll
do a special for you as well down there,
man. Like, you get
>> cuz it's too nice. But it filled me up
for a day and a half.
>> Why don't you get tea masala? [clears throat]
>> Nah, that's what Nlex has as well.
>> I'm not big. I'm like a [ __ ] space
lover. Me, lad.
>> My belly just rumbled. Now we're talking
about that again, bro.
>> Could you eat another Indian now, mate? >> Huh?
>> Could you eat another Indian now?
>> Say again.
>> Could you eat an Indian now?
>> Who you? >> You?
>> Probably, bro. Probably.
>> I love Indian food, bro. I just love Indian food.
>> And it filled me up for a day and a half
cuz that was the day before the dentist
in it. And I got hungry after about
1:00. So it filled me up for a long time. >> Yeah,
>> it does fill you up. Like I said,
whenever you eat in, it seems to fill
you up for much longer for some reason.
>> I think it's cuz it's less watery, isn't
it? I'm guessing.
>> Just a second, Peter.
>> Okay, Captain.
>> Just brushing me teeth, lad.
>> What did you think of the chicken ticker
when it come out sizzling greasy?
[snorts] Oh, lush. Isn't it?
>> Yeah. Look,
>> and um yeah, I think it feel longer
because it's not as watery, I'm guessing.
>> When you take it away, it's so watery, isn't it?
I had a savone chips yesterday and ribs,
so I don't know what I'm going to have
today. Oh, I had a singer burger
yesterday as well. Grievy from KFC.
>> You had what, Pete?
>> I had a singer burger from KFC. But that
always gives you the [ __ ] isn't it? Or me.
>> KFC my way. [ __ ] [ __ ]
>> Yeah. It's either good or Yeah. There's
good ones and bad ones, isn't it? It's
not like McDonald's where it's all the
same, is it? It's either good or bad. Yeah.
>> I might have a mack tonight. I tell you,
>> say again.
>> Might have a Macky's for tonight, lad.
>> Oh, bless. Well, like just some nuggets.
>> Nah, probably one of them big arches, mate.
>> I might have a McDonald's to be fair.
>> Yeah, it's better than gambling, Pete.
>> Yeah, bro. I I was I've got an account
online. Yeah. I was so tempted to play
some online roulette, but I'm not going
to do it. It's It's addicting, is it?
>> Not addicting. I probably
>> I spent 50 yesterday in the arcade. So,
>> you've done what? Sorry.
>> I spent 50 pound in the arcade. I should
show I should go to the I should go to
the arcade greasy and show you it. You'd
love it. Like the penny pushes and the
grabbing machine. I spent £50 yesterday.
£50 on my P like on like just the
>> like grabbing machines and you know
collecting tickets. Like I can't explain
it. You know where it's like an it's
like an arcade
>> for kids. It's an arcade but you
understand what I mean?
>> Yeah. Loads of teddies and [ __ ] like
that. [clears throat]
>> Yeah. But and there and there's tickets
you can win and [ __ ] and like you can
win prizes. It's addicting as [ __ ] bro.
>> What did you get? Your ticket wins.
>> Um I didn't me and my sisters got about
2,000. We haven't changed them up yet
because we were uh rush for time. So, we
have to go back. And there's like a
Scooby-Doo thing. Yeah. You pull the
barrel and it has to land. Um it has And
it lands and it's how many tickets you
get is what it lands on. You get me?
>> Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
>> Yeah. It's fun, bro. It's addicting
though. It is addicting. You
>> play them pushes.
>> I didn't have a go at the pushes though. No, >> no,
>> it was just the grabbing machines and
the barrels and and and [ __ ]
>> Didn't you win Stitch?
>> Yeah, I won Stitch yesterday as well. I
was trying to win [ __ ] Crash
Bandicoot. I couldn't win the [ __ ] I
put 20 through it. Yeah. You can't you
can't win it, man.
>> Now the scam them claw mach.
>> The thing is with Crash, it's like if
it's a soft toy. Yeah. And you can get a
good grip on it, you can you can get it.
Like I've won Tiger and I won Stitch
because it's soft and you can grab it.
But with stuff like um Crash Bandicoot,
you can't because it's unless he lands
on his back, you got no chance. You know
what I mean?
>> Yeah. Yeah, man.
>> Did you used to play them?
>> Well, take the bed up [ __ ] early. Yeah.
>> Yeah. Bowling bowling. I'd love to go
bowling on a date, bro.
>> Yeah. You done a bit of bowling with
your mom, didn't you?
with my mom and my sister.
>> Did she enjoy?
>> Huh? Yeah.
>> It's expensive though, you know.
>> Is it? >> Yeah.
>> I [ __ ] two bar or something. Well,
this is where I am.
>> Nah, it's expensive, bro. It's
expensive. But it's fun. It's fun.
>> I don't think I could be dealing with it
though on like a Friday, Saturday. It
would just be Rammo, isn't it?
>> Yeah. Be chut lad. and it would just
ruin it, I think. But if you're bowling,
then it's too busy. I don't enjoy it
when it's too busy, you know?
>> Yeah. Yeah.
>> Well, obviously yesterday's Thursday and
it's January. It wasn't as bad. It was
all right, you know.
>> Yeah. Yeah. Did you end up going out for
any dinner yesterday then after the the
I know you want to be read, did you
after your [ __ ]
>> No. What did I have? No, I had a Sablo
chips and ribs.
>> Where? From the chip shop.
>> Yeah. The Chinese. Oh yeah.
>> Yeah, bro. It was nice.
>> Yeah. Yeah.
>> So you So you reckon if I come off
YouTube for 6 months, they'll start
going for nons legs?
>> They'll get up. Give up in the end.
Yeah. Well, in the end cuz you're not
retaliating. You're not back on you.
We'll have to move on eventually to someone else.
>> Yeah. What if she Mark will be back?
>> No. They've got him off.
>> And money in it.
>> I tell you what's tough, right? These
people the [ __ ] people are saying the
community is dead and that but it's
going to be dead. They've got seaside
off. Tim Eldridge is now off. Monty's
>> It's dead. It's dead because of them and
they're repeated. They've got themselves
to blame in it.
>> And then the wins when there's no content.
>> Yeah. Well, if they stop repeating
themselves, right, these people say
they're not disabled. Yeah. So, if
they're not disabled, just do and say
different things and then it will be a
good community, isn't it?
>> Needs to get It used to be good when
Brown Source and the government that
were on before, man. Yeah,
>> good and all. That was when it was at
the peak at the peak this YouTube like. >> Yeah,
>> I bless you then. You're You're too deep
in this YouTube. You are.
>> No, I can get off anytime. Me, lad. Anytime.
>> You know, it's madness, bro, isn't it?
So you So do you So do you think this Jo
is a fraud now then?
>> I think he's I don't know. I don't think
he's a fraud. I think he's just [ __ ]
like he just shows you what he wants to
show you. You know what I mean? He shows his
>> Yeah, pretty much. >> Yeah.
>> Yeah. I've not tried that 100 to one
roulette. Well, I have tried it years
ago. Years ago, but that's got to be
harder to win. That's got to [ __ ]
surely be harder. If I play roulette
again, I'm just going to play it online,
bro. Not that I will, but I'm not. [ __ ]
that roulette. And it in the bookies.
>> Online's worse, I think.
>> Yeah, it is. It is. It is. But it's
hard, isn't it? They're both They're
both bad in different reasons, isn't it?
>> For different reasons.
>> But would you say you got more chance
winning online? Yeah,
>> there's worse round if you go to the
bench shop. I know. Under 200 quid in
your pocket and then just don't take
your bank card and then when it's gone,
it's gone. But online, you can just
deposit, deposit, deposit. It's dangerous.
>> Yeah, but I think you got more chance of
winning online though, is it?
>> Yeah, I'd say so to be fair. Like
>> it's just hard. Yeah, but obviously it's
easy to just lose all your money. I get
what you mean. Yeah,
>> you're having them you haven't got that
green bar because of these online.
>> Yeah, that green bar is just um and it's
not even that is what annoys me is like
we said before. It'll give you a win and
then you'll lose the win trying to get
the next spin and it knows. It knows,
bro. It knows, you know,
>> like and another thing it does, let me
tell you another thing. Yeah. Say, so my
numbers are 1720. Yeah. >> Yeah.
>> On the second dozen. So say I hit it
right and I get 4050 pound up. So I put
50 in and say I get to 92 pound it will
miss miss miss miss miss miss miss miss
miss miss miss miss miss miss and even
if I do get a spin it will constantly
keep going next door to the jackpot numbers
>> cost it is or it's 10 to one it's 10 or 20.
>> No no no even the norm even like the the
normal one with the three zeros like
even even like the normal one with the bar.
>> Oh yeah. Yeah.
>> You get what I mean? So it will
constantly go next, next, next, and then
you'll hit 20 again when you're on your
last spin. Like when you're on your last
spin, you will hit again. What's a coincidence?
>> Yeah, exactly, lad. Yeah, I've seen you
do that, actually. Yeah, it's [ __ ] isn't it?
>> When you get a good win, it takes it all
back off your head.
>> Yeah, it's annoying, isn't it, bro? I
was just going to Yeah. Can't even
[ __ ] win on them nowadays, man. might
have a I might have a score in the
blueprint maybe in the bone in a bit.
>> What the roulette?
>> No, I don't play that. I play that um
sevens Ben or something it's called um
[ __ ] what's the name of it? Sevens.
>> Yeah. Record it in it.
>> Oh yeah, I might. I might do actually,
mate. Yeah, I could do. Yeah. Yeah.
>> Show us some content.
>> Yeah. I might upload, lad.
>> Show how it's done in it.
I one way I lose. But you're the only
man who wins.
>> Yeah. He wins every time, is it?
>> How? It's just not sustainable though,
is it? Come on.
>> No, it's bollocks.
>> It's [ __ ]
>> Like if it was online, you could kind of
believe it or like a you know a real
life casino, you could kind of believe
it, you know.
>> Yeah. He just Yeah, that's he just
especially on that 100 to one. He's wins
all armor now as well. It's like, how
the [ __ ] you even won that 100? >> Yeah,
that that bar roulette is a scam, isn't it? [snorts]
>> Yeah, it's terrible that
>> But I'm trying to not get into like deep
into gambling again, bro. I already 150
the other day, you know.
>> Yeah. Yeah.
>> I don't want to get deep into it again.
>> I You had a [ __ ] When did you last
go? Yeah. You had 100 quid the other
day, didn't you? Huh?
You lost 150 yesterday, didn't you?
>> Yeah. And then 200 two weeks ago, so
it's not too bad. You know what I mean?
Could be worse. No good at all. >> Huh?
>> It's [ __ ] no good that gambling, man.
>> I know it's not. I'll probably do it
again probably next month.
>> Cuz if you're just doing it every week
all the time, you're just wasting money.
You know what I'm saying? >> Yeah.
>> Whereas if you done it every month, 150
or even 200, like it's not really as
bad. You know what I'm saying?
just have like 100 quid a month or
something in it. I don't
>> 150 max, isn't it? 150 max.
>> Yeah. Yeah.
>> What about what if I put £500 on the
roulette right now? Do you reckon I win?
>> No, you lose.
>> Yeah. What? Online? >> Yep.
>> What? Do 100 pound spins?
>> Why don't you just give send you a 500
quid win for you?
>> Yeah, right, bro. Yeah, right. >> [snorts]
>> online. You have to pay the There's fees
like depositing fees, isn't it?
>> Say that again.
>> There's depositing fees online now, isn't it?
>> What do you mean?
>> So, when I deposited £200 on the spin
dog, it never told me they took £217 out
of my account. [laughter]
>> What? So, they charge you a deposit now? >> Yeah.
>> What? Remember that [ __ ]
>> They used to charge you to withdraw, but
it was only something silly. So, say you
withdrew 1,500. Yeah. It would take like
20 or 30 pound which isn't too bad
obviously if you're winning in it but
they shouldn't charge you to deposit. Do
you get me?
>> That's mental. How the [ __ ] you Why
would you even bet with someone like that?
>> I don't that's what I didn't I didn't
realize and I haven't been back since.
There's another site I found but they'll
probably take a fee as well because it's
it's all IBAN. You know the ones that
are not on GameStop you have to enter
your bank IBAN so they pay you to get it.
>> Yeah, I know what you mean. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Like
>> so once you give the eyeband they they
send the money to you.
>> [ __ ] mental it.
>> Yeah. Obviously with bookies there is no
fees is there? No. So
>> no as a [ __ ] >> Yeah.
>> Yeah. Do the only thing I used to like
about like the bookies the cinos you get
your money there and then is it?
>> Yeah. But even online that was instant
mostly in online now.
Do you understand?
>> What's silver surf?
>> You're very obsessed, Silver Surf.
You're another one that's also been
doing this for years. >> Yeah.
>> This guy is another one that's been
doing it for years. I don't know why
you're so concerned about me, bro, when
you don't know me. Like, I'm not even
being rude or argumentative. You get me?
>> To be honest, I've never seen the silver.
>> No, he's been doing it for years.
>> You not seen him? He's been doing it for years.
>> Haven't seen him now. Bro,
>> no. Years, years, years, years.
>> Yeah, he has been doing it for years,
bro. To be fair, most of them have, to be honest. >> Yeah.
>> You should go to Nottingham for a piss up.
>> You think they get sick of it, wouldn't you?
>> You would have thought they'd get Yeah.
Yeah. Every day as well. You would have
thought they'd get It's not like they
done it over CO and then I spoke to you
over CO. Do you remember?
>> Yeah. Yeah.
>> So, I could understand it over co, you
know, nothing was open. People was going
mentally insane. And then the first
thing, you remember, do you remember
when we spoke on the phone and the first
thing that opened was KFC? Do you remember?
>> Oh, yeah. Yeah.
>> It was KFC and then it was other things.
And it's like, okay, then we could
understand it. But it there's not co
anymore. So, why are they still doing it?
>> That's it. It's over now, is it? But I
think they just got t too deep in over
that co and they can't get off there now. Maybe
>> maybe maybe. Yeah,
>> that's all I can think, man.
>> I I like gambling. I like his gambling
videos, Timmy, bro.
>> Yeah, he plays like barrel 25 on the
shape, man. I like his roulette videos, mate.
>> At least he shows losses, isn't it?
>> Yeah, he does to be fair. But yeah, he does.
>> I thought I was going to get a lot of
hate, you know, losing like when I lost
on the roulette, but no one really said anything. >> Yeah.
No, people know what the them is about
>> and they know that Joe's full of [ __ ] as well.
>> Yeah, I thought when I got to 140 I
thought, "Oh yeah, my lux in it." But nah,
Triple H, you weren't having it for
toffee in it.
>> No, just lose after lose on them in it. [laughter]
Left side of the zero. That's what it's
doing for me as well.
Yeah. Death side of zero and [ __ ] 10
to one isn't it? >> Yeah.
>> So when did you used to like the global draw roulette?
>> Yeah, I used that mate. Yeah.
>> Are you still obsessed with me poo?
>> I don't know how you people live to be
obsessed over people you don't know
every day. But that's one thing I'll
never I'll never understand. That's your lives.
>> Why do these people do this? >> Huh?
I don't know why these people are
continuously doing this.
>> They've got a lot of time on their
hands. Is it too much, haven't they?
[snorts and laughter]
>> Do you remember? Do you remember when
someone asked Monty? Yeah. Who's caused
all of this? And then do you remember
Monty said Pat mustard?
>> Yeah. Yeah.
>> Well, you remember it?
>> That must have attacked him from day
one, didn't he?
>> Yep. He's the cause of a lot of it. >> Yeah. mate.
>> What did you say?
>> I' got that co me. I'm [ __ ] here.
>> Yeah, you might have co man.
>> Oh, yeah.
>> You might have co Oh, have you ever Have
you ever lost Have you ever lost your taste buds?
>> Yeah, I have no like now.
>> That's the worst thing. The worst thing
is when you lose your It's so [ __ ]
annoying, bro. Is it? I can't taste smell me.
>> I lost my taste buds during co uh and
also I lost my two
bro I lost my taste buds um years ago as
well. Horrible isn't it?
>> This co's getting rife again is it?
>> Bless you then. Bless you >> belly.
Bless you. Triple, you want a Guinness today, lad?
>> I don't know. I don't know if I'm
drinking at the minute or not like I'm
sweating and nothing. >> I'm try
a bath. Have you got a bath?
>> Have I got a bath? Yeah, I've been in
the bath last night, mate. I'm going to have
>> Yeah, I was just going to say try having
a really hot bath in it. Steaming it out.
>> Yeah. Yeah,
>> that's all you really can do. Maybe have
like a hot curry or something should
help you, bro.
Have a hot curry and a shot in it like
what I had. It'll be better in no time, lad.
>> Yeah, I seen that strong comment on your
um about your Sam Ba shot. John
commented on it and he said he'd never
had a shot of summit.
>> How does that make sense?
>> I thought
he's a [ __ ] idiot, mate. [snorts]
>> Yeah. Where's Where's Fiona McDonald?
I like that little account Fiona M.
>> Let that voice of reason up. He's all
right then, Peter.
>> Nah, he's a projector, bro. He's a
self-reflector. He's not coming on my
channel. Little self-reflector.
No, these little self-reflectors don't
come on my channel. It's like what Monty
man used to say, ain't it?
>> Yeah, but just give them one chance.
>> All they're doing, all they're doing is
just self projecting. So there's no
point letting people like that up on the panel. >> Reason,
>> he's a [ __ ] [ __ ] That's what he is.
Yeah, you ain't coming up. See you
later. [clears throat] No self-reflectors.
I like people that can actually have
normal conversations, you know.
>> What do you like? I want a reason. Yeah.
What's that voice?
>> What is he like?
>> He's a [ __ ] [ __ ]
>> He's a virgin as well. Have you seen him
hanging around autumn?
>> Yeah, these people are sad, bro. Really,
really sad. They're not even worth
talking about, bro. To be fair,
>> I think that V's quite funny. me.
>> Yeah, he takes the piss out of me, but
it's trolling. It's harmless trolling.
>> Yeah, that's fine. It's just harmless
trolling that is. So what? [laughter]
>> He also takes the piss out of other
people as well.
>> Yeah, I'm bad. I'm having a bad
>> You know what it is, JD? It's because Do
you know what it is, JD? Yeah. Let me
It's just what I was saying to R. It's
because they've got no life outside of
YouTube and they're too fat, ugly, and
skint to go out and and meet a woman in
like a pub or a bar. That's why there's
so many white knights and simps on here, lad.
>> He was talking about this earlier.
>> What's the what's the other stuff I pour in
>> because they because they don't have a
social got no life and they're only on
here. You see, that's why me. I don't
give a [ __ ] about any woman on this community.
>> The other thing is crazy.
>> Never have, never will. It's because
they got no life outside of it, you
know? No. Um, and they're too ugly to
pull anyone in real life or like get a
number. By pull I mean like get a number and >> Sorry. [snorts]
>> Does your head ever hurt? Like just
going like knowing your life for six
hours the other day. Does your head ever
hurt? My head's busting and I've only
been on an hour.
>> Yeah. Reading these people's comments.
>> [ __ ] know these people do it every
[ __ ] minute of the day.
>> No. My my head hurts when I go on LJ's
uh panel or even go on the chat. That's
why I don't go on it.
>> That lav block me lad. So I [ __ ]
don't even entertain this.
>> Yeah, you get brain damage going on that
bro. You get brain damage going on that
>> be my bath. I've got in as well. Greath. [snorts]
>> So yeah JD, what I meant by Paul, I
don't mean literally like meet someone
and have sex. I mean just like talking
and getting numbers and talking. You understand?
But then these are the same people JD
that will sit here and call you losers.
This is also what we was talking about.
They like to self project their life
onto others. It's weird. But anyways, yeah.
>> You know what? I've not had for ages.
Yeah. I've not had a kebab for ages.
>> I got a um I ordered a big I got a 12in
pepperoni pizza extra cheese yesterday
from um to watch a Liverpool match with.
I could only eat two pizzas. cuz I think
>> yeah Chinese me
>> Chinese is nice. Yeah,
>> but it's pointless getting all that [ __ ]
as I can't taste her out at the minute. So
>> yeah, exactly. Exactly. Exactly. That's
what that same problem with me when I
lost my taste buds. You might as well
just be eating the cheapest thing cuz
you can't taste anything anyway, isn't it?
>> Exactly. Yeah.
>> No, I tell you. No, no, I tell you the
wor No, I tell you maybe the worst pain
I ever had. You ever had that? Um, you
ever had that strep throat?
>> The what? Sorry.
>> Have you ever had that uh strep throat?
>> No. No.
>> Where you swallow and it feels like
you're swallowing knives.
>> Oh, like razor blade for what they have. Yeah.
>> I literally when I had that Yeah. I
could only eat a [ __ ] chili conani
and it took me like 40 minutes to eat
it. I couldn't even swallow properly.
>> That was I think that's got to be the
worst to be fair.
>> It keeps coming back up, doesn't it? I
was I just drank like hot drinks and
that me like
>> Yeah. I've only had it once. It was in
February as well. I remember it. It was
one February. I'll never forget, bro.
>> Oh, it's bad.
>> Yeah. Yeah.
>> Yeah. That's bad, lad.
>> So, how you doing out of deer then?
>> Probably not, bro. I just probably go
get some food in a bit and just chill.
>> What you going to have for food?
>> I'm not sure.
>> I'm going to try and get a a pint down
me, I think. I'd see how I get on.
>> God bless you then. If you want a little pint, then
>> have a little pint and I'm just going to get some
>> You just
>> One second, bro. Yeah, I was I was I was
at I was in I was near Pepe's um yesterday.
>> Go and have it. I don't know what I
want. I don't know. Maybe fish and
chips. I like fish and chips in it. Why
don't you go to Mack?
>> Because it comes cold in it.
>> Not Not all the time.
>> Most of the time though.
>> Where are you from? Like Smash videos, lad.
>> I don't know. I'm getting I'd like a
savoy with fish and chips, but obviously
the savo is [ __ ] chicken cuz it's
allowing it. So yeah.
>> You wouldn't know that because uh the
area that you live, but yeah. Forn
is he from far away that
>> How did I know that on T lad?
>> Yeah, mate. What?
>> How did I know that lad? >> Nah,
>> you have.
>> Oh, do you remember that place? Um, Spennymore.
>> Hi. Hi.
>> Oh, that sounds funny. Imagine imagine
saying I'm from Spennymore.
that voice of reasons when you're back.
He wants in.
>> Yeah, he's not coming in. He's a little
keyboard while he's irrelevant. He's not coming in.
>> Just let anyone normal actually wants to
come in and have a conversation. Uh, you can
>> just let the voice of reason in for five minutes, mate. >> Nah,
he's a keyboard warrior, bro. I'm not
letting him in.
>> He might have some new crack.
>> Yeah, really.
I tell you what, put your camera on and
show your face and I'll let you in. How's that?
>> Is that a good deal?
You put put your put your camera on and
show us your face and I'll let you in.
That's as good as I can be. Greavesy,
I'm sorry. That's the best I can offer.
[clears throat] Hey,
>> that voice a good fell.
All right. What did What did Greavesy
say? This community is
>> enough to kill a lad.
>> What [clears throat] did he say? Do you don't remember?
>> [ __ ] hell.
>> You don't remember? >> No.
>> You said that it's a copycat community.
Copycat community. [snorts] >> Huh?
>> Just reasoning for five reason. All
right. My lad.
>> That Smash videos. I can tell you who
that Smash videos is. I I want you to
guess who that Smash videos is. I can
tell you exactly who it is. It's too obvious. >> Dad. >> Huh? >> Cory. >> Nope. >> Um,
>> I know exactly who it is. It's too
obvious. See, these people Yeah. when
they try to troll behind these fake
accounts, they make it too obvious. It's them. >> Who?
>> It's uh It's that Ponty.
Oh, 21. Yeah,
>> the in that Indigo account, it's too
obvious. You know what I mean? [laughter]
>> You can actually tell that it's them.
That's how that's how mad it is. It's
just like Terry, you know, when Terry
comes in on a fake account, you you can
you know it's him. It's too obvious.
Just like that Kieran. I know whenever
it's someone behind them accounts, it's too obvious.
>> They've got that many accounts. That's
why. What about Fiona McDonald? >> Yeah,
>> that's pathetic, isn't it? Fiona McDonald.
>> Well, it's not pathetic cuz you'll find
it funny and you laugh at it or [laughter]
>> I don't cuz I like the name Fiona. Is it?
>> Why would you like the name Fiona?
>> I just think it's a cute little name. >> Yeah.
>> Yeah. Yeah. Do you know Gre I I said I
wanted some digestive biscuits and
Greavvesy started calling me a copycat
because of that.
>> Cuz you want cuz you like digestive
biscuits isn't it?
>> Greg's a little troll behind the scenes
what she said there. Smash a lot has a
few accounts as well. >> Yeah.
>> To honestly
no I've actually only got one account
but you know Trip You don't even know
what Crash Bandicoot isn't it?
>> Yeah I used to play it years ago when I
was a kid. So
>> what animal is it then?
[ __ ] gas for me. [ __ ] no.
>> I think it's a [ __ ] fox in it. [ __ ] no.
>> It's the orange thing in it.
>> There was a Did you hear that account
went about insulin the window or
something? That was another account.
What? Did you ever see that account floating? >> No.
>> How much is that insulin the window?
That was an account.
>> No, I never saw it.
These people I don't know why these
people keep doing this.
>> Well, hopefully Red Star is not on
YouTube today. Hopefully
>> he is on YouTube. >> Really? >> Yeah.
>> You sure? >> Yeah.
>> Grezy, do you when I next go to the
arcade, do you want me to record it and
show you all the little machines and stuff?
>> Would you like that?
>> He needs to get laid. [laughter]
He needs to get lied. He does. Yeah.
>> He's going to die of virgin.
>> How come he's always at the station?
That's not like
>> cuz he's [ __ ] skin. That's why.
Yes, please, boss. That would be a lovely sight. >> Grievy.
Grievy, can you get me some digestive biscuits?
If these people have a life, why why
they got so many accounts? >> Yeah, you know,
>> I liked I liked I liked Monty's
Christmas live stream to be honest. I
thought that was class.
>> Hey D, it
>> was got the most accounts on it.
>> I've just got live Christmas just to see
who's come on in it.
Yeah, but he copied me though. Greavvesy
Monty copied me cuz I done that first. I
wanted to see who was on here Christmas.
He just copied me.
>> You know what? They would have just they
would have just been best off um
admitting that they was on YouTube
Christmas. You know that
they pretend they're not on it
Christmas, is it?
I agree with you. Do you remember when
all the little girls fancy Justin
Bieber? [snorts] Do you remember that? Triple H. >> No,
>> you don't. You don't remember that,
Grezy? In 2011, 2012, um, all the like
they were crazy over Justin Bieber.
Surely to god you remember that? >> No,
>> you don't. What? You don't remember that triple? >> No.
>> That was Justin Bieber's. Do you know
who he is? >> Yeah.
>> Yeah, that was a that was a thing back
in 2011 2012. What's your opinion on that, Greavvesy?
Yeah, that was a thing, bro. That was
that was Justin Bieber's peak 2011 2012.
>> Right, lad. I'm going to jump in bath
now. So, I'll um I might jump back on
the phone if you're on.
>> All right, lad. And if you have a go
later, make sure you record it. Yeah.
>> Yeah. All right. Right.
>> All right. Catch you later.
>> Bye-bye now. Tah. So, what was that all
about, Grievy, when they were all
obsessed with Justin Bieber?
What's your opinion on that?
Yeah, they were all obsessed with him.
Grezy, I'm sure you remember that, don't you?
What was the reason for that?
So what? To fit in? They done it with
Harry Styles as well. Do do you remember
Harry Styles? They done it with him, too.
So what you what what was it? Was it a copycat statement?
Yeah. All the girls used to copy each other.
Yeah, they Yeah, it was a trend.
Definitely. Definitely definitely a trend.
Yeah, they all they all shoot which is
ridiculous because think of it Grezy.
Yeah. If Harry Styles wasn't famous, no
one would have wanted him. Think about
it, bro. No, no one would even fancy him
if he wasn't if he wasn't famous. So, it
definitely is a trend.
Yeah. Well, I'm not sure how he's doing
that when he's dead, but Yeah.
But yeah, they um
definitely definitely definitely copy
him. Marsho Maro with the Harry Styles
one. Grezy with Justin Bieber. You can
kind of see it, you know. But not back
then. You just look like a normal like
just normal like a normal kid in it like
back then. And they had so many people
obsessed with them.
So what you're saying that they all
copied each other Greavvesy
and obviously for the boys it was the it
was the chevel car one they used to all
copy each other with that one there
loads of different trends going around
there was loads of different trends.
Yeah Beyonce they Beyonce Beyonce
Rihanna Justin Bieber Yeah.
weird isn't it?
They've even done it with YouTubers.
Greavvesy. They even done it with
YouTubers. Bro, do you want to hear a story?
Right. Do you want to hear a story?
I can tell you. This is definitely
definitely a trend. I've actually got a
story about this as well. Grievy, can I
tell you it?
And that I can tell you it's definitely
definitely to fit in.
Yeah, this one's definitely definitely
to fit in as well. Yeah. You want to
hear it, Grezy?
It's about a YouTuber. They do it with
YouTubers as well. Well, they used to
back then back in 2013, 2014. They all
used to copy each other. All the girls
and stuff, the teenage girls, they all
used to copy each other.
There was this guy on YouTube, right?
And nothing special about him. He looks
a bit weird and he's got a lisp and he
was doing like a meet and greet. So I
thought, you know what, let me go to the
area in London and see how many people
turn up just to see. Bro, the whole
place was rammed and the guy's cringe.
Like the guy's definitely definitely
cringe. And he's got like a lisp and
that proper proper weird guy. And the
amount of little girls, bro, that was
obsessed with with this with this guy.
It was mad. It was it was mad. Like it's
just just copy each other.
Fit in is it? Yeah.
They used to copy each other. Little copycats.
[snorts] Little copycats. Well, I agree
with you. They little copycats.
Are they little copycats?
Are they little copycats? [snorts] Yeah, bro.
and it keeps banning me again, bro.
Must be a power thing, is it, lad? Must
be a power thing.
Must be a power thing.
Must be a power thing, lad.
What [snorts] do you think? 45year-old.
I couldn't believe that 45year-old
thinking that she was better than me
yesterday. That is cheeky, bro. That is
really, really cheeky.
Really cheeky. That was Jesus Christ.
Thailand will be finished in 10 years,
by the way. Yeah, 10 years. Thailand
will be completely finished.
Be completely finished, lad. Hey Baby. Anyways,
I'm gone. Yeah. So, catch you later. I
was only on only to say what I said. So,
catch you later. See