Yo,
won't be on long. What the [ __ ] did I
[ __ ] start, bro? Jesus Christ.
Just had to bloody ignore that. [ __ ] me.
[ __ ] up. What the bloody hell did I [ __ ] start?
Never knew someone could get so touchy
about their boyfriend. [ __ ] hell.
Jesus Christ. Espec Especially when
people are uh are supposed to be I mean,
bro, it must have took you about a
million hours to write that.
Yeah, that's what happens. He he's been
emailing me again, bro. He's been
emailing me again.
He's been emailing me again, bro.
Oh my god. What the [ __ ] bro?
He's an idiot, man. He's another one,
lad. He's another nod legs. That's his
boyfriend. People are very very touchy
about their boyfriend and he's no he's
no different bro.
He's an idiot. The only one that's been
bullied is him. He's not known nowhere,
bro. This guy is not known anywhere.
That's why he acts a big man on YouTube,
bro. He's not a bad man. I don't know
why people believe this guy. I've been
out all day. I've just come back. I've
looked on this. We all watched a female
brand. You would have turned bun and
I've had more women than you. So that
must mean you're the ba. You're ugly.
You look like like a gorilla, bro. This
guy looks like a gorilla and he's
talking about people's looks. Seriously, bro.
I said that you were sucking your
boyfriend's dick, which was you was
doing that. Yeah,
bro. Did you not see it before? Oh, he's
got a girlfriend. Little batty boy. Go
suck up your boyfriend's dick, bro.
Don't come emailing me, bro. I don't
want your [ __ ] I don't care about you,
bro. I don't know why you're emailing
me, bro. Leave me. Like, yeah, just stop
emailing me. What the [ __ ] Shouldn't
you be sucking your boyfriend's dick,
crying about his girlfriend? What the
[ __ ] you emailing me for, you little
[ __ ] You little was up batty man.
Bro, I'm blocking them now. Anyways, how
do you even block How do you even block
people on here, bro?
I don't know how you block people in
this email. I don't even think you can.
Anyways, so yeah,
>> uh that's that, bro.
But I don't think you can.
Either way, I won't be responding. So,
this is 2026. We We don't want to go
through the same habits again, bro. We
don't want to go through the same habits
again. Ridiculous. Now, ridiculous. Ridiculous. Ridiculous. Yeah. Anyways,
yeah, just another insecure little
[ __ ] That's the only thing I can say
about that one, lad.
Another insecure little [ __ ]
Because the thing is with these people,
bro, you like to, you know, you like to
give them the the benefit of the doubt.
You see, you like to give these the
benefit when they start sticking up for
their boyfriend noddle legs. you you're
able to rule them out quite quickly.
So when they're not intelligent, because
none of them are intelligent, they then
start like trying to insult people. You
see, get out of here, bro. No one's
scared of you. The only reason people
ain't done nothing to you is because
you're not worth losing their liberty
over. You're not worth losing your
liberty over, bro. No one's scared of
you along with along with most of the
people on here. Sorry, I've not long
gone back, but that's what it is, bro.
And you need to stop living four or five
years ago. No one cares. No one gives a [ __ ] [ __ ]
you know, about your biased remarks or
your bias. No one gives a [ __ ]
Seriously, they don't give a [ __ ]
And that's that, bro. You know what I
mean? This is 2026 now. This is a new
year, bro. I mean, that's how I see it.
I don't know how anyone else, but yeah. So
[ __ ] idiot, bro.
Still arguing with someone in 2026. The
[ __ ] bro. Get a grip. Yeah. Um,
yeah, bro. Going to start this food
soon. I'm hungry anyways.
I don't know anyone on here that's not
the same as these people except Charlie.
How hard can it be? You know, etc.,
etc., etc. It's [ __ ] so sad. It's
like they all suck each other's dicks,
but they all try to act different.
That's the thing on this on this. They
try to all act different.
[ __ ] miles better looking than this
guy will ever be. Bro, you mad and can't
even show his face and he's giving it
the big [ __ ] out of here, bro.
And now he's bringing USA is up. Bro, no
one cares about any of that stuff.
That That's not going to affect anyone,
bro. You're living The thing is with
these retards, bro. They're living in the past.
Like they're literally living in the
past. Like you can go on about old
sloppy seconds. No one's bothered, bro.
We've had new sloppy seconds before
that. We've had new sloppy seconds after
that. No one really cares about that. I
mean, we all know that she ran to the
police. We all know that she went crying
to the police and crying to her dad. So,
I mean, why are you even bringing up
that? No one cares about that.
You know, she was the one running to the
police crying multiple times and she
even admitted it to her friend, her best
friend. I spoke to her best friend for
like 5 hours. Not that it matters
anyways, but I spoke to her best friend
for 5 hours and she went to the police
so she can laugh about you to me all she
wants. No one cares. She wasn't laughing
when she was running to the police
crying for them to arrest me. So good
for you, man.
[ __ ] [ __ ] bro. Stupid little bias Yeah.
And that's that, lad. That's That's simply that.
Why is there only eight people in there,
bro? My [ __ ] [ __ ] Yeah.
You're still obsessed with my sloppy
seconds. Thinking [clears throat] that
bothers me, bro. Oh, [ __ ] me. [laughter]
This guy is so sad, bro. I've never
known someone someone so sad in my life,
bro. I really, really, really haven't.
Really, really, really, really, really,
really, really haven't.
Mad mad mad mad m bad m bad m bad m bad
m bad m bad m bad m bad m bad m bad.
Well, I can't check my messages on this.
Mad mad bad.
Really, really is mad.
You need to try to say something that
doesn't apply to yourself, man. Seriously. Um
yeah, I ain't got time for these people
anyways, bro. So I said what I wanted to say.
Yeah, I could do could do could do.
People should know about it by now.
Yeah. Could you believe that this guy is
still going on about my sloppy seconds?
Is that supposed to bother me, bro?
Like, really? Really? Is is that
supposed to bother me, bro? Only in your
head, some was up [ __ ] bro, from 3
years ago could bother me.
Seriously, bro, he must not be getting
no attention lately, you know?
I need I'm still on the [ __ ] wrong channel, bro.
Yeah, something like that, bro. Monster.
No, I'm not lying for him, bro. I'm not
giving him no more attention. He's a sad
bastard. Just like Joe. Just like a lot of them,
you know? Just sad
sad ass people, bro. Really, really,
really, man. Yeah. Okay. So,
uh maybe go back on the other one.
>> No, we're not live about him, bro. He's
not even worth talking about.
>> So sad. And And you know the maddest
thing I was thinking about? Yeah. kind of is
that you know these people you don't
actually even know them in real life.
How mad is that?
You know what I'm saying? You don't even
know these people, bro. And they're
arguing like they know you and that.
It's mad, mad, mad, mad, mad, mad.
Yeah. And you're gone. Bye-bye.
See you later. Another one of my jealous
stalkers. See you later.
Oh, [ __ ] Did you just say that spray
and you're gone? I told you I don't
entertain these people anymore, bro. Yeah.
Did you see my video on LT UK asylum? I
was pretty bag on, wasn't I? I was
pretty bad on, you know.
I'm not going to have someone [ __ ]
talk to me like that. That is definitely
definitely definitely not happening.
Yeah, it was bang on, isn't it? He is
biased. What did you think of it? Since
I know that you talk [ __ ] behind my
back, am I lying? Am I lying about
anything that I'm saying?
There's no point going back and forth
with this guy, bro. They're seriously
seriously seriously seriously isn't. You know,
he's just some washed up loser just like
the West rest of them. And I'm not
losing my liberty over this [ __ ] cuz I'm
not scared of him. Yeah. I don't care
about anyone else. Yeah. I don't care
about what anyone else is. I'm telling
you I'm not. Yeah. Do you understand? So,
no, I don't need to meet him. I don't
need to meet him, bro. I don't need to
meet him. What I'm saying is the truth.
And you know it's smoking me. He's
biased. All I wanted to tell him is that
he's biased. He's been emailing me
again, chatting a load of wank. He just
sent me a 2hour. I'm not even responding
to it. I'm not arguing with some stupid
idiot all day in 2026, every day who I
don't know. You're a biased [ __ ] and
that's it. You're a nobody and that's
it. Yeah, simple.
No, it doesn't need to get resolved. All
I had to say is what I said. You are a
biased bastard. Simple. You defend your
boyfriend. That's it. I don't need to
say anymore. You've emailed me a load of
[ __ ] talking about USA Izzy. Bro, no one
cares about any of this stuff. Only
you're in your head. You care about it.
I don't give a [ __ ] about this stuff.
You're making up stuff. Stop [ __ ]
stirring. You know, even even Joe says
it as biased as a country as he [ __ ]
stirs. We all know that USA was [ __ ]
scared. We all know that USA went
running into the police. Yeah, we all
know the full story. No one even cares
anyways, but it's just an example of how
you like to [ __ ] stir things to your
advantage. Yeah, simple, bro. No, I
haven't been back on it.
[snorts] Going to make some food soon. I
went to a dentist today. Last appointment done.
I actually done a video at the dentist,
by the way.
Should put it up. Should put it up, man.
It's a message for all of the people
here on benefits, you know.
[snorts] Yeah, man.
This guy is very sad. Very very very
very very sad.
Yeah, he wasn't me. He wasn't. Yeah,
that's what he's like, bro. That's what
he's like. He is like that. He's been
doing it for years, bro. That's why I
don't entertain him, lads. I don't
entertain him. I simply don't uh
um I don't I don't entertain him
anymore, bro. He will never meet anyone.
That's That's what it is, isn't it?
Lucky. He was lucky. I replied to him
today. this LT. He's very lucky cuz I
don't reply to people anymore that do
this broke. This [ __ ] But you know,
he emailed me back and I just wanted to
state I was biased.
What do you think, Smokey B? Do you
think what I'm saying in the video? Am I
Am I lying? If I'm wrong, bro, you can
tell me I'm wrong. I I don't ban people
that tell me I'm wrong.
I don't ban people that tell me I'm
wrong. I ban people that [ __ ] hate and self-p. Yeah.
You will never meet anyone.
You will never meet anyone, lad.
What do you mean the same as Joe? Yeah. Just
M Yeah. Like I said, bro, you can like
him. I'm not trying to turn you against
him. I'm not trying to turn anyone
against anyone. I'm just saying my
opinion on it. And he's trying to say
stuff to affect me. Bro, no one cares
about some dead USA, is he? No one cares
about what you've got to say. It No one
cares. Literally, no one No one No one
cares after what I said. No one really
gives a [ __ ]
No one really really really cares.
I just said, "I don't understand why
you're being biased and sticking up for
your boyfriend." And it caused all of that. Simple.
And then he's the one talking about
family members. So, in 2026, so [ __ ]
him, bro. I won't I won't going to hold
back. You know,
this whole thing still seems weird to me
how we don't even know these people in
real life, man. Ah, bro. This seems so
weird. It generally feels so weird. This
Anyways, [ __ ] it, bro. Okay, so
Yeah. Yeah. I'm not I'm not denying that
he will, but I'm telling you that the
guy is is biased. That's That was my whole point.
Yeah. That was my whole point is that he
is literally biased. Like, listen, bro,
they're not worth meeting on here. It
could be anyone. LT, Terry. Why do you
think I don't waste my time meeting them
anymore, bro? Cuz they're just jealous
ass losers. I'm not scared of them. I'm
not scared of Terry. I'm not scared of
Non legs, but he doesn't meet anyone
anyway. I'm not scared of Joe. And I'm
not scared of LT. I am not scared of any
of these people. You know, these people
say seem to forget yet that this [ __ ]
was four, five years ago. A lot of these
L's, I'm not scared of them. They're
just not worth it. You know, they're
just literally just not even worth it, bro.
Cuz we know why they do this [ __ ] Deep
down. We know why they do this [ __ ] So,
come on now. Come on. Let's let's let's
come on now. Really? You know? Yeah.
Anyways, [ __ ] it all, bro.
It's all irrelevant, isn't it? Yeah,
he's still obsessed with that USA, is
he? Bro, I'm surprised cuz they're not
It doesn't um That doesn't affect me.
I'm surprised he would even bring that
up. That does not affect me cuz she
wasn't laughing when she was running to
the police when her friend was telling
her friend told me everything. I spoke
to her best friend and her friend and
the only reason why her friend was like,
"Can you just please leave it now? Just
allow it." And I said, "Okay, I'm not
going to say anything anymore. I'm not
going to do anything anymore.
That's why I don't do Well, I weren't
going to do anything anyways. I allowed
it anyways, but I just thought if I ever
got angry again,
um then I would have just started up
madness again. But then I was like,
"No." Okay, well, fair enough. Um
um just leave it in it. So,
well, yeah, that Joe doesn't Well, that
Joe doesn't talk. Yeah.
Well, that Joe doesn't talk. So,
yeah. I mean, I'm sure I've heard you
talk before, Smokey B. I'm sure I [ __ ] have.
Long time ago, but I'm sure I have. He
doesn't talk, bro. What the [ __ ]
Oh, he is on his channel. Uh,
I'm sure I have heard you talk. I'm
pretty sure I have.
That's why I mistaked you before having
issues with LT. But maybe it was
it was definitely you. But anyways, I
don't care. That's between you two. I
don't give a [ __ ]
I can fight my own battles by myself. I
don't need people to fight my battles
for me. If I've got a problem with
someone, I'll say I've got a [ __ ]
problem to someone.
>> Yeah. Joe F don't talk.
No, that's why I don't go any shadow. I
unsubed from him like two weeks ago.
Yeah, I don't care about that punt, bro.
He's another biased one.
Yeah, bro. Like I said, if if you don't
have a problem with him, that's fine. I
I don't mind if you do or you don't.
Yeah. I just don't like biased biased
people. That's just me though. Is it
bro? And it goes for the police as well.
Um even even there, you know, any
anything to do with biasness like people
police. I just don't like and the police
are another one that are biased that's
got fa that do favorism as well. So I
mean I just don't like biased people,
bro. It's just something in me is it? So
yeah, that's fine. You can have um Yeah.
Agree with me on what, bro? Yeah.
going to make my t-bone steaks, dude. Yeah,
I used to like L J, but the thing is
with L J. Yeah, he uh what I didn't like
about L, I can tell you exactly what my
problem was with L J is how he would he
would target vulnerable people
and then other people he would choose
not to meet. That's what Lord Jay used
to do. And yet he would still try and
portray like he was some kind of bad
man. That's why I fell out with him
because I was actually defending Timmy.
Some of the people I fell out with, it
was actually defending Timmy.
I didn't like the fact that he'd go for Timmy. Yeah.
Uh and then I would have to say mad
stuff in order for him to come on my
[ __ ] door. You know what I'm saying?
Like he he he's he is another one. He he
was a he was another one, bro.
That's why I fell out with him because
that's why I went on about his kids and
[ __ ] cuz I was like, "Oh, well are you
going to be fast enough to come for me? [laughter]
Took a long time to get him to come over
here, bro." So,
he picks and chooses who he fights.
Yeah, definitely. Definitely, definitely. Definitely.
And I'm not even going to bring up
names, but he has avoided people
uh he has avoided people that's tried meeting him.
>> He has. He has, bro.
Why do you think he he never even tries
to threaten me anymore, bro? Because he
knows that it's not going to be how he
thinks it is. He knows that he's not
going to be able to come on someone's
door and it's not going cuz think about
when he come on the door four, what was
it like four four years ago? when you
come on the door four years ago, bro, I
open that door and I screw out a mouth,
which was four years ago. I couldn't I
didn't even need to open that door and
let's just say I done some things, you
know? So, if he's trying to do it now
four or five years later, it's not going
to work, bro. You know, he didn't think, you know.
So he's um
he was very picky with who he went for. Yeah.
Where's your name? Anyways. Yeah. Basically,
basically, bro. Yeah.
Yeah, I know. They they all got their
own agenda. They used to do it with Pat
Mustard, bro. They used to do the same
thing with Pat Mustard.
That's why I fell out with Candid Man. I
used to like Candid Man, but when he was
trying to make excuses for Pat Mustard,
I was like, "What? No, he's put Monty
Man's kids up. He you don't like Monty
man because what Monty man said but yet
Pat can put Monty man's kids up and says
it's public domain. [ __ ] off Candid man.
And I used to like Candid Man until then
I got put I got put off him bro. You
know back in the day bro when [ __ ]
Candy man I don't know if he's still on
it but he used to do the same thing with
Pat Mustard their own little agenda.
They done the same thing with him bro.
They done the same thing with him when
he used to put people's kids up.
Yeah, because they're Yeah, cuz they're
biased. Obviously, bro. Like, like I've
said, a lot of the stuff on here is biasless.
A lot of the stuff on here is biasless, but
Oh, wow, bro.
is what is it?
[ __ ] knows, lad.
It's just all weird, bro.
The only people that I can say that 100%
are normal people on here. Yeah, is
unworthy clock. How hard can it be? Ben Furvy.
Even kind of that Chris guy that goes on L J's,
you know, there are there are a few
people, but it's I'm sure there's other
people. I mean, them people, they're
just kind of like just normal people
that just have no agendas and they just
don't get involved. I mean, there are
some people, you know, but yeah. Yeah.
I just don't know why this guy is going
on about my sloppy seconds, bro. Don't
you not realize, you know, in that April
with USA Izzy, do you know how many
women I got within that month before it
got like really bad, bro? Like Jesus Christ. Madness. [ __ ] mad.
This is so weird what this guy does.
It's so weird. This guy is supposed to
have a family, bro. And this is this is
really weird, you know.
I don't stalk that USA. I've not gone on
that USA's profile for months, months
and months and months and months and
months. We don't even know why he's
bringing that up.
That is that is this guy is weird, bro.
Why is he even bringing that up?
What the [ __ ]
Yeah, but it was a two-way thing, bro.
They spoke about dead relatives. I spoke
about kids. They spoke about dead
relatives. It was tit for tat, man. Cuz
you know, the thing is back on
PlayStation, no one ever spoke about
kids. You do realize that there was no
obviously nons and that and you know,
obviously there was probably nonses on
there, but no one ever spoke about kids.
There was no kid talk. There was no no
talk. There was nothing.
There was none of this [ __ ] until even
with Monty until basically we come on this community.
You know, it was tit tit for tat, man.
It is tit for tat.
You know what I'm saying? And another
thing is, bro, I mean, it's not it's not
it's okay. Yeah. Not to like someone.
No, but what I don't understand is Yeah.
Okay. So, you say you say something
[ __ ] up, right? So, then you just
don't like that person. But the thing
is, I don't get it, bro, with these
people like Red Star, how they dedicate
their whole life to someone because of
what they've said
years ago. It to me, it's it's weird.
Like, to me, that is that is so weird, bro.
Like, if you want to go by logic, I
should go to America and kill that
woman. I should have went and killed a
[ __ ] you know? If you if you if you
want to go if you want to if you want to
go by that way, like if you want to
think of it like that. Yeah, if you you
know, think of it, bro. Like, you meet
someone once, you get intimate with
someone, they [ __ ] you over, you're
being told you're weird for going on
about this for years, but yet how the
[ __ ] can these people sit on here every
day for years dedicating their life to
someone? It's weird, bro. It's [ __ ]
weird, you know?
But yeah, you just if you don't like
someone, you don't like someone. But
what my argument is that it's like it's
these people are [ __ ] bro.
Really, really, really, really [ __ ]
If you've said some mad stuff, these
people should block you or just not like
you or slag you off the whole time, but
they don't do that.
That is weird, bro.
It is. It is weird. It is weird.
How can I say? I mean, because adults
can play with Lego.
Yeah. Okay, bro. Whatever. I mean, you
want to say You want to say stuff is
weird, Smokey Be. Yeah. Let me tell you
something that's weird. They told me the
other day they told me the other day
that I went to an arcade for kids.
Now, to me, that's a bit nonsy, lad.
That is very, very, very non why
somebody would even think of that. Think
of it. Think of it, bro.
Think of it.
Just just just just think of that, bro.
Yeah. You You've gone to an arcade
and the people are trying to turn it
into a pedo thing. Does that not tell
you how a lot of the people on here
think if they're prepared to say them
kind of kind of things, bro?
But, you know, I get what you're saying,
Spok, but a lot of it, you got to
understand. Yeah. A lot of it like what
they do is also like projection from
their own life as well. A lot of it, a
lot of it is because, yeah, they might
not like you, but because of what you've
said. Yes. But then also at the same
time, a lot of these people are um
but also a lot of these people are down
bad, bro. Themselves
cuz how um
what's the word? How um
what's the word I'm I'm looking for?
Yes. But there's other things as well,
bro, like going on in these people's
life. Do you understand what I'm saying?
I don't know, bro. I don't know what how
your mind works, but I'm saying that
like, okay, so this is the way I I I
would work it. If I found someone that
said stuff about like kids and stuff or
someone said mad stuff, I wouldn't
dedicate my whole life
to [ __ ] with that person. That's what
I'm trying to That's what I'm trying to
say. So, there's got to be deeper issues
within these people that are doing it.
There's got to be There's got to be
more. There's got to be more to it.
There's got to be there's got to be more
to it, bro. You know,
because that red star what that red star
does is very very very very weird
to do that every day for years. It's
strange now. Come on, man. You know, and
it doesn't bother me anyways. I don't
really care cuz like I said, I know what
these people look like. I know, you
know, what happens when these people get
docked. I generally don't care. But at
the same time, we can say stuff about
it, you know. Oh [ __ ]
You know, so there's definitely there's
there there's definitely underlying
issues with him, bro.
It's not that they've stumbled across a
community. Someone said stuff about
kids. There's got to be more than it
like within themselves as well.
I can't. You know what I'm trying to say
in it? Like there's got to be, bro.
And that was years ago with the USA
thing. Anyways, um Smokey Be. Yeah. But
but yeah, basically
I'm banning you now. Anyways, see you later, man. Yeah,
it is. It is weird.
Are you still there, Smokey B? This is
what I'm trying to explain, bro. Like,
yeah, it is weird.
I do think a lot of these people still
are jealous though. I I'll still I still
think that I still think a lot of them
are jealous, but obviously may probably
some a lot. But I do I I I've got my
reasons for it, bro. At the end of the
day, just based on the history with with them
because of what I was saying yesterday
and [ __ ] in it. So, you know,
I don't know, bro.
Yeah, I told you I was done with the
gambling, mate. [ __ ] done, bro. [ __ ] that [ __ ]
But also, what a what LT done as well.
He he would say a lot of the stuff on
the phone, but then when you saw him two
weeks ago on the live stream, he's
saying something a bit different.
So, he's kind of being he is kind of being two-faced
at the same time.
There's something not right with that
guy, bro. Even even if you can't like
put a pin on it, bro, there's there's
something not right in in his head, bro. Trust me.
I can't explain it, bro. Like, he might
he might come across as a normal guy,
but there's something not right there, bro.
There's something seriously seriously not right.
Somewhere there, bro. Somewhere there is not right.
But that's what it is anyways, man. [ __ ]
Oh, I want to make the steak soon, bro. I'm hungry.
Yeah, I know what you mean about the
birds, but I just didn't like when that
USA is he done. She was a [ __ ] and she
was nasty about it as well.
And I gave them the opportunities to
apologize as well, but they didn't
apologize. So, I thought, okay, we'll do
it the hard way. Simple, bro.
Me and Grezies had the same problem with
narcissists. You [ __ ] do realize
that, right? We've had the same problem with narcissists. Yeah.
I [snorts] ain't tried dating for
[ __ ] months, bro. I ain't tried
dating for months, lad.
[ __ ] that, man. I don't know if I'll
ever get back into it.
Uh, I don't know if I ever will. [ __ ]
knows, man. I don't know.
I [snorts] approach sober for ages.
That's going to be funny doing the first
one in god knows how long.
They still ain't closed my casino
account down yet.
The link's there. I want to join him.
Isn't that your mate, Jo? Smokey B.
Isn't that your Isn't he your mate?
That's your mate, isn't it?
Right. I better start my prepare my dinner.
Sorry. Is your mate now? Yeah.
No, no, no, no, no.
Why is this not it's not
in the neck, bro?
There we go.
Going to start my dings.
Going to start my binding now.
Oh, that smell like it smells like when
someone that guy was pitting with
[ __ ] um pitting with blood.
I think the guy died. Remember he was
pissing with [ __ ] blood, man.
Yeah, he was pissing with [ __ ] I
think he went in um Homer. So
yeah, I'm cooking it, man. I'm [ __ ] starving there.
Put some salt on it. Lemon as well.
Yeah. So do I.
I snake for ages cuz of the toothp.
I wasn't able to cuz the two bees.
I saw loads of cats about today. So many
cats. Why is there so many bloody cats? [clears throat]
I hate cooking the washing up, but I
mean what other choice do you have in it on Yeah,
you have a good state, right? Y
>> can you hear me?
>> No, I can't hear you, man. >> Hello.
>> My phone is fine. >> Hello. Yo, >> no.
This phone is [ __ ] bro.
Yeah, he has he has been talking. One
second. Let me reset my um let me reset
my phone. One sec.
Man, I've reset my phone, so hopefully
it works now. [ __ ] [ __ ] phone, man.
I think it's just phone, bro. I think
it's on its way out. Yeah.
All right. Try it again.
Doesn't work. It's my phone, bro.
Well, it is my phone, but yeah.
Oh, [ __ ] Huntington's phone, man.
Let me try again. Hello. >> Hello.
>> No, it's my phone as [ __ ] bro.
Let me try again. Hello
Nah, my phone is [ __ ] >> Yo.
>> Can you hear me? Yeah.
>> Yeah. Yo, can you hear me?
>> Yeah. My thing was [ __ ] bro. It was
echoing and [ __ ]
>> No, [snorts] I can't hear you.
Yeah, they're weird though, isn't it?
>> Wow. I mean, amongst other people.
>> Yeah. So, it's [clears throat]
>> But why why haven't you ever heard that Joe talk?
>> No. Dude's never been on a panel.
>> Jew's not been on a single panel.
>> Yeah. He talks a lot of [ __ ] though for
someone else talking about the way.
>> Yeah, but he [laughter]
he he talks a lot of sense as well.
>> Yeah. And then he acts two-faced.
>> N but same as LT. LT was talking sense
to you, too.
>> Yeah. But he's biased. You have to agree
he was being biased. >> Yeah.
>> But why?
>> Nah. Why is he Why is he biased?
>> Because he's got an agenda in it.
>> What's his agenda though? I mean, I've
explained it in the video. So, [laughter]
he is obviously he's biased, bro. It's
no biggie. Anyways, >> why?
>> Cuz he is.
>> Yeah, but explain why. >> Because
because he does do not do not do not
know what that means having an agenda.
>> Of course. >> Yeah.
>> So, what would his agenda be? Cuz he
doesn't come on here. He doesn't.
>> Well, when I was calling Well, when I
was when I was calling Nons a virgin, he
had a lot to say. But when he was
calling me a virgin, he had nothing to say. So,
>> yeah. Yeah. But he's just talking about
like what's in front of him. It's like
obviously nonslegs has a [ __ ] bird. It's disabled.
>> Yeah. But Yeah. But I've actually proved
I've had sex.
>> That's what I'm trying to say. [snorts]
>> Yeah. But I mean, it's like
>> No, but you don't you don't think you're
getting the point I'm trying to make. Whatever. Like,
>> no. But it's still grown men in their
30s arguing about who's [ __ ] someone. It's a
>> Yeah. I don't care. I'm just saying he's
biased, isn't it? I don't care, bro.
Like, is what it is. >> No.
>> So, where Wait, wait. Where do you Where
do you actually live then?
>> Me? England.
>> But you're Irish. No. >> Yeah.
>> Oh, okay.
>> I've been here for about 15 years.
>> See, it's been so long I couldn't even
remember how you sounded. That's how
That's how long it's been. Yeah, it's
been a long time since I've been on a panel, but
>> maybe two and a half years. Three years,
isn't it? It's got to be years. Got to
>> Couple years. Co probably last time.
>> Well, you actually you actually live in Milton Kings.
>> No. Well, I don't obviously I don't live
in [ __ ] Milton Kings, but I don't
live far away from Milton Kings.
>> Yeah. Maybe Northampton, is it?
Something like that. Yeah.
>> More south.
>> So, what? You from Belfast? >> Yeah. Okay.
>> but yeah, you just have to I just have
to you just have to ignore all this
[ __ ] about being [ __ ] virgins and all this.
>> No, I don't care, bro. It's like it's
like to skip this. I don't I don't care
about it, bro. I don't care.
>> You don't get to the fact that I was
just trying to call you a bluff. That
was the difference, you know?
>> Yeah, but why why would I need to show
you two grounds for you to meet me,
though? You understand how people
wouldn't believe it then? You understand
why people would believe in it, is it?
>> Yeah, but you still don't get it. I was
calling your bluff.
>> But you did edit the post.
>> Well, I edit I must have edited the post
because I spelled the word wrong. But I
didn't edit the post being based off of
its like main thing was was calling you
out. [snorts] If you had showed me 2K, I
would have come to your house. I made
posted the next day, the next day, which
were all exactly the same.
>> Yeah, but why you lost a buy? What? Huh?
>> Well, if you lost the fight, then what?
>> The [ __ ] It is what it is. I'm from
[ __ ] B. I think it's the first time
in my life I've lost a fight.
>> No, obviously not.
>> Yeah, exactly. You think I give a [ __ ]
about that? Doesn't [laughter] matter.
>> No, I'm saying [ __ ]
>> Yeah. So, that's that's exactly what I'm
saying. It's like if I put it out there,
if you had called my bluff, then what
the [ __ ] else do I have to do? This is
my one account on here.
>> Going to disappear. obviously would have
just shooted up.
>> Have you you've been playing that roulette?
>> No, not for a while. Lost
>> [ __ ] in it.
>> I lost a [ __ ] loot the last time I
played it. So, not for a while.
>> It's so annoying losing. I don't know
how you can lose any effect, bro. It's so annoying.
>> Yeah, but it's different. It's like
obviously if you have a bankroll and
money that you're willing to lose, it's
different. But if you're [ __ ]
gambling to like be able to go out for a
night out or some [ __ ] like that, then
it's different than it everyone.
>> What was that? What was that site you
used when you got that 2 What was that
site you used when you got the 2.5K?
What site was that? I'm just wondering. >> Mhm.
It's probably Skype or something. It was
>> Oh, it was a UK one, isn't it? Yeah.
>> Yeah. Yeah. Well,
>> bro, this site Yeah. I tried to I tried
I tried to close my account. Oh, we'll
see to it. We'll see to it. Yeah. It's
been two weeks. They still ain't closed
my account. I said, "Okay, can you just
put a deposit limit on?" And I was, "Oh,
what if you want to play more?" And they
were like trying to go with me and not
doing it, bro. It's [ __ ] dodgy, is it?
>> This This is the difference. And Joe is
Joe has said this to you like multiple
times that it's like he gamles like how
I gamble. So, if you go to the bookies,
I don't play the bookies anymore, but if
you go to the bookies,
>> you take like three, four, 500 quid with
you because you're looking to win a
jackpot quick. If you win it within like 200 quid,
>> you're 300 up. You leave.
>> You don't.
>> Not. But Joe hasn't shown a win for
ages, so he must have lost a lot of money recently.
>> Yeah. Well, yeah. But he might have
lost, but it is what it is. He's like He
said it's boring.
>> Would you show just like con constant losing?
>> Yeah, but I used to always got wins and
losses in it. Like videos.
>> Yeah, I know. But you were still
gambling like 20 to 100 quid and then if
you lost, you were spitting on the
[ __ ] machine. It's like a
>> No, I'm talking about two I'm talking
about two years ago, man.
>> Well, yeah, but your situation was very
different two years ago than it is now, obviously.
>> Yeah, but like what I'm saying is like
if you if you put gambling content on,
you have to show the losses as well as
well as you know what I mean. It's
boring and but you get me.
>> Well, it depends what you're putting the
content up for.
>> You say if someone comes and they see
that they think you're going to win all
the time and they lose [ __ ] on them.
It's like they're [ __ ] grown ass
[laughter] people. It's like you want to
put all your money on the [ __ ]
roulette and you lose then is what it is.
>> It's just harder. It is harder to win
now is it than 3 years ago.
>> Well, they tax in the bookies more. So,
obviously it's harder to win.
>> No, I mean even just like online and
that do you not, bro? Do you not
remember like 10 years ago online when
you used to be able to win more frequent?
>> To be honest, I've won more probably in
the last 5 years online than I've ever
won in the last 20.
>> Okay. But okay, but it's it's [ __ ]
now than it was 2 three years ago then
in terms of like frequency of winning.
>> Well, depends what obviously the odds
have been worse, but depends what you
play and what what you play. So
>> yeah, I just play roulette to be fair.
>> I tell you one thing though, you making
that video to LT is like only going to
end up bad for you,
>> bro. I don't care, bro. I'm not The
thing is I'm not scared of him. I'm not
saying I don't care if you ain't got a
problem with it. So be it, bro. So be
That's that's that's that start in it,
bro. That's my problem to be honest with
you, bro. Like
he just emailed me a load of [ __ ] in it. So
just ignored him.
You still there? Yeah. Hello. >> Hello.
>> Yeah, man. I was just saying, yeah, I
don't so be it, bro. I'm not I'm not
scared of the dude, so whatever. It
>> I mean,
>> that's me in it.
>> He's clearly from Tottenham and he's got
family and he's got cousins and [ __ ]
like this and he sent all them people to
your mom's house before. It's like,
>> yeah, years ago. Yeah.
>> Yeah. I mean, a couple years ago, but
it's like he's not bothered, is he? Hey. Yeah.
>> How how do you know? How do you know?
How do you know about Potman?
>> Well, I mean, I've been worked in London
for like 10 years.
>> But the thing is, if he's going to talk
about my family, bro, I'll just state
facts about he he's the one that brought
family, not into it. I do.
>> Yeah. But what? You don't have people in
your family, but they can do the same
stuff as he has in his family. So, >> well,
>> it's probably not the smartest, but it
is what it is. It's on It's up to you.
You can do what you want. Yeah, I don't
I don't mind anyways, bro, because to be
honest, I just I just think the guy is
weird straight in it. That's my opinion. So,
>> well, I mean, I still it it is a bit
weird that obviously you both live in
[ __ ] London and it's for the last
what, three, four years and we haven't
managed to meet up. So,
>> it's been longer. I think it's been a
bit longer than that to be fair. [laughter]
>> It's like everybody on here in YouTube,
nobody wants to meet up. It's like
>> I I went to you saw when I went to No's
area three times, didn't it? He didn't come out.
>> Yeah, but look look at the look at look
at [ __ ] Sean. You know what I mean?
He's not exactly going to pull up and
slap the head off you, is he?
>> Yeah, but he talks a lot of [ __ ] more
than anyone, bro. Even more than me.
Come on now.
>> Yeah, but him to be fair, him, Red Star,
they are a little bit more obsessed with
you than the average person. I'll give you that.
>> Of course. Of course. Red Star is the
worst, isn't it? That's what their whole
channel is about. But at the same time,
it's like if you have a faceless account
like Red Star and you're giving you [ __ ]
and you're putting stuff on you and it
triggers you and you go [ __ ] nuts and
lose money on roulette and then [ __ ]
want to piss on the bookies and do all
whatever you want to do, then it's like
it's the they win. >> Yeah.
>> So, and it's like and they're a faceless
account. You're out there. Everybody
knows everything about you. people can
literally all of your information is online.
So it's like they they still would just
win by doing that. You would win if you
just didn't react to that.
>> Yeah, but they would they would never
stop even if you didn't react.
>> Yeah, but why why what incentive do they
have to stop?
>> They would Yeah. No, but I'm just saying
like this is what I used to explain to
LT. If you if you Okay, you you done
videos for three years. Yeah. You
disabled comments. you stopped going
live and you went back on their channel
who think they would have stopped even
though they didn't get a reaction. No,
>> no. But it's like it's like all of those
people. There's loads of people online
who are just like this and people just
rip the piss and just make shorts and do
all of this [ __ ] and then you become
one of them lull co or whatever it is
like people just want to laugh at and
make fun of and clip. Then you just
become like that. If you feed into that
it becomes worse. Like look banger has his channel.
>> He doesn't give a [ __ ] If you come in,
you chat [ __ ] you just get blocked.
>> So why do you go for Timmy anyways?
>> Who? Tim? To be fair, Tim is the whole
reason why we're all on here.
>> Yeah, he is. To be fair, I got into
because he's [ __ ] gambling videos. To
be fair, man.
>> Tim is the reason why 90% of people are
on here. Tim in the last couple years
has [ __ ] sniffed his brains away and he's [laughter]
>> Yeah, but you do cocaine as well, it >> No.
No, I'm pretty sensible to be honest or
not, but it's like Tim has just went on
a bit of a mad one the last couple years
and he's he's [ __ ] [ __ ] up for
himself. He had a good channel, could
have made money done when everybody on
here comes on here with the >> like,
>> you know, you know, you know it's harder
to make money on YouTube now, is it?
>> No, it's not that hard to be honest.
>> You know, you know, when I tried before,
it told me I wasn't eligible unless I
had 10 million public views and I had
about 40 on my main channel when I had
all that damning [ __ ] up. What the [ __ ]
>> Yeah, but to be honest, like, do you
think you could make money off of your
channel? Because anyone who gets any
type of exposure is going to make money,
people are going to look into that. Do
you think if as soon as someone knows
your [ __ ] real name and they Google
you, you're going to be able to make money.
>> True. Yeah.
>> You go and change your name by Dpool,
you might make some [ __ ] money. But
other than that, like, you're cooked. You've cooked.
>> Oh, you you watch the side, man, isn't it?
>> Huh? You watch the Sideman, is it?
>> No, I'm like [ __ ] 30 years old. I
don't watch the Sideman.
>> Do you know who they are?
>> Yeah, them [ __ ] KSI and them.
>> Yeah, they make money on YouTube, isn't it?
>> Yeah, of course. But they're [ __ ]
aiming at like [ __ ] teenagers. >> Yeah,
>> you know.
>> Yeah, they do. Like
>> that's what they're aiming at, is it?
>> Yeah. But the people on here and the
people who make money, look, look at
Banger. He makes a couple hundred quid.
>> True. Yeah. He He doesn't have to put
his details out here, but he just
doesn't entertain all of this other
[ __ ] that like all of you entertain.
>> Yeah. Get you. Yeah. Yeah.
>> You know that's
>> What you doing? What you What are you doing tomorrow?
>> Working. Same as every day.
>> Well, you not going for a drink?
>> No, I don't really drink that much to be
honest. Not this year.
>> No, I had a bad hangover the other day.
Them sambuka shocks killed me, bro.
Yeah, but you've got [ __ ] all else to do
with your life. So, I mean, you might as
well just get drunk in it.
>> No, [ __ ] off, man. You can't say that,
bro. What the [ __ ]
>> I mean, there's a million one other
things to do than drink.
>> Yeah, but what what else do you have to do?
>> I mean, that's You could go to the gym,
you could go to new places, you could
build Lego on the floor. I mean
>> Yeah. And do you do any of these things?
>> Well, I do Lego. Yeah.
>> Yeah. Well, you Okay. No, but I'm just
using examples of things that you can
do. Is it?
>> You got DC, man. [laughter] That's
>> Oh, you got disconnected, man. [ __ ] My
phone is [ __ ] bro. Really [ __ ]
>> [clears throat] [laughter]
>> Still doing my steak, lad. Yeah, didn't
let me add you back. [ __ ] knows, man.
Don't let me add you back for some reason.
What the [ __ ] Why you back? No. No.
>> Yeah, it doesn't let Oh, here we go. >> Yo, >> hello.
>> Yeah, I think it was your connection or
some [ __ ] man.
>> I know. [clears throat] I closed my
phone there. Close my phone.
Yeah, my phone's [ __ ] to be fair, man.
>> No, you're [clears throat] all good.
>> I need to get a new one.
>> You're you're [ __ ] building Lego on
your floor. Like, apart from that, what
else do you have to do in the day?
>> Well, nothing cuz obviously not work, is it? But >> yeah.
>> No, it wasn't even like a normal
hangover the other day, bro. I ordered
takeaway and I took it back. I was
prepared to eat it and it just made me I
I was being sick. Had a headache. I
couldn't even eat the food, bro.
Yeah, I know. But just being hung over. >> [ __ ]
>> But don't know. It's like
your channel is cooked to be honest. >> Why?
>> Just all the [ __ ] that you said and all
like the amount of people.
>> Yeah, but you don't that long is a pedo.
He's even said that he get with a 15y
old and that like you I'm sure you've
heard of [ __ ]
>> Yeah, but that does you need to stop
focusing so much on other people. No,
no, I'm not. I'm just saying that they
give him a pass in it. Have you noticed
a lot of people do give him a pass?
>> Yeah, but of course they're going to
give him a pass.
>> Do you think people on here genuinely
care what anybody has like said? The
people don't necessarily really care what you
>> people on here have said worse things
about families on here.
>> Do you think anyone said worse than me?
I mean, it'd be very [ __ ] hard to do that, but
>> I mean I mean, did you ever used to
watch Monty man? He don't come on it
anymore, which is a good thing.
>> It's good he doesn't it?
>> Well, Monty Monty is different. He's a
he's just a [ __ ] [laughter] >> Yeah,
>> but he is he is he's [ __ ] complete >> Yeah,
>> it's different. At least you you seem
like you actually know what you're
saying, which makes it worse.
>> Yeah. The reason he said all of that
stuff that was because of Pat and that it
>> well Pat just drew you all out and made
you like [ __ ] crash out a lot of the time.
>> That's on him in it. Pat's a [ __ ]
wrong as well for the stuff that he
said. Banger said that.
>> So why why don't you really drink anymore then? >> Just
why why would it? I'm like I'm too busy.
>> Yeah, true. I
>> you know you know what they say about
Irish people in it.
>> Yeah. Well exactly. Yeah. But if I
wanted to drink then I can go and drink. But
>> you ever you ever been to the O'Neals
>> where's where? >> Soho. >> No.
>> You know what it is.
>> I don't go to London that much to be
honest. I was used to work in London for
like 10 years then.
>> Yeah. What part though?
>> All over London to be honest.
>> I know London probably better than you
know London. And I'm not even from there.
Okay, name me some places you worked
though, like two places. Did you ever
work in East London?
>> I used to work on the island dogs. >> Yeah,
>> I've worked in the Gurgen.
I've worked all around like the
embassies, all around like Palm. You
name it, I've worked everywhere.
>> You never You never traveled it.
>> What? That's I mean, this is the thing,
PJ. You've got to stop assuming stuff about people.
No, I'm asking you. I'm not assuming.
I'm ask I'm asking you, bro.
>> Of course, I've traveled.
>> No, I'm saying you don't travel now like
frequently in it. I'm talking generally,
not abroad. I'm saying you don't you
that's what I'm asking.
>> Well, I don't travel so much for work anymore. Luckily,
>> I never assumed. I was asking. [snorts]
>> Yeah, but I don't travel that much for
work anymore. But I still travel quite a lot.
>> Yeah, man. That's good, isn't it?
>> You think I live in England? I don't.
I'm not from here. You know what I mean?
Of course, I trouble.
>> Yeah, mostly bro.
>> But that's the thing. You can't assume
anything about people online.
Everybody's different. Everyone comes
from different walks of life and it's
just it is what it is, you know.
>> Yeah, I know. I know. I wasn't I was just Yeah.
>> And that's the thing. It's like chatting
[ __ ] about people who's [ __ ] You're
in your like You're nearly 30. People
are most of the people on here are like
30 years old probably plus. And we're
all just sitting around talking about
like who's [ __ ] had sex. It's like
it's absolutely [laughter] [ __ ]
>> It is pathetic, isn't it? It is pathetic.
>> Of course it's [ __ ] pathetic. It's
That's why I don't even entertain any of
that [ __ ] [snorts] It's like who's
>> Oh, do you reckon? Do you reckon that
account's real? I saw you said something about that.
>> No, of course she is.
>> I don't know. Cuz some a few a few a few
people was thinking it was fake in it. That's why.
>> No, but all right. She just seems like a normal person.
>> Yeah. You know what they like on it?
They make there's a lot of people that
make fake uh accounts of you know you seen
>> most most of most of them are like them
Discord lot you just have and a lot of
them [laughter] come on
>> yeah you you hate them on the Discord in
it you always go on about him
>> they're just a bunch of [ __ ] freaks
that's why they've got nothing better
>> what Jay did [laughter]
>> yeah I don't hear I don't hear about him
much now to be fair
>> but they're all there like literally if
you go on your life you can see they're
just a bunch of sad [ __ ] that are on YouTube 24/7.
>> Do you think that suck? Do you think
they do you think they they gave um
>> Seaside Mark a hard time or do you think
he deserved it?
>> To be fair, that whole seaside Marie
[ __ ] was [ __ ] Like I'm I'm pretty
sure he understands that that was
[ __ ] That's partly the reason why he left
>> is because
>> Yeah. He never he never come back in it.
N. Yeah, but he obviously he was going
to know that's [ __ ]
>> whether what he was going through in
this time that time of his life and he
was just on a mad one, but it's just like
>> it's just he he just left them Discord
beans hassled the [ __ ] out of him and he
probably just thought what's the [ __ ]
point? What am I getting out of this in
my life? Like
>> you reckon do you reckon he'll you
reckon he'll ever come back? >> Nah,
>> he probably will. It's like it's this
shit's pretty addictive. Like anyone could [laughter]
>> you can take a little bit of time off.
I'm not on here like 24/7 like the rest
of them, but it's like
>> I still check in. If I'm doing
something, you'll check in see what's
going on. But so like I'm sure sees
>> just want to see if it's like the same
people that it
>> Well, it's not even that. Just [laughter]
people just want to see if anyone's done
anything mad and [ __ ] crashed out and
lost the plot or something like this.
People half expect you to do that [ __ ]
>> The Monty and Natalie thing was
entertaining though. It
>> No, but they're [ __ ] too spastics.
>> Yeah, it wasn't. I don't know why. I
just found it entertaining. [laughter]
>> Nobody pays it. Nobody ever paid
attention to like Natalie. Apart from
when she was getting off her head and
getting her tits out and [snorts] Monty,
come on. Whenever he lived with like
Key, that whole situation with them. >> Yeah.
>> Insane. They deservedly lost their kids,
which was good for them. And then one thing
>> Yeah, man. Too can't. If it wasn't for
me being introduced to gambling, I got
introduced to gambling from the FBI and
I went on YouTube. I watched FBI videos
and guess who come up? Timmy.
>> Yeah, I'm insane. Timmy brought
everybody on here, didn't he?
>> Yep. Greasy come on here. Oh, Timmy's
Timmy's ruined about [ __ ] 10 lives
with his [ __ ] F.
>> Yeah, pretty much.
>> And I got I got Monty on here, but to be
fair, he did have chances to get you
know the thing is that people blame me
for that Monty thing, but people don't
understand. Yeah, people done what they
done to him before they done it to me.
>> Monty's a grown ass man, PJ. Monty's
well in his 30s. If you had some if you
had a family and anything to do with
like YouTube was affecting your outside
life, you just turn it off, you delete
the app, you don't come back on, you're
gone. But you could
>> you you move on. These people go live
like when the [ __ ] police are at
their door. Like it's insane. >> Yeah.
>> It's like people like that. You can't
teach stupid. People are never going to
leave whenever that shit's happening to
them. If I got if I got docked and some
[ __ ] like I don't really care to be
honest because I've not nobody has
anything on me. It wouldn't make a blind
bit of difference to me. I don't even do [ __ ]
>> Does any does anyone on here know your name?
>> Yeah, of course.
>> Well, L.
>> Yeah, a few a few people on here that
know me where I'm in a WhatsApp group
and my [ __ ] photo of me and my misses
is like on there. Doesn't make a blind
bit difference to me. I could go live
right now and put my camera on. It
wouldn't bother me.
>> Yeah. Yeah, it's like
>> you know you know you know who do you
think that when that pack got doxed who
do you think done it someone that he
gave his info to on here is it
>> not necessarily I think he just got a
bit brazen in the end
>> and it was almost like he wanted to
because he needed an excuse to leave and
[laughter] some people are like it
>> no but some people do some crazy [ __ ]
like that they just
>> they get too brazen he pushes it too far
he almost wants to like have an excuse
to be able to leave and then once that
[ __ ] gets real life then people can't
handle and they just [ __ ] disappear like that. >> Yeah.
>> But that's he's at least done what you
need to do. If that happened to anybody
else, then you would just you would just
be gone. You would disappear. Why would you stay? >> Yeah.
>> Loads of people. You didn't leave when
you should have. >> Me?
>> Yeah, of course.
>> Okay. When when should when should have
I left? As soon as someone came to your
door, like when LT came to your door and
people started smashing up your m your
mom's house and all.
>> Yeah. But do you not understand when
you're Yeah, but do you not understand?
Yeah. When when uh when um when when
when [ __ ] when you're in something
too deep, is it?
>> Yeah, but exactly. That's the whole point of
>> Well, look, you see this account right
here? Yeah. That's trying to [ __ ] Look
at this, bro. Yeah.
But the thing is the thing is these are
the same people, bro, that used to big
up Pat when they used to put Monty's
kids up. Do Do you see?
>> It's not. These people are trying to
just stir [ __ ] It's like I It's like
you can talk about that and go speak
about Banger. I speak to Banger every
day. If Banger had a problem, Banger
would message me and we would speak
about it like men. That's the difference.
>> Do you remember Do you remember that candid man? Hey,
>> I said, "Do you remember that candid man?" >> No.
>> You don't remember him? >> No.
>> The Oh, the American. Okay. Well, I used
to I used to be all right with him until
we started, you know, sticking up for,
you know, and [ __ ] That's what I'm
trying to say, bro. Yeah. But you get me in it.
>> But it is. You've just you've just
absolutely [ __ ] yourself. That's the whole thing. >> Huh?
I said you have [ __ ] yourself. >> Me?
>> Yeah. With all the crazy [ __ ] that you said.
>> Yeah, but you Yeah, but you I don't
think if someone come on your door, you
would have left YouTube.
>> Well, that's But yeah, but I would have
dealt with it. Banger came through your
door and called you out on your street
and you did [ __ ] all and then tried to
spin a different narrative.
>> No, I didn't try to spin. I I'm not even
getting into that again, bro. >> Yeah,
>> I've already said what I've had to say.
That's it, is it?
Yeah, but Lord Jay came on your door and
like called you right out and you could
have done all of the [ __ ]
>> I mean, I went to I went to the same
location as him after. Why didn't he put
his camera on?
>> That doesn't matter. He was on your
>> It does matter though.
It does. It does kind of matter though,
doesn't it? And I didn't need to do
anything. I don't really care anyways,
bro, to be honest.
>> But it doesn't really matter anyways.
I mean, what would have you done? What?
>> If someone come on your door from YouTube.
>> Yeah, but it depends why they coming on
my door. That's the difference. You
called everybody out to your [ __ ] door. >> Yeah.
>> So then that's the difference. You
called everybody out to your door as if
you were going to do something and then
people came to your door, but you didn't do anything. [clears throat]
>> So if I went to Mil Kes that time, we
was arguing, you would have let me.
>> Of course.
[laughter] If you have me 2K, like when
I asked you to, I would [snorts] have come. >> Okay.
>> All of those times, PG. All of those
times, everything I said, I would have
backed it. That's the difference.
>> Well, and you would have come with your wife.
>> Well, not necessarily brought her cuz
like why the [ __ ] would I have to bring her?
>> She You don't. But that's what you said, is it?
>> Yeah, but of course I said that [ __ ] to
try and draw you out even more. The
whole time [laughter] I was trying to
call your bluff because you chat so much [ __ ] >> [laughter]
>> And then it's like when someone calls
you out, but you can't back you can't
back it up, you know.
>> But I have tried to meet bomb in it.
>> [ __ ] bomb is another [ __ ] He
just ran away as well.
>> Yeah, but you saw But what I'm saying is
I'm just listing people that I have
tried meeting in it.
>> Yeah, but you could have said you tried
to [ __ ] meet anybody. I can you could
this guy in the [ __ ] chat, Nightlife
UK. You could call him out tomorrow and
he doesn't meet and you can tell I'll [ __ ] take
>> Yeah, but Yeah, but B used to come in.
more people out who are going to do something. Sure.
>> No, but bomb Yeah, but Bomb used to come
in the hangouts.
>> It's a bit different, you know.
>> No, Bomb is just full of [ __ ]
>> Yeah, I'll put the link out. I'm not
going back and forth with you anyways, Kevin. Yeah,
>> he's someone who always showed up, too.
>> No, he doesn't. No, he doesn't, bro.
>> He called through King out and he
[ __ ] showed up,
>> bro. When I when I when I was in
Liverpool, listen, I'll tell you the
story. Yeah. When I was in Liverpool,
they all went quiet. Nah, I can
guarantee if you had properly called Kev
out and went live, could you do a lot,
>> bro? He said he wasn't even in Liverpool
when I was there.
>> You do a lot of pre-recorded videos and
all sorts of stuff.
>> Pre-recorded, bro. Bro, I was live in
Liverpool like three times.
>> If you had have been live and stayed
live for any length.
>> I was live in Liverpool, bro.
>> And called out ice work,
>> bro. I was I was live. It was in January
three years ago.
>> I know. I know. Yeah. But
>> you remember it? So [laughter] I was live, bro.
Nah, if you was you went live on some
steps or something.
>> There's a lot of people. There's a lot,
bro. There's a lot of people.
>> There's a lot of people.
>> Is Liverpool not the one where the feds
came and busted you in your hotel room?
>> There's a lot of people, bro,
>> on Liverpool in Liverpool and they
haven't met anyone. You know that.
>> Put the Put the link out though. Put the link out.
>> So, I told him anyways if he's about
anything, he can come to London.
>> That's that.
>> Why? Why? Why do people
>> I don't I done a two-minute video. I
done a two-minute video. No, no, listen.
Jay Widow, bro. Everyone went quiet.
No, no. Listen, bro. Everyone Okay, I'll
tell you. McFry went quiet. Uh, who was
that one? Fruit King went quiet and Kev
went quiet and Harry went quiet and
Harry went quiet as well.
>> That's That's the only people. Harry
Fraud. He's not going to meet anyone.
He's been on here from
>> And Kevin went quiet as well.
>> Day one. Fruit King
>> and Fruit King went anyone
>> because LT No, no, no, no. Listen, LT LT
went to Liverpool the day before me.
Calling Calling him out. Yeah. Calling
calling him out and he didn't meet up.
But I was like, "Okay, [ __ ] it." And I
went the next day and he still wasn't.
>> There's only like two.
>> PJ, I got a question for you. PJ, you
don't about people uh calling you out
and [ __ ] What? When when uh you uh
asked me to come out with you and me and
Kayie went all the way to your location,
tell the public why you never turned up.
Bro, but it wasn't even my fight.
>> We wasn't even turning up for a fight,
PJ. We was turning up to meet you.
>> Yeah, I know. But why does that matter?
That wasn't even a fight. You remember that anyway?
>> Yeah, but why why would I meet up with a
fight with you? You set me a [ __ ] up, right?
>> How did I set you up? You had your own problems.
>> You already admitted it live online. You
seted me a [ __ ] up, [clears throat]
>> bro. You had your own problems.
>> Yeah, you talk about you talk about
that. Oh, people don't leave and people
are weak and people won't turn up to do
this and do that. Let me ask you a
question. Who have you ever turned up to
go at anyone's house? No. And you're a
coward. You don't turn up to no one's house.
>> Who have I turned up to anyone's house,
bro? Do I know where these people live?
>> Well, you you know most of people that
lives on this internet and you sit
there, right, criticizing others, right?
Preaching. Yeah. You're preaching right
to others and you can't even get off
your ass and even win on any like on a
bandit mate. You're crying like a little [ __ ]
>> Bro, this guy doesn't make any sense be
if I called you out right now. Would you
come to my location?
>> Uh, bro, why would I come to your
location? What are you?
>> Well, cuz I got beef with you. I want to
beat you up, right? I want you to come
off my location now.
>> You got beef. If you got beef with me,
you can come to me.
>> Well, that's that's the point. I'm I'm
showing you. You're telling people are
too weak to come to you. Yeah. I'm
asking you to come to me or I'll go
whatever. Would you come to me if I told
you where I lived?
>> I don't I've done where you lived and I
still didn't cuz I have a problem with
you. I don't care about you.
>> Yeah. So, you're telling this guy in the
chat here about oh when uh people offer
you out you go and do it. But I'm
offering you out now. Come and beat me.
Come and meet me and I'll beat the [ __ ]
out of you. Yeah.
>> Oh my god. This guy is a [ __ ] You're an
idiot, man. You don't get it, do you?
You're preaching about, oh, people are
too weak to come and meet you. But when
somebody calls you out, you make some excuse up.
>> Okay, but you can tell yourself that.
>> Am I right or wrong?
>> You're wrong. You're not make you don't
make nothing you say make makes any sense.
>> You don't know. No, I'm making it to a
total sense. You were saying people who
will call you out don't turn up and
people when uh you ask people to come to
you, they don't turn up. No, I'm asking
you. I got a problem with you cuz on the
day that you never turned up, can you
come to my location so I can beat the
[ __ ] out of you? So, I'm calling you out now. >> No,
that's my case.
>> Yeah, don't even make any sense what he's saying.
>> I'll put the link up. He's not joining.
One second. I'm going to show you what I cooked out. Very
well cooked. Look at that lush t-bone steak there. Lush.
>> Right. Let's see what this [ __ ] wants. [ __ ] it.
>> Hello. Hello. I I just heard you I just
heard you say there that the reason you
don't go to people's houses is because
you don't know where they live.
>> I live in 43 Blackwood Street in the Armor Road.
>> I don't believe you.
>> Are you going to come to my house?
>> Of course you're not. Of course you're
not. Wait here.
>> You're never you're never you're never
even going to ever come to London again
when you're promise you that.
>> Well, I mean I don't need to go to your house again.
I'm saying I'm ask I'm saying that
you're never going to come to London and
>> you have such you have such a problem
with Shaunie. Shy drinks in the same
place every week.
>> We've been over this. Bye-bye. What happens?
[ __ ] off. Repeater.
Kevin, you don't come on. Anyone welcome so nice.
Oh my [ __ ] god, bro. Oh, [ __ ]
You like it, huh?
I had to wash it out.
>> [clears throat]
>> No, you're not coming in, bro. You're a repeating bastard. Shut up.
Oh my god. You can't speak to them
people for too long or you get brain damage.
Yeah. [ __ ] look at that. That is
perfect at steak. Oh, it's like a bit
pink, but no blood. W
I lost one.
Well, you're on my live stream, so
you on YouTube 24/7 every day. So, I
only you know, bro.
M I love in about 10 minutes.
Yeah, I'll follow up in about 10 minutes.
Talking about yourself again, bro. I'm
still eating it.
Why don't we go?
[ __ ] those mates. [snorts]
Why is there so many projectors on this
community, man? Come on. Bing
bing, bro. Come on. Bye-bye.
They don't smoke to be with Irish. My Well,
I'm going to knock him out.
What's up, man? God, I hate that. Hate
what's up. What was it? No.
So, what's up people?
Who side are you on?
Let's vote, bro. Who side are you on? My house is Peter B. Why?
My my mom just says, "Don't waste your
time with him. She's dead." Yeah,
that's what my mom said.
It is true to be honest. You're not.
This community is very weird. Very weird. So weird.
Do you understand my point about the
bias though? Black black Steve.
You not understand my point about the virgin thing
or well I don't think anyone really
understands the point I'm trying to get at
because I want to
every time I fall in a virgin he cries
and says bro he's got a girlfriend.
Sorry I'll rephrase it next time. He's a
virgin with a girlfriend. Does that
sound better? Yeah. When he says about
me he's nowhere to be seen.
Did I buy a cup, bro?
I wasn't going to have someone let me
talk talk to me like that, bro. I wasn't
going to have it. Why is he biased to
someone that had problems with him?
That's so weird. The guy has lally got
I don't know why you're on my channel
anyways, PC. You're another monk.
You're another one that talks [ __ ]
behind my back. I don't even know why
you're on this channel, bro.
You're another one of [ __ ] L.
I don't like people that [clears throat] was nice.
Yeah. You'll notice, bro, every time you
try to call him a virgin, he gets a lot of backup.
Yeah, they he gets a lot of backup by
the he's got a lot of boyfriends on
here. But you on the other hand, well,
we know the answer.
I think a lot of these people are
[ __ ] sick on here, bro.
They're very sick, man. to come out with
the the arcade thing being a pedo thing.
Stick in it, man. They're very sick on
this community. A lot of people, the way
their minds think, why would anyone even
think of that, bro?
Um, no, I didn't finish it. I've left
it. I'm too busy with other things, bro.
I can't think about it right now. I need
to tidy this >> [sighs]
>> Hello, matey.
>> Hello, weirdo. You all right?
>> I'm swe Pepes.
Wow. You actually sound like that, bro. Huh?
>> You actually sound like that, huh? Yeah.
>> Yeah. You're another one that's too
faced, ain't you?
>> What do you mean?
>> You're too faced in it, bro.
>> Why am I too faced?
>> I don't know, man. I catch you talking
[ __ ] by my back. But it's okay.
>> Ah, thank you.
>> Why do you do that anyways, bro? It's a
bit weird, is it? It's >> funny. Really?
Yeah. I don't think it's funny. I think it's weird.
>> To be Do you know I think it's more
weird how these people are obsessed with you?
>> Yeah, it is weird. But that's their
life, isn't it?
>> They they want they want to bum me or
something, bro. I mean, that's their
life, is it? Leave them to it.
What do you think?
>> Very very very weird behavior. >> Yep.
>> Are you drinking alcohol or something?
>> I'm with my peppers. [laughter]
>> You have that like every day.
>> It'll be a lovely sight.
What the [ __ ] bro? [laughter] Mute.
No, I can't talk to this guy, bro. I'm
sorry I can't talk to you. You're weird.
One second. Yeah, I'm just going to do
some washing up. Give me like 10 minutes.
Wait, what do you mean I'm right, Black
Steve? What am I right about? One
second. That's a That's a thing I forgot
to ask. What was I right about?
Do you even know what you're agreeing to
or disagreeing to when I said about the virgin?
How How am I right? Have you Have you
even seen it yourself?
Yeah. Like I said, bro, if if a [ __ ]
doesn't count, then a girlfriend don't
count in my book. Yeah, they are biased.
And it's very strange that he's biased
when he's had problems with the same guy.
Obviously like Red Star and other
people, L J and stuff, you you kind of
expect it uh you expect them to do that
cuz that's them in it. But yeah.
Yeah. I don't care about some
girlfriend. He's a He's a virgin with a
girlfriend. So if that sounds better,
then it's better. And then he was trying
to say that I was paid for it. Yeah, he
did, bro. He He No, he didn't ignore it.
He was making up excuses saying that I
pay them. [ __ ] biased [ __ ] Yeah.
He's very touchy though. He's very He's
very touchy about his boyfriend.
He's very touchy about his boyfriend.
And I won't say anything for the future,
but it don't make sense why he's biased
because he's had problems with the same
guy. That's the bit that never made no
sense because he has had problems with
this guy trying to [ __ ] Sir, I just
been Well, just don't think about it.
The more you think about it, the more
you do great stuff. You need to know.
>> Did you like that black? Did you like
that uh black sleeve?
When I said, "Did you like that, lad?"
When I said the business, I've shown you
the business on the camera. Cuz you
said, "Oh, you really think they've been
in a relationship and they and they
ain't done the business?" I said, "I've
shown you the business.
I've shown you the film, the business,
but you ignored it."
Then he started getting aggy in that.
How do these people really think of this community?
How did everything?
>> Yep. Weird, bro. It is strange.
Then he started saying some mad stuff to me and Yeah,
he said some mad stuff to me, bro.
He was talking about USA. He said, "Oh,
me and USA laugh at you." I said,
"Really, bro?" Really? That's nice, man.
We all know that's [ __ ] because I've
spoken to her friend. I've spoken to her
best friend. That's one of the only
Well, it's not the only reason. I'm not
obsessed anyway, so I don't give a [ __ ]
But it's one of the reasons why I would
never do it again because
I didn't speak to someone on the phone
for 5 hours for no [ __ ] reason, bro.
Yeah, it's weird.
It is. It is weird, lads. That's it.
I need to watch my team for that in style.
I have to clean up this [ __ ] thing
now. Only thing I hate about cooking.
Well, stuffing that steak, you know. >> Yeah. It's quiet.
It's strange how. But the the thing is
though, what why what I found it was
weird with him cuz like he portrays
himself as this normal guy. But it's
like I was just saying if you're normal,
why are you being biased then?
Why are you being biased defending your
boyfriend? Why is that? Like
Yeah, I know they're on Discord. Well, I
know all about it. I know all about what they do.
>> Yeah, man. That L kind of got me in the mood today.
>> I won't be on tomorrow. Facts, lad. I won't.
>> What was the excuse? Oh, yeah. You don't
come on here anymore cuz Laney says that
you can't come on here. She really
all I said was my mom doesn't like me on
here. So I'd rather respect her wishes
because it's her home. Of course I can
go on wherever I want. But for what,
bro? For what? Really? For what? Arguing
with stupid people that you don't [ __ ] know.
with stupid ass people that you don't
[ __ ] know. Like what?
Clean this up. [clears throat] So annoying.
need the kitchen in a state like that in it.
You know, I done a video, you know,
about the dentist today whilst I was in
the dentist. I said, you know what?
Yeah. [ __ ] is the people, the women. Oh,
I don't like police either. The men, the
women, the the system and [ __ ] Yeah. I
mean the the good thing about England is
you get to take advantage of the dentist death there.
I've done it but I did get to put the
video up. I think that's fact. You know
there's so many people here that's got bad teeth
but there's no um
uh there's so many people here that's
got bad teeth missing teeth and there's
no reason for it.
>> Why? But another thing this black uh
street you know it's also the police are
biased as well. They're also they've
they also have favorism.
Police do it as well bro. It's not just
people in the community. There's actual
even these police have favorites.
They've got favorites as well. They're
biased corrupt [ __ ] as well. You know
it's not just it's not just people but
police also like it too.
I could tell you a billion and one
stories my encounters with them brother
they're very very very um pick and
choose who they go for when these people
swear an oath and they're supposed to be
law they're supposed to be the law but
even they're biased with who they go for as well
systems [ __ ] that's another thing that's
[ __ ] about England the police the police
system the police, the the people, even
the men as well. A lot of them obviously
there are good people out there. I'm not
saying that, but there are they are a
lot of [ __ ] especially in London.
But I mean, you got the dentists, you
know, [ __ ] hard to get appointments,
bro. It's take advantage of that [ __ ]
They don't know. People here,
people like Benny are disgusting, bro.
It's the Dustin. Absolute Dustin. He's not leg
makes you wonder, doesn't it?
Yeah, man. is
do you not think it's weird LT brought
up USA is he bro if you fancy her yeah
if you fancy her yeah then
should ask her out to go for a date sometime Yeah.
What about you smoking be? You want to
do you want to you want to ask out the USA? [laughter]
What do you think? Yeah. [snorts]
Kieran says it's biasness. Black Steve
says it's biasness. But I don't
understand why the police are biased.
They're supposed to be impartial. That's
their [ __ ] dog. But no, they are they are biased.
I can't even say they're sexist cuz
they're not sexist. They got they got uh
they got I learned that with no legs
about their favorites and
other things as well in the past. They
have favorites and
yeah they they discriminate. It's
discrimination and favoritism.
I'm sure that's a word. Favoritism. If
not, I've just made it up. So
yeah, they are they have got favorites. [clears throat] They discriminate.
[ __ ] why they're doing it.
Good old England there.
Keep washing up.
>> [clears throat and cough]
>> I don't brush my teeth now.
Tell my mom about this. Yeah.
>> Yeah. Sorry. I just gave some to lady.
I don't think [ __ ] Okay, we go. Never mind.
Washing up with a lot.
Probably brush my teeth before I go to bed.
the world to be honest.
Love my electric toothbrush. It's lush.
We change the head every six months. Lovely. Oh,
really tired, you know. Another
Just have to take a long wash out, mate.
Blinding a bit. Yeah. Is >> Yeah. Mama mama. No, no.
I want to try some of this Lego, you know.
Right. I'm going to try some of this Lego.
One sec. Here we go.
Right, let's get stuck into this [ __ ] Okay.
So, we are at number.
There we go. Oh, first try.
No, we're not. There's no
trying to do this with bad eyesight is very uh
Oh, no. is
hate this, bro.
Pretty sure that's supposed to be like that.
So hard, bro.
That is it.
I hate this, bro. I [ __ ] hate this
You know, it's not right cuz that's not
even clipping on that. Right.
That is not right. Uh
don't have the patience for this [ __ ] man.
I really don't have the patience for this [ __ ]
Have to fight all over again.
Look at this [ __ ] man.
Try again. All right.
Want to try to make a solid effort. [clears throat]
Same boring thing again.
Boring this is man. So boring. Good [ __ ]
Maybe we have to put the black pieces on it. Oh,
I hate this so much. Take this.
My eyesight really isn't that digital.
So many things I need to go [ __ ] sex do >> [snorts]
>> Where's that page then? Holy hell.
Maybe that's why it wasn't.
No, that's not right.
No, that's definitely not right.
Oh, people are here biased. Um, Smash videos.
Yeah, [ __ ] biased.
No, I've done it the wrong way. And I slept.
I done it the wrong way.
Would you say the people in here are biased then?
you would you say that they're biased on
it or not?
>> Yeah, they are, bro.
probably LT is biased, bro. Not good, man.
Yeah, they're very biased, man. Would
you believe I'm building Lego on a [ __ ] Thursday?
I need a detox, bro. That was [ __ ] wild.
Why is that not going in?
There we go.
That's a double one. Yeah.
Well, El says I haven't proved I've had sex
according to him. So
well he says I have improved I've had sex
you need to have words with him lad
right let's try this again with this [ __ ] black piece
There we go. Here we go. I mean,
a [ __ ] is proved that proof that
you've had it. I mean, lying in bed,
lying in bed naked with a woman is is
proof that you've had it. I mean,
I'd say that's solid proof.
I mean, I would say that is
>> Well, then a girlfriend's not proof then.
Showing a fat ugly girlfriend's not proof.
As far as I'm concerned,
your girlfriend ain't proof.
Yeah. Well, that's not proof then.
He could have erectile dysfunction. He
could not have a dick. Um,
they might be in a sexist relationship.
So many different reasons, bro. If a
[ __ ] is not proof, then a
girlfriend's not proof.
That's the way I see it.
That's the way I see it, lad. E.
That's dark, though, isn't it?
Yeah. Well, that's not proof then,
cuz [ __ ] lead to sex. And I don't
care if he's got a girlfriend. He's a
He's a girlfriend with a virgin.
So, he's a girlfriend with a virgin.
He's a virgin with a girlfriend. Sorry,
I'll rephrase it for you because you
like to talk about the girlfriend. Okay.
So, he's he's a virgin with a girlfriend
instead of a virgin.
I don't know why so many people defend
him, bro. And he that that to me is so odd.
That to me is so wild. Like why they
defend him like that? That is weird as [ __ ]
That to me is so odd.
They think showing a girlfriend is more
proof than someone actually being having
a [ __ ] And and that is [ __ ] weird, man.
Yeah. I'm not friends with biased
people. I don't like biased people.
>> It's going like
[ __ ] going. It is.
You want to make sure you put this on
solidly as well.
>> Well, you do know if I have because
you've seen a porno of me getting a
[ __ ] You've seen women in bed with
me naked. You saw my friends with
benefits. So, you you do know.
Well, you do know because you've been
shown more than enough evidence.
Well, if someone has if someone has got
a [ __ ] on video and show them naked
in bed with women, that proves they've
had more than someone showing a girlfriend.
Oh, that's the wrong way. That's the
wrong [ __ ] way.
You're [ __ ] putting me off, you
stupid [ __ ] man.
Well, I'm pretty sure someone's showing
a [ __ ] and them being in bed naked
with women. I mean, that's
I mean, that's that's more than showing a girlfriend.
That is definitely more than showing a girlfriend.
That No, this is wrong. You're putting
me off, you [ __ ] [ __ ] man. Shut up.
A [ __ ] is 100% proof. A [ __ ] leads to sex. That's wrong.
So, I mean, what what more proof do you need?
So, what I just had a [ __ ] and
All right. Okay.
Yeah. Okay, bro. Interesting.
Shut up. You put me off this [ __ ] thing now.
[snorts] Jesus Christ.
But no, unless we've seen proof, lad,
he's a virgin in my book.
So that's the way I see it. I don't care
about girlfriends. I don't care about
any of that [ __ ] Unless I see actual proof,
then yeah, he's a he's a virgin in my book.
Simple as that. It's like I'm a virgin
in people's book even though I've shown multiple women.
Why is that not going in?
It's got to be a hole.
Yeah, I'm conjured it to myself.
Anyways, when I opened this
conversation, I said what I had to say
about the biasness,
so I'm not I'm not getting into this,
bro. I don't really care.
I'm not having this conversation, bro.
You're talking to yourself. I'm I'm not
asked. I've said what I've had to say.
So, you're all biased anyways. You do it
with multiple things. You do it with
money as well.
You even do it with the money.
>> Yeah. I can't handle all the debate.
Yeah. You keep telling yourself that.
No, you're just all biased. I said
everything I had to say. That's that.
And I'm trying to build this
this um Lego and you're
putting me off, lad.
I'm sure this is right. Let me see if
there's any other pieces.
Same question to you. Surely if
someone's got a [ __ ] and they've been
in women's beds naked, surely they've
had sex more than once.
Same same question to you. But you don't
say anything when he's calling me a
virgin cuz you're bias.
I mean, that's that's actual proof. A
relationship is not proof.
That's not proof.
You haven't even seen her go down on
him. You don't know their sex life.
So, stop it. You're biased anyways. I'm
not having this conversation. You're
talking to yourself now, bro. I'm
building Lego. We know that you're biased.
So, shut up. We're not We're not having
this conversation. I'm tired of it.
You're bi You're biased and that's it. Yeah.
We seeing how you people move. Uh so yeah. Yeah.
A [ __ ] and what I've shown is more
than a girlfriend. I've shown more than
a girlfriend multiple times.
multiple multiple multiple multiple
multiple times I've shown way more than a girlfriend [ __ ] sake. Yeah, man.
Decided to take up a new hobby. Eh,
I don't even know right. Doesn't matter.
I think this is this is the piece. Got
to be the piece.
Oh, what am I doing, bro? I'm doing it
wrong now. Will you shut up?
More money, more women. Women admitted
to sleeping with me, me kissing women.
I'm showing more than a fat, ugly
girlfriend, which is what I said to LT. [ __ ] Hopefully
I'm going to try and do half of it tonight. Busy tomorrow.
Now I've got to build a [ __ ] wing. I
need you to shut up now, bro. I need
concentration when I'm doing this. This
was a [ __ ] one. I remember this.
So, I'm going to need you to shut the [ __ ] up.
This is the bit I got stuck on for about
half an hour yesterday, but I know how
to do it. I reckon
this is the [ __ ] bit, but it doesn't
stop it happening again. No,
no, bro. I don't care about these losers.
So, what did you think of my video on LT then?
Yeah, that is light. No.
Where's the other piece gone? Did you
like the video?
No. But the biasness.
No. [ __ ] all that. I'm talking about the biasness, bro.
Where's the other wing gone?
I'm talking about the biasness. It's the
tr It's the truth, isn't it? Surely
to God if if you can defend someone for
having a girlfriend apparently not being
a virgin, you can you you can you can
defend someone that's had a [ __ ]
I just don't understand, bro. These people.
This is a wrong piece.
No, I think I've lost a piece here, bro,
cuz I can't see it. [clears throat]
No, there's two parts to it. There's one
part and then there's another part.
No, it's the wrong one. Right.
Oh, it's got to be this one, is it?
Yeah, that's the baby. Got it.
Good. You know,
you want to make sure you don't do any
of these pieces wrong.
This was the [ __ ] one. This black one is
I started all over again. I've only been
been at it for about 10 minutes.
I had to start all over again. [laughter]
There's this bit now. I need
concentration cuz this bit is a [ __ ]
This black thing now is a [ __ ] bro. I
was stucking it for about half an hour
yesterday. Now I do need concentration with this.
And then you need to
put the gold.
I got the hang of it, but it was hard
yesterday. You need to do it a certain
way. And it's not up.
It needs to be a bit lower. Bit lower.
How do they expect this? How do they
expect kids to do this? I shall [ __ ] never know.
There we go. I think that's the baby now.
That's the baby. There we go. So, look,
you have to clip the wing.
It's all about clipping the wing. Look,
you see you need to do it a certain way. Oh gosh. Okay.
Where does the black bit go?
That's the bit I'm stuck at now.
No, I do know this part actually [ __ ] long.
People going to start [ __ ] copying me
with Lego now. Ain't it little copycats?
What do you think, bro? Little copycats.
Don't [ __ ] copy me, little copycat. Little copycat.
Oh, you little copycat.
You little copycat.
You need really good eyesight when
you're doing this, bro.
You little copycat.
Who's a copycat? Rat boy.
Who's a little copycat?
Who do you reckon? The biggest little copycat.
The little copycats. The little copycats are out.
Who do you think is the biggest copycat?
Where's this [ __ ] black Hunt peace.
Yeah, I'm building it. Little wing now.
That's what it is.
Nah, Gre will never meet anyone. Remember
that little trend?
Remember that little shovel trend?
Do you remember that little shovel trend?
We used to copy each other.
Why is that not going in there?
It's got to be the wrong P. It
remember that you used to copy each other
of the copycats. It was better than
[ __ ] at one point, bro. [ __ ] better.
It was better than TV, bro.
It was actually better than TV watching
a load of people copy each other.
What do you think? Nah,
that doesn't make any sense cuz that's
telling me to put that there.
Unless I've got some sort of piece
wrong, but I don't think that.
>> No, there's got to be some other piece,
bro, cuz that ain't right.
>> I'm not gay. I'm not gay. [ __ ] knows. Okay.
>> That's what you used to say, bro.
>> I'm okay. I'm okay. I'm okay.
Stinky little copycat on you. Bro,
you're just a stinking copycat.
You're just a big fat stinking copycat.
Where the [ __ ]
Why is this not going in, bro?
No, that doesn't make no sense.
Always got stuck on one part in it.
Nah, not a Scooby, mate.
I haven't got a [ __ ] Scooby,
right? Have to finish it tomorrow.
Uh, not a [ __ ] Scooby, mate.
>> Not a [ __ ] tunning Scooby.
Well, I'm going anyways. See you later. Oh.