on the bright side of life. One second.
Oh, I live on the bright side of life.
Oh, that's very cozy. That's very, very warm.
What the [ __ ] is going on here, mister?
Give me back. Yeah.
I'm worse on this [ __ ] on this
[ __ ] football, man.
>> Yeah, the odds have got bloody worse on
that [ __ ] football.
your [ __ ] bro.
I'm not doing that. [ __ ] that. Yeah.
So, we was just looking at football,
seeing the odds on the football, and
they're utter wank. They've got worse
than [ __ ] football odds.
They put 50 on a both score, no draw.
Double both score, no draw. [ __ ]
returns 280. [ __ ] that, bro. That's
That is [ __ ] bro. I'm [ __ ] not doing that. No,
it's [ __ ] It's [ __ ] wank. It is.
No, I'm not doing that.
No, I was just looking at the foot.
Yeah, basically. Uh yeah.
Yeah. [ __ ] £50, 230 profit. No,
that's not good enough. It has to be
like£300. I'm not [ __ ] doing that,
bro. [ __ ] that. I don't I don't see the
point in even betting on this [ __ ] football anymore.
It's so hard to win on it.
And um the odds are [ __ ] now as well.
You see, if I'm going to put loads of
money on a double, both both teams just
score. I'm not b at all. So, yeah. But
then that makes it less likely. I don't
want to do more than two teams. I'm not
doing more than two teams. is just
pointless. You always get [ __ ] over
when you do more than two teams
cuz that extra team is a lot more harder
to come in. So,
nope. Two teams are two teams maximum. I do.
No, two teams maximum.
Other than that, it's just a mugs game
the way I see it.
No, doubles. Doubles the best. Doubles
are the best.
Everyone's got a different way of
betting, but mine's doubles. Doubles are That's it.
Cuz the thing is, if you do more than
two teams, you might win twice a year.
If you only do two teams, you'll win
continuously. Sometimes you'll lose, but
you win more times. I just think it's
better that way.
Yeah, but it's very unlikely it's going
to come in. I don't know. Treble. Both
teams to score. Last time I bet both
score, no draw. [ __ ] got [ __ ] by
one team. I'm not doing more than two teams. Yeah.
No, I'm not doing more than two teams. [ __ ] that.
I'd rather stick 150 on two teams. It's
easier that way.
And that returns about 500
480. It makes more sense doing that in
my in my opinion.
And you're very close as well. Very close.
There's some teams playing home today.
I'll just stick 150 on two teams.
Let me see how much that pays on them.
The only way to seem you seem to be able
to win now is is this way.
[ __ ] you can't [ __ ] win on no [ __ ] roulette.
You can't win on roulette. You can't win on [ __ ]
You can't win on anything but the
football it seems.
Let me see how much this pays. Hold on. Um,
let me see.
We have to see how much it pays.
Well, that's [ __ ] as well.
So, 150 for 392 back.
That's quite [ __ ] to be honest.
The odds have gotten worse. What's the Wait.
Yeah, the odds have definitely
definitely gotten worse.
Yeah, cuz £78 that used to be a 20 return.
Yeah, the odds have definitely gotten
worse on it. I'm not even going to
bother to be honest. [ __ ] it. The odds
have definitely gotten worse. Nice
shot, bro. Shut
yesterday. I was so tired.
I was so so so tired.
So, I had some food and I went and I
went to bed.
I need to get a [ __ ] haircut, man.
But I can't be asked.
Can't be asked. Oh,
can't be asked, matey. Look, my bed's
got long as [ __ ] Oh my god, bro. Look at that.
Need to go to the barbers. Yeah,
this channel doesn't come up.
Yeah, I'm out today as well. Stuff to do.
Yeah, but it's not simple because you
rarely win when you do it that way.
Yeah, but then you you rarely win.
You rarely rarely win doing it that way. So,
[ __ ] those, man. [ __ ] those. Yeah.
Yeah, you might win once or twice a year.
That online ruler
that on Oh, [ __ ]
Um, Slow and Enfield Town.
Yeah, Slow and Enfield Town.
I was thinking slow and Enfield Town. Um,
depends. I might do a bet maybe 10 or 20
pound, but let me see what the other one says. M
I don't know, bro.
Yeah, I was going to do them and I was
going to do them as well. Yeah, that's
the other team I was thinking. You read
my mind. I was literally going to say
that team as well.
Yeah, I was going to do them as well.
Maybe I'll just put 50 pound of three
teams, both teams to score normal.
still be [ __ ] But
I was literally going to say that one as well.
You read my mind, you [ __ ]
I was literally looking at that
Darlington game as well cuz not every
week does the National uh North and
South League play
South. Okay. So,
one second. Let me think here.
We got SL. Yeah, I was going to do slow, Enfield,
Scarra, Kitty Minister. I want to do
them as well. And Lemonton. No. Yeah. Darlington. Yeah.
So, I want to do four.
Maybe I'll do three.
Maybe I'll just do three. But that's not
going to be good odds just to both teams to score.
That's not going to be a good team. Not
going to be a good return.
What if I do three teams um correct
score? Three nil nils. Oh,
that would be a lot of money, wouldn't
it? If you predicted nil nil in three games.
Yeah, that would be a lot of money.
Right. I'm going to I don't even know
where I'm going to do the bet. I'm
banned from so many bookies for spitting
on the machines. Um,
[ __ ] those, bro. [ __ ] those. What man? Who knows?
Yeah, I've already I already got my
three, bro. I've already got my three.
Enfield, slow, and
slow, and Darlington.
I've already got my three, bro. Yeah,
but it's what am I going to do? Just a
normal both teams to score or you understand
a normal both teams? It's going to have
to be a normal both teams to score in it
cuz they're both going on a draw.
is it's hard.
No, bro. I'm not eating now till later,
man. Peter Belly's Peter Belly needs to
stop eating as much cuz Peter B is going
to get really fat and he'll start
looking like Joseph Ferrar and [ __ ]
L. I ate once yesterday.
No, bro. I'm inter I'm in what's it
called? Intermittent fasting. I'm I'm
not eating like that anymore, bro. [ __ ] that.
That's how you become like these people.
on here, bro. [ __ ] that. No way.
[ __ ] that, bro. As soon as I see I
really need to go to the gym as well,
but I just haven't been asked. Soon as I
see I'm getting 1% of like these people,
bro, that's like, nah, no, no. It's time
to cut back
cuz that's how you end up like these
people. You see,
they can be nice all they want.
Could be nice all they want, bro.
[ __ ] that [ __ ]
You end up like these people. Jo,
Smokey B. No offense. No offense when
I'm saying that, but they are clearly overweight,
you know. So you you know
bomb they're all fat.
I I don't really have a problem with
Smoky Be but I'm just saying bro you know.
Yeah. Yeah man. [ __ ] that.
I should have already wanted to gym by
now to be honest. There's no real reason
why I haven't. There's no excuse why I haven't really. But
yeah, I'll pick three anyways. I'll pick three. Um,
and that's it.
But I don't know how much I'm going to
put on it.
But it makes no sense like trying to win
150. I don't need £150. What the [ __ ]
I don't know, bro. It's It's hard, isn't it?
I can do a both score no draw, but
that's just harder to come in and then
the buzz just isn't the same. When you
do a both score, no draw, I find the
buzz just isn't the same.
Does that sound weird or do you
understand what I'm saying? Like when
it's a both teams to score, all they got
to do is score and there's no way of
them [ __ ] you over. Whereas with a
both score, no draw, you can get [ __ ]
over at any minute of the game.
The buzz just doesn't feel the same with
a both score draw because you know it's
a lot harder to come in.
I can't explain it, bro. I'm sure what
I'm saying makes sense.
Yeah, maybe I I could just play roulette
if I wanted to. No, I'm not playing that [ __ ]
Yeah, we're not playing that [ __ ] bro. [ __ ] that. Um,
yeah. I don't know, bro.
I have no idea.
I'm probably just going to do 20 pound, bro. Yeah,
I was thinking of doing a football bet,
but the odds have just got a lot worse.
So, I'm not sure what I'm going to do,
man. because I want to do me. I I prefer
the both teams to score because there's
more of a buzz than the both score no
draw cuz it's more easier to come in.
But the odds of this got so bad I just
don't see the point in even doing it.
I just don't see the point of it.
I was thinking of doing three both teams to score
but I don't see the [ __ ] point.
No, I'm not playing the FB, bro. I lost
50 on it yesterday.
No, I'm not. If I want to If I was to
gamble, bro, I'll just I'll just do it online
if I'm playing roulette. But I'm not
playing that [ __ ] bro. But yeah, I don't Yeah,
just seems to be no way of winning nowadays.
You play fobies, you get [ __ ] over.
You play online, you get [ __ ] over on
dodgy sites. I don't know how people
even win nowadays. I'd love to know how people win.
Yeah. So, I mean, I've not played that
100 to one roulette. I've not played
that. I think I think I have played it
ages and ages and ages ago, but no, bro.
It's not a good idea.
But I would just play online roulette if
I was going to gamble30 to be honest
with you. I'm not playing.
But that's even bad as well. I mean, I I
I haven't been back on that site since
they refused to close my account down.
I can't go back on that site, bro. I I
don't trust it. When as soon as they
started being dodgy about like um the uh
uh the the deposit limits, Yeah. and
closing the account down, I was like,
"Nah, bro. I just I just don't go back to it.
cuz to me that is dodge. How they're
trying to like make excuses why they
can't uh let you put a deposit limit on.
If they can do that, what more can they
do? So that's why I was like, nah, bro.
It was it was only cuz I was busy
yesterday. I just popped into the
bookies. But I don't I don't trust that, bro.
I seriously don't trust that. Yeah, but
what's the chances it's going to win,
bro? Come on. Um
What do you What do you think's worse?
What do you think's worse yet? Online or
these betting shops?
I just can't play. I can't bring myself
to play on that site anymore, bro.
I just can't bring myself to play on that site.
Is there sports on there?
Online is so rigged though.
Yeah, online is so [ __ ] fixed. It's
on It's so fixed online, bro. You know,
you go on the roulette table right now.
Yeah. You'll see 8 11 52. You see all of these numbers.
Yeah, I know, bro. I've seen it. I've
been in it.
But and online's fixed as well. That's the thing.
Online is really really fixed, bro. It's
not It is
You jump on the table right now and
you'll see all of these um numbers
Let me go at it right now. And I I guarantee you,
you will see all of these numbers that
have come out.
I'm so tired, bro. So tired.
Yeah. See, look. You see eight, you see
all of these numbers, but when you
partake on the game, you don't see any of them. Yeah.
Does the [ __ ] doesn't even [ __ ] look
natural on that table?
It don't even look natural, does it? No. Live 14
14 hours ago.
Yeah, I used to like them big sit down ones.
I know the ones you're talking about.
They have them at Aspers as well.
Nah, I'm just going to do a football bet
and that's it, bro. I'm not I'm going to
do a 20 pound football bet
and that's me done, bro. I don't want to
start getting into these [ __ ] shitty
ass machines again, bro. [ __ ] that. Yeah.
What I'm going to do, I reckon.
No more [ __ ] off the LT. That's lovely, isn't it?
Don't know why he got so aggressive just
cuz I called him biased.
Don't know why he started getting the man
cuz I was calling him biased. Strange. Yeah.
Don't think too much into it.
That's how you lose brain damage.
And look, this even this even proves
that they're biased as well. Look,
banks, I will be giving this to the
police. Four thumbs up. Five thumbs up.
Yet they claim they don't like grasses.
If that's not even more evidence that
these people are biased over the virgin
thing, then I don't know what is. I
don't know why he's biased though
because he doesn't like the guy and he
doesn't like cowards.
So, I don't know why he continuously um
defends a virgin. I just don't understand it
and I won't even try to understand it
anymore cuz that's how you lose brain
cells and end up like these people. You
see, when you try to when you try to understand Yeah.
slow people that are uneducated. That's
how you like you you start becoming dumb.
That's how you start, you see.
That's how you start um becoming like these people, you know.
Maybe I'll just put 60 on two teams. [ __ ] those.
Yeah, I'll just put 60 on two teams. [ __ ] it.
You all right, Captain?
Yeah, bro. I done two approaches last
week. Uh, the first time in two months,
bro. I was drinking.
Yeah, it's just the same old [ __ ] bro.
I won't be drinking now until probably,
I don't know, February. I can't be
bothered with it anymore, bro.
I really can't be asked with it. It's
[ __ ] It's boring as [ __ ] bro.
Yeah, I don't I don't do it anymore,
lad. I just went for a game of all year
with someone I knew and that I didn't
even plan to drink and yeah, I just
thought [ __ ] it. We'll see if if if
anything stiffen in 2026
and nothing's stiffening in 2026. So
yeah, I don't know when I'll be out
again, bro. Like that drinking and [ __ ]
long time, bro. I can't be asked with
it. It was giving me mood swings every
day in the tourist for like two weeks
and then it stopped.
>> Yeah, it was really bad, bro.
back when I was going to the dentist and
[ __ ] and then it just stopped.
I just can't I can't The thing is I
can't justify trying again, Notorious. I
can't justify it. Obviously, I was out
and it I didn't you know when I used to
go out I used to plan to go out and I
used to plan to do it. Do you understand
Notorious? But the thing is yeah I can't
I can't bring myself to try anymore bro.
I can't justify it because in my head I
shouldn't have to try and I've already
tried and the thing is Notorious I've
done it. Uh I was out Monday and it just
happened that I was drinking.
Do you understand? I just happened. It
just happened that I was drinking bro.
So I just thought [ __ ] it in it. It's
2026 but I don't I will never go out to
just do it again bro. I shouldn't have
to. There's no reason why I should have
to. I've tried more than enough and
that's that. That's the way I see it.
Simple, bro. So, that's that, lad.
Um, yeah. I've not had a date since
April, Victoria, last year, and I've
been out a lot since last year. It's
dead in this country, bro. It's a waste of time.
I had a really bad hangover from Monday
as well, bro. I thought I was going to
die, bro. I thought I had alcohol poisoning
and I was like, "This is not worth it, bro. Seriously."
So, yeah. I don't really think about it anymore, bro.
Yeah. It's nearly a year. Yeah. It was
but it was on it was during the bank holiday season
because all that happens all all that
will happen notorious is if you go out
or stay Saturday say you go out today
you're going to hear the same [ __ ] hear
the same excuses deal with the same
[ __ ] and get numbers that just lead
you on. There's no difference there.
There's nothing different that's going to happen.
So it's a waste of everyone's time, bro.
And then you just have a you just have a
hangover by the end of it. It's just
never going to change. It will never change,
you know. So,
if I am going to drink again, it will be
I don't know, March, February, March,
bro. It's not going to be anytime soon.
I can't be annoyed with it anymore, bro.
It's boring. It's the same [ __ ]
And do you know what? I don't even find
them attractive anymore, bro. You see
these women and and they've just got the
same look in their eyes. They just all
look stuck up like walking around. They
all look like NPCs.
So they're not even [ __ ] attractive
anymore. They all look the same cuz they
are all the same. But they all look the
same. So I was like, "What the [ __ ] bro?"
So yeah, that's it.
That's the end of that, is it? Yeah.
They're all the same, bro. They're all
bad. Americans, English, they're all
they're all [ __ ]
Simple as that, bro. Like, [ __ ] them. Anyways,
I can't remember the last time I done a
sober approach months ago.
I don't think I could do it again. So, I
probably could, but I I wouldn't want to
because I don't know. You It's just
always the same [ __ ] I'm getting too
old for it now, bro. It's boring.
But people on Reddit, notorious says
that you'll meet people.
Yeah. Well, you're not a woman e. Well,
you're not a woman. Uh, bomb. So, yeah.
Bomb under that account. Self projector.
Boring. We heard all of this in 2025.
That's very, very, very, very boring.
I had to put LT in his place Notorious
about his biasness and then he started
talking about family members. I had to
put him in his place about being biased
and then he started bringing up family
members. The [ __ ] bro?
Yeah. I had to um I had to put him in
his place about biasness.
Sorry, bro. I just don't like biased people.
Then he started getting all Then he then
he started getting rude about it.
So I I I don't think we'll ever know to be honest.
Weird people. And you need to stop that
M stuff. That M [ __ ] is very very boring
now. Really really really really really
boring. You need to stop that. It's so
Like I'm actually pitying someone.
Why don't they just come out with
different things? That's so boring, bro.
So so so so boring.
You know, and I could I'm not explaining
all of this stuff again, bro. Do you
know what I'm saying? I've already
explained all of this many many times
before. You know, you know
that M thing is so boring
and it's so embarrassing because someone
that they're calling a Ma is better
looking than them and had more women
than them. How's that? How does that
work, Notorious? If someone's a m Yeah.
Why are the Why is a M better looking
than you? And why is a M been with more
women than you? Then you must be an
ultra M if you think about these people,
bro. Really, that is so so so boring.
Anyone that puts themselves out there
drinking and got a life is going to deal with someone
uh projecting their insecurities onto
them at least once in their life. That's
going to happen.
That that is literally going to happen.
If someone goes out drinking every week
or they put themselves in situations
where there's [ __ ] they will come
across an insecure
woman that will project their
insecurities onto other just like a a
man will do it. You know, that's just
that's just normal, bro. I mean, look
what happened on the train.
I mean, you know, that that's going to
happen with anyone that actually has a
life. Have you ever have you ever have
you ever have you ever watched these streamers?
You know, have you ever watched these streamers?
You should watch them, bro.
Should watch these streamers, lad. You
should watch these streamers.
Have you watched these Tik Tok streamers
streamers like that?
I got a bit of food stuck in my [ __ ]
gum, you know, bro.
[ __ ] in it.
[ __ ] is that?
Oh, wait. Weight loss.
Yeah, you need to stop that. See, the
thing is, right, yeah, is that these
people claim that they're intelligent,
but they just repeat the same [ __ ] every day.
We don't sew our faces because we're
intelligent, but they just repeat the
same [ __ ] every day.
They're repeating little bastards that
have got no new content. And that's why
we call them disabled.
That's why we say that these people are
disabled. It's not even picking on
people because only disabled people
would sit on the internet for 15 years
regurgitating the same crap every day.
Only disabled people would do that. If
you look at me, I've always come up with
new words, new content, say it for a
month, two months, move on to something
different, or just simply stop saying it.
Like the the the shovel copycat trend,
we don't say that anymore. Taking a baby
away from its mama, we don't because we
come out with new things, new content, new words.
With them, it's just all repeating.
Yeah. repeating bastards. Yeah,
that's making me want to go Manchester, bro.
Every time I see videos of someone in
Manchester, bro, it makes me just want
to go back there.
on a session. I love a Manchester
session, bro. I can't lie. Yeah.
Makes you want to go back up there in it.
That's one thing I might do, you know,
bro. I don't know when.
I just love a piss up there, bro. I
don't know what it is.
Maybe I'll have to set up a little trip
at some point.
[ __ ] no, bro.
Is anyone out? Is anyone out drinking
today? I'm not [ __ ] drinking. [ __ ] that.
Am I fat drinking? Nah. No.
No. No. No. No.
So, you think it's rigged then? The
online roulette, Chica.
Do you think it's ultra rigged?
It's [ __ ] rigged as [ __ ]
It is, man.
So, you can't even win money anymore to
get escorts. If you wanted to have like
sex or like a [ __ ] you couldn't even
do that anymore.
It's a country designed to [ __ ] you over
in every way.
This is a country designed to [ __ ] you
over, bro. People don't even realize it.
Yeah. I don't use escorts, bro. I don't
use I don't do nothing. [ __ ] that.
I just want a good movie in a cinema, bro. Uh, nothing's out.
Nothing's out, bro. So,
anyways, I'm going in a minute cuz I got
stuff to do today. So, yeah.
Nope. Not even playing Lego. I'm going out today.
got stuff to do.
I haven't touched the Lego actually.
I haven't been back on it. I had an
early night yesterday. I was so tired. Really? Yeah.
Oh, this guy made me laugh. You know,
the UK biggest nons with these community
posts. I was like,
he's not even worth even responding to.
Not even worth responding to, bro.
Whoever that is, I was like, "What the [ __ ] bro?
I went on Skint Boy channel, the Skint Virgin.
Um, and there's an account called Do You. Yeah.
And the fact that it got 19 thumbs up as
well. Crazy, bro.
Look at all the [ __ ] I caused, bro.
Like, look at all I don't know why L I
don't know why LT got so aggressive.
All cuz I stated the fact that he was being biased.
Don't know why he had to get so
aggressive. He's not the only one. JF
does it. They just like to defend a
virgin and ignore evidence. A lot of
people on here do it. I don't know what why
why you getting why you getting assy.
I don't know why he was getting sassy, bro.
Oh, I'm going to have a bath today. That
reminds me. Yeah, I'm going to have a
bath today. Actually,
all I said is, "Why are you being biased
defending your boyfriend?" That's all I asked.
That's all I asked. You know, don't have
to be Don't have to start talking about family members
because because you know I'm right as
well. Don't [ __ ] interrupt me every
time I'm calling him a [ __ ] virgin
about this [ __ ] girlfriend. I'll talk
about it as much as I [ __ ] want. We
don't see you saying anything when he's calling me.
So that's what my point was. Why did it
have to turn into to such a big thing?
[ __ ] the [ __ ] And like I was saying
yesterday, [ __ ] the virgin thing, bro.
They've done it with money as well.
They've done it with money. They've done
it with police. So it's not just one
thing. Yeah. How much How many times
this guy state that he doesn't like
grasses? Yeah. I've not seen him call
these grasses grasses
or or has he, bro? You know, like it's
it's it's like
a lot of people on here they they
reason why they take this guy's side is
because they're ugly like him. So when
he's got a channel obsessed with me,
obviously they're ugly like him. So they
see they see themselves um in him and
that's why they all like go for me
because obviously you're better looking
than these people and the people that
are going for you are [ __ ] ugly and
he's ugly as well. So you know it it
naturally they will take his side because
yeah they just don't like anyone better
than them on this community. That's
that's that bro. Anyone that's got hope
unlike that's that's what it is
cuz let's be let's face it here right?
No offense, but most of the people right
that go on LJ J's channel, they are
rejects to society. Like, they don't
even fit into society, bro. Like, that's
that's why they're obviously on here
every day calling people that they don't
know, ain't got a life because they're
rejects to society. We all know that.
So, I mean, anyone that's like, yeah,
better than them, um, they turn their
nose up because they're all, all of
these people that do this on here and
talk to each other, they literally are
all the same. Why do you think they
don't bother me?
Cuz, think about it, bro. Jo, fat ugly
bastard. Large a fat ugly bastard.
Like, we can go on and on and on and on
and on. So, you know, that's why it's
laughable, bro. It's just all laughable. Um, yeah,
I might bring my tracksuit today and
have a little um
shower. Have a bath. Bring my tracksuit
and have a bath in my tracksuit, I reckon. Yeah.
But you get what I mean, is it?
Well, I was going to do I remember this
Rangers, lad. He used to be all right,
man. I remember you from years ago, but
then you stopped coming on my channel. I
was going to do Enfield Town slow and
Darlington, but I bro the odds have got
so bad on the football. I don't even see
the point in doing them now, man. Cuz
personally, yeah, I don't like doing
more than two teams. And if I put 50 60
pound on two teams, it's like 130, 140 back.
And I personally don't like doing more
than two teams cuz I always feel like
you get [ __ ] over. And now I was
thinking, oh, I could put 150 on two
teams, but if I put 150 on two teams,
it's 392 back.
So, the odds are really bad.
The odds are really bad, bro.
The odds are bad, man.
What about you? What are you doing?
And we both scor. I just don't get the same buzz.
Do a double and over.
Yeah, that that could work, bro. That
could work. Yeah, cuz the south the
south game. Yeah. Do a double and over.
So that's like So any more than two
goals, isn't it?
So is that any more than two goals or
any more than three goals? I'm pretty sure it's
more than two goals, isn't it?
Yeah, I've been playing. Yeah, three
goals. Okay. Yeah, it's three goals.
Yeah. Yeah, I could do that. Yeah.
One second. Let me see the odds.
I've been playing roulette a lot. Um,
Rangers, man. I've had to quit it.
It's so [ __ ] fixed, man. Online. It's
so fixed. Roulette on online is so
fixed, bro. And the bookies, you just
can't seem to win anymore. Okay,
I only bet the National Leagues, by the way.
Right. Let's see. Okay. So,
right. Match over. Okay. So, over 2.7.
So, over 2.5 4 to 7. [ __ ] bro.
I don't know how people win on it. I
never win, bro. On on roulette.
And you know what? Yeah. This site.
Yeah, I tried to put a deposit limit on
and they were trying to go me to keep
playing and ever since they've done
that, I've not gone back on the site.
I've said, "Oh, like can you close my
countdown for like a month?" They said,
"Oh, we have to we have to put it to
another department." 3 weeks later,
they've still not closed my countdown.
So, I was like, "Okay, let me try and
put put a deposit limit on." And they
was like, "Oh, well, um, what if you
want to play more? You know, is that a
good idea?" So, since they've tried go
to me, I don't trust them anymore.
Simple. I've not gone back on the site
since they've tried going me into um
going me into um keep going basically. I
I trusted it since then. Right.
Yeah. So over
right. So that's
the same odds that both teams to score.
Yeah, I was doing like 120 pound spins.
I play different. I will keep doubling
it. So say I put 150, I'll just double
and double and double until obviously I hitting it.
Yeah, they're [ __ ] odds. Just that's
what I'm trying to say to you. The odds
have got worse, lad.
Yeah, I was I was thinking of reporting
them to trading standards because
maybe I just thought, "Oh, maybe I'm
just being a sore loser, but no, it's
that's got to definitely be rigged
because they shouldn't be saying that to
you." I've got the exact thing that
they've said, bro. One second. I'll tell
you the exact thing. I was going to do a
video um about this
um one sec. [ __ ] sake, bro.
One second, lad. Yo,
I think it's not yo
yo. Echo, where the [ __ ] is the other
Streamyard? Hold on.
Where's the other stream?
Echoing like mad.
Yeah, sorry about that. Yeah, so B. No, still echoing.
Why the [ __ ] does this keep echoing?
There's no other stream or tab. What the [ __ ] bro? Stream.
Oh, maybe here.
Yo, still doing it. Yeah.
All right, let's try again.
Yo yo. Oh, for [ __ ] sake. Why is it
still doing this, bro?
[ __ ] sake. Can you still hear me?
[ __ ] bastard, bro.
Yeah. Yeah. Okay. So, even though it's
echoing, I'm just going to tell you what
they've said. One second. Let me I'll
pull up exactly what they've said. And
after this I didn't play again. I don't
think I didn't know.
Okay. So, where is it?
Cuz they said it in a specific way.
Okay. My eyesight's getting worse. It's
called Brick Casino. So, I said to them,
"Can you put a deposit limit on my account?"
Oh, one second. Hello, Peter. Can you
put a deposit limit on my account? And
then they're like, are you sure such
boundaries are necessary? It will take
time to remove the limit afterwards.
What if you want to play more? Now, that's dodgy.
At the end of the day, bro, they
shouldn't be asking you that. You know,
if you want to do responsible gambling,
they should either close my account
down, which I asked for for like a
month. I decided just shut it down for a
month. And then they then then I was
like, "Okay, let me put the positive
on." And then they're trying to entice
me to play more. So,
it's pretty obvious that they can rig
the roulette table if they're if they're
doing dodgy stuff like that.
So, you know, I just didn't didn't
bother after that. But yeah.
Yeah, I will be, bro. I will be.
I'll probably do it later.
You can't put the limit on yourself.
That's the whole point. You can't time
your account out or put the limit on yourself.
That's the whole point of it. It's not a UK site.
It's not a UK site, bro. That's the whole point, you know.
Yeah. There we go. Now it stopped echoing.
It's not a UK site, lad.
No, it's not a UK site.
No, it's not. No, you can't type. You
can't do it yourself. I think that over
2.5 goals is solid on three games, bro.
I reckon on three games, three or four
games, that's solid. What you've just
said there, bro. I reckon you got a good
chance with three or four games. Over 2.5.
I reckon that's got a good chance with
three or four games, bro. In the National League.
I reckon I reckon that's got a chance, bro.
On about four games. what you've just
said. Darlington, Enfield Town, slow and dagen red.
No, it won't pay out huge. Well, on the
double, it's it's 210.
Yeah, I'm going to do Darlington
and um Enfield,
right? Let's see the odds for that.
Let me see.
Well, it's not A treble is not going to
be much though, is it?
A treble is not going to be a treble
won't be much cuz if two's 217
that was 80 pound.
No, it needs to be over. You know, it
needs to be over two. It needs to be three goals.
Yeah, your bet's [ __ ] then. Yeah,
obviously. Well, obviously that's the
whole point of it.
Nah, I don't think I'm going to even
bother gambling today, bro. [ __ ] it. I
can't be asked.
I can't be [ __ ] lad. I'm just going
to go somewhere, have a bath, get in my
tracksuit, and just chill.
Nah, I don't think I'm going to bother.
I could have done with a bath yesterday.
I was so cold. Yeah,
I don't know how you can win anymore
Rangers. I really don't know how people
win gambling anymore on anything football.
I really don't know, bro. I really don't know.
Maybe I'll just do a 30 football bet in it.
I think I'm going to put 30. Yeah. On.
I might just put 30 pound on just a
[ __ ] I might just put 30 pound on
five of them, bro. [ __ ] it.
Well, bless you then, JNA. If you if you
go on the lottery, bless you.
I'm worse than [ __ ] When was the last
time [ __ ] was on YouTube, bro?
When was the last time [ __ ] was on
YouTube? I mean, I'm going out in a
minute. I need to leave soon. So, I'm
doing stuff today.
Yeah, I'll be leaving in about 5 minutes.
I'm gone, bro. When was the last time
[ __ ] was on YouTube, bro? Come on. Yeah.
[ __ ] what? Two months
maybe, bro. But the online roulette is
that is definitely fixed, bro. The
online roulette is definitely fixed.
That online roulette is definitely
fixed, bro. Because there's no way, bro,
that online roulette is definitely fixed
on this site, bro. What the [ __ ] man?
I'll never play on that site again after that.
You know, when you think about it,
gambling is such a waste of time, is it?
If you actually think about it, it
really is such a waste of time.
It really is a waste of time, isn't it?
Waste of energy, waste of mood swings,
just it's just a waste of everything,
isn't it? Really, if you actually think
about it, you need to stop using that
word tragic, bro. It's really boring.
I can tell you definitely from the
levery side, the bongo side of YouTube.
You need to stop using that word. It's
so boring, bro. And you're just talking
about your [ __ ] selves every day.
I can't believe in 2026 you're still
talking about yourselves.
Well, I think it is, bro. But
it's all about opinion, isn't it?
You need to stop that word. That's so boring.
[ __ ] boring. You call, this is what
makes me laugh. Yeah. With a with a lot
of use on here. Yeah. Is that you,
you call people disabled. Yeah. But yet
you are the ones that on here 15 for 15
years every day repeating the same [ __ ]
Repeating exactly the same [ __ ] for 15
years. And you call other people
disabled. Like you you really I don't
even you know what? I I don't even think
I don't even think you really know that
you're talking about yourselves.
I think it's part of like what whatever
disability that you've got, you don't
even realize that you're actually
talking about yourselves.
It's got to be something like that, bro.
That's why I don't judge because Yeah,
I'm on about you self projectors. Why
are you still using the word tragic,
bro? You're tragic. Anyone that goes on
LJ's [ __ ] channel are tragic.
Sad, ugly, fat people that ain't got no
life sat on YouTube 24/7. What the [ __ ]
bro? How Who are you to judge anyone?
Who are you to try to judge anyone's
life? I'm on about you. It's not what
I'm on about. I'm on about you, bro. You people.
It's a madness, bro.
Switch up the content. Switch up the
words, man. Come on.
No, I can't go on that channel, bro. I
get brain damage. I don't know how you
can go on that labyrin channel, Rangers.
I remember you from years ago. Uh,
Rangers, years and years ago, man. I
don't know how you can go on that
channel, bro. I mean, even with even
even with L even with LT, I started
getting brain damaged.
Even even even when I like I I find even
when I talk to him, I start getting I
start losing brain cells, bro.
Yeah, you can go on whose channel you
want, bro. I don't I I don't
discriminate, bro. But you do what you want, bro.
I know there's a few normal people on
here, you know, like how hard can it be
and Charlie and Ben and you and you know,
but uh there were a lot of retards on
this community, bro.
Hate hate to say it.
Yeah, even LT makes me lose brain. He
makes me lose brain cells sometimes,
bro. I can't I can't even with him, bro.
I can't even with him.
The [ __ ] was that email all about, bro?
I don't even know what that email [ __ ]
did that have to do with anything. Mad,
mad, mad, mad, mad, mad.
I don't know. I All I asked him is why
is he taking sides? because he doesn't
like this guy. He says that he doesn't
like this guy yet. He says he doesn't
like grasses and he's the biggest grass.
He's the biggest coward. He doesn't like
him more than me. But then he's fast
enough to to to rescue him like Superman
whenever I I call him a virgin. It's so weird.
And he's not saying what's right because
what right what is right is what I've
shown. So don't even try to use that excuse.
claims he doesn't like grasses. When
have we ever seen this guy call this guy a grass?
No, instead they get thumbs up. I don't
know why they do it and I don't know why
someone like him does it as well.
You know, it's weird. It's so strange,
bro. So strange.
Yeah. See you later, bro. See you later, man.
I haven't even seen anything good in the
cinema to be fair.
Then again, I only like horror films.
Nah, no thanks, bro. I don't want to
meet L's. He's a [ __ ]
Yeah, they like taking sides. I don't
know why they don't just not say nothing.
You know what I'm saying? I don't know.
Um, Smash, why they don't just say
nothing. Someone calls me a virgin. I
call them a virgin. Let's just not say
anything about anything.
But no, it doesn't quite go down like
that, does it? You call someone a
virgin, they get rescued like super they
get rescued by Superman.
They're very very touchy, you know? They
get very very very touchy about someone, you know. [ __ ] weird. Mama M.
I'm actually getting hungry now.
Well, anyways, I'm off. Yeah, so I'll
see you later. Peace.