All right with you, Virgin.
Is that okay with you, Virgin C?
Oh, I thought they accepted another
follow. Good thing they didn't. Yeah.
Is it Saturday today? I keep thinking
it's Friday and then yesterday I thought
it was Thursday when it actually was Friday.
You just never know, do you? Let's
see about today.
How many subs have I got?
I'm going to put my link on this channel again
in case people don't know it. They don't
know. They'll know now. Love people
[ __ ] subscribing to the [ __ ]
Why is there no one come on here?
I won my football bet, by the way. Don't
know about you people. [gasps]
Make sure I'm putting this right channel on.
Yeah, I won my football bet.
[ __ ] ace, bro. Ace.
I was thinking, "Oh, I hope one day I
get three." I got five. So, even better.
Yeah, even better.
Oh, it went in. It went instantly as well.
Yeah, that was ace, bro. That football
bet was sick, man.
Oh, it's so fixed that roulette, bro.
Because how can you do five teams on a
football? Yeah. And you've won. Yeah.
And then on roulette, you seem to never
win. What's the chances of that, huh?
Oh, that's not bad. Then at least you
get your money instant with this site.
Not going to say what site it is. It's a
UK regulated site, but not going to say
which one it is.
What's the day? So, Sunday, tomorrow. Yeah.
Yeah, they've got fish and frenzy
roulette on this site, but I was like, nah,
I ain't playing that [ __ ]
Yeah. Yeah. When he [ __ ] pays the [ __ ] thing. Yeah, man.
Do you know I felt like going Manchester
today, bro. I'm not even joking.
It put me in even more of a mood to when
I won the football bet, but I ain't
going out generally, bro. That's a waste
of money. [ __ ] that [ __ ] [ __ ] going
out January, bro. [ __ ] that.
Absolutely [ __ ] that, bro.
Maybe mid-March. I don't know,
bro. [ __ ] that. It's dead, bro. I can go
out today if I wanted to.
It's dead. It's literally pointless,
bro. Especially in January. It's so pointless.
I didn't even plan to go out on Monday.
It just escalated.
Shut up you two face little [ __ ]
[ __ ] Don't come on my channel asking me
questions when I've seen you slagging me
off behind my back. You little wanker.
And I've seen you on Ed Matthews channel
as well. The only waster is you little cell.
I done a football bet. I won a football
bet. I done five teams today and they
all come in.
I literally won a football bet today. I won £223.
Don't know what you're talking about,
mate. I done a football bet and I won five teams.
I done a football bet. I put 20 on five teams, mate.
So yeah, you were talking to my sister
B. You don't speak to any members of my
family and you don't bother no one. Go
seek attention somewhere else, you sad,
fat, ugly bastard. little low life. See
you later. And yeah, I done five I done
five teams today and I won. I tell you
the teams I done. I done Enfield Town,
Ti, Slow Town,
uh I done Charlie FC, I done Western
Super May, and I done Lemington. And
they all come in. They all come in.
I got the bet right here, mate. I done
it online. Got the bet right here, mate. Yeah.
You know, I want my football bet today.
I done I done five teams.
I think three of them was a both score
low draw though but hindsight in it. I
was happy with the 223 pound.
I don't know why you mentioning family
members. Bro, that doesn't bother me.
It really really doesn't bother me, bro.
You're just you're just bothering yourself.
No. And on five teams.
Oh, three of them was a Please don't
tell me three of them was
SL versus It was five.
Oh, three of them was as well.
Endfield. Oh, man. Oh, well.
Yeah, three of them was both scor as well,
but I would have never done that. So,
it's too risky them bets.
Yeah, I was just happy with the 223.
No, I done Enfield Town versus Ti United
and I done slow town FC versus
Tombbridge. Then I charlie FC versus
Darlington. Western Super Mayor versus
Horn Church and Lemonton versus Carzan
Aston FC. That's five teams alone.
I only put 20 pound on it, but put 223
pound back. Sorted it.
I was happy with that to be honest. Yeah,
spent some money today as well.
See you later, V. You're not getting
attention. Don't even waste your time
coming on this channel, bro. You're not
getting a reaction out of me. So, yeah.
Dad bastard. Fat ugly virgin.
See you later.
Oh, just got a nudge. Low and No, it was notification. Yeah.
I can't believe these people are still
doing this in 2026, bro. I don't even
react to them anymore. These [ __ ]
clowns. Cuz I know what they are and I
know what they're about. So that's why
they don't bother me, bro. like they
might do c they might do other people
because they're just self projectors
so they don't bother me. We all know
that they're fat. We all know they're
ugly. We all know they're on YouTube
24/7. And in my opinion, bro, that
people like that can't judge no one.
I'm sorry to say, bro, but
Chase, that's the story of your life,
bro. I've been in your I've been in your
city multiple times and you've kept your
mouth shut just like your boyfriend
which is probably probably why you get
on so well you Welsh little bog you
[ __ ] you know what's so mad is bro
you you didn't even let anyone know when
you was in London cuz you're a [ __ ] bro
that's why you're a [ __ ] and the only
time you went to the train station is
you when you knew damn well
that I wasn't even coming
let me ask you a question now You still
got a patchy ass beard.
We all knew you couldn't grow a beard.
Did that do me, mate. We all knew you
could never grow a beard fully.
You're in my Weather Spoons right now. I
know you [ __ ] well. Ain't do a video
right now. Show me you're in that
Weather Spoons and I will literally come
right now, mate.
No, bro. I used to speak to him on kick.
I knew him before anyone.
I would [ __ ] knock two shades of [ __ ]
out of you, bro. It wouldn't even It's
not even a joke.
Seriously, I need to be careful
actually, bro. What the [ __ ] You know,
that's another thing.
Yeah, that's another thing, bro.
That's another thing. We've got glasses
on this community.
Oh [ __ ] that's another thing I forgot about that.
That Peter Files is a mega mega grass.
Um, whoever it is.
Um, yeah, I think I did mention it
yesterday, didn't I? Yeah, he's another
he's another grass.
He's a dirty dirty grass, bro. That um Peter Files.
Yeah, I had to go to the police thing. I
had to go to the police station
yesterday and they were asking me a
bunch of questions over that kitty thing, Grezy.
That uh you know that kitty stream and I
thought, "Oh, maybe they're the ones
that reported me and that." No, it's
that Peter Fowls. He's a grass, bro.
Proper proper grass.
Yeah, they're all sell projectors on
here, slap, bro. They're no different. I
won a football bet, Greavesy. I won 223
off 20 pound. It's quite good, man. Is
it quite good?
Yeah, that Peter fight foul is a grass, bro.
Yeah, proper proper grass. The one that records everything.
a little grass, bro. Yeah.
No, I didn't get arrested or anything,
but I still had to go down there and [ __ ] So,
yeah, I done five both teams to score.
No, I don't I on five teams.
I won for five teams
cuz you remember all that mad stuff I
said in November about [ __ ] USA easy
and stuff and when I was arguing with
Kitty. Yeah, I did win when I was
arguing with Kitty. Obviously the idiot
recorded it all
cuz it wouldn't have been Kitty and that
and that Lex. Do you remember that Lex?
the one on Tik Tok and it wouldn't have
been them that done it. So, it was
obviously him. He's a grass, bro.
No, he's a dirty grass.
No, Kitty, the one the one that blocked
me on the on the on the on the Tik Tok.
Yeah, they were asking me a bunch of
questions like, "Oh, why did you say
this? Why did you Yeah, bro.
They didn't arrest me or anything, but
they said that I had to go there." Yeah,
he's a grass, bro. That um Peter fight
fouls. He's a He's a loser, bro.
Proper proper loser.
Proper freak, bro.
No, it wasn't. It was November.
Yeah, I done five teams and they and
they all won.
Yeah, I had macaroni cheese today.
Yeah. Loads of grasses on this
community, bro. Loads of grasses.
Yeah, on five teams 223 off20.
I bought some t-shirts today, Grezy.
I bought a Spider-Man one. And I bought
a a B a Spider-Man one and a um
a Spider-Man one. And what was the other
one? A Simpsons one cuz Yeah, I'm kind
of running out of t-shirts.
I've had more Mrs. than you, Chase.
You're you're you're Bro, you can't even
grow a beard, bro. You've got patchy
hair in your face.
You've got patchy hair in your face.
Shut up, bro. [snorts] Stop trying to
talk about other people, you self
projector. Like I said, let me know when
you're whenever you're in London again,
bro. Whenever you're in London again,
just let me know. Simple as that. That's it. Simple. Uh,
you ain't even got a girlfriend. And
unlike your friend, I don't I don't
target disabled women unlike your
friend. Same can't be said about your
friend. I've never targeted women with disabilities.
Nope. Haven't gained any weight. All of
my t-shirts are very, very, very old.
Nope. Here comes another self projector.
Uh cuz they took the house back.
Nope. Nothing to do with t-shirts not
fitting. Another self projector. Do you
self projectors not get bored
in 2026? Yeah. I'm going to do nothing
because you're not in no op.
Yeah. Is that Bro, listen. You're not in
no op. You're in Wales by yourself doing
nothing. We've seen your fat fingers.
No, bro. You're talking about yourself.
Anyways, moving on. Um,
so no. Yeah.
Yeah. people in this community like LT.
I don't. See you later, self projector.
Yeah, that's you, bro. You live with
your nanny, bro. You live with your
stinky nan. Tell everybody that you live
with your stinky nan. I'd rather live
with my mom than live in a cancel bed
sit with a woman that's got
disabilities, but that's just me. Anyways,
yeah, at least I don't live with my
nanny like you. You sad bastard.
Um, I've already ate.
Yeah. Tell your boyfriend. By the way,
the dentist is on the NHS, so you don't
actually have to pay. So, there's no uh
there's no excuse for having bad teeth.
There's no excuse for having missing
teeth, you [ __ ] [ __ ] Tell your
boyfriend that, by the way, as well.
I've done a video about this. So, I
haven't uploaded it yet. There's no
reason to walk around with missing teeth
looking like a [ __ ] [ __ ] when you
can literally get dentist on NHS.
>> Yeah. Report that back to your boyfriend.
Um Yeah, bro.
Just check the
No, it never.
I've got it right here, bro.
I bet on Lad Brooks. I got the bet right here.
Probably want to reuse that site again
to be honest. Oh, actually they can't do anything.
No, definitely definitely 223. We got it
right here, man.
And that's what they paid me. So one second.
Let me get this up.
I can't believe this chase guy is giving
it the big and he's another coward, bro.
He's another coward, bro.
No, it didn't, mate. It's right there.
Okay, let me put it up on my uh thing actually.
Oh, I'm not showing you nothing.
Bye-bye. Go away. You sad bastard.
Another fat virgin. Oh, I just clocked
that was him.
You people are such wasters, bro. You
people on here are real real wasters.
Honestly, you are actual wasters.
Like I was actually saying to Laney,
yeah, in 2026, yeah, I I actually
thought these people were actually going
to change on this community, Greavvesy.
I Bro, I was actually giving them the
benefit of the doubt,
but they're they haven't changed, bro, have they?
They're rejects by society. Not everyone
on here. Some people on here is all
right, obviously, but you know what I
mean. They're proper proper like outcasts.
Like, I think that's that's the word to
to to to put him, bro. it.
Yeah, I got some mouthwash today, some
toothpaste, some t-shirts.
They're proper They're proper proper
wasters, aren't they?
Ain't it, bro?
I've never met
I've never come across such wasters in
my life, bro. I'm not even joking. I've
never ever in my life, bro. Seriously. Such wasters. Just madness.
But yeah, I got five teams. I always
said I wanted three teams, but I got
five teams. Yeah, Greavves. I got a
Spider-Man t-shirt. I got a Spider-Man
t-shirt and I got a Bot Simpson t-shirt.
It cost me [ __ ] £26.
Yeah, I done five teams and I won £223 of 20.
I got some mouthwash and [ __ ]
toothpaste today, so I probably spent
about [ __ ] £50.
Yeah, Bart Simpson. Yeah. Well,
obviously it's adults. It's for adults.
I can show you when they come. Yeah.
Yeah. Five teams. Both teams to score.
Yeah, when they come I'll show you.
cuz I didn't I was running out of
t-shirts. They're all [ __ ] old and
[ __ ] I've got designer clothes. I've
got jeans. I got trainers. But I don't
really have any wear and about t-shirts.
Yeah, bro. They're trying to They're
trying to make up, bro. Don't even call
them trolls, bro. They're just [ __ ]
idiots. That's what they are, bro.
They're just idiots.
They're just wasters. They're not even
trolls, bro. They're just utter wasters.
[snorts] And now they're trying to say
that I haven't won the bet now. They're
[ __ ] idiots. Sad sad bastards, bro.
They are sad, aren't they, lad?
Yeah. Yeah. I got a Bart Simpson one and
a Spider-Man one
cuz I didn't really have about t-shirts
greasy. So, I thought buy a couple
t-shirts in it.
Got socks, got boxes, got designer
clothes. I love wearing about t-shirts.
Oh, you know the funny thing is [ __ ]
Yeah. Have you seen what these people
look like? Every single time they've
shown their faces as well. That's why
they don't bother me. You know these
people that do this? Yeah. They they
don't bother me because you know when
you when you see what they look like.
Yeah. Either they show their faces now
or they get exposed later on. Have you
seen actually what these people look like, bro?
That's why they don't get me angry, bro.
Cuz I know it. I know it's I know it's self- projection.
I know. I just know it's self projection
with them, bro. That's why they don't
bother me. See you later. Bye-bye. Yeah.
And I'm I'm not going out though, Slot
Maker. I'm not going out in January even
though I went out last Monday.
No, but it's not just him, bro. Bro,
bro, it's not just him. Yeah, it's it's
it's it's not just him, bro. It's Nonss.
It's LJ. It's Bomb. It's Pat. It's a lot
of these people, bro. It's a lot of them. Um,
it's a lot of them, bro. It's a lot of them.
And there's other people as well. You
need to see what these people look like,
the people that are doing this. And
then, like I said many times before, you
find your answer very quickly on why
they do what they do. It's just
self-reflection with them, bro.
So, that's why I just laugh at them. You
got someone that's got missing teeth.
How does someone have missing teeth when
they get literally dental care on the
NHS? I went to my last dentist
appointment on Thursday. Yeah. Which was
two days ago, and I got a crown and that
was it. I went to three dentist
appointments, all free of charge. So,
what's what why I don't understand why
these people have bad teeth? There's
about three people in here that's got
bad teeth, bro. Yeah.
Why have they got bad teeth, bro?
How have they got bad teeth when
you know you get through uh dental care.
Do you want to see some some some stuff
I bought today? Greasy.
Yeah, but these people don't work. Nons doesn't work.
Doesn't work. Maveli doesn't work. These
people don't work.
Yeah, but these people don't work. If
people worked, then I could understand,
oh, they've got to pay hundreds out.
They might not have the money, but these
people get it for free. These free [clears throat]
That's the funny thing about it. They
actually get it for free. So yeah, it
makes you laugh, doesn't it, bro? It
really does make you laugh
when these are the kind of people that
are trying to call you when they're
walking around with [ __ ] missing
teeth, gaps between their front teeth.
And these are the and these are the
people that are trying to call you.
Yeah. Okay, bro. That's the way you got
to look at it and laugh at it, bro.
No, but you get treatment so your
[ __ ] teeth don't fall out in the first place.
You know, you you you do so your teeth
don't fall out. I mean, if they went to
the dentist in the first place, their
teeth wouldn't their teeth wouldn't be like that,
you know? Simple as that. They're
missing teeth because they don't look
after their teeth.
Simple as that, bro. If you go to a dentist,
they they'll sort you out to the point
where you it would never happen if you actually went
How the How Okay, ask okay, ask yourself
this question. How are you missing front
teeth at 30 years of age?
Think of it. How are you missing front
teeth at 30 years of age? What's What's
the reason for that, bro?
Cuz that doesn't make I've got one tooth
that they took out from the back right
at the back and I'm 28 and that's the
first tooth that's ever been took out
right at the back. So, how are you 30
with missing front teeth? How how does that happen?
That doesn't make sense, bro. Obviously
people get feelings people, you know,
obviously that happens, you know, but
people don't just start losing teeth,
bro, at 30 years of age.
I don't know who that is. Anyways,
I'll show you what I got today if you want. Yeah,
I'll show you what I got.
I've been going to the same dentist
since I was a child. Look, I tell you
what I got today. Look.
Now, you want to see? Look, I got this mouthwash.
I got this mouthwash. I got this
toothpaste and that toothpaste.
There you go.
That's how I take it serious now, you
know. Simple as that. I don't drink as much Coke
and I brush my teeth three times a day
minimum. So, you know,
look, I slept with Oh, I didn't show you
the toy, did I? Grizzy, one second.
I didn't show you the toy.
Oh, I didn't show you. He I won him. I
slept with him yesterday. He was kind of
beat up. So, what are you doing? Go back
to bed, silly. Yeah, I want him on the claw machine.
He was a [ __ ] together. Yeah.
Yeah. He's His name's Crash.
Yeah, his name's Crash. Yeah.
Yeah. So, I got uh [snorts]
I'll show you my t-shirts when they come
greasy. Like I was saying, I haven't got
many t-shirts just to wear about. I got
jeans, I've got jumpers, I've got
designer stuff, but I don't really have many t-shirts.
They're all very very old and faded and that
to the point where they're just not wearable anymore
cuz they're so [ __ ] old. So yeah,
I just got Spider-Man one and a B one.
It's good, isn't it?
Yeah, they're just casual t-shirts to
sleep in and just quickly go out in. I
mean, the Spider-Man one you can go out
in that, but I wouldn't go on a night
out with it.
Yeah, they're just old.
They're very old, isn't it? The
materials done in on him. You know what
I mean, Greavvesy?
The materials done in on him.
They weren't cheap as well. One of them
was 14 pound Grezy the t-shirt. Yeah, 145.
And to me, that ain't cheap for just a graphic t-shirt, is it? Yeah,
that's not cheap in my book. Not for
obviously you expect it from All Saints
that I don't think that's cheap, bro.
What the [ __ ] £15 a t-shirt, bro. It's
[ __ ] It's not really cheap, is it? So,
I'll show you, man.
These are the ones I've got.
I mean, look, I've got a couple. These
are all I've got. Look,
a couple of t-shirts, bro. What the
[ __ ] So, I had to buy some new ones. I
still got my basketball shorts and that.
I need to fold them up.
Yeah, they're just not as Yeah, bro.
Nice 223 pound win is it from 20.
They had a fish and frenzy roulette
greasy. I said, "Should I go in it?" I
was like, "Nah, nah."
Yeah, the basketball shorts are fine.
You can basketball shorts last forever,
but these t-shirts are very old, bro.
I don't really have many t-shirts, but I
had to buy some new ones.
The basketball shorts, they last
forever, man. They last at least 5 years.
I've got a couple of t-shirt.
I'm going to chuck them. I think these ones. Yeah.
Got one. Two. I only got about four
four good t-shirts. Maybe
got brand new trainers and brand new
jeans, but just not t-shirts.
Maybe I might get a new Lego set.
Saying that I haven't completed this one yet.
>> Oh, [ __ ] Just a patience, man.
I just haven't had the [ __ ] patience
for the [ __ ] thing. I need to do this though.
I'm stuck at this part here. Look, I I
can't get over this. Look, Grezy.
I can't get over this.
What the [ __ ]
Look, I want to get the Georgia set, but it's £120.
Maybe I'll get in two weeks. I don't
know. I do need to try to build this,
bro. This is hard though, man.
Maybe I'll spend some of the winners on
this on another set,
bro. I don't know. I'm stuck at this bit here.
Who really has the patience for this
[ __ ] you know? Bro, who actually has
the patience for this bollocks? At >> [snorts]
>> least LT stopped emailing me. I don't
need to go back and forth. I've said
what I've had to say in it.
Isn't that right? I've said what I've
had to say. So,
I think you're a biased [ __ ] and that's it.
What is that one there?
I don't know about that. All I know is he's biased.
He was saying about that whole USA easy
thing and I'm thinking, bro, you know
when you're writing this stuff, you're
writing it to me, not anyone on YouTube,
you're writing this to me. You're
writing to someone that knows the truth.
You're writing to someone that knows the whole story.
So, I mean, it doesn't make any sense.
which are writing to me when I literally
know exactly what's happened from start
to finish and I know things that you
don't know. So, I mean, who are you
trying to fool, bro? Me. Someone that
knows knows it all.
Why are you going to even try that with
me, bro? When I literally know the whole
story of that [ __ ] stupid idiot.
It's just biased, isn't it?
How do you do?
Oh, that might be the one. But no, it
can't be the one because it's No.
Oh, here we go. Yes, he has. Greedy. We
got it. He has.
He has. We got it. Nope. I'm never
uploading approaches on this channel.
I've got approaches on my other channel.
I'm not I'm not approaching again. Oh god.
Right. I got that part.
Do you reckon I can complete this
greasy? I reckon I can complete it.
No, it's not a gambling channel.
I don't do approaches anymore.
Approach coach. I don't do them anymore.
Where is this [ __ ] thing that splits open, bro?
I wonder what happened to Monty.
Could be in prison for all we know. Yeah.
Do you think LT is biased approach coach?
Yeah, he is biased, bro. Why? Why? Why
is he biased against Peter Belly? Why?
Why are you biased against Peter Belly?
Well, I don't understand why he actually
is biased. I don't really understand why he is.
So someone's allowed to call me a virgin
when I prove they've had sex.
But then when I call him a virgin, oh we
it's World War [ __ ] free. And also
why is it then and then he says that he
hates grasses. Yeah. And then what?
Because I said that he's biased
and then and then he says that he hates
grasses. And then he says he hates
grasses. Yeah. But then when [ __ ]
other people grass that's completely
fine. when other people's talking about
grass, everyone praises them. But this
is what what he don't understand. Yeah.
He doesn't He says that he doesn't like
biased people. So why is he being biased
himself? He literally says he does not
like biased people. Oh, I've been to
Scotland. People pretend it never
happened. So why are you being biased
yourself then? If you don't like biased
people, why are you being biased yourself?
This doesn't make sense, bro. That that
guy does not make no sense. Why are you
being biased yourself?
You've been biased with the money as well.
Yeah, they saw No, they saw the [ __ ]
video. They saw me in bed naked with
women and they've seen women admitted to
sleeping with me. I mean, what what more
proof do you want? And also with money,
they're biased with money as well
because when I've shown money, they made
different excuses. Oh, you need to show
the same amount of money again when I've
literally put the money in the bank. So
why is he being biased to someone that
he had a problem with? It doesn't make sense,
you know? So you so it's it's okay for
someone to call me a virgin, someone
like me who's been around the block, but
then but then but then when I call
someone a virgin, we don't hear the last
of it because they've got a girlfriend
or some some stupid excuse like that.
[ __ ] make it make sense, bro.
Make it make proper proper proper sense.
I used to have the same argument with I
used to have the same argument with Joe.
So weird, bro. It's so weird.
It's so [ __ ] up, bro.
Where's this other little piece? I'm
trying to find there's another piece. Yeah.
I just think he's biased. And then he's
talking to me about USA, is he? He's
talking to me about USA, is he? When I
know the story. You're talking to me,
bro. You're not talking to someone on
the community that doesn't know
anything. You're talking to me, someone
that knows what they've done.
I know they've gone to the police about
me about three times. There might have
not been five times, but they've gone to
the police. I have spoken to her friend.
She has told me that she's gone to the
police uh and whatever.
She has gone to the police and
Yeah. So why are you saying that she
hasn't when she blatantly is not about
that life? Why are you trying to make
someone about that life when they're not
about that life?
They've proved they're not about that
life. Because if there were anything
about that life, bro, they would be they
would be egging you on. They would
literally be egging you on like that
person on the train. Well, the person on
the train, there would be something like
that. They'd be like, "Oh, come then."
Bro, they didn't do that once. They
So, just remember that you're you're um
you're talking to me, mate. You're not
talking to some [ __ ] idiot on YouTube
doesn't know anything.
You are actually talking to me.
So, you don't you just don't make no
sense at all. And po
Greavvesy P [ __ ] was in the middle of it.
Greavvesy the poor [ __ ] was in the
middle of it.
Yeah, poor [ __ ] He was in the middle
of it, was he? Yeah.
One second. I need to get my phone
charger. My phone's about to die, bro.
Yeah. Around the festive period. together.
I'm not going.
I'm not gay. Oh, [ __ ]
Oh, [ __ ] me.
Just walked up the stairs.
I'm going to have a nice snooze today.
Grievesy, is that okay with you, Captain? God, Captain [ __ ]
You're right with you, Captain C. [sighs]
I'm going to have to do this with a can
of Coke, bro. Gives me energy in it.
What do you think of that little win?
£223 or 20 quid, Grezy, that was nice, isn't it?
Five teams, eh?
Yeah, it was good, isn't it?
Yeah, it was good, it
odds are so [ __ ] now, though. I should
have got more for that five teams. The
odds are so [ __ ]
What do you think of that? Gre Greavesy
playing fishing frenzy roulette.
[ __ ] that, bro. I'm not playing that
[ __ ] again. The last time I played was
Friday after I come out that police
thing. [ __ ] that, bro. No [ __ ] way.
But play that [ __ ] again.
So [ __ ] fixed.
I'd love to know how people win on that. No.
Maybe Crash can help me do the Lego Greavesy.
What do you think? Little Crash can help me.
I'm going to try and complete this tonight, bro.
I can actually focus now. I've got no
police, no nothing,
no worries. I should be able to do this.
Maybe Crash Bandicut can help me.
I don't take his I don't take his
sticker off because,
you know, I I haven't took Crash
Bandit's uh sticker off because it
proves that he's the original. Yeah,
he's obviously the original in it. So, I
can't take his uh Yeah.
Nah, bro. Not not as chunky as you,
Chase. Not as chunky as you, mate. My
weight is completely fine.
Nah, not not like you, mate. Do you know
what you'll never be able to do?
You'll never ever be able to grow a
beard like me. Oh, you can't see me.
It's too dark. You can't You can't grow
a beard like me. No. Not like me, mate. No,
never. You'll never be able to go be
like me, mate. [snorts] No, yours is
Yours is patchy
and you're shorter than me as well.
Yeah, you're you're shorter than me. Yeah.
I've never had a woman's touch.
No, mate. That's you.
I came to your city and had loads of
women's touches. Is that right, Grezy?
I actually remember the first time I
went to Wales. I had loads of touches.
Loads of kisses, loads of touches. I
remember the first time I went to
Cardiff on the train. Yeah.
Oh, [ __ ] hell, bro. Poor
If I can complete this tonight, um,
Greg, I'll buy the I'll buy the next one
with Jar in it. I'll buy the next Lego
set with Jar in it. Okay, boss.
Is that okay with you, boss?
Obviously, I have to run it by you first.
Okay with you, boss. [laughter]
Oh, I can say I can say it better than anyone else.
Okay with you, [ __ ] [laughter]
All right, JNA. I want a football bet.
Yeah, I want to five both teams to score. Yep.
Crash Bandicoot is my favorite character.
I got 223 back from 20 which is quite
bad to be honest. It should have been
more than that for five [ __ ] teams.
You struggle to get three teams.
So to get five teams, [ __ ] hell.
But it's still better than nothing, is
it? Still 20 fucking3 pound, but it
should have been more than that.
Yeah, I won't be going on no nights out
until a very long time, if ever again.
Yeah, I'll probably just buy some more Lego Greezy.
I haven't been on a proper night out for
[ __ ] like 3 months. Can't be bothered
with it anymore.
I just can't be annoyed with it anymore.
And I'm not going out in January either. [ __ ] that.
I'm not going out drinking in January. Yeah.
Yeah. I was going to put like 2050 pound
on that fishing frenzy roulette, but I
was like, nah. Any
money you get, whether you win it,
whether you save it, whether you get
given it, every single time you're
playing that roulette, you just lose. Yeah,
but I I I've just given up with the
whole [ __ ] women thing of that.
It's just boring, bro. They're all the
[ __ ] same, bro. All the same stuck
up. That's why I can't be bothered
anymore. Oh, almost sprayed my [ __ ] face. Yeah,
I [snorts] just can't be [ __ ] with it anymore.
Yeah, I'm thinking maybe if I do go out
maybe midFebruary or March,
it's not money. I've got the money to go
out. I can I can go out today if I
wanted to anywhere. Not that it's just
can't be bothered. [snorts] Yeah,
I can't be asked. Can't be annoyed with it.
What's a mug's game? Going out drinking.
Well, yeah. You You go out drinking to
try to meet someone and you never meet
someone. So So it's like what the [ __ ]
Yeah. It's not going to start picking up
until probably midFebruary, March anyways.
Yeah, dating is a mug's game. Well,
yeah, roulette is a mug's game, but I
mean on the football you can actually win.
I mean, you can actually win on the football.
I had loads of savings from the
football. But yeah, roulette and that it is
anything other than sports. It is. Yeah,
cuz with the football it's very hard to
do your balls in.
Yeah, [snorts] maybe until February,
maybe until March.
And even then, I still might not go out.
But yeah, roulette and slots definitely
is a bugs game. It's rigged as [ __ ]
It's so [ __ ] fixed. I don't know how
anyone [ __ ] wins on on that [ __ ]
It is [ __ ] fixed, bro.
Yeah. So, maybe I'll go out March.
Maybe I'll just go into Maybe I'll just
go to the gym next week or something.
And yeah, I don't know, man.
Probably just start going to the gym
until March, probably. Well, I'll still
go in March, but yeah,
probably to be fair.
Yeah, I didn't go I went out on Monday
drinking, but I didn't plan to drink.
No, I'm never going to live his
lifestyle, bro. I go out. I do things.
I'm out every day. I just don't drink
anymore. Well, I drunk Monday, but yeah.
No, I'll never live his lifestyle, bro. You mad. [ __ ] that.
Yeah, I'm not going I'm not going to no
Italy, bro. I'm not Why am I going to go
somewhere like that?
I got my new t-shirts coming. I'll
probably just go to the gym to be
honest. I'll probably just buy some more
Lego and go gym
and then see maybe March. Probably go
out March. There's a couple of bank
holidays in March. So, I might go out in
March or something. I don't know, bro.
But I've got um
I ain't going to [ __ ] I'm not going
to Italy, bro.
The only place I'd be will wanting to go
is [ __ ] Thailand or [ __ ] I don't
know. Not Italy.
The women are bad in Italy as well.
Stuck up anywhere [snorts] like that.
No, I wouldn't go Italy.
I might just go Paris and March. I said
I was going to go Paris in March, isn't it?
Yeah. I said I was going to go Paris in
March. So, I might just go Paris in
March. [ __ ] it. Yeah.
For like two days.
Yeah. I was going to go New Year's Eve,
but then I thought it was just it's just
too overpriced. New Year's Eve is a mugs
game, bro. New Year's Eve is such a mugs
game. I didn't do anything New Year's
Eve. It's such a mugs game. It is like
the biggest Mugs game going.
Like New Year's Eve is a Mugs game.
Double prices, everything. They they
charge people to get in places and
there's too many [ __ ] about. It's
just a Mugs game, bro. New Year's Eve is
a proper proper Mugs game.
New Year's Eve is a Mugs game.
Yeah, I I just prefer Thursdays in
April. March, April on a Thursday. Done.
Not full of [ __ ] No, not too much
competition. The weather's not too cold,
not too hot. Perfect.
March and April. either mid-March, April
on a Thursday, bro.
Or Friday, but mostly I prefer Thursdays. So, yeah.
Yeah, bro. I've been to Chinatown many
times. New Year's Eve, bro. I used to go
to the O'Neals. I used to love the
O'Neals Water Street.
You know the O'Neals? The Water Street? nails.
I used to cane that place, bro. Oh, [ __ ]
>> Yeah, I've been there a couple of times.
New Year's Eve.
That's where you want to go if you're in Chinatown. Yeah,
you know the place I'm talking about.
Yeah, the Chinese is on nice. What What
else is in Chinatown? I'm thinking of
something. I want a football bet, Dusty.
A five. Both teams to score.
You've never been in the O'Neals. That
O'Neals is the best, bro. I got so many
[ __ ] there, bro.
April on a Thursday. I used to get so
many [ __ ] there, bro. American
[ __ ] Cuz loads of American people
used to come.
So, obviously on Thursdays,
£223 from 20.
Yeah, I know. Should have been more, but yeah.
Where else? What else is in Chinatown? I
used to do the deliveries in Chinatown
when I had that Uber account.
Yeah, bro. JNA.
Bro, you don't need to tell me about Chinatown, bro.
I used to go there three times a week.
I know all about it, bro. I literally
know all about it. I used to go three
times a week, bro.
I used to go all the time. I've done
deliveries over there. I know all about
central London, bro. >> [laughter]
>> I used to go I used [snorts] to go every
Thursday, every Saturday to Chinatown, bro.
I know all about it. The arcade in the
corner, the O'Neals, the Bet Fred next
to the O'Neals, the Chinese next to the
O'Neals. Bro, I know this. I I know I
know Chinatown, bro. It's where I used
to I always used to go to the O'Neals. Um
there's a Patty Power as well. used to
be in Chinese. Yeah, I know all about
them places, bro. There's a bet Fred
next to the O'Neals.
I haven't I I haven't ate much of the
Chinese food there. I have been there.
I have obviously I've been there, but I
used to do a lot of deliveries there. A
lot of the deliveries was Chinatown,
Chinatown, Chinatown, Chinatown, Chinatown.
But yeah, that O'Neals used to be epic,
bro. Either March or April.
On a Thursday, March or April, probably
April, to be honest. I used to have the
best luck with dating in April. March
and April, and then after that, it was
it was over. It just went downhill from there.
I remember I come back from Wales. Yeah.
I had two dates in one day. I [ __ ] one
of them off and then I went on the other one.
Yeah. I used to [ __ ]
I used to can that O'Neal's bro. They
hated me. They hated me, bro. Trust me.
I always used to go This is what I used
to do J. Every Thursday I go to the
casino, win money cuz I would always
win. Then I'd go to the O'Neals with
like load of 50 notes. It used to be
just And then I go out the Saturday
and Yeah. Then I would go out the Saturday.
I could never do the The reason I used
to go out the Thursdays is because it
was quieter. It was better. And
obviously you're hung over the next day.
So you could also go out Saturday, you see.
And then obviously you recover on the
Friday, you go back out the Saturday cuz
obviously I used to drink rum and I
couldn't do two days in a row. I could
never do two days in a row when I was drinking rum.
If I do Guinness only beer, I can do two
days in a row. But I can't do two days a
day of rum. So I used to just go there,
go casinos, gamble, go to the O'Neals, approach,
get numbers, go back,
win some more money. [ __ ] escort, go back home
and then um and then uh text the numbers
when I got home. It used to be a repeat
every every year,
every week. Sorry. It used to be I used
to go every week, bro. And there used to
be a B at one. Do you remember the B at
one, Dusty, in the in the in the corner
of Piccadilly? It used to be called B at
one. They've closed it down now.
Yeah, it was called B at one. And I used
to go there as well. It was like a small
little place, but the music was good. It
smelt good. The toilet smelt good. You
could just tell that it was an upper
class place, but then they closed then
they then they closed it down.
Yeah, it was called B at one.
It's going towards Piccadilly Circus
like by It's hard to explain where it
was, but Yeah.
But it's closed down, bro. There used to
be an American uh bouncer there.
The only thing I don't like about these
places is they try to sit there and say,
"Yeah, you can't um
you can't you can't wear tracksuit
bottoms." I think that's wrong. I think
you should be able to wear what you
want. If you want to wear tracksuit
bottoms, you should be able to wear
tracksuit bottoms cuz when I go out
again, I'm wearing tracksuit bottoms.
So, if I've got to stay in one place,
I'll stay in one place, bro. I don't
mind. And I'm not wearing jeans. I don't
want to [ __ ]
I'll wear tracksuit bottoms. I want to
be comfortable, you know? Simple. So,
I'll just stay in one place and go to
little Weather Spoons and pubs that will
allow me in with with the tracksuit
bottoms. I don't Who the [ __ ] wants to
wear jeans, bro?
Yeah, but they're not upper class
things, bro. We're talking about like an
O'Neil's or like a Simmons.
We're not talking about like But I'll
just go I'll just drink in the Weather
Spoons. I prefer Weather Spoons in
central London anyways. I prefer Weather
Spoons. I I prefer a pub. It doesn't
need to be Weather Spoons, you know.
Yeah, but you could be You could be a
road man with jeans, though. You could
be a road man with jeans.
Think about it, bro.
But it depends anyways. But
But yeah, I I'll just go in pubs, bro.
Oh, [ __ ] I I'll just go in one pubs, bro.
I will just go in one pub. I I like the
Weather Spoons. I prefer pubs anyways. So,
I'll probably stay in one place and then
just go to pubs. Pubs will let you in
with tracksuit bombs on. So,
what are you talking about, bro? I don't
get what you what what you even on about.
But yeah, I just like tracksuit bottoms, bro.
>> I just like the tracksuit bottom sometimes.
>> So, I'm probably going to buy a new Lego
set and then probably go to the gym to
from Monday to be honest.
And then maybe I don't know. Maybe I'll
go out March. I don't know.
Probably. I probably not. [ __ ] knows. I
don't really care anymore, bro. Who knows?
Yeah. I lost 50 yesterday in the
roulette. I went mad, bro. If I if I
lost today the football bet, I would
have been I would have been upset, bro.
Cuz one one [ __ ] one goal would have
cost me 20 [ __ ]
20 because of one stupid goal.
So, I wouldn't have kicked off, but I
would have been.
But yeah, I'm done with that roulette
anyways. I I I'm not I'm never playing
on the online site ever again. the one
that I need to report to trading
standards. But I was just I
Yeah, I go to it all the time, bro. I go
to it all the time, Dusty.
And do approaches, bro. Dusty, I've been there.
I'm from London, bro.
I've been there next to the Simmons.
I've been there, bro. You don't need to
tell me, lad.
That one's not as big as the other one.
No, it's not as big as the other one.
The other one's massive. That one's not that big.
It's not as big as the other one.
The Totten Road one is massive. That
one's not as big, bro.
Yeah, I went to Romford last time. I
went drinking, but I prefer central London.
Yeah, the other one I can't get into.
Yeah, I know. It's massive.
Yeah. Yeah, it's massive, bro. I know.
Yeah, I can still get into it. Well, if
I go at like 9 10:00, they they're not
going to notice me, bro. It's so rammed.
So, I still go in it.
I still go in it. I do still go in it.
I do need a good piss up though, bro. at
some point. My friend from Redden still
wants to meet me.
Yeah, that one, bro. Yeah. Yeah, we're
talking about that one. It's [ __ ] massive, bro.
The one in Liverpool Street's um big as well.
Yeah, we're talking about that one.
The Lester Square spoons is good though.
You always get little [ __ ] in there, bro.
Yeah, like do some approaches and that.
But trying to get a date. I don't know
if I'll ever get I don't know if I'll
get a date this year. Probably not.
Probably not, bro.
I want to go Manchester again though,
Dusty. That's where I want to go again.
I want to go Manchester. I like the
drinking scene. I like the vibe there.
I like Manchester. Um,
no. Sometimes I watch that Secular
Slots. I used to watch all of them, but
No, I don't.
I miss Manchester, bro, for the drinking
thing. I just like the way Manchester is
for like the drinking and that.
I like [snorts] Manchester. I remember I
was in Manchester before for 2 days,
bro. Like, hey, JNA, bro. This is how
I've never gone to Blackpool. This is
how I've never gone to Blackpool because
I was in Manchester Friday. Yeah. I used
to go out I used to travel on a Friday.
Yeah. I used to just get drunk on a
Friday and come back on a Saturday and I
was supposed to go to Blackpool on a Saturday.
I was supposed to go to Blackpool on a
Saturday in it, but then there was a
train strike. So, I was stuck in
Manchester. Had to book another hotel.
Then had another night out there. Don't
ask me how I done it cuz I was on a run.
And then on the Sunday I just come back
to London. I was like, "Fuck it. I'm too
[ __ ] now." It was worth it though. I
remember it though. The two days of
Manchester. I know Liverpool is better
than Manchester. I've only been
Liverpool once. I've only been Liverpool
once though. But I know it is better than Manchester.
I know that for I know I know you're
right about that. But I've never I've
only been once
and not properly. I went on a night out
there, but it wasn't proper.
But no, I I I believe that, bro.
No, I don't even know where the [ __ ] that is.
And that's how I've never been to
Blackpool. So, yeah.
I think the best night out though, what
what can I say the best night out is?
It's New It's Newcastle. It's got to be Newcastle, bro.
Edinburgh was good, but it wasn't as
good as Newcastle.
Edinburgh was good, but
Newcastle was better, bro.
From what I can remember, Newcastle was
always the best.
Just the whole apart from getting
[ __ ] arrested the first time.
I tell you what, we be good, Dusty.
Yeah. Go Newcast. Go Liverpool on a
Friday. Go uh
Yeah, but bro, the women are so easy to
get there. Like I I when I went to
Newcastle, I had women approaching me. Um but
I reckon it'd be good if you went
Newcastle on a Friday and Liverpool on a Saturday.
That'd be [snorts] good, bro. It But
you'd have to only drink beer the first
night cuz Newcastle is good though, bro.
Cuz the women are easy to get there.
Well, they were for me anyways. Every
time I've been there,
I went to Leeds once. I didn't like the
people. I didn't like the bouncers.
I had a really bad experience with the
bouncers, but I'll try again one day.
Oh, Sheffield's good as well. I like
Sheffield. I don't know, man. Sheffield
was good. Sheffield was good. I like Sheffield, man.
Sheffield was good, to be fair.
No, when I went to Sheffield, I went to
I remember I went to Sheffield. Yeah. I
[ __ ] bro I ended up with like hanging
around with 10 different people. Bro,
Sheffield was so good. I met this guy
and then this other guy. We all got on a
piss right until the next day. And you
could never do that in London. This is
what I say. You could never ever do that
in London because people in London are
just [ __ ] They think they're
better than everyone. Sheffield was a
vibe, bro. There's like a there's a
brothel called a paradise, bro. And we c
we met some people in Iber. And by we, I
mean me. I went by myself. It was funny
as [ __ ] bro. There was this guy. Yeah.
He was some [ __ ]
gypsy guy, bro. He was giving us jokes,
bro. Sheffield's good, man. Yeah.
Yeah, I just build. Yeah, it's the same
way in it. Leads, but I didn't like
leads, but I didn't like it. Me.
People say, "Oh, yeah, leads is good."
Nah, bro. The the the bounces I didn't
like the bounces.
I had two arguments with two different bounces, bro.
Yeah, sometimes bounces can act up, bro.
Yeah, sometimes they can act up. You
don't really get it as much in London.
You you you don't really get it much in
London, but you Manchester, you've never had it.
I've never had it.
The people's all right, but the bouncers
were [ __ ] bro. The bouncers, I'm not
even going to tell you about the the
story, bro, cuz it's just negative, is
it? And then they get away with it. You
got police right there, and they allow
it. And then if you hit them, you get nicked.
The people was all right. Yeah. But the bouncers weren't.
Yeah. I remember in the I wasn't Yeah.
Yeah. They are to be cuz I remember I
was getting my haircut in the barbers.
Yeah. And this guy was like, "Oh, do you
want to come out with me?
Do you want to come out with me? We go
in the pool and that." And bear in mind,
he's waiting to get his haircut whilst
I'm getting my haircut. You'd never get
that in London.
You'd never get that in London. This is
what I'm trying to say. You'd never ever
get anything like that in London.
But yeah, there's a guy I met from Leeds
in the in the London Weather Spoons. He
was good as well. Cool as [ __ ] Just a
bouncer was a [ __ ] bro. In Leeds,
he was a proper [ __ ]
They think they can get rude and they
think they can scare people. I'm not
scared of you, bro.
And there was a guy. Yeah, I had a bad
experience with a Simmons bouncer as well.
And he said, "Oh, don't give me attitude
or I'll snatch it off you." I said,
"You're not going to you're not even
going to put your hands nowhere near me,
mate." And he tried and he tried like
like taking the drink back and it almost
went everywhere. I said, "You're not
putting your hands on me." [ __ ] idiot
moving mad, bro.
Mad, mad, mad. Obviously, it's rare it
happens, but there's times it stuff like
that happens, bro. You know what I mean?
Nah. Why are you going to travel all
over England? I've already traveled all
over England, bro. [ __ ]
Why did you do that all again?
Have you ever had problems with bounces,
Dusty? I'm sure you have,
but you don't really get it much in London.
Yeah, they try to abuse their powers sometimes.
I said, "You're not putting your hands
on me, bro. You're not even thinking
about doing that. I'm not scared of you,
bro. Cuz I have it in my head. Yeah. If
if they if they win against me, I'm
going back. I am literally going back. So,
I will go back, bro. Trust me, I don't care. So,
who wouldn't, bro?
Yeah. You got banned from loads of places.
What did you get banned for? Yeah, it's
in Germany, is it?
Yeah, that's Germany.
America's scary, bro. I've seen I've
seen I've seen I've seen Ed Matthews
live streams. America is so scary, bro.
Just how like big it is. And you have to
get like cars everywhere. It's not like
here, bro. It's scary, isn't it?
America's scary, bro.
Cuz of how big it is. It's so scary, isn't it?
It's scary, bro.
No, it's not even just motorways, bro.
Just the whole thing. It's all
boulevards and avenues and it's
boulevards and avenues. Like, not in New
York and that. Obviously, New York is
bigger than London, but there's public
transport. Somewhere like [ __ ]
Tennessee and [ __ ] Georgia and all
that [ __ ] bro. You're [ __ ] if you're
stuck in the middle of nowhere, you're
you're it's dangerous, bro. Isn't it?
No, you can you can get trains from
states to states, but I'm saying like
say you're in Florida, you need a car.
There's no public transport like there is London.
Do you get what I'm saying? No, you can
get you can get trains to to states, but
I mean like getting around the state,
there's no public transport, so you're
driving everywhere. It's it's scary, bro.
Well, there are some of them that don't, bro.
There's there is places that don't.
So why did you get banned from places, Dusty?
Was he showing off?
Yeah. Hillbilly towns like Georgia.
There is places, bro. I know there is
places. It might not be specifically in
Miami, but there's there's got to be
places in Florida cuz I remember my
friend went there and he says you have
to walk everywhere or there states, bro.
There were It's scary, bro.
It's scary, bro. It's just scary.
It's just scary, bro. So, yeah. >> [snorts]
>> So why did you get banned from places anyways?
What did you do, Dusty? Why did you get banned?
I've been I've been banned for
approaching people before in one place
even though that's what it's there for.
You know, the whole country doesn't even
make sense. It was only one place.
The thing is with with this Simmons bar,
I'm not talking about Waxies or O'Neal's
that was you can do what you want there.
But with these places like Simmons, the
staff has got attitude and any they will literally
they will report people for anything
because they hate their job. Trust me,
bro. Trust me. Waxies don't do it.
O'Neal's don't do it. No weather spoons
does it. It's only Simmons. If you go to
any Simmons, you will see, bro, they
will because they they don't like their
job. They will take it out on other people.
Like, I mean, it's a bar. It's a social
event. It's a free country. You can
approach who you want. You can talk to
who you want. And if they reject you,
then they reject you in it. That's that.
If they give you their number, they give
you their number. Like, it's a free
country, bro. Like if you're a single
man, you ain't got kids. You could do
what you you could do what you want. All
you're doing is trying to find a [ __ ] partner.
That's not a crime.
Think about it, bro. Really. Like, think
about it for one second, you know?
And O'Neal was never banned me for that.
O'Neal was banned me because it was
probably someone on YouTube. Big
difference, bro. You know,
and I know it was them. I knew it was
the staff. It wasn't no woman that told
him because I've approached because the
thing is Dusty, I've approached people
for years and no one's ever ran to the
police or ran away. Trust me. And that
was not a coincidence that it just
happened there. What it is is the staff
will complain about you. Maybe you're
wearing your wearing tracksuit bottoms.
I mean, I got banned for calling someone a [ __ ]
in the Simmons, the same brand. I said,
"Oh, so you're acting like a bit of a
cunt." I got banned. Blacklisted.
Yeah, cuz she was being stuck up and I
said, "Oh, there's no need to act like a
cunt." And then they just ban me.
Simple, bro. They ban you if they just
don't like like the look of you cuz they
don't like their job. That's how it
works in the Simmons.
In that Simmons, that specific Simmons,
that is how it works.
Yeah. Well, it's a free country. It's
not against the law. You're allowed to
shoot your shot. If I want to talk to
people, I can talk to people. I'm
single. It's not the street. It's a bar. So,
yeah, exactly. Yeah, bro.
obviously they can. That's what happens
in Simmons. It doesn't happen anywhere else, bro.
It only happens in Simmons. Trust me, it
only happens in Simmons. I was going to
that O'Neal's for years, bro. And I got
banned because someone on YouTube. It
wasn't because I was approaching people.
Waxies don't ban you for approaching
people. where the spoons don't ban you
for approaching people.
It's a free country, bro. If you're a
single guy and you want to approach
people, you're in your rights to do
that. If you if you was on the street
doing it non-stop, you're not going to
get nicked. No one's going to report
you. You're allowed to do that
considering that's the only way you're
going to [ __ ] probably get a [ __ ]
date. So, it's like,
yeah, it's what the [ __ ] bro? It's a
free country, man. I was some Polish
bouncer going to try and tell me what to
do and then try and tell me he's going
to put his hands on me. No, that's not
happening. And that's probably, you know
what though, to be honest with you, bro,
that's part of the probably the reason
why I don't go out anymore either as
well because of how toxic it is.
Like that's probably one of the reasons
why I don't. And by go out, I mean going
out drinking. Obviously, I [ __ ] go
out, but that's another reason because
of the toxicness as well with it all.
But yeah, Simmons, if they don't like
the look of you, they will just report
you to the security.
Trust me, bro. It really is like that in
that Simmons. It's nowhere else. It's
that Simmons. Trust me, it's nowhere
else but Simmons. So,
um, they seem to have their little own
agenda in that Simmons. Any Weather
Spoons you go to, you're fine. Um,
unless online wants to report you or
whatever, you're fine anywhere but there.
And trust me, no one reported me. No one
complained. You just saw me. You hate
your job. You was probably jealous the
fact that I was drinking, not you. And
yeah, you had your own agenda.
And it's not even that, bro. You go to
any you go to any Simmons in in central
London dusty and you will see their
attitude. You will actually see the
staff's attitude. It stinks, bro. Proper
proper stinks. Um there's this one from
Canada, bro. She works in the Simmons in
um Leicester Square and anyone would
think her [ __ ] don't stink. The way
she's walking, the way she's acting,
like you can see the look in her face.
She told me she lives in Elephant and
Castle and she um she literally thinks that
I don't know, bro. I haven't tried going
back in there and I'm never going to go
back in there. So,
but they've got their own um Yeah,
they're making it impossible to date,
bro. It's bad enough that the the women
are stuck up with unrealistic standards
and then you got people trying to tell
you you can't approach people.
What the [ __ ] Free country, bro. It's a free country.
Look it up. There's no law against it, you know.
But no, I don't know, bro. I'll probably
never go there ever again to find out
I've won my toys and everything. So, I
don't really care. Yeah.
But yeah, they do have their uh cuz I
was saying to the women I was like, I've
been approaching for years and not one
time has anyone ever has anyone ever
ever reported me. Considering I've done
more approaches than someone like I've
done more on the street, there's no way.
Stop lying. Stop blaming people. You
just didn't like the fact that I was
doing it and that's it. Just be honest.
I don't care. I'll leave your
establishment with pleasure and never come back
and I'll give you my money. Simple as that.
Do you understand? And don't make
excuses. Stop blaming people that never
done anything. You know, it's like that
O'Neals when they b me off for 3 years,
I said that's fine by me. I'll go somewhere else.
You know, they got they used to get a
lot of money out of me as well. So,
obviously they're going to make more
money from people. I get it. But they
used to make a lot of money, bro, even
in January. So, that's it's their loss,
bro. No skin. I'll find somewhere else.
Plenty of other places to go to.
You know, apparently I was reading some
reviews on this O'Neal's dusty and a lot
a couple of people were saying that they
got banned because they sorry, they
didn't get banned. They didn't get let
in because they didn't want to drink
alcohol. So the manager says, "Are you
drinking alcohol?" And the people that
didn't turn around and said no. And then
they turn around and says, "Oh, we can't
let you in."
And a lot of people was complaining about that.
I know the guy that O'Neal's manager,
some Indian guy.
His name's uh what's his name again?
Jamie. I know all of them there, bro. I
know all the staff. I know all the
bouncers. I got the bouncers numbers as
well cuz I used to speak to them. I used
to get on with them. So, I know everyone.
Even the bartenders, bro.
Like, that's how much I used to go and I
knew everyone there.
and the and the bartenders were actually
all right. They never had attitude. They
were all cool and everything, but that
Simmons, bro, the bouncers was all right as well.
And to be honest, the managers was all
right as well to be honest with you. So,
but they were a bit they had their own
little agenda as well to be honest. One
of them did. Yeah,
one of them had their own uh little
agenda, but it was nothing like that
Simmons, bro. It was nothing like that.
Simmons, trust me,
I knew was all right, bro. Yeah.
But like say if you was arguing with a
woman, there was one time I was arguing
with this woman. She thought she could
shout over me, the one in front of her
dad. I was like, "You're not going to
shout over me." It was just an argument.
And he says, "Oh, can you go? You can
come back another day. It's fine, but
can you just go for today? I said,
"What?" She started it without even
hearing the story. He was like, "Oh, no.
You you have to go." So, yeah, it was a
little bit of an agenda, but you know,
not permanently, bro. They wouldn't ban
people permanently for no reason
like the Simmons do. They will literally
blacklist your name as well. They'll
make up their own rules. They're mad,
bro. If you go on that Simmons, you go
on that Simmons, you look on the
reviews, you'll see a lot of people say
the same thing, bro. It's not only me.
We spoons is fair though, bro. They
don't they won't they don't discriminate.
What they doing in that Simmons? That
Simmons is the worst for it. Yeah.
So, how else are you supposed to date if
you can't approach an approach in a social place?
It's not like you're throwing fuss. It's
not like someone's not giving you their
number and you're arguing and you're
causing problems. You're literally just
moving on. So, I don't know what is it
got to do with them. That's not in their
job title to It's just Yeah. This
country just doesn't make sense, bro.
Yeah. So, they want you to what? Go on
dating apps that don't work. They don't
want you to speak to anyone and what?
make new friends.
Why? Why not, bro? No one's complained.
No one's arguing. So why why are they
not allowed to do that?
That's what you call discrimination.
You understand? That's the definition of
discrimination. You see? They discriminate against people.
That's why they're not worth They're not worth you.
They're not worth giving their money to,
bro. Your money to.
Yeah, you might as well just drink a
bottle, buy a bottle, and just approach
on the street. [gasps]
I'd still say pubs are fine, though.
Pubs are fine, bro.
Waxi is good, bro. I like waxies. [snorts]
I ain't been for ages, man. I need to
hit that place up again.
In good time, bro. In good time. Um, boom.
No, no, no, no, no.
What is that?
This guy still posts on [ __ ] YouTube.
It's funny as [ __ ] bro. [sighs] [snorts]
This is [ __ ] I need to get a new
phone soon, bro. July in it. July. July. Yeah, bro. Definitely July.
>> [clears throat]