Oh, it won't turn on cuz the blankie is on.
That was nice bit food. Oh,
in my stomach.
Now I'm having a
biscuit. I just did you just come on
just to see if it's the same people.
Same [ __ ] people every [ __ ] day, mate.
Maybe today. Today. Well, it's not. You
never know who really knows, you know.
[ __ ] gold out there.
>> Yeah, just checking to see quickly see
if it's people.
Maybe it won't be 2026. Yeah,
we'll have a have a see. E, we'll have a look.
Progress is good, isn't it?
Well, I just got everywhere. This biscuit.
I love this biscuit, man.
It's a happy hippo biscuit.
Hope yourself today.
I I ain't seen a thingy about for ages.
No, I haven't.
What the [ __ ] bro?
Doesn't come on this channel anymore, does he?
No, that's t that tends to happen.
There a lot of self projectors on this community, man.
It's a lot of self projectors.
Doesn't matter what time, what day, what place, what, whatever.
It will always be the same people.
Always be the same people.
That's [ __ ] boring, isn't it?
They've got some time on their hands,
man. People got a lot of time on their hands.
But I mean, that does that that's that's
what tends to happen when people are,
you know, unhappy in their own life,
haven't got anything going for
themselves. Cuz let's face it, that's
why a lot of people are on here doing
this. Come on. I'm I'm just thinking out
loud now, you know? Yeah. Mad. No.
Well, that's another self projector.
Seaside fug. That's another self-reflector.
Yeah, that's another account that used
to go on seaside Mark's channel. Another self projector.
Cuz what makes me laugh here is that
these these people these self projectors
can say what they want about anyone, but
we know that they're on YouTube 24/7. We
know what these people look like. So
anything that they say is just
laughable. That's why people can't even
get mad at it. That's why no one can do
anything but really laugh at these
people. Really, if you think about it,
you're another one pit. You call people
skin, but you skin yourself. You're on
YouTube 24/7. That's why I just laugh at
it. That's why I don't take no um I
don't take no offense to what self projectors say.
really really doesn't bother me because
when you know people have got a history
on here of talking about themselves
because they all they always talk about
themselves. You just laugh at them. Just
absolutely laugh at them. And again, I
don't care who's got friends and who
doesn't have friends. I really don't
care. I just know that they ain't got a
life. I don't use having no friends as
an insult. That's not even an insult.
But yeah, you get my point. A lot of
self-reflectors, bro. A lot of self-reflectors.
Weird though, ain't it? You should.
People need to grow up, man. You're
older than me for [ __ ] sake. Really,
really older than me, bro.
A lot of people need to grow up. [ __ ] me, man. Sad.
I don't know how you can sit there for
like that many years stalking people
that you don't know.
That is really, really, really, really
sad, bro. I know you won't be able to like uh
comprehend it cuz you don't have the
brain power, but it's very weird. Very strange.
More self projecting.
Bye-bye. Got plenty of money. Thanks.
See you later.
This is what I mean. And all of this
stuff, bro, it just proves that you're
unhappy in your own lives
when you're doing this. I've got plenty
of money, though. Thanks.
So, yeah, it's it just goes to show how
like you just have got nothing in your
life. So, you've been doing this for 15
years straight. It just shows
you people need to look a bit closer to home
and you find the answers. Simple.
That's why I don't get mad. That's why I
just laugh at it. I laugh at these
self-p projectors cuz I know that
they're all uglier than me. They're all
fatter than me. They're all skinnier
than me. None of them leave. None of
them leave their house. None of them got
a lie. So then it just becomes laughable.
They're quite embarrassing really to be
honest with you. But yeah.
Oh well. Anyways, moving on. Yeah.
Sad, sad, sad, man. Sad, sad, sad.
I couldn't comprehend what LT was
saying. Bro, the guy's biased. End the
story. And he's been biased more. He's
been biased on more than one occasion. So yeah,
people that uglier than me calling me a
m. These people really, really, really
can't comprehend their own lives, can they, bro? Seriously. Yeah. Yeah,
to be honest, I'm on YouTube today cuz
I'm doing literally nothing today. It's
one of them days. It's Sunday and I'm
doing literally nothing but chilling. So yeah,
that's basically why. Yeah.
But you people seem to be on YouTube all
day every day, don't you? All day every
day criticizing other people.
Isn't that funny?
All day, every day.
But you talk about other people that are
better than you.
Maybe one day someone can explain it to
me, bro. Maybe. Maybe someday. mad.
You know, I'm not subscribed to anyone anymore either.
Well, I'm subscribed to Timmy actually,
but anyone else I'm just unsubed to, bro.
Bye-bye. See you later.
Bye-bye. So, uh yeah, actually I'm
actually subscribed to Timmy, man.
Yeah, whoever that is.
It's so boring today. It feels like a
Sunday. It's so boring, bro. I'm not
doing nothing today.
Why do I repeat myself?
Cuz it's fun, bro. It's funny. It's great fun.
Yeah, I love it, bro.
So, anyways, why do you people do what
you do every day? Anyways, just wondering.
Obviously, Monty's not on here to ask it
anymore, so it seems I'm the only one.
Why do people do what you do every day?
I'd love to know, you know. I'd love to
know the answer.
Probably best not to ask it. That's how
you stop becoming [ __ ] brain damaged.
Trying to understand
people on here, they're [ __ ] idiots.
So, yeah, that that work, is it?
Yeah, [ __ ] those bro.
I have no idea.
I guess I'm just going to watch some [ __ ]
Oh, that's self projecting. See you later.
Oh, this is what I'm saying, bro. Like,
you people have really got sick minds.
So, what you think? Somebody that wants
that somebody that plays with Lego that
is actually made for adults is a pedo.
So, like you must have that [ __ ] Like,
bro, you must have that [ __ ] in your
head. To think people that are pedos for
doing that. You You must be one
yourself. To have that in your head.
Yeah. To literally have that in your
head. You must be You must be one. You
must be one yourself.
Yeah, you've done the same thing with
the arcades as well, bro.
Because I do like because I want to.
Lego is not just for kids. It actually
states that's also for adults.
I mean, why I mean only this community
could turn that into a pedophile thing.
So something tells me a lot about them,
bro. If they're calling you that, why
would why would they turn that into a
pedo thing? I mean, it literally says
eight and and above and adults, why do
they turn it into a nons thing, bro?
See, only people on this community would
think of something like that.
Because it shows me, yeah, that they've
got something to hide themselves because
only people on here would say that stuff.
That is so weird, bro. weird.
Yeah, bro. Like you go into an arcade.
Yeah. They say, "Oh, you're a pedophile.
You do Lego, call you a pedophile."
You sure you ain't got anything to hide yourselves, bro?
Yeah. Really, bro? No one cares what LG
says. He's irrelevant.
and he's disabled himself. So, good for
him, bro. Why do you turn it into a pedo
thing anyways? That I'm I'm starting to
think you've got something to hide, bro.
The people that are saying that,
why does that go to your head? Like, so
someone goes to an arcade. Yeah.
And you think people go there, bro? L2
couldn't destroy anyone, bro. He
couldn't even fight his own battles, let
alone destroy me. Anyways, we're not
talking about him. He's irrelevant, bro.
So, stop bringing irrelevant people up.
He The only reason he reacted like that
is cuz he knows I'm I'm right. What I'm
saying, the only reason he reacted like
that is cuz he knows I'm more
intelligent than he would ever be. I'm
literally more intelligent than he will
literally ever be. That's why he reacted
like that because he knows I'm right.
He literally knows I'm right. Anyway,
see you later, lad.
You're banned. So, um yeah.
Yeah. He reacted very strange, didn't
it? All I said is why do you keep
defending your boyfriend?
Um every time I'm calling him what he's calling me.
Yeah. Yeah. I I doubt that very very much.
I doubt that very All I ask him is why
is he being biased
and then he started reacting like that
cuz he is biased. So what? Just own it.
You're biased, bro. You got favorism and
you're touchy about your boyfriend.
That's all you got to say. No need to
stop threatening me, bro. Cuz it doesn't bother me.
You know what I'm saying?
All I asked him is why was he defending his boyfriend?
I wasn't trying to rage bait or
anything. I can ask questions if I want to. Yeah.
Strange, is it why somebody would react
like that? That's supposed to be intelligent.
Odd. But anyways,
so anyways, why do you think people that
go to arcades are um pedophiles anyways?
Why do you think people that go to
arcades are pedophiles? Why do you think
people that play Lego are pedophiles?
That's strange to come to that
conclusion all of a sudden, isn't it?
You sure you ain't got something to hide yourself, bro?
That is very, very, very, very, very
strange. You've come to that conclusion.
Strange people. very very strange people
on here. I think they need to get a life
to be honest. Serious. And I'm allowed
to say this on a Sunday. I'm not doing
anything today. I'm chilling.
I I can say it, bro. Straight. You know
what? So that means that someone likes
kids. So because someone's playing with
Lego, that means they're a pedophile. Is
that is that the way your brain works?
Oh, is that so that's the way your brain works then? Okay.
Stop asking stupid questions.
That's my answer to your question there,
Timmy. Stop asking stupid questions.
Um, so that means that some so you you
assume that someone's a pedophile.
Oh, okay. Is that the way your brain
works then? Yeah.
Ali never destroyed anyone.
And he was bringing up USA Izzy as well.
He was bringing up USA Izzy when I'm
literally the one that knows more than
him and he's trying to talk about me.
He's trying to tell me like I'm the one
that don't know more than him.
Really, bro? Like, take a step back,
man. Come on.
Yeah. Only in your minds would you think
that, bro? Only in your minds you would think that.
Only in your biased minds would you
think that cuz you probably got
something to hide yourself. Yeah. Oh man.
Yeah. All I said is that he was being
biased. Cuz he was being biased.
So what, bro? He is biased. He's a biased [ __ ] Simple.
Everyone's destroying me. Nope.
Bro, we're not talking about that. This is 2026.
We're not talking about things in the
past. That's only autistic people like
you that's obsessed.
That's the way you try to justify your
jealousy. No one's interested in that,
bro. This is 2026.
>> Yeah, this is 2026. No one really really
cares. So, take your repeating somewhere else.
No one cares about that [ __ ] And that's
how you know, right? This is how we know
that you people in here are actually like autistic
because you you you hang on to things
from like four or five years.
Yeah. As well as other things. That's
how we know that you're autistic on here as well. Yeah,
that's how we know, bro. Like, is that
literally how your minds work? Like,
no. Like, bro, like educate me cuz I'm
like, I'm actually interested.
Weird as [ __ ]
So, like if someone So, you come across
someone on the internet and they say
some some mad stuff, you you just obsess
over it for years or would you not just
get on with your own life?
I don't know, man. Help me understand.
I'm really like I want to be educated on
this cuz I I don't understand it. I'm
not going to pretend I understand it
when I don't.
Like, is this So, it's got to be like
real life to you then. Is it like
YouTube, bro? It's got to be It's got to
be It's got to be real life. If I heard
someone say mad stuff, bro, I wouldn't
be talking about it four or five years
later or even weeks later. Is that
really how your minds work?
Is that really really how your minds
work, bro? Seriously? [ __ ] me. Seriously. Well,
I'm not trying to justify it. I don't
care. I'm saying that you're obsessed,
bro. I'm literally saying to you, I don't care.
care. I'm not trying to justify
anything. I literally don't care. And
there's other people that said stuff
more than worse than me, but they're But
you're biased. You're biased anyway. So,
we're not going to get into that bison
because I'll give myself a [ __ ]
headache again. I'm not trying to
justify anything. I'm I'm telling you,
you're obsessed. When have I when have I
tried to justify anything,
you know? You had no problems with
[ __ ] Pat Mustard putting Monty's kids
up. You had no problem with [ __ ] Pat
Mustard putting my sister's kids up.
Just shut up. Just shut your [ __ ]
mouth. Yeah. You had no problem with him
talking about dead relatives. Just shut
up. Again, biasness. That's a big thing
on this community. You literally had no
problems with that. So, don't come at
me. Simple as that. Do not come at me.
You had no problems with this man
putting kids up all over his YouTube.
So, don't come at me. Simple as that. Do
not do not worry about me, bro. Simple
as that. Simple as that. Yeah.
So, anyways, why did none of you people
say anything about Pat Muster putting
Monty's kids up?
ask I I want to ask you that question,
man, because I'm trying to I want to understand,
you know, why did you why did you not
say anything to Why did you not um say
anything to Pat Mustard when he was
putting people's kids up?
Think about it, bro. No, no. Okay,
answer the question then. So, when he
was putting people's kids up, when he
was putting people's kids up, he had
kids on his phone. It doesn't matter
what he said. He had kids on his phone.
Listen, listen. And he had kids on his
phone and he's put he put kids all over
his YouTube channel. Shut up. Do not
even try to say anything to me. Yeah.
Simple as that. It doesn't matter. He
had other people's kids saved on these
devices. Imagine going on someone's
phone. Yeah. And seeing people's kids on
their phone. Like he he saved pictures
of people's kids and he put them all
over YouTube. So yeah, there we go. And
you had no problem. So yeah, simple as that.
And you're banned. See you later.
Yeah. And your band as well. See you later.
No, they didn't, bro. He left because he got doxed.
That's why he left. He left because he got doxed.
I got a new channel cuz [ __ ] um I
couldn't go live on my other one, bro.
Cuz of the Streamyard destinations.
because I had so many um
like I had so many accounts on
Streamyard so I had to make another
account because I couldn't remember the login.
Just a Streamyard problem, man. But I'm
on here now. So yeah.
Oh, please tell me that's Rocky Ride.
Please tell me that's you. Come on, bro.
It's been months now, isn't it? The only
one I can actually speak to that doesn't
give me brain damage. Well, there was a
few other people, but they're never
really on here either.
Please tell me this is you, bro. Come on.
Yeah. Like, um, yeah.
Yeah. No one had a problem with Pat
putting people's kids up.
Yeah, I'm not literally doing nothing
today, bro. [ __ ] Or probably sleeping,
bro. There's nothing to do today.
But yeah, it's still the same people on
here. Rocky Ride, if that is you, bro.
Nothing's changed in 2026. I thought it
was going to. I take it you saw all the LT stuff.
I take it you saw all the LT stuff, huh?
Yeah. Bet you please you didn't get
involved in it in it.
He didn't put me in my place at all,
bro. I completely wrecked him in that video. Oh [ __ ]
I completely wrecked him in that video,
bro. Everything I said was facts.
Everything I said about fact was facts
about biasness, bro. Yeah.
And you know it, bro. And you know it as well.
Madness, isn't it?
I don't really come on here much
anymore, bro. Cuz it's pointless. Yeah.
I don't know. But yeah, that's why I've
got this new channel, bro. Cuz uh
something with the Streamyard too many
destinations connected and I didn't know
the login to remove him. So that's why
we're here basically.
Trying to think what to do today. Boring.
Nope. He didn't get me arrested and it
wasn't him either.
Nope. He didn't get me arrested. I
didn't even get arrested. Try again. Sad bastard.
And like I said, the more you do this,
the more it proves what I say about you
being jealous of me. The more you do it,
the more it shows what I'm saying. And
you didn't get me arrested. I didn't get
arrested. And it wasn't you either.
Every single time I say something, you
try to earrop and twist the story. Like,
you got my money stopped. You never got
none of my money stopped. I've got more
money than you, which I've stated
multiple multiple times. But you keep
telling yourself that anyways. You
didn't get anyone arrested. I didn't get
arrested, you [ __ ] idiot.
You [ __ ] [ __ ] And even if you did
get someone arrested, which you [ __ ]
well didn't, that's you being a loser.
That's not winning. That's you being a
loser. Only a biased community would
think that's winning. Only biased people
would think that's winning. You sad
bastard. Low life. Anyways,
yeah. Do you like the t-shirt, Grezy?
So, yeah, man. Like, a lot of people
think, "Oh, I went too deep and whatever
with the with a with a with a LT thing."
But why would I want to be friends?
No, I didn't say I've been in the sales.
No, I did not. Not once did I say that.
Anyways, moving on. Now, this is how you
start losing brain cells with these
people. So, the thing is, Grezy, yeah,
the re uh I know a lot of people thinks
about the LT thing. Oh, like I shouldn't
have said anything and I should have
left it. But why am I going to
why am I going to interact with biased people?
Why am I going to be friends with
someone that's blatantly biased? Who in
their right mind is going to do that,
bro? Who's going to Who's going to
interact with someone that's biased? Not
me. And I don't think no normal person
would as well. Why would anyone want to
associate with a biased person?
Come on now, bro. Who Who really would
want to do that?
I had breakfast, Greavves. I had some
eggs and bacon.
Who who do you think's right in this
argument? Grievy, do do you reckon it's
me or do you reckon it's him?
He is biased though. Who? Jo. He is biased.
LT is biased. If you think I'm wrong,
tell me I'm wrong. You're not going to
get blocked. I don't care, bro. But I I
know he is biased
just like a lot of the people on here.
It's But it's very strange as well. Yo,
certain people that do it. Yeah, of
course it is. Didn't you know that
Christmas period, bro? Yeah.
I think I emailed him twice. I said,
"Uh, are you going to talk about this
19year-old? Are you going to talk about
this [ __ ] video? Are you going to
talk about Sig?" Uh, excuse me. You've
got yourself involved now. Someone's
calling me things. Do you wanna No, just
want to let that one slide. like a
Michael Jackson album. You're just gonna
pretend you ain't heard it? Yeah, of
course you with your bias, [ __ ] Why do
you think I got such a reaction, bro?
Because I'm right.
And with people that that that that
aren't intelligent aren't um more
intelligent than you.
You know what I mean? Yeah.
Yeah. And they're just jealous bastards.
Hujas, I can't believe in 2026 they're
still doing this, bro.
I really, really can't believe they're
still doing this in 2026. I was saying
to Laney, I was giving them the benefit
of the doubt.
I thought these losers was actually
going to get a life instead of coming on
here calling people what they are every
day. Bro, I'm shocked. I'm actually
shocked to be honest.
Sat on YouTube, no life, nobody, no
future, talking about other people. But
I thought, you know, you know, 2026, nope.
Nope. They can't, bro. They can't.
And I thought obviously because they
said they don't show their face because
they're intelligent, then they weren't
going to repeat themselves in 2026.
Yeah, it was a good win yesterday, bro. Yeah.
It's weird, isn't it, lad?
Why do I think people are jealous?
Uh because of what you people do on
here. Because of what you people do on
here and what you've been doing for years.
That's why. That's why I think a lot of
people are jealous on there. Yeah.
And the patterns that has immensed over the years. That's why.
Yeah. I've got the answer for it, bro.
Because of what people do and what they
end up looking like when they get
exposed. I mean, I got the answers right here.
So I can actually explain the reason
why. I'm not just saying stuff for the
sake of saying it. Okay. All of the
people that hate on me that show their
face, they're uglier than me, they're
skint, they've got less life experience
than me. The people that show their
face. The people that haven't shown
their face, all of the people that's
been exposed before have been uglier
than me, fatter than me, everything
other than me. It starts it starts it
starts building a Lego piece, doesn't
it? You know, that's why that's why.
No, I didn't say I was in the sales. No,
I did not. Anyways, bro, stop shiting on
my channel cuz you're not going to
you're not you're not going to get a
reaction or get or get justifying.
There's no point making stuff up on my channel, bro.
Yeah. Because of the patterns that's
happened over the years with the people
that's done this.
Now, I I I unsubscribed from that Jo
about what, two and a half weeks ago.
I'll never go on that channel with her
again because she's another self projector. Yeah.
So, yeah. Yeah. That's why I just said
that he was biased. Yeah.
Why would someone like him be biased
when he doesn't like cowards? I just
don't understand it. Instead of instead
of insulting someone, you could maybe be
able to answer it.
You said that you don't like cowards.
These people have tried to get you into
[ __ ] multiple times via email telling
you where I am. So you could get in
trouble and you're being biased and
you're being biased. How does that make
sense, bro? It makes sense. Someone
other than him because they're just all
jealous losers on their him really, bro.
What the [ __ ] mad.
Yeah, I saw it, bro. Bro, there's
nothing chubby about me and there's
nothing fat about me either. He's self
projecting. He's another self projector.
There's nothing fat about me. There's
nothing chubby about me. The guy's
obese. Yeah, I saw that. It was like two
weeks ago and then I unsubed from him
again. This is classic projection.
Yeah, bro. It's classic projection from
him. Have you seen his hands? Have you
seen Smokeoky Bee's hands, his hands,
and then my hands?
Like, bro, the guy is obese. These
people are obese. Bomb Joe, all of these
people that have done this in the past,
bro, they're obese. There's nothing fat
about me. There's nothing chubby about
me. And even if I was fat, let's just
say for example, I was fat. I'm not fat.
These people are fatter. So, again, I
repeat myself. It's self projection with these people.
So yeah, I saw you talking [ __ ] about me
as well, Jay Willow, man. That's not
good. I didn't think you was going to be
too faced, man. I thought you was
genuine, but I caught you talking [ __ ] as well. Okay.
Well, I'm definitely definitely not fat
and that Joe definitely definitely is.
So that's that. Hey, I saw you, man. Jay
Willow talking [ __ ] bro.
What was you saying about teddies and
stuff? Yeah, whatever, man. Sorry if I
upset you with the um Sorry if I upset
you with the LT thing, bro. I just don't
like biased people, man. I'm sorry, man.
Yeah, bro. It's just self projection
with them. Like, I already know Hugh,
bro. I'm better looking than them. I've
got I've got more of a life than them,
bro. I've been out every single day, Hey, bro.
I've been out every single day. This is
the only day I've not gone out because
I'm tired as [ __ ] today, bro. You know,
I've done loads of stuff over the past
week, bro. I've actually got a life,
lad. You [ __ ] Bro. Yeah, he's that
that Joe is a self projector. He's another um
Yeah, he's another biased self projector, bro.
So, did you did you see my video on LTJ Willow?
Yeah, I do need to go to the gym to be
honest. I even said that. But yeah,
but how is this guy trying to call me
when this guy is literally obese and
he's older than me?
It seems to me everyone loads of people
in this community. Yeah, it seems to be
everyone on this community um
it seems to be anyone in this community
has got a problem with someone that's
younger and better looking than them.
That's the way it feels. Well, not
everyone, but a lot of people. It seems
to be that way, bro. Like Jo,
Nonss, Red Star, it seems. Anyone that's
better looking than them, they go for.
I've noticed that. And you'll notice
that as they get exposed again. It's
It's wild, bro. Really, really wild. Can
you give me examples of the word bias? I
don't need to, bro. I've already gave examples.
Yeah, I emailed him asking him why he
was being biased. Jay Willow,
he he definitely definitely would not
waste me, bro. This is not 5 years ago,
lad. This is not 5 years ago. And I'm
not an old woman. No, he definitely
definitely would not. Trust me. Trust
me. He definitely would not.
And I don't even know why he's saying
all of that stuff because, bro, all I
said was he's he was biased. I emailed
him asking him why is he being biased?
That's all. And then he started talking
about [ __ ] family and [ __ ] And I
weren't going to let him talk to me like that, bro.
Trust me, I'm not scared of him, bro.
Trust me, you don't know how my mind
works. I'm not scared of him, bro. This
is not four or five years ago. Believe
you me, I'm not scared of no one. Yeah.
All I asked was why are you being
biased? That's all I emailed him asking
why are you being a biased? Yeah. That's
what I asked. That's all I asked.
Cuz you got to understand, Joe Willow.
This guy don't make sense. Listen, Jay
Willow. Yeah, this guy says that he
doesn't like cowards. These people have
tried to [ __ ] with him. Yeah. Multiple
times tried to get him to do his dirty
work and he's there defending them up
their ass. And he says that he doesn't
like biased people. He says, "Oh, people
were biased when I went to Scotland. So
you you're aware of what they're like,
but you're doing the same thing."
Oh, he's got a girlfriend. He can't be a
virgin, bro. But yet when people are
calling me a virgin, you don't bring up
the 19year-old, the porno that I put out
there and all the other things. What's
going on, bro? What's really really going on?
And then when I asked him why he done
it, he's coming with all of these
threats. I'm asking you why are you
being biased? If you're speaking your
mind, go speak your mind when someone's
calling me stuff. Bring up the
19year-old. Bring up the porno. Don't
bring up some [ __ ] girlfriend who
we've not got. Like it sounds immature,
but it's Yeah, I'm sick of going over
this. And it's not even just about that,
Jay Willow. He's been biased with money
and police as well with the police
thing, with the money thing. They've
done it with money as well, bro. They've
done it with multiple different things.
So it's it's three things they've done
it about. So at the end of the day, bro,
if you don't like cowards, but this is
what I'm trying to say. If you do not
like cowards, if you know these people
have tried [ __ ] with you, why are you
to their rescue? It doesn't it doesn't
make sense. Like this is what I'm trying
to say. The guy's saying that he's
supposed to have a degree. Yeah. Okay.
So why are you to this guy's rescue like
Superman every time I go for him. It's like
it doesn't make sense.
It doesn't make sense. You know these
people have tried [ __ ] with you.
And then he says, "Oh, well, you pay
them." I said, "Yeah, okay. I pay them a
million pounds. Every woman I've had sex
with, I have paid them a million
pounds." Okay. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Okay. A
million pounds. I paid every single
woman. Yeah. Yeah. Okay. So, and and and
your point is what? And you can argue,
okay, I paid them all a million pound.
I'm going to I'm going to pretend you're
right. And I've paid them a million
pounds. And what? Still more than a
girlfriend. So, why are we not seeing
you on any of these channels?
Don't cut me off if someone's going for
me. Yeah. And calling me a virgin and I
want to call them a virgin. Don't start
cutting me off trying to over talk me
about, oh bro, he's got a girlfriend,
you know. Don't start cutting me off,
bro. When you're not going to cut anyone
else off with evidence that you've
actually seen. Don't do that, bro. It's annoying.
Yeah. Yeah. See you later.
So that's that, bro. You know what I
mean? Then he starts getting all aggy about it. It's weird.
So yeah, Jay Willow, I just I just say
it how I see it. I don't like biased people. Simple.
Just do not like bias people. And you
wouldn't expect it from someone like him as well.
You would not ex you would not uh you
would not expect it from someone like
him who knows what these people are like
that's got a history with these people
and them being biased pretty much the
same as me. It don't make no sense, bro.
It does not make no sense.
It's not an opinion, bro. The guy is
biased. I've explained it multiple
multiple times now. Yeah,
you know, it's happened multiple times
with multiple different people.
So, simple as that.
And they're also biased with the police
as well. Monty man Monty Man Monty man
calls Listen, there's another thing.
Yeah. Monty man calls the police, he's a
grass. Peter Belly calls the police,
he's a grass. Someone else calls the
police, everyone gives them the thumbs
up. Bro, it's blame and biasness. It's
more than one example,
you know. It's it's more than one
example. Don't cut me off when I'm
calling someone that's calling me. If
you ain't got opinion on them with the
[ __ ] that I proven, I don't want to hear
about this girlfriend. Simple as that.
And if no one's going to say it, I'll
I'll say it. And I said it. Simple. That's it. So, yeah.
Weird. It is strange, bro. It is
strange. Um, yeah, they're biased with
the police as well. Monty got called a
grass multiple times as well. Monty got
called a grass.
Monty's been called a grass. I've been
called a grass as well. Um, so
you do have to start questioning people,
J Willow. You really have to start
questioning people, mate. So
that's that, bro.
Don't want to hear you ever talk about
anyone being biased again if you if you
if you try to meet someone. Simple as that.
>> Yeah. Anyone from that channel, they're
all the same story.
Anyone from that channel is the same,
bro. Anyone. Most people. I mean, Jay
Willow's all right. [ __ ] how hard can
it be is all right. There's some people
that are right but majority of the
people from that and that Chris seems to
be all right as well. Even though he
doesn't come on my channel, um he seems
to be all right as well. There there's a
few but majority of them, bro. They're
just wasters, bro. Absolute wasters.
I don't even know why anyone even goes
on that channel, bro.
To be honest, I don't know why they go
on that channel, lad.
Yeah, Mont, you're talking about
yourself. See you later. But yeah,
that's that, bro.
I got a beef tade early hours in the
morning, bro. Yes. Um before before I
went to sleep. Yeah.
Yeah. I was speaking to my friend in
Amsterdam. Yeah. I just got some food. I
just fell asleep, bro. Yeah.
Anyways, I don't want to hear this bias
thing again, bro. It's giving me a [ __ ] headache.
So, yeah, that's it.
Yeah, we got another t-shirt coming.
I've got I got a medium, bro. And it's
still a little big to be fair. It's
still a little big to be to be honest
with you, bro. I'll show you. Look.
Hopefully when I wash it and that
hopefully when I wash it, it should be a
bit Look, this is a medium and it's
still a little bit too big. Well, not
too big, but it's just a bit loose in it. So,
[ __ ] hell, bro. I am so tired, man.
So tired. [ __ ] Got B on it, man. Yeah.
Where the [ __ ] is Steven? You're
supposed to help me with this [ __ ]
Lego. The [ __ ]
What should I do today, bro? I don't
even want to stay in. But there's
nothing to do today. There's nothing in
the cinema, Grecy.
There's literally nothing to do, man. >> Yeah.
I think you secretly like the me and LT
thing, don't you, Greavvesy? I don't
like it, bro.
I don't like any of it. I think it's all [ __ ] weird.
I think it's all weird. Me,
but I shouldn't even really be on here
to be honest, bro. I do actually really
need to come off this [ __ ]
Like the [ __ ] that people do on here and
that, bro. I really do need to actually
come off here, bro. I really actually do, bro.
Seriously, like I really really do. It's
not even a joke.
The grassing, the [ __ ] jealous
people, the repeating and [ __ ] It
doesn't offer anything, does it?
Really, bro? If you think about it,
I really do to be honest with you need
to come off this [ __ ] But honestly, all jokes aside,
I'll probably start going out drinking
again soon. Where are we now? January.
I said March, but maybe midFebruary. I
don't know. But yeah, as soon as I start
going out again, I think I'm Well, I'm
done anyways. I think, bro.
It's such it's just so do you not find
it the most weirdest embarrassing
community ever. Greavvesy
do not think like being a normal person
how weird this place actually is
because majority come majority people
come on here because of Timmy.
You come on here, but do not think how
just weird it is.
Now, all jokes aside,
you got people that are older than you
self-projecting every day. You got
people arguing with people that they
don't know. It's so weird, man. Is it?
You got people jealous of people that
they don't know. What the [ __ ] man?
It is weird, isn't it?
Yeah, I had egg toast and egg toast and
bacon. I had
I might go and play some pool, I think.
Practice a few game of pool. A few a few
games of Paul, I think.
I don't know, bro. I don't really want
to be in today, even though there's
nothing to do.
practice a few games with Paul Grezy.
Do you see little Yoda this morning?
Grezy. Oh, bless.
He's cute, isn't it? In that little position.
But yeah, most of the most of it with
these people on here is self projection.
Joe self projector. L J self projector.
Literally all of them are self projectors.
Cuz why don't you tell that Joe F to
come on camera and show us what he looks
like. Exactly, bro.
You'll always win that way, bro. Sure.
Straight onto YouTube again.
Are you going out today, Gregy? [ __ ]
nothing on the cinema. The [ __ ] all to
do, bro. It's boring as [ __ ] Yeah,
I don't know what I'm doing, bro.
I'm done with that roulette [ __ ] now.
Anyways, I won that football bet, so
that's good, isn't it? Um,
yeah, but it's not a horror film, bro.
And I'm only interested in horrors.
I might just go and play a few game of
pause, bro. I might just practice.
No, I don't. Nope.
No, it's not really, bro. It's not
really, Grezy. Come on now. No,
I don't really suffer from Well, I'm not
going to say anything much on here
anyways, bro, cuz there's too many
grasses. But yeah.
Well, you're wrong.
You're very, very, very wrong.
Nope. I don't get no mood swings no
more. I do my washing and everything. Nope.
I was only depressed when I was dating.
And two weeks after that was so
depressing, bro. Oh my god. It took ages
to go away. That's the only time I was depressed.
No. Not really.
Unless I lose on roulette, I'm fine.
I don't, bro. I literally literally don't.
No, I don't. I literally don't. I only
did when I was [ __ ] dating.
That was depressing. I agree. That was
depressing, was it? That dating [ __ ]
Yeah, that was that was very very depressing.
It was bad, bro. It was [ __ ] bad,
bro. It was bad as [ __ ]
>> No, I'm just tired.
Remember, Greavvesy, you can't deprive
Greavves of content, [ __ ]
I wonder what that guy looks like in
real life. That that that said that, bro.
Yeah, because they ain't got a life of their own.
Who does? Why, bro? Why do you think
Listen, bro, why do you think they sit
on here 24/7? Yeah. Calling other
people's skin and they're the ones sat
on YouTube 24/7.
Why do you think that, bro? Just put two
and two together. It's obvious.
You'd be depressed if you live with your mom.
What the [ __ ] are you talking about? But
yeah, why do you think that anyways?
Yeah. Again, he's obsessing over my life again.
They obsessed over other people's life
cuz they ain't got a life of their own, bro.
Cuz they ain't got a life of their own.
That's why That's why they're sat on
YouTube 24/7 calling people skin when
they skin themselves.
Don't think too much into it, bro. It's
just self projecting with these people.
Always has been, always will be.
I think I'm going to go play a few games
of pool, I think, bro. Yeah,
I'm not staying in all day. [ __ ] boring it.
Oh, I'm so tired. Musicy,
you don't have a job, Timmy.
You still there? Who? J.
Bless you. You poor [ __ ]
Grievy. You poor [ __ ] So what you
saying is that guy picking his moment
when to come back on.
A look at you just picking your moment.
So what you saying? He's picking his moment.
Yeah, just picking his moment.
Oh, look at you
just picking your moment.
Yeah, maybe if I do like an approach
video and pull it up, he'll come back in it.
Yeah, cuz when I started doing
approaches, he started coming back in it
saying people on Reddit say you can get
sex whenever you want.
So, what did you say, Greasy? So you
said if I was you said if I was like if
I was into men Yeah. and I started
showing my bad experiences with men
they and I started showing my bad
experiences with men
they would um
and I started showing my bad experiences
with men they would make excuses.
They they wouldn't make excuses. You
said in it you What did you say? They
wouldn't make the same excuses
like they do with women.
That's what you said, is it?
Yeah. That's funny that, bro. They
wouldn't make the same excuses, is it?
That's funny as [ __ ] is it? Yeah, man.
All right. This guy is a proper stalker, bro.
This Peter Files, bro. Proper.
Here's another one that's jealous of me, bro.
And you know all of this. This is
because they're unhappy with their own lives.
Yeah. He's the account that's been doing this, bro.
Oh, you're bad. Why have you got a
picture of me, bro? Someone that's
better looking than you.
That's nice, bro. That's a nice picture.
Someone that's better looking than you,
bro. Thank you. Oh,
that's another one that's jealous.
That's one of the reasons I want to
leave YouTube, though, cuz this guy is a
proper proper uh he's a proper proper grass.
This guy, this Peter Fight Files, he's a
proper proper grass. Bro,
I'm going to report this account. Hold on.
I've actually blocked it.
Yeah, I'm reporting this account. Uh
Hopefully get banned in it.
Imagine that C gets banned. He has to do
it all over again. Could
you imagine? He has to do it all over
again, bro. One second.
Everyone, yeah, report that Peter Files account.
I'm going to get my friends to do it as well. Yeah, man.
Yeah, reported it, bro.
Who do you think that account is?
Who do you think that account is, bro? Grezy.
Yeah, man. I'm going to come off this
community, I think, soon, bro.
If that account don't get banned.
Yeah. He just sits there and stalks me
in it, bro.
All right, Indigo, what did you say
about my beard, bro? What did you say
What' you say about my beard?
What' you say about my beard, bro?
Let's see your beard.
Let's see your beard, bro. Come on.
No, I'm not too bad, bro. I've just I'm
just doing nothing today.
Let's see your beard, bro. Talking about
my beard. Yeah. Yeah. Let's see your beard, bro.
Py, there's no point talking [ __ ] on
people's back, bro. And I'm literally
way better looking than you'll ever be.
Just like a lot of the these other
people that do it, bro. It's just really pointless.
Oh, just Peter Files.
Yeah, I've reported it.
He's going to be the reason why I come
off of YouTube, by the way, as well. I
don't want someone watching me 24/7
that's grassing, bro.
Yeah, I might. I am coming off here
anyways. I really really am coming off
here like Monty just not doing anything today.
I'm just going to get all the genuine
people to email me, bro. Like [ __ ]
other people. If they do, if they do, if
they don't, they don't. I don't care. I
know what this guy following me about,
bro. He's a grass as well.
He's a nasty little grass. Cuz we know
it wasn't We know it wasn't uh we know
it wasn't that [ __ ] people from Tik
Tok that reported me.
Yeah, but who wants to stay on here
though with a bunch of repeaters?
Who wants to be on here with a bunch of
repeating little grasses
that ain't got no life? Who really wants
to, bro? I can't blame him. I'd rather
be told I run off to be honest. So, I'd
rather be, bro.
Think about it, bro. He stays on He
Okay, so the guy stays on here and then
what? So, he stays on here. He goes live
and then what? You see the same people,
the same projectors. Okay. And then
what? Bro, what does what does he
achieve by doing that in his defense?
Come on. Come on, man. That account is
weird. That Peter Foul account is weird, bro. Yeah,
he's a he's a dirty little grass as well.
Maybe he's a dirty little police informant. Yeah,
he's he's a grass, bro. He's a dirty
grass. I didn't get arrested, but he's a
dirty grass anyways.
Dirty dirty grass.
Why did you see that Yuki when the
police went on Yuki's door? Grely, they
went on Yuki's door.
They went on Yuki's door. Yeah, bro. Peter Files.
Yeah, he's a stalker, bro.
And what it is is because they unhappy
with their own lives, that's why they do
this. People like this thoughts of Peter
fight because they know their lives are
over. They want to try to [ __ ] other
people's life up.
That's what the pattern is on here, bro.
Because no one no one gets affected like
that, Gregy, for just saying stuff. All
of these people, bro, that do this are
worse looking than me. They got less
money than me. They got less of a life
The same people that comment on that
channel as well, bro. You know what I mean?
Oh, Mr. Pip.
Oh, you wrote a comment. Uh,
well, I don't even know who that is.
You met a 15y old and you couldn't tell
if he was 15, he was 30. Oh, at least
someone said something to him. That's the first.
That's the first. Oh, that's good, man.
You don't really get that,
bro. They're proper proper nerds on
here, is it?
Yeah. Well, it is with these people,
like I've said multiple times, they hate
anyone that's jungle and better looking
than them. They find problems with
they don't like anyone that's not
wasters like them. Because let's be
real, they are wasters on this
community. Most of them, bro. They are literally wasters.
What could they possibly have if they
wanted [ __ ] all day?
Proper proper wasters.
Yeah. Weird, bro.
Yeah, man. Oh, [ __ ] hell.
Bum bum bum.
I don't go on you. I don't go on you. I
don't go on YouTube live all day. This
is the first day I've not actually gone out.
So, I'm not doing the same thing. I'm
literally not doing the same thing. How
do you work that one out?
Come on, man. Nowhere near the same thing.
Yeah, I am actually coming off this
thing soon though for real. For real,
bro. That account is weird. I've
reported it for copyrights as well. Yeah.
Yeah, I've reported it for copyright.
[ __ ] off, bro. Hey, did you see Did you
see the football battle I won, Steven Howard?
It was lovely, isn't it?
It was lovely, bro. Was it?
Nothing, bro. It's just talking about
these self projectors. But, uh, yeah. Oh man,
I'm so tired today, bro.
I don't have five both teams to score,
bro. I put 20 pound on it. I won 223
back from 20 pound.
It's on my community post. Sorry, I've
had to go on this channel now cuz
something to do with the Streamyard and [ __ ]
Yeah, man. It's on the community post.
Yeah, I just done five in it cuz I was bored. So,
I should have paid me more than that.
Five is hard to get, bro. It's hard
enough to get two sometimes. Yeah.
Did you see my videos on LT Steven Howard?
Yeah, the odds are so [ __ ] bro.
I was playing I was playing roulette. I
was playing roulette a lot last week.
Just wasn't winning nothing, bro. You
can't even win on that [ __ ] anymore. The
odds are [ __ ]
The odds are so [ __ ] on it now. It is.
That's for me to know and you to never find out.
You don't need to know that.
Yeah. on my other channel. I can't go
live on it because something with the
Streamyard destination. So, I've had to
make a new account.
I was playing online roulette Steven
Howard uh last week. [ __ ] so fixed,
bro. So fixed.
You can't win on anything now but
football it seems. So
what to do today.
Yeah, I know, bro. Yeah.
All right, everyone report that um Peter
Foul's account, by the way. All right,
Stephen Howard, report that account.
Oh, look at this, bro. All right, I'm
reading this guy. This description
is a This person's a sad bastard. I'm
reading this. Yeah.
Oh my god. In 2023, he approached a
woman called Morgan from Boston after
she rejected him. He engaged in a
stalking and harassment campaign that
continues to this day. No one rejected
me, you little sado. This is what I mean
with these people, bro. They write up
stuff and make stuff up.
He's a grass as well, bro. This per this
this account is a grass.
I'm actually going to make a new
channel, bro. Like to go live on where
this [ __ ] can't find me. I'm actually
going to do it, bro. Cuz this guy
actually is a grass, you know?
I've already reported it. I'm going to
link it. Yeah. Report this account. Try
and get this account closed down. Then
he's going to have to put all them
videos back on another channel.
Yeah, I've just read him, bro.
I've just linked it, bro. Report that account
because I'm just going to make a new
channel, bro. If that's the case, bro.
Cuz I'm not going live and this guy's
recording everything. He's a little
dirty grass as well, bro.
He's a proper proper police informant as well. Yeah.
I should know better, bro. At this
stage, I should know better than these
people. If this account doesn't get
banned, I'm I'm making a new account,
bro. So, that's the way it's got to be.
So, it's either like you're going to email me
the genuine people and then you're going
to f and then we can still go live and that.
Yeah, I heard about that on Instagram
in the elevator was it? So, that's the
way it's going to be, bro. Cuz I don't
want this guy following me about.
No, no, we don't, bro. Because he's an informant.
No, no, no, no, no, bro. Because the
guy's a grass. No, no, no. Because the
guy is an actual grass, bro.
So, I don't want And I don't want these
people following me in it. Simple. Why
do you think I've got another channel
for all of my approaches and [ __ ] Oh,
you don't know about the Lego?
One second, Captain. Let me show you
about Lego. I got some Lego.
Look, this is I I got some Lego Star Wars.
Look at Yodi.
I have to do this bit. Look, I [ __ ] up somewhere here. Yeah, look.
He's so cute, isn't he?
Back in you go, Yodi. He comes out as well.
Yeah, you you are a little grass, bro.
Shut up. Cuz how come your channel come
up then? When I went when I had to go to
the police station, I didn't get
arrested anyways. But still, obviously
it's you. It is you because your channel
come up. They showed me your channel.
So, it was obviously you.
I love your little madeup stuff in your
description as well about I got
rejected. No one got rejected by any
[ __ ] American, bro. You make up
You make up [ __ ] You make up
literally [ __ ] mate. That's not
what happened. That's your madeup little
version of things.
That's your little madeup version.
Oi, did you did you see the thing with
the LT, Steven Howard? Hey, you know
what makes me laugh here is LT calls you
a troll. Yeah, but you're the only one
that's not unbiased. That's what I find
strange. Yeah, he was calling you a troll.
Someone with an agenda is calling you a
troll. Yeah, that's funny, bro, isn't it?
Steven Howard's a troll. Steven Howard's
trolling you. So then if Steven trolling
me, why are you the one that's biased
and not him? That's a good question.
The amount of times I defended this guy
when people used to dismiss him going to
places and then he's being biased about me.
Then he's then he's being then he acts
biased towards me. What the [ __ ]
That's not fair, is it? Mad.
Do you like Little Yoda? He's a lovely
character, isn't he, Grezy? I'm going to
I'm going to order some more Legos soon
when I complete that one. Greezy,
it's going to cost over £100. But this
one's got more characters. Yeah,
I just emailed him asking him why does
he keep defending thingy when I call him
a virgin, but then when he's calling me
a virgin, he doesn't say anything. And
then he started getting assy about it in it. So,
I'm sure you saw the videos.
I'm just going to come off here
eventually, Grezy. I really, really am.
So, I'm going to I'm going to do an email. Yeah.
So, all the genuine people going to
email me and then we're just going to go
live on that channel and talk about I
want you know what? I want a channel.
Yeah. Where there's no bullshitters, no
projectors, no red star watching me, no
nothing. And I don't want these people
watching me, bro.
Bro, you're talking I haven't achieved any goals,
bro. Are you sure you're not talking about yourself,
bro? You know, you do realize you're
talking about yourself, lad.
Read what you just wrote. It's funny you
still come here and yet you're still
lonely after all those years. It's like
you haven't literally bro. You do
realize you're talking about yourself.
That's why no one's getting mad. Bit
like what you do every day is talk about
yourselves. So yeah, go figure, lad.
I don't use lonely as an insult. Do you
know? I never say to these people that
they've got no friends, you know, even
though they don't have no friends. I
never use that as an insult.
Do you know why I never use that as an
insult, Steven Howard? When these when
these self-p projectors are saying that
I've got no friends or whatever, you
know why I never use that as an insult
back to them.
And I'll tell you why if you want to
know. Do you know why I never tell them
that they've got no friends?
Stop talking about yourself, rat face.
Stop talking about yourself. Another self projector.
Go to the dentist and fix your gaps
between your teeth. You get it for free,
mate. See you later. Sad. Anyways, so do
you want me to tell you why I I don't
tell these people that they got no friends?
Some of the some of the insults LT was
saying to me was just such he said he he
he told me that I got no kids.
You've got no kids as an insult. Is that
really an insult, bro? telling someone
they ain't got no kids.
But no. Anyways, the reason I tell them
they ain't The reason I don't tell them
that is because even if someone
generally had no friends, they could
actually get a life. They could still
have a life. They could still go out.
They could still socialize. They could
still meet people. So to me, when
someone says someone's got no friends,
that's not even an insult, bro. I mean,
you could have no friends and go to
another country, live in another
country, you know, [ __ ] that. That's
not even an insult, bro. There's loads
of things you could do and no one even
needs friends anyways. That's why I
never use it as an insult. So
yeah, I could go on kick though. I could
I don't want these jealous people
[ __ ] All I said to him, Steven
Howard, was why are you so fast enough
to defend um your boyfriend every time
he's calling me a virgin? You're you're
so fast to butt in. But then when I'm
calling him, when he's calling me one,
you don't say anything about it. You
don't bring up the 19year-old. You don't
bring up Sig. You don't bring up all the
women that I've proven and I've been
with sexually. But you're so fast to
talk about this girlfriend.
And I was I was getting so pissed off at
it, bro. I just kept I emailed him twice
and I said, "Why are you being biased?
That's what I said." And he come out
with a [ __ ] long ass paragraph.
Like they're all the same on here, bro.
They really really really majority are
all the same on here, lad. Except from a few people. Trust me. Yeah.
So biased. So so so biased. I can't
stand biased people.
You've seen it before though. Joe F used
to do it as well. Don't you remember the
same conversation I used to have with
Joe F, Steven Howard, about the bisonness.
I know they pro. Yeah, that's literally
what they're doing. They're white
knighting him. And I said to him as
well, I said to the guy, and do you know
the maddest thing about it? I said to
the guy, "Yeah, bro, he's calling me a
virgin. Do you not want to talk about
the 19year-old? Do you not want to talk
about Sig? Do you not want to talk about
the one in Manchester? You don't want to
talk about the one in Nottingham. Oh,
you paid, bro?
Oh, so I paid now. Is that the excuse
you're using? I know it's And you know
what's so mad? No, no, no, no, no. But
you know the maddest thing is that this
guy has caused him problems before. This
guy has [ __ ] stirred before trying to
get him in trouble and he's he's the
biggest coward ever, but yet he white
nights him. I know. It's mad, isn't it?
It literally literally That is That's
the mad thing, bro. That literally is
because he knows what these people like.
He's had problems with these people himself
being biased and stuff.
Yeah. And then Yeah. Like you said, they
white night him. Yeah. That is literally
what they do. Yeah. You put in a better
way than me. Yeah. It is literally white
knighting. They literally do do it. Yeah.
It's weird, bro. It is very weird. And
the money thing, Stephen Hour, do you
remember the money thing?
I showed these people £5.7,000 in cash.
Do you hear the excuse? Oh, well, uh,
you can't show it now. And they made up
by their own little rules for me. And
then when Monty called the police, he
was called a grass. And then
And then when Monty called the police,
he was a grass.
And then um when when he does it,
everyone gives him a thumbs up.
Strange someone like him would be biased
though. Strange someone like him would be biased.
Him of all people. That is weird, bro.
Yeah. I unsubed from that Jo about two weeks ago.
Steven Howard about two weeks ago. Yeah.
Yeah. I unsubed about like two weeks
ago, bro. On the arcade thing because
the guy is just completing a self projector.
So, I just unsubed it.
Yeah, it is weird.
Yeah, it's Timmy.
So, yeah, Stephen Al, we're going to
have to do something about this channel, bro.
We're literally going to have to do
something about this channel, man.
Yeah, we're going to have to do
something about this channel, bro. Yeah,
I don't want to entertain these weirdos
anymore, bro. I don't entertain them
anyways, but I don't want them watching
me, bro. They're not even worth talking about.
I saw a sher co advert today.
Reminded me of someone.
Oh yeah, I saw it on the TV, bro. It
reminded me of someone.
Yeah. So, anyways, back to the football.
Yeah. I don't know why the odds have got
so [ __ ] bro.
Did you s Did you see my roulette video, Steven Howard?
I'm not ever going back to that [ __ ]
again, bro. [ __ ] that.
Never again, bro. Never again.
Never [ __ ] ever [ __ ] a [ __ ] again.
It should have paid way better. It
should have been like4500,
but it's still £220 from 20 in it.
It's still a good win, but it should
have been way better. But that's the
odds now, unfortunately.
That's just the way the odds are now. Unfortunately, bro.
Yeah. People used to say Sher Walker was
attractive to fit in though.
That's They used to just say that to fit in. Steven Howard.
Yeah, the 100 pound one. It's so rigged
that roulette, bro.
I'm not playing that again, bro.
I think football is the only way you can
win money now, bro. I really Well,
obviously there's probably other sports
and that, but I don't think, bro, that
roulette is so fixed.
So so so fixed, bro.
I've done a lot of gambling recently, bro.
And it's just so fixed. You can't win on it, bro.
Yeah. The 100 pound one. Yeah.
Yeah, I tried to shut the account down
and they come out with all excuses why
why they wouldn't do it. They come out
with all these excuses why they wouldn't do it.
Yeah, these gambling sites, bro.
Do you think you can win on roulette
anymore, Steven Howard? I don't think
you can in it.
I don't think you can in it.
I don't think so.
No, I don't I don't think so.
Yeah, I was playing the Brookies one as
well. It wasn't having it for toffee.
Steven Howard, it wasn't having it for
[ __ ] toffee, man.
It wasn't having it for [ __ ] toffee. Yeah,
I'm coming off in a minute, bro. I'm
going to go and do something today, bro.
I'm [ __ ] bored, bro.
Smokey B. Smokey
Yeah. Well, I'll be back later, bro.
I can't be boing.
Reason I haven't been going out drinking.
It's too cold, bro.
It's too cold, man. Yeah.
Anyways, I'll be back later. Yeah. See you, man.
Yeah. I'll be back later.