Yeah. What the hell? [ __ ] hell,
bro. What the [ __ ] [Music] [ __ ] hell
me. I' had a roast for ages,
but I don't think I'm going to go for
one today. I think
so. I don't think
so, man. Stop being weird. Stop saying
weird stuff like Sunny. That's so
weird. Yeah, man. I [ __ ] had some broken
sleep. Speaking to this woman yesterday
on Reddit. She lives in America. How do
you uh feel about me coming to America
and seeing you then? She was in the East
Coast, too. So, kill two birds with one side.
E. Yeah, we was talking in it. road country,
eh? Yeah, I remember speaking to you
yesterday about um my friend went out
yesterday approaching. Same [ __ ]
Boyfriend, that's why I stayed
in. I woke up with indigestion. I I woke
up with indigestion because I I ate
McDonald's before I went to sleep. I
spent like4 on food yesterday. Jeez.
I'm scaring the police. So these people say Prince.
What? Where are
you? He done a video saying that he's quitting YouTube now. Uh yeah,
man. What odd one? Cuz he said that he's done with
YouTube. Yes, but he done a video on
that channel said that he's done with YouTube.
Uh, I'm thinking of buying um buying Sha
an escort, you know. I'm actually
thinking of buying Shan an escort so he
actually gets to experience sex for the first
time. I'm not even joking, man. I was
actually thinking no one should be a
30year-old virgin. Not one person should
be a 30year-old virgin.
So I might I might buy him an [Music] escal 200
pound. Yeah, nice tree.
E can't want somebody die a virgin,
mate. Go well 30 is a [ __ ] virgin. I
can't have it. I can't [ __ ] have it,
mate. I'm sorry. I can't [ __ ] have
it, cult. I'm not made that way, mate. Sorry, lad. [ __ ] [Laughter]
Yeah. Don't want somebody [ __ ] die a
virgin. [ __ ] nah, mate. You can't
have that. Won't [ __ ] have that, lad. Can't have
Ving a little virgin, mate. Who's
there? Ding, man. Are
you want to die?
Yeah. 1502 200 pound. I was actually
thinking yesterday like he he actually
really really is a virgin. Just just
because someone's in a relationship, it
doesn't mean nothing. There are people
in relationships that go months without
sex. There's people in relationships
without a [ __ ] dick.
There's people in in literally sexless
relationships. He's literally a [ __ ]
virgin. There's people that are in
relationships that get more sex than
people that are in relationships. You
know, if you really are not a virgin,
which you [ __ ] well are, prove it.
[ __ ] prove it like I've done on
[ __ ] five, six different occasions.
And if you're not willing to do that,
then you're a [ __ ] little virgin.
Simple. You're a [ __ ]
virgin. I love how when you call him a
virgin, everyone's like, "Oh, he can't
he can't he can't be a virgin cuz he's
got a girlfriend." That literally means
nothing. Bro, I have literally proved
I've had sex about five
times. Like, they're literally all
[ __ ] biased on
here. No, he definitely definitely is a
virgin, man. Something is not happening. in that bedroom.
Yeah. Oh, I love that, man. I'll be I'll
be on most day talking to myself. I'm
not going to be on it most of I wasn't
yesterday. We the YouTube spastics. I
love how you say we. We all know. Yeah.
The the YouTube spastics that don't
leave the house. That's the we. Yeah,
that's what what you mean by
we. Yeah, I'm not on YouTube most of the
day ever. I'm hardly ever on here
anymore cuz Yeah, it's just the same
atmosphere. Same same [ __ ] people
that ain't got a life. Same
atmosphere, same [ __ ] shitty
comebacks. Yeah. Oh, I'm not talking to myself. There
there's you YouTube every day. You can't
take one day off of YouTube. Imagine
that. Imagine you can't take one day off
of YouTube. [ __ ] hell. That is a
madness. Yeah, he literally does. He
needs to go get laid, lose his virginity
as well. But um yeah, it's it's mad how
these people can't take one single day off of
YouTube. I can't get over it. No, no,
no, no, no. I'm not repeating. I'm not
repeating. I'm I'm generally I'm
generally like I generally want to know
why you people can't take one day off of
your chores. Like cuz you call people
skin, you call people lonely, you tell
people they ain't got no friends, right?
Yet you people on YouTube every single
[ __ ] day of your lives repeating
yourselves. So it doesn't look good,
does it, man? I'm I'm I'm asking a
question. No, no, no. I'm not repeating.
I'm asking you a
question. You know, you're you're
deflecting by saying that I'm repeating.
I want to know why you people on YouTube every
day. Hey Cole, do you know what? I
looked up something yesterday, right? I
looked up, is there any McDonald's,
right, in the whole of UK that's halal?
And there isn't, which is mad
really. There's halal KFC's. Obviously,
there's halal. You know what, mate?
They've just opened a [ __ ] hot dog
shop right near where I live. And guess
what? It's halal. Absolutely [ __ ]
pointless. What's the point of like
putting in what's the point of putting
effort and [ __ ]
into into like a [ __ ] shop if it's
just and it is a hot dog shop and it's
allowed which means it's not going to be
pork. It's going to be chicken. Boring,
man. It's [ __ ] [ __ ] bors me. It
does. But yeah, there's no McDonald's
that's allowing the whole of England or Burger
King, which obviously is good, but I'm
surprised to be fair. Not one. I wonder
why. I think it's because obviously, you
know, the chicken
nuggets, they can't obviously make it
allow if they're making chicken nuggets
and obviously bacon and and stuff maybe,
but none of them are allowed.
Uh, not even in like proper proper like Muslim areas. Nope. None.
Mad. One second, bro.
So, so do you
think do you think Sevil Cole's good-looking
cult? Yeah, I know, bro. I got a lot of
haters, man. A lot of haters. I need you to be
fair. Yeah. Sean says, "If you don't find
Sher." I know. They're hypocrites.
They're hypocrites. It's They ain't got
They ain't got a life, bro. I'm on it
today cuz to be honest with you, I'm
quite bored. I've got nothing to do
today and I didn't go out yesterday.
They have no life. They've been doing it
for years. They've been doing it for years, buddy.
years. Yep. You already know, bro.
Exactly. And bro, you can see that I'm
not on here much anymore. And that's
what I'm saying, bro. Like, they come on
here and they call me skin and they
don't know me. They don't know how much
money I have. They don't know where I
live. They don't know how many friends
I've got. They're self-reflectors. Yeah.
Yeah. They are skint disabled virgins.
That's literally what they are. And
they're mters as well. Have you seen
their faces? They call me ugly, bro.
ugly, right? But have you seen right?
Have you seen when these people's faces
get out there how ugly they are?
Everything is just a self projection of
their own life. Because like you said,
what I've been saying, they wouldn't be
on here. They wouldn't be every day.
They literally would not be on here
every [ __ ] day if they wasn't. I was
off of YouTube over a week. I didn't
look at it once. Yeah.
fatkinned virgins and and you catch them
out as well cult because if you go on
Lord Jay's right
and when they type you will see some of
them say that they're
skinn Yeah. You will see some of them
they will say they're skint until this
day that day. Bro, I've not been skinned
in about three
years. Absolutely no money. Three years.
A whole 3 years, bro. Literally, a whole
three years I have not been skinned, but
they still say that I'm skinn every day
because they're self
projectors. You see what I'm
saying? They all look ugly. They've all
got nothing. They're the same. They're
the [ __ ] same people, bro. All
virgins. They defend women, yet they
don't even leave their house and speak
to women. So, what would the [ __ ] would
they know what women are like? And
that's what makes me laugh, right? is
like these people sit here defend women
and try to critique you. But hold on a
minute. When was the last time these
people went out and spoke to
women? When was the last time these
people went out and actually had a woman
and spoke to a
woman? Come on, bro. And that's And
there you go. You'll find your answer.
Yeah, they all fat, ugly, disabled
virgins. That's why they order every
day. Can't get a life. Been on it for
years now. [ __ ] years. Yeah. this bro life.
Yeah. Yeah, bro. Anyways, [ __ ] enough
about these haters. We know what they
are. We know why they do what they
do. Yeah. They don't fit in society.
Simple. But what makes me laugh though,
one last thing. Yeah, we haven't sp this
for ages, is they tell people to get a
job, but they don't have a job themselves.
They literally don't even have a job
themselves. They sit on YouTube on their
skin pathetic asses every day telling
other people to get a job. And if they
find out that you had a job, they'd grass you
up? You think, bro, if I ever had a job,
I would ever tell any of these people?
Do you really really think I would ever
tell these little skin [ __ ] virgin
[ __ ] grasses anything? Are you
[ __ ] having a bloody, mate? No
way. No way,
bro. Yeah, I've been to Leads. They're [Music]
const hated it.
Yeah. And and it's like what you said,
these people are talking as if they
wouldn't they they would go and approach
they would sorry they would go and
approach a woman and then the woman
wouldn't say they've got a boyfriend.
It's like what you were saying. They
think that they any different? Would
they [ __ ] get any different,
bro? They'd get rejected more than
you. Yeah. I've been all over as well. I
would never tell anyone anything, bro. He's
mad. Why would
you like remember do you remember that
virgin? What he used to do was um try to
find out women um that I've been with so
he could try to [ __ ] up for me because
he's a virgin and he's never been laid
and he's too ugly to get anything
himself. Yeah. He used to like I used to
have to now like I don't trust this
community. So what I do is whenever I
get a woman I get her WhatsApp because
obviously it's encrypted in it so no one
can find them. Um never had people on
Instagram nothing just in case cuz that little
virgin would um always try to find out
who they were and then like [ __ ] it up.
Try to [ __ ] it up cuz he's an ugly
virgin that can't get nothing himself. I
like my voice. It's actually quite nice,
isn't it? Yeah, I think it's quite nice,
buddy. Is it a virgin? Rusty little virgin. [Music]
Yeah. So, what's your favorite city in
the whole of the UK,
cult? Uh, what is mine? I would say
London. It's got to be London
it. And then the second one maybe Edinburgh. Edinburgh.
Edinburgh I think is my second in terms of like
um in terms of like it being nicer than
anywhere else. I'd say it's in London
than Edinburgh I think.
Yeah, I think so.
Yeah. Don't know about you. I don't
know. It just looks very nice. Like the
builders are nice there as well. [Laughter] Yeah. I think
Yeah. box. Here we go.
You're coming to London. Oh, yeah. That's
nice. I won't be meeting
you. Sorry, mate. I don't entertain this
bastard community. You come all you want. Join the link. Come
on. Not any real money, man. Is it Bye-bye now. [Laughter]
That's not the real body, man. Anyways,
you can tell by the [ __ ] hashtags,
bro. [ __ ] You can tell by the
hashtags. Mug should be coming tomorrow.
18 quid. That cost
me. Oh, [ __ ]
me. 18 pound. That
[ __ ] monger. Oh, self projectors.
These little fat ugly skinned people
keep coming to my channel. Self
reflectors get blind. They don't get a
uh they don't get a platform on my
channel. Self-reflectors don't get a
um don't get a platform on my channel.
Sadly, it's so mad um cult how you can't
go a whole day on YouTube without
hearing the word skin.
It's mad. Like these these mongos have
been repeating themselves for [ __ ]
over a decade. Imagine that. Over a
decade just talking about their own
lives on YouTube. These people's parents
must be so proud. still single
ladies. Oh, no one cares, Beex. Nobody
cares. But you are single and you are
undesirable. Stop sell. Listen, if you
wasn't any of these things, you wouldn't
be on this community.
You know, you are single, you are
undesirable, you are scared, you are
ugly, you are ma. Everything you say is
about your own lives. And this is why
you can't get off of
YouTube. You can't. This is why you
can't get off of YouTube. You literally
talk about your own lives. Why else
would you be on this community? You want
If you weren't any of them things, why
else would you be on
here? You know, [ __ ] hell. It just
goes to show. And I've caught you as
well. I'm saying how skint you are on L
J's. I've actually caught a few of you
out. You know what I'm saying? Yeah,
deck chair making stuff up. Listen,
Becks. Yeah, this is fake. Beex, you're
sat on YouTube every day alone with no
money. Stop talking about yourself. It's
no good for your mental health. I've
said this about a million times. All the
you on here, no money, no woman. It's
your own lives that you're referring to.
It's your own reality. This is why
you're on here. And every single time
you come on YouTube, you prove that you
are skin, you got no woman, you got no
money. You being on here every day
proves my point that you've got nothing,
not even any friends. And that's why you
are on here talking to each other
because you're all sad little loners on
benefits. Got no friends. And that's why
you're on here every single day because
you have absolutely nothing. And that's
why you hate on people that are better
than you. Look, I was off YouTube for
over a [ __ ] week. I don't care about
this [ __ ] community. I come on when I
want stay off for ages. But the main
thing I'm trying to say is you people
can't get off of YouTube because it's
all you [ __ ] have. And you know what
I'm saying is the truth as well. You
know it's true.
Yeah, I know. I've seen seen all over
the same website you can watch the bear
and the big blue house on. Yeah. [Laughter]
Yep. Oh, yeah. His phone got seized as
well. [ __ ] that, bro. If my phone got
seized, I'd be [ __ ] I've got so many
contacts on there. Like, I wouldn't want
to lose this phone, bro. So much
contacts. I've already had my [ __ ]
phone stolen. I had to start
again. You know what I'm saying? Madness. Awesome.
Oh my god. Greavves. I was speaking to
this um person. Yeah. On [ __ ] Reddit
and why is it? Yeah. I don't care about
this. I know how it is and whatever.
like these people you'll say like you'll
show them your approaching videos and
they'll be like maybe they do have
boyfriends. No, they literally don't
because the problem with it is is most
men are not in relationships. There is
loads of women that are celibate. There
are loads of women most women hate men.
There's loads and loads of women if you
go on Facebook that are not in
relationships because some of them just
don't need men.
So, no, they don't have
boyfriends. They literally I would say
people that say they've got boyfriends,
probably three of them do out of
10. Yeah. Stop projecting your ugliness onto me.
Yeah. You know what I find so mad about
these um self-reflectors?
um cult right do you know why I find so
mad is that
um is that what's so mad but they don't
have boyfriends they they do not have
boyfriends every single time you go out
right and they say they've got
boyfriends I would say about three out
of 10 actually
do there's no there's just no way it's
it's it's a boring conversation cult
it's a boring argument
It's a boring topic because it's just [ __ ] Why
have Yeah, stop calling yourself
disabled. Do you know what's so mad
about these people car? They tell me I
can't get a woman, but I've had more
women than them. Just the women I put on
YouTube. Why do these people
self-reflect their [ __ ] lives on to
people every day? It's crazy, isn't it?
They're such mongos. They're such
retards. If their lives were so good,
why are they on here every day? They
can't answer it. They literally can't
even answer the question. [Music]
Yeah. It's mad, isn't
it? But yeah, their lives are a good
cult, right? They're not skin. They got
all of this all what they want in life
yet they're on YouTube every day trying
to troll people. Make it make sense,
isn't it? Make it make sense. Yeah.
They've got all these things and you're
all these things yet these people can't
take a day off YouTube. Think about how
it makes no sense. Just think about it,
bro. How it makes no sense.
Oh, that's funny,
mate. But yeah, dude. Well, how many
would you say have boyfriends out of 10
that say they've got boyfriends? I I
would say three out of
10. I would honestly say three out of
It's so hard to believe the ones that
are actually telling the truth because
it's literally they all they always say
that they don't have boyfriends, bro.
Trust me, there's a lot of independent
women out there that don't need men.
Trust me. Especially
nowadays. There's no way, bro. No way. You
know what would you say, Cole? I'd say
three out of
10. Yeah. I'd say about three out of 10
actually do. There's no way they will
have boyfriends, bro. That's the ones
that say they do. There's no [ __ ]
way. No [ __ ]
way. It's just what you get in England.
It's what you get in these West
countries. It's like if you went to
America, they' be like, "I'm sorry, I
have a boyfriend." That's what they'll
say in America.
They'll use the I'm
sorry. How do I know these things
really? I spoke to a lot of people. So,
in America, they'd say, "I'm sorry, I'm
not um I've got a
boyfriend or I'm sorry, I'm just not
interested." That's what they say as well. Say
that lot of American people. It's crazy, isn't it?
It's crazy, Col. [Music]
No, not at all. I don't give a [ __ ]
anymore, Grezy. I don't I'm leaving I'm
leaving the country soon, lad. I don't
care. Why do you think I don't try
anymore detox? No, I don't care,
bro. But no, it really really doesn't to
be honest with you. No, it doesn't. I
don't even have a high sex drive anymore, lad.
Yeah. No, it doesn't bother me, bro. Really?
No, I've got other things. I've got this
um film in the cinema coming out Friday,
you know. I'm leaving England soon. So,
yeah. No, not anymore. It used to, but
not anymore. It doesn't bother me, bro.
Because they're all the same. They've
all they've got all the same minds, you
know? So, why would it bother me?
I'm just saying when people always say,
"Oh, maybe they do have boyfriends."
Well, they literally do not. That's what
I was saying. I don't really care either way,
bro. I'm not going out this week. I'm
not going out next week. I don't give a
[ __ ] [ __ ] them, bro. It
Stop stop talking about yourself. Stop
calling yourself disabled. It's not good
for your mental
health. You didn't you didn't
You are disabled. Stop talking about
yourself. And do you know what proves
you people are disabled? I'm not talking
about you, Grezy. Do you know what
proves you people are disabled? That you
have been coming on YouTube every single
day for over a decade repeating
yourselves. That's how we know that you're
disabled. That's how we know that you
people are disabled because you come on
here every single day without failure
repeating the same old [ __ ] That's how
we know that you're
disabled. That's that's that that's a
banger from [ __ ] Peter Belly cuz you
wouldn't be on here. You would not be on
here if your lives were better than
anyone else's. Why would you be on this
[ __ ] community every single day?
Every single [ __ ] day. Why would you
be on here? Why would you be on my live
stream now? Why are you watching me?
Exactly. It says everything about your
own lives and you don't see it. And
that's why you can't answer my
questions. Because I'm right. Because
I'm [ __ ] right. In six years, I've
been abroad. I've been all over the UK.
I've made different friends. Been with
many women. You've been sat on YouTube
repeating yourselves for over a decade.
You are the disabled ones. It's your
selfish you're talking about skin and
disabled. It's your own
reality. Anyway, bye-bye now. Go
self-reflect on another channel, you
mong. You people are nothing but fat,
ugly mongos in your 40s. You got [ __ ]
all but disabilities and [ __ ] your
[ __ ] little benefit bum change. And
that's why you come on here every day
sad with your lives, waiting for anybody
who's better than you to go live so you can
self-project. Skint, you are skint m.
You 100% are the muners. Have you seen
your faces? Have you seen your [ __ ]
ugly faces when it comes out on YouTube?
You're ugly. Your skin, you've got
nothing but YouTube. It proves it every
day. I will go on L J's right now and I
guarantee you it will be the same
spastics without a life, without a
woman, without any money. They don't
like what I say because it's the truth.
Everything I say about these people is
the [ __ ] truth. They don't like it.
That's why they can't answer me.
these little [ __ ] mongos,
man. They they ruin the channel, don't
they, Grezy? These little mongos
literally ruin the channel. Dead, I'm
going for a KFC today.
Yeah, these little mongos, they ruined
the whole channel. It's just self-p
projection after self-p projection after self-p projection.
Literally, I think I'm I think I'm going
to use my main channel, bro, and [ __ ]
this this [ __ ]
off. You know what I'm going to do? I'm
I'm going to actually Yeah, I'm going to
keep my main channel to post content on,
I reckon. And I'm gonna have
like another live stream, lad. Because
every day with these self projectors,
they ruin the channel. They literally
ruin the [ __ ] channel. These [ __ ]
40year-old spastics. They ain't got a
life. Like come on here and self project
cuz it's all they
have. No, I don't think I'm going to get
a Sunday roast to be honest. I was going but I dec could
do could do. Yeah. Then it means
traveling. Then it means [ __ ]
man. Means traveling bro to get a
[ __ ] roast. I'm not doing that. I
can't be today. Honestly, no. Self projection. Self
projection. I feel sorry for these
people having nothing in their life but self-p projection.
And it goes to show really that these
people have been bullied their whole
life. That's why they're in their late
30s, 40s. They've got a mind of a child
and all they have, all they can do every
day is sit on YouTube and self-project.
Yeah. Don't know what I'm doing, mate. I
don't know what I'm
doing. Cuz the thing is, if you go solo,
you don't get much
meat. You don't get much food for your money, you
know? I'm not going to horn church. That's [ __ ]
long. That's [ __ ] missions,
bro. Go Central. Yeah, but not [ __ ]
Horn Church. That's [ __ ] missions, bro. Sheesh.
God, these self
projectors. I do feel bad for him
though. Feel bad for these little self
projectors, do you? Fancy
follow. Yeah, it's fun, too, cuz you
people don't bully no one. You get
bullied every day of your lives. That's
why you're on YouTube every day. You
little rejects. Any bullying that you
people think that you do, people on here
has made me move house. No. No one on
here has ever made me move house. Okay,
let me let me let let me let me let me
explain something to you, right? If you
little bongos, you little skid bongos
bullied me, I wouldn't be on here
laughing at you. Think about it, bro.
Think about it. I'm on here laughing at
you keyboard warrior little bully
victims because you don't bully no one.
Do you understand? Like, at the end of
the day, you've never bullied nobody. I
wouldn't be on here. If you if you
really bully people, right, you like,
bro, life has bullied you people from
the time that you've been born. You're
all skin. You're all virgins. You got no
woman. You got no money. You have no
friends. That's why you're on it every
day talking to each other because you're
bully victims. This is why you're on
this community because you have nothing
in your life. You people don't bully no
one. You bully yourselves. You bully
yourselves. Like that's literally all
you do. Honest to
God, you little mogos bully nothing. You
are the bully victims. And you prove it
every day when you're on YouTube with no
money, no woman, no friends. Listen, out
of these hold these many years I've been
on YouTube. Why have we never seen you
with a girl? Why have we never seen you
with your friends? Why have we never
seen you at work? And why have we never
seen you with any [ __ ] money? Because
you have nothing. You
contribute nothing to society. You
literally, right, you
literally you literally contribute
nothing. You're just a [ __ ] fat ugly
mongos that come on YouTube every day.
That's literally all you are. Like, bro,
you are literally fat, ugly little
mongos that have nothing but YouTube.
What could you bully? What could you fat
little downies bully? Bro, man's been I
have done more in three years than you
have done in your whole entire decade.
You fat ugly people bully nothing. You
get bullied every day. You probably try
to walk to your corner shop and you get
slapped up for being so [ __ ]
ugly. That's why most of you got
anxiety. You can't get off of
YouTube. Listen, I don't know anything
about anybody on here. Okay? Well, I
know that you're a [ __ ] ugly, [ __ ]
Can you prove me otherwise? Okay, here
we go. I'll give I'll give an example. I
know that you're skin and you're ugly.
Prove me otherwise. There we go. There
we go. You're an ugly skin [ __ ] man.
Prove me wrong. The link's up there. You
said I don't know anything about you.
Prove me wrong then. Prove that you're
not a ma. Prove that you're not an ugly
ma. Come on. Come on. Come on.
Come on. Come on. Come on. And put your
camera on and show everyone that you're
not the M that you keep calling people every [ __ ]
day. Exactly. No, you'll [ __ ] leave
when I tell you to leave. You [ __ ]
little [ __ ] You [ __ ] fat ugly
bongo. You people don't bully no one.
You've never made me You have never made
me move house. Listen. Right. I left
Listen, listen. I left that house before
anything come to anyone's address. Yeah.
Because I had problems with the
neighbors. The first house, my mom
wanted to move anyways. Yeah. I did not
live by myself. Trust me, you little
reject muners do not bully nothing.
Trust me, you are the victim of
bullying. You are the victim of
bullying. You do not bully nobody.
People that gets bullied do not come on
YouTube every single day. Just like
these people get bullied every day they
leave the house, which is why they don't
leave the house. Think of it, Cole. If
these people really bullied people, you
wouldn't be on here laughing at
them. You are the Hoover. No. No. Normal
people don't have to. No, you listen.
Normal people don't have to prove them
things. You people are not normal. You
are not normal people. And yes, you do
have to prove them things. When you are
on a community calling people this,
that, and the other, you do need to
prove them things. Yes, you do. Because
you're only as good as what you can
prove. And you people are not normal. You're
spastics. So, there's that one out the
window. Because you're not normal.
You're [ __ ] spastics. They ain't got
life. So, that's the thing, lad. Yeah.
First of all, you do have to prove
yourself cuz you're on there every day
hating. So you kind of do have to prove
something. A B you people are far from
normal. So what the [ __ ] You
know. No, I'm not back, bro. I'm just on
here today. I was on it yesterday. I'm
just just bored, bro. To be honest with
you, I'm bored of these people, lad.
They're [ __ ] boring. It's the same
atmosphere every day. They're not even
like proper [ __ ] roasts.
They're [ __ ] weirdos,
man. These people here are [ __ ]
idiots. I know what you would what you
class them more idiots or weirdos.
Huh? I am on the same boat as No, I'm
not on the same I'm on the same
I'm Listen, listen listen. How am I in
the same boat as all the user? You
people don't leave your house. You
people don't have no
money. We know you
are. Yeah. You don't know where I am.
And no one cares about your little
letters. Nobody cares about your
letters. You can send what? Whatever you
want, wherever you want. No one cares.
No one's bothered. And you don't know
where I am. Send a million letters.
Nobody cares. Lad, be my guest. Even if
he was to find out where I was. Yeah. I
I I know. Okay. Okay. So, I know that
you got no friends. I know that you got
no life. And I know that you got no
money. Yeah. And I know these things
because you're on YouTube every single
day without failure. So, that tells me
if somebody's on YouTube all day, every
day, they can't have any of these
things. your you like your YouTube
activity gives it away. Like it
literally gives it away. That's how I
know you have nothing. Hold on. I'm on
YouTube every day. Okay. I was off of
YouTube for over a week. I was off of
YouTube for over a week. You people
can't take one day off of YouTube.
That's how I know what you people have
and what you don't have. It's that
simple. It's that simple, mate. It's as
simple as that. Literally.
Yeah. So, I'm not on here every day. I
was off of YouTube for over a
week. Any dates this week? I'm not
[ __ ] telling you, bro. Don't you
worry about what what what I've got,
what I don't have. [ __ ] off, man. You're
all [ __ ] weirdos. Yeah.
know where I am. Never ever ever ever
know where I am. And even if you did
know where I am, you can send posters as
much as you want. Not one person is
bothered. Literally, not one person is
bothered. You little keyboard warrior.
Send two million. No one cares.
No one cares what you little bully
victims do. You don't bother me, bro.
You'll never run me off of YouTube like
you do Monty Man. Understand
that. So, yeah. Anyways, bye-bye. I'm
going to ban these idiots now.
Yeah. Yeah, man.
Nice try though,
buddy. What a nice try. They're [ __ ] absolute
mongos. They're absolute [ __ ] mongos,
mate. They really, really are. I feel
bad for him,
man. I really
You will never make me move
house. You will never bully me like you
do, Monty, man. Never. Ever. Ever. Trust
me on that one. Trust me on that one, bro. Believe
that. Sad little
retards. Yeah, because I've got a life
unlike these people. Yeah, cuz I've got
a life unlike these people.
Tradal fat ugly m ain't got a life.
These people are on here every day
because they're all fat and ugly. They
ain't got nothing in their [ __ ] lives.
Why they do what they do, bro? Fat, ugly
little m rejects on benefits. That's
what they are,
bro. You know what I'm
saying? Yeah. I'll be offer again,
lad. Yeah. Bye-bye now.
This is why This is why you don't see me
on here, bro. Why you don't see
me? Because of these mongos. These [ __ ]
spastics. Ruin the whole channel. Little keyboard
warriors. You're mad,
bro. Oh, I remember that. That's sick.
Was that 11 years ago? Look at them kitties.
11 years ago.
E I know I'll be laughing, mate. I'm out
of here soon.
Anyways, believe that. One
sec. Believe that.
They can be arranged. Ah, [ __ ] hell.
You need to get get a life, man. How
long are you mongos going to keep doing
this [ __ ] for? Like, how long are you
mongos really going to keep coming on
YouTube every day doing this for? It's [ __ ] madness.
Yeah, I'm going traveling soon. Yeah,
cuz I got my passport last
week. I'm going to go a few different places. Yeah, believe that. Yeah.
Oh, I feel sorry for these people,
bro. Imagine living every day to hate.
Just imagine that. Like waking up every
day. Yeah. Living just to hate. Imagine
it, bro. Sorry, man. It weirds me out mo
more. It It weird It weirds me out more
than like most people. Yeah. Anywhere is better than
England. And it's not just a women. It's
a It's an amalgamation of things as
well. It's amal boring. Bye-bye. [Music] Boring.
Boring. And then you're saying you're
going to send letters. Bro, you don't
even know where I live. And even if you
did know where I live, the neighbors
would laugh at you. Nobody cares.
Trumodal. Literally, not one single person cares.
Like it's not even a case of I'm calling the police. Nobody literally
cares. You know, I I left my mom's
because I had beef with the neighbor
over something different. Nobody cares
about your little keyboard warrior
tactics. You're not going to make
anybody move, you keyboard warrior. You
know what I'm saying? And that's it.
Oh, is that a man that used to do the scratch
cards? Wasn't that the man that used to
do the scratch cards?
Huh? Rings a bell, huh?
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah, I do. Yeah, I remember
watching him years
ago. How did he
die? Oh, I assume he killed
himself going by some of the
comments. What did he do? Kill himself.
Oh, madness, bro. It [ __ ] Yeah, I
remember the scratch card
videos. As soon as you told me it rang a bell.
Yeah, a lot of people die nowadays, huh?
It's [ __ ] up, lad. [Music]
What gamb? What? He didn't have a
gambling problem, did
he? Really? He didn't have a gambling
problem, though, did he?
Madness, isn't it? It's the [ __ ] madness. Yeah.
Was he playing roulette or was it just scratch
cards? Yeah, I remember Sandwell
mobiles. Yeah, severe anxiety talking about yourself
there. Yeah. Have you noticed right
everything that these people say is
about their own
lives? Like literally everything that
they say is
literally about their own
lives. Do you not find that so
mad? It's literally their own lives that they're talking
about. They literally It
literally is like severe. Let let's just
talk for a minute, right? Severe
anxiety. How can I have severe anxiety
when I go out my house every single day?
Huh? I literally go out and approach.
How could I have severe
anxiety? That doesn't even make any
sense. They're just self projectors.
Think of it, right? Remember that bomb
years and years he used to come on here
calling people ma, saying that people
are scared of flying. And look what he
turned out to be like. They are just
literally sad people in their 30s, 40s
that have achieved nothing in life. Very
fat, very ugly, have got nothing. So
they just come on here and hate because
they're sad with their lives. It's why I
don't bother with it. But they [ __ ]
bother with it every single [ __ ] day.
They [ __ ] bother with it cuz they
ain't got nothing else in their lives
but YouTube. No life but YouTube. But
YouTube, I got severe anxiety, bro.
Coming from people that don't even I
wonder when was the last time these
people left their
house. Cole, I I wonder when was the
last time these people actually left their house, lad. Sheesh.
Stop calling me Pete. It's [ __ ]
weird. And things are good, man.
Yeah, things are
good. Yeah, man. Just on a detox, taking
a break from approaching, taking a break
drinking. Yeah, I can't believe I
literally come in the other day
drinking, smashed my Spider-Man mug and
pistol over the floor.
That was a mad and I had to buy a
[ __ ] whole new Spider-Man mug.
Madness. Bomb and Pat managed to get off
it. Um, no, no, no. Uh, let's let's do
the correction here. Um, actually
um Bomb and Pat got exposed um for being
the ugly montage they are and they come
off of YouTube so people would stop
harassing them. No, they got bullied off
of YouTube. That's the difference. They
didn't willingly get off of YouTube.
They literally got bullied off of
YouTube because people was tormenting
them every day. Get your facts right,
buddy. Because we all know that if Pat
never got exposed, he would still be on
here making 20, 30 videos a
day and they literally would be doing
exactly the same thing. It's the same as
Traumadol. when he's ugly when he when
he's ugly face actually gets out there,
he will run a mile just like Fraser,
just like the rest of them. The only
people that has left on their own will
reel is um Ant-Man, some guy called
Donna Birmingham. There's a few people,
but most people got bullied off of it. So,
yeah. No, no, no, no. Pat didn't choose
his wife over YouTube. He literally left
YouTube so people would stop [ __ ] with
him. So no, he can't let it go. No, no,
no, no, no. He literally got bullied off
YouTube. You are [ __ ] [ __ ] man. You
You really are
stupid. He He went off of YouTube
because his ugly face got exposed.
That's why he left YouTube. He had no
choice but to leave YouTube.
You know, he never owned no one,
mate. The only person that he [ __ ]
owned was that Fantasy Stories. He never
owned no one, mate. He never owned one.
He was a typical coward keyboard
warrior. He's literally never And I'm
not reacting to you anymore. I know what
you're trying to do. It's not going to
work. Don't know who you
are. No, I don't know who you are,
buddy. Yeah. Anyways, bye-bye now. Bye-bye
now. A bye-bye
now. [ __ ] mongos on this community,
man. People ever stop.
Anyways, I'm out of here in a
minute. I know, man. They stalk me, lad.
They stalk me.
They stalk me,
man. I think they're deep down jealous of
me. That's what I think. They're deep
down jealous of me, buddy. That's what I think.
Yeah. Calling me around everywhere.
They've got nothing else to do. They're little
losers. They're [ __ ] absolute losers,
man. Absolute [ __ ] losers. They ain't
got nothing in their lives.
This community will never
change. This community will never
change. Ah, not this boring thing again.
Somebody will be in
Stratford. Boring. We've And this is
exactly why I don't come on YouTube no
more. This is exactly why I don't come
on YouTube no more. Boring.
We've heard all this for the past two months. I'm
yielding. Boring. You're sending me to
sleep. You're sending me to
sleep. I've never yawned so
much. I'm falling asleep, mate. This is
boring me. I feel like I just took a
load of [ __ ]
cocoon. Yeah. Someone's coming on your door. [Music]
Boring. Stop trying to find out where
people live. You're never going to know
where I live. Everybody knows I don't
live there. You will never know where I
live. Get a life. Get off of
YouTube. [ __ ] sake. I'm gone after
today for a couple of weeks. Death, bro.
After this, after
today, after this live stream,
um, we're going to stay live for a bit.
I'm literally coming off for two weeks.
You know, because when you hang around
um mongos, right, for the longest time,
you you you sort of become like them.
You know, you are what you surround yourself
with, you know? That's why you have to
take breaks of this [ __ ] [ __ ]
place. It's [ __ ] proper
disabled. Like, you will never ever ever
ever ever know where I
live. So, get out of your [ __ ] head.
Like, but it's boring. It's the same.
Like, I I wouldn't mind that if you come
live and you have people trying to [ __ ]
with you, saying different things, but
it's just the same self-reflection every
day. It's literally just the same
self-reflection every single [ __ ]
day. That's why you you kill the
community. This is why people don't
bother coming on or bother going live
because you just killed the [ __ ]
community. You do. You got You must have
something wrong with your brains in it.
You must have something seriously wrong
with your [ __ ] brains, bro. Cuz it's
not normal, man. It really ain't normal.
When are you going to get a
life, you know? When are you actually
going to [ __ ] get a [ __ ] life,
bro? It's [ __ ]
sad. It's really sad. I still haven't
decided what to eat
today. And like you don't
psychologically [ __ ] with anyone's head.
You don't bother no one. You just
embarrass yourself and bore
people. Yeah, they're all boring on
here, bro. Why do you think I don't come
on here much
anymore? After this live, I won't
be I won't be on for long time, bro. I
can't be bothered with it. It's boring.
It is. It is actually so boring. You go
live, people call you what they are,
skin a manta. Then Greavvesy comes on
and it's it's just the same [ __ ] every day. Same
retards. Yeah. It's a [ __ ] madness,
lad. When are these people going to grow
up, man? You know, almost every single
one of them are [ __ ] older than me as well.
Oh, when are these people actually going
to grow up? No, I don't think they
are. And what is their obsession with
money every day? Calling people skin.
What What is their obsession with money?
I I don't understand.
We hear it every day. [Music] Yeah, [ __ ]
crazy. Yeah, I think I'm going to go for
a roasting. Me thinks
Yeah. Nah, I was around Jim Bongos for
years. Not Monty, man. I come on here
when I was like
22 and it's been the same [ __ ] since I was
22. Same fat, ugly
self-reflectors. Not I'm not telling you
where I'm going, bro. Like, I'm going to
tell you where I'm going. Come on, man. My bad.
Yeah, I'll find
somewhere. Let's have a nice roast dinner. [Music]
When do you reckon these people will get
off of YouTube and get a life? Anyways,
Stephen, when do you think these people
get off YouTube and get a life?
Dad, it's getting silly now,
man. Oh, here we go. Same repeating.
Yeah, this is boring, bro. Very
very of your
job. Yeah, everyone has a life. Well,
you're not living your lives being on
YouTube every day projecting, right?
Yeah. Nothing like a nice detox,
Stephen. Is it a nice approaching a nice
um approaching detox and a nice [Music]
um kind of nice
uh a nice
um alcohol detox?
Can't beat it, can you, man?
Your life is currently laughing at you.
No, your life is laughing at yourself.
Think about it. You're on YouTube every
day. You can't get off of it. The only
thing you're doing is laughing at
yourself every time you look in the
mirror. You want to convince yourself
that you're laughing at me. But in
reality, you're laughing at yourself.
Cuz think about it. I'm younger than
you. I'm better looking than you. I've
got more money than you. I've been to
more places than you. I've had more
women than you. All been put on YouTube.
It's all on YouTube. So actually your
life is actually laughing at
yourself, you know, when your crippling
um depression and anxiety um tries to
make you think that you're laughing at
someone else, but actually you're just
laughing at your own lives cuz you're
you are the ones that are on here. Say
no more. You are the ones that are on
here every single day without
failure. Say no more. That's all I've
got to say, bro. It's like you do you
know what I used to do, right? I used to
um LJ used to go live every Saturday,
right? I swear to God, every Saturday or
Friday, he would used to go live and
just before I'd go out Yeah. drinking,
meeting people. I would go on it and it
would be the same spastics, literally
the same bongos. And then I'd be like,
"Let me uh come back, you know, five
hours later." Because he used to do a
long live stream, bro. I'd come back
five hours later and it would be the
same people. Hold on a minute. Are these
the ones that aren't skin? Are these the
people that supposedly having have all
these friends, but they're on YouTube
all day every day? You know what I'm
saying? Like, you catch these people out
with their YouTube activity. They have
got nothing. Trust me, they have got
nothing, mate. Why do you think they
tell people that they ain't got a pot to
piss in and because they know all about
their own lives? They
know the life that they're living. You understand that?
And that's why they do what they do every day. They're
sados. Sad [ __ ]
people. I ain't got a life.
Yeah. It's sad.
You know, this is mad,
bro. No, we're not even just talking
about clubbing. We're not even You are
lonely. Yeah, stop talking about
yourself. You are lonely. I know. Stop
talking about yourself. And it's not
even just about clubbing. It's about
anything. Think of it, right? These
people come on here calling people skin
every day. Why are these people not
Okay. Okay. So, why are these people not
traveling the world? Why are these
people not at work every day? Why are
these people not doing their hobbies?
Let's just take it for example that they
don't drink, right? Why are these people
with all this money sat on YouTube every
day talking to one another? It doesn't
add up. It's like zero plus zero doesn't
add add up to anything. You understand?
It's like these little mongos. If they
had all of these things in life, they
wouldn't be on here. They literally
would not be on here. That's That's how
it is. Yeah. L went to Vegas and guess
what? He was on YouTube the whole [ __ ]
time. The whole [ __ ] time. Like a
sad. Yeah. He might as well have not
just went, you know. But it's like you,
Tyrone. You are lonely loner. Mr.
Lonely. That's why you on YouTube every
day speaking to other lonely people. You
are Mr. Lonely. Aon made a [ __ ] song
on you, man. Prove me wrong and get and
take one day off of YouTube. Okay. Okay.
Okay. Right. Prove me wrong and take one
day off of
YouTube. Stay off of YouTube for one day
and prove me wrong. But you can't
because it's all you
have, you know, because it's literally
all you have,
lad. Um well, firstly, um there's
there's a bit of bad news. Um no one's
going to be going to my house. A because
they don't know where I live and B um
nobody would come even if they did know where I
live. They don't know where I live. All
of this right is them trying to find out
where I live. They don't know where I
live and they will never know where I
live. All of this is to try to scare
people and it doesn't. It's just
incredibly boring now. Boring to the
[ __ ] eyeballs, you know, and that's
why you don't see me on here. And this
is how you know that these people are
disabled on here as well. Because why
would they come on here every day just
to talk about the same old, same old,
same old, same old, same old? Because
they're disabled people that have not
got got nothing in their life. It's
simple. It is [ __ ] simple, you
know. Yeah. Life, man.
[ __ ] life because it's hilarious.
Yeah. Only to you little disabled
mongos. It's only hilarious to you
little disabled repeated mongos because
you've got special needs. But it's not
it's not funny to normal people. To
normal people, it's
boring. It's it's spasticated. You
people, you know, on from Lord J's
channel, you are well and truly
spasticated. only spasticated people
would find that
funny. Why do people watch Love Love
Island and gossip about it? Um because
with Love Island, it's different people,
different things, not the same old
mongos repeating themselves every day
like this daily community because it's
not the same [ __ ] every [ __ ] day.
Think about it. Would you watch the same
movie every single day? You know, on
here it's the same rejects, the same
spackers, the same skint fat, ugly
people. Would you watch the same film
every single day and call it hilarious?
Only disabled people would do that. And
that's what these people are. They're
disabled. They ain't got to lie, you
know. They don't even talk about
different things. I could understand.
Yeah. If they was talking about
different things, but it's the same old.
This one's skin. That one's skin. That
one's got anxiety. That one's a virgin.
[ __ ] hell. How How long are we going
to hear it
for? I know. It's crazy, isn't it?
Yeah. Imagine being so desperate to
prove people that you don't prove to
people you ain't got anxiety that you go
all the way to Vegas to [ __ ] join
YouTube channels. That's [ __ ] sad.
Yeah, that's [ __ ] sad to be honest.
And he has got anxiety. Like most of the
people in here's got anxiety. Lo's got
anxiety. Bomb's got anxiety. Pat's got
anxiety. They've all got [ __ ]
anxiety for real, bro. It's
madness. It's crazy,
man. I'm kind of hungry now, though, to be
fair. I think I've missed breakfast, though. [ __ ]
Yeah, I've definitely missed breakfast. Definitely
have. Oh, what I could
eat. Maybe get some wings or something.
Yeah, I'll probably get some wings. I'll wings and
then get a rice later
maybe. Yeah, something like that.
Right. A minute. Got something to
do. Can't be on YouTube all day like you
people, man. [ __ ]
pathetic. Trying to stop the temptation of drinking
Guinness. But oh, it's so addictive.
It's addictive, isn't
it? But you need a you need a you need a
detox, man. You do need a
detox. Does it get boring hearing about
make believe boyfriends? So, you need a nice break,
eh? I can't believe my parents flew
away. I'm greedy and left me. They flew
away and left
me. Yeah, Grey. Sometimes I come off of
YouTube and then I come back to pop my
nose in just to see if it's the same
spackers. Every day I pop my little nose
in to see if it's the same spackers. And
guess what? It's always the same
spastics. Yeah, my parents left me in
the nesticles all by
myself. It's not nice, is it,
Greavvesy? Yeah, it's funny, bro.
that they disowned me. Who disowned me?
Huh? Who disowned me? What? People on
YouTube. What are you talking
about? How's people on YouTube disown me?
No, I pop in sometimes on YouTube and
then to see if it's the same spastics every day. Oh
yeah. Yeah. She met a match. I can't
believe Stephen. I just said I I
messaged her dad yet. I messaged her
dad, right? And her mom. I said,
"Listen, you're calling me a keyboard
warrior and I'm not disrespecting them
anymore because that makes me a keyboard
warrior like them." I was like, "Listen,
you're calling me a keyboard warrior.
You're the one that makes group chat to
people, so you must be the keyboard
warrior in it." But I said that you must
be you you must be the keyboard warrior. You must Yeah. Yeah,
man. But I'm speaking to some people in
America anyways. Might go back, bro.
Around the East Coast.
Yeah, good brakes. These people repeat
themselves every day and I'm getting sick of
it. And I'm getting sick of
it. Yeah, I pop my nose in
sometimes. Yeah, I'm about to get some chicken capra. Some chicken.
Yeah, some chicken, lad. I'm [ __ ] hungry,
man. Going to get a roast dinner later.
Yeah, bro. That's what's on the [ __ ] agenda,
bro. That's what's on the agenda, Triple
H. Okay with you,
boss. Triple H, is that okay with you, boss? Yeah.
What's the date today? The 23rd.
Yeah. Seems to go long, doesn't it, lamb?
I know they're [ __ ]
here. Just going to go just going to go
for a roast
dinner. Maybe I'll just save I'll just
save myself and then just go for the roast dinner.
Yeah, that sounds I spent like4 on foods
yesterday, bro. I had a few takeaways.
What the [ __ ] was I doing,
bro? Madness, eh? [ __ ]
madness. Save myself and then just go
for a roast in it, I think.
If I go to that one, but that means
traveling all the way there. I don't
know what I'm doing,
bro. I was just going to stay in bed. [Music]
What you did? Don't know
man is not really that filling is
it figure out. Anyways, I'm out of here. See you.