Yo yo
[ __ ] boring as [ __ ] Yeah, man.
Just checking to see if it's still the same people.
These breaks are going to get longer and
longer and longer, lad. You know how it is.
Welcome back. I'm not back.
Look at you straight on YouTube.
Straight on when I've gone live. You
literally are just waiting on the
YouTube app. Is it, bro?
Yo, bro, you're sad bastard. You really,
really are sad bastard on YouTube 24/7.
Oh yeah, bro.
Literally on YouTube 24/7 just on the
app, in it just waiting.
You're [snorts] sad, bro. Very sad.
You're a sad sad bastard.
Very, very sad. Just like a lot of the
people on here, bro. Just wasters. I've
only I've only gone live for a little
bit. So, I'm waiting for somebody to
send me [ __ ] and I'm bored and I'm not
tired. So, [snorts] I thought, [ __ ] it.
Why not speak to the genuine people
who come on? See if anyone joins. Yeah.
Welcome back. I'm not back, lad. I'm
only on for a little bit. [snorts]
Just waiting for someone to send me
something and I'm bored and not tired. So,
nope. I don't know how you people on
YouTube 24/7, bro. It's so boring.
Very, very, very boring.
Very I don't know how you do it, man.
It's dead as [ __ ] It's so boring.
It's just the same old [ __ ] man. I
don't know how people can sit on it in a new year. Well,
you know, I don't actually know how you
can do it, bro. Seriously. >> [snorts]
>> No, I'm not on Reddit. I was on Reddit
just a minute ago.
You shouldn't really go on Reddit that
much, man. I was actually going to do
like a video, you know, but obviously
I'm not. I was like, I'm not going to do
it. I was going to do a video, but uh
just about the double standards, but never bothered.
That's none of your business, lad.
That's completely none of your business. [sighs]
So, yeah. Uh,
[clears throat] any any Valentine's
dates lined up for you?
Let me let me ask you the same question.
Any any Valentine's date lined up for you?
I I'll ask you the same question. See?
[clears throat] Oh, who's there? All
right. All right, Dusty. Yeah, I was on
Reddit again and this woman is clearly I
don't know what they are. Are they Are
they um Are they sexist or are they
biased? I think they're both. I think
they're sexist and they're biased. I
think it's a bit of both, isn't it?
Yeah. Because they're defending women.
Uh well, this woman is defending women
just for being women. [snorts] Um and
it's funny because yeah, she's talking
about like uh people's attitude. She she
might want to look a bit closer to she
might want to look a bit closer to her
own gender cuz they're the ones with
attitude. So I This is what I wrote to
her, right? And she didn't um she didn't
reply to this. We did reply back to
this. I said, "Do you tell women no one
owes them anything too?" and my
attitude. Women are the stuck up ones
who lie and lead people on. You're very
anti- making women accountable for
anything, aren't you? It's like it's too
much for your ego to admit women are
ever in the wrong. You dismiss all the
shitty things that they do to protect your ego.
And she didn't reply back because she
knows I'm [ __ ] right. She knows I'm
right, bro. Anything to do with biasness
and double standards, I know all about it, bro.
Yeah, he needs a wingman. Good for him,
bro. He can find his own ring man.
Good for him.
Yeah, it's it is the truth though. It is the truth.
What I'm saying is literally the truth.
They literally just make excuses for
them. That's why the world can never be
equal. You see? So, I don't know why
people are still wanting [ __ ] to be
equal when it's never going to be equal
because the double standards and the
sexism and the biasness. How could it be
equal? doesn't make sense.
So that's that, bro.
Doesn't even make sense. How could it
be? But how could it how could it be equal?
It doesn't make sense, bro.
And she says, "Oh, dating is hard for
men and women." I said, "No, dating
isn't hard for women. Dating isn't hard
for [ __ ] women, mate. No, no, no.
Women don't need to go out there
approaching men to get dates. No, women
is dating is is is not hard
at all for women. Not like it is men.
[clears throat] No [ __ ] way, bro. You
mad. It's they're not even comparable
the difficulty levels. So, anyways, [ __ ]
[ __ ] all about that. Anyways, yeah. Um,
yeah. So, I won't be live long anyways.
Yeah, I had a nap today, so I'm not that tired.
Yeah, this is the waster community.
People like L J and people that go on
LJ's channel, they're all just wasters
that ain't got no life. That's why I
don't really come on here anymore.
Yeah, just a waster community.
They're [ __ ] ones to talk about other
people, mate. When they're on [ __ ]
YouTube 24 fucking7 ain't got no [ __ ]
life, aren't they, mate? They're on to
talk about [ __ ] other people, aren't
they, mate? Yeah.
What is this guy doing, bro? [snorts] Might
go for a drink soon.
Maybe midFebruary. Don't know yet.
I told you I weren't going to go on a
night out in January. It's pointless.
Cold. No one's going to really be out.
Just [ __ ] in it. So maybe maybe some
some maybe at some point. Yeah. >> [snorts]
>> maybe midFebruary.
It won't be it won't be won't be um
won't be this week.
I said I weren't going out in January
and I meant it. So
yeah, maybe bro
we'll go out soon. Maybe
just to drink, you know, just to go for
a piss up. I haven't been out for months, so [gasps] [sighs]
my t-shirt came today, by the way. My Spider-Man t-shirt.
It looks good on H.
Yeah, looks good on lad.
I had a Chinese today.
It was nice. Very nice.
I brush my teeth three times a day now.
My teeth look good, bro. I look after myself. Yeah.
Yeah. Spider-Man t-shirt. Yeah.
Made for adults.
Oh [ __ ] One second.
Oh, here we go. [ __ ] hell, man. What
is this response?
No wonder I struggle to get girls. Not
going to even answer that
self-projecting comment. Anyways, uh is
it too much? Okay, bro.
Yeah, we're going to ban these retards
anyways cuz we're not having this on my channel.
Uh, I'm trying to read something in the
middle of this. See you later, bomb. Uh, is it
You don't have to pay for that. You
don't have to pay good attitude about it
because you clearly don't wish it
on both sides. Differences you see in title.
They just don't get these people, do
they dusty? They really just don't get it, lad. I'm saying
about the [ __ ] One second.
I just don't don't get it. They just do that. Madness.
[snorts] Yeah, man. Anyways, why is
there so many um why is there so many
haters on this community as well?
Why is there so many haters on here, man? Mad.
I don't know how you can be on YouTube
24/7 every day
but then try to talk about other people.
That's what makes me laugh.
Just makes you look very silly. Doubt
you care though. But yeah.
She's doing it. They're doing it again
on Reddit. See, look. You're wrong on set.
Why don't Why can't they take any
accountability? I just don't understand
it to be honest with you. It's shitty to
get stood up. Of course it is. It's been
through it, too. But looking at the text
from women you've got where they say
this isn't going to work or I change my
mind is a completely human thing. No,
they've led you on on purpose. I don't
understand why they can't take
accountability for any shitty thing they
do. Even if it three times out even if
it's three times out of 10, I don't
understand why this population don't
want to hold them accountable for any
shitty thing that they do.
But then they want to be equal. How can
that How does that make sense? I was
saying this to Laney earlier, right?
They say they want to be equal, right?
They're saying about how they want to be
equal and but yet the people are biased
and they're sexist. So, how is that ever
going to work out?
It's like when with with with the whole
dating thing, it's not an individual
thing. It's a gender thing. And when you
realize it is a gender thing, then you
know, you get your answers. Do you understand?
You don't change your mind. People do
not change their mind. You wouldn't be
saying that men change their mind, which
is the whole problem with what I'm
trying to say. You You get me? They will
not have it that someone's [ __ ] you
over in any way. They'd rather stick
pins in their eyes than admit any wrong
that they do. And they think that's
normal, but then they want to be equal.
I don't get it, bro. Maybe maybe someone
can help me out here. But
it just to me it doesn't make any sense.
Like they're they're [ __ ] They are
literally [ __ ] I mean any anyone
that's got bias and sexist would would
admit this. And I don't know why they
keep making excuses for them.
I really really really really don't.
It's madness. Actually madness, bro.
So mad. The sexism and the biasness in
this day and age is is unreal, bro. mad. [snorts]
You know, people don't just change their
mind like that. It's evident that people
have led you on and I don't know why
they will not admit it. You know,
it's actually annoying seeing it, bro.
is is it, you know, because if if they
were judging people individually, then
it'd be different. But they're not
judging people individually.
They're going by what they are, what
gender they are.
That's the thing that's annoying about it.
That's the thing that is annoying about
it, bro. They are sexist. They are
biased. Simple. It's not an individual
thing. when they're given dating advice,
it's not an individual thing. It's a
it's a gender thing.
So that's why when I go out drinking
again, I'm just like, I don't really
give a [ __ ]
cuz you know what what what what they're
like and other people should know what
they're like as well. It's mad.
It's going good, man. And I'm just on
Reddit and this woman's making excuses
for women again.
When I've shown them clear evidence of
what they've done, they're still making
excuses for them and acting like they're
angels. And I don't know why they do it.
I seriously don't know why they do it.
They will not hold account. They will
not hold um they will not hold women
accountable for anything. It's [ __ ]
mental, bro. really really really really
really is mental.
You know, they will not hold them
accountable for anything that they do. It's mad.
I don't know why they do it, bro.
You know, they'd rather stick pins in
their eyes. Don't admit that they've
done anything. Very worrying, isn't it? Very concerning.
No, they didn't lead you on. Um, yes they did.
Um, yes they did. One second.
They literally just make excuses for
them because they're women. They're not
even blaming you individually.
They literally just defend women for
being women. That's my That's my problem
with it, bro.
They would rather stick needles in their eyes than
No, they are leading you on. You don't
you don't need to meet someone and go on
a date with someone to lead you on. What
the [ __ ] bro? Is this
Yeah, they will not hold them
accountable for anything, mate. You've
got more You got more chance of getting
blood out of a stone.
You seriously seriously I don't [ __ ]
protect them [ __ ]
I don't [ __ ] protect them [ __ ]
They're [ __ ] evil, bro. That's why I
don't have anything to do with them
anymore. They're all the same and
they're all [ __ ] evil. And life's been great.
Life's been great, lad.
You don't need to meet somebody or go on
a date with someone for them to lead you on.
Yeah. They will literally not have a And
you know the mad thing is Yeah. The
annoying thing is about this. Yeah. If
it if it was a baby or if it's a child
Yeah. you'd be like, "Oh, a child innocent. Oh,
see you later." Um,
like it's mad. Wouldn't you be biased
towards men as
self-projecting? See you later, lad. You
get kicked. Um, yeah. Like they It's
different. Like if it was a child or a
baby, then we can say children are
innocent and babies are innocent. But
they are not innocent. These women are
not innocent. and they keep defending
them like they [ __ ] are when they're
[ __ ] well not.
You know, that's that's the thing that
is annoying. Wouldn't you be biased
towards men as a man?
No, [clears throat] no, no. Because men
do it as well. No, no, no, no, no, no,
no, no, no. Because men also defend
women for being women.
No. Sorry, I just cropped on what you
meant. No. Because even when it's men,
men will men will also make excuses for women.
So, no, no, no. I I know what you mean.
Yeah. But no, because men men men do
exactly the same thing. They will not
hold a woman accountable for anything.
They'd rather stick pins in their eyes.
No, no, no. Because they do it for women as well.
Yeah. But Okay. Okay. Yeah. You you
you'd stick up for men, but if a woman
Okay. Okay. Okay. So, but if you if you
would but if you would stick if you
would stick if a man if there was proof
of a man being wrong in black and white,
would you still defend a man?
Yeah, but we're not talking about women
being threatened. We're not talking
about that, Dusty. We're talking about
women doing shitty things and leading
people on and people not taking
accountability for it.
We're not talking about that, though.
That's something completely different.
We're talking about dating and we're
talking about people basically
dismissing and making excuses for all
the shitty things that they do. We're
not talking about that.
That's something completely different. Oh yeah,
we're not talking about that. We're
actually talking about blaing D list.
I'm not going to court. We're talking
about bla and biasness.
See you later, self projector.
I don't need to know what it means. I
already know what it means and I'm not
your [ __ ] mate. Um, that's the second
thing. Yeah. So, firstly, uh, I know
what it means. And secondly, I'm not
your [ __ ] mate. Never will be. So, I
don't know how many people I've had to
say that to. So
yeah, we're not talking about people
being threatened us. So okay.
Yeah. So we're not talking about people
being threatened. We're talking about
dating and it's blatant um biasness and sexness. Sexism. So
I just want somebody to be unbiased. I
just want someone to be not sexist. I'm
biased. I want someone to say I'm wrong
here. I'm wrong here. They're wrong.
You're wrong here. They're wrong. But
you won't get any of that. So
they will never say that you're wrong
and they're wrong. They will just always defend them.
That's what makes me die about it.
That's what makes me laugh about it because they
you can't always be wrong and they can't
always be wrong.
So if you send 10 screenshots,
well well not well, you know what I
mean? But they they will never hold them
accountable for anything.
That's funny as [ __ ] bro.
[laughter] That is funny, bro. Like
they're innocent. Like they're not
adults. Like they ain't got a mind to do
what they do. It just makes me laugh,
bro. I will never understand it. I'll
never ever understand it, you know?
Like they're worse than men. Like
there's women out there that will even
admit that women are worse than men.
They're [ __ ] around with people.
They're playing games. They're [ __ ]
people around. And then you got people
making excuses for them.
They are literally making excuses for
them just because they were women.
That's the [ __ ] I don't get. I really
don't get it, bro. Seriously, seriously don't. But yeah,
don't know why they do it, lad.
That's why I don't entertain him anymore, lad.
I don't entertain NPCs out all the same.
I don't even entertain him. I ain't
entertain them for months, mate. I
probably never will again. I keep saying
I'm going to go out drinking, but I
never end up doing it, bro. To be fair. Yeah.
I'm never going to Spain even if you paid me.
Never going to Spain even if you paid me
a million pounds, lad. It's not happening.
I'm I am asexual. I'm already asexual, bro.
I'm already there, lad.
I'm I'm already there. [laughter]
I'm already there, bro.
Why the [ __ ] am I going to go to Spain,
bro? Are you mad?
Go to Spain full of English people.
Yeah, why am I going to go and do that?
Yeah, I'm already asexual, bro, to be fair.
>> [clears throat]
>> Yeah, I I pretty much am, lad.
it's not like the 70s. It's not like the 80s. So,
yeah, I pretty much am already there to be fair.
Why do you think I ain't been out in so
long, bro? drinking and approaching.
[ __ ] all that.
[ __ ] all that, bro. I'm not dealing with
people that all the [ __ ] same. [ __ ] that, lad.
I would never go to Spain. My mom's been
Spain. I'd never go to Spain. I'd never [ __ ] that. seen yesterday
because it's full of English people
and it just doesn't appeal to me.
It doesn't matter if it's soft. I just
don't want to go there. Simple.
I'd go motor. If someone booked it for
me, I'd go, but I wouldn't go to Spain.
I'd go m [ __ ] Yeah.
Benador coming to you. Paul. Well,
that's [ __ ] cuz Antman's been to Benadorm.
Ant-Man's been. There's loads of people
that's been. It's just full of English people.
I was watching the Ed Matthews. Yeah, I
was watching Ed Matthews. I watch all of
his streams, Dusty. And even this guy,
Even his friend. All right, bro. Even
his friend that come from America said
it's hard in England. It's harder than
America. He was even saying.
Yeah, he was saying that it's harder
than America. He said it all stuck up on that.
And that's another [ __ ] somewhere from
the [ __ ] West. Yeah, it is probably
to be fair England. England probably is the hardest.
Probably is to be fair. But it depends
where in America. England is is is terrible, bro. Terrible, bro. Terrible.
Obviously, most countries are banning
that. No, I haven't seen him.
I don't know. No, I haven't seen that
one, bro. I watch him though. It's funny, bro.
But no, I don't know that one. No.
Oh, the one that looks like Quagmire.
Yep. I saw him in Blackpool and No, I
wouldn't go to Greece.
Oh, yeah. The one that looks like Kragmar. Yeah.
Yeah, I have.
Yeah, his name's He calls himself Lynx, Johnny.
Yeah, I have seen him, bro. Yeah.
Yeah, I've seen him, bro.
He's not funny, man.
The other one's funny, bro. He was
giving me jokes the other day, bro. He
was off his [ __ ] head. Yeah, the
northern one. I'm trying to work out his
accent and I can't work it out, bro. I
know it's not a Manny accent. I don't
know what it is. Yeah, he's northern.
That northern guy with the muscles. I
don't know where he's from, bro. I'm
guessing like Leeds or something. It's
not It's not It's not a Manny accent. I
don't know what it is. I'm trying to
figure out where what that accent is.
It's definitely Yorkshire. I don't think
it's Manchester. It's not. Cuz
Manchester is sort of like
Yeah, that one. Yeah. Yeah. What is it,
bro? I'm sure it's not Manchester. It can't be.
Yes. That sounds more like Leads.
That sounds more like Leads or or or
Sheffield or something. Yeah, I'm trying
to work out. He was giving me jokes the
other day, bro. He was giving me jokes.
It was about a week ago.
Nah, it's not Derby, bro. That's not
Derby. No, no, no, no. Derby is like
Mashtag. N Derby is That's That's East
Midlands, bro. That's very easy to spot.
No, no, no, no, no. It's not Derby, bro.
Cuz Derby is similar to Nottingham.
That's like a mash tag accent. That's
not I don't know where it I don't know
what it is, but it ain't Manchester.
It's definitely definitely not
Manchester cuz Manchester's
like once you hear someone from
Manchester, you can say they're from
Manchester in it. But I don't know where
he's from. It's not Derby though.
That's not Derby. I don't know, bro.
Somewhere in Yorkshire. But it could
even be somewhere like Pre Preston or
something. It's not It's not Manchester
though. I know that for a fact.
talk about to women. I don't speak to no
women, bro. I don't want nothing to do
with them [ __ ]
I think when I go out drinking again,
I won't even do any approaches to be
honest. I can't be annoyed with it.
Yeah, it's shitty. But holy [ __ ] you
don't know them period in the story. Don't know
cancel me one hour supposed to I had a
man cancel on me 1 hour before we were
supposed to meet because he was tired.
I'd already done my hair and makeup and
recognized my entire day to come to I
saw the text and I was turn on the TV.
I don't understand how she can say that
dating is hard for women and men though.
to be honest with you. Nah,
I don't I don't It's not hard for women
just You might come across shitty men.
You might come across men that only want
sex, but think about it realistically.
You're meeting all of these people. So,
if you're meeting all of these people,
eventually you're going to find someone
maybe a year, two years, 3 years. If you
can't even so much as even get a [ __ ]
date and have to keep putting up with
[ __ ] then obviously it's harder for
men. There's no like two ways about it. Whereabouts? Philippines. Yeah, Philippines.
What is this guy doing, bro? I've been
[ __ ] all day for this [ __ ]
bro. Who cares what they like, bro? They're [ __ ]
Who cares what they like? They're
[ __ ] [ __ ] lad.
Who gives a [ __ ] what they like and what
they don't like? They're [ __ ]
[ __ ] bro. Who cares?
You saw his uh I don't even know his
channel to be honest, bro.
Yeah, I already Bro, I already knew
about him. Why do you think I don't
waste my time,
bro? I don't even email that guy because
I don't I've got nothing to say.
I don't even know the guy's channel.
I knew about him, bro.
It's when he started talking about the
girlfriend thing with nons legs. I knew
I smelled him straight away, bro. It's
the same thing with that Jo. As soon as
they do something like that, bro, you
know what they're about. You know what
they're about, bro.
He hates it cuz he knows I'm right.
That's what it is. cuz he knows I'm
right with the email that I sent
when he started defending [ __ ]
nonslegs and this [ __ ] girlfriend of
his when and I start talking about what
I showed and he started denying it. I
knew it, bro. He's another Joe F. I knew
it. I don't care.
It's so obvious when they start doing
stuff like that, bro. You you just know
what they're about and then all of the
other stuff comes with it like we and I
knew what you was about. Anyone that
starts sticking up for that wronging
right when I'm going at him and they
don't have the same energy when they go
when he's going at me, you know, bro,
that's it, isn't it? Simple. I knew
I know all Yeah, he's just another one
of these people. Simple.
Yeah, man. So, yeah.
Anyways, [snorts] so yeah, man.
Yeah, I don't even have his channel and
I don't want to know his channel to be honest, lad.
Nah, bro. They're just [ __ ] They
don't have a clue about anything.
They're just straight [ __ ] Simple.
Nah, they're they're just complete and
utter [ __ ] lad. That's what they are.
Nothing else but [ __ ] Simple.
They are literally just [ __ ] I
don't bother with them anymore and I
won't ever again. Simple as that. Yeah,
they're shitty people in the story. So
yeah, [ __ ] that.
Never again, lad. Never again.
They've proven what they're about.
They've proven that they're all the
same. So that's it.
They're not clued up on anything.
They're [ __ ] stupid [ __ ] bastards.
That's what they are.
All got disgusting attitude as well. So yeah.
You sound like a simp. Oil Clint,
you sound like a You sound like a s to
be honest, lad. No offense.
Well Well, yeah, [clears throat]
you do. Yeah.
What does it say anyways? This post,
read it to me, bro, because I'm not I
don't want to see it.
I'm not that interested, lad.
I don't really give a [ __ ] to be
honest, lad. Whether they know about it
or not, I really don't give a [ __ ]
Honestly, I don't really care, lad.
They're just [ __ ] idiots.
But yeah, just tell me anyways.
No, I haven't gone back to it to be honest.
Yeah, tell me what the post is about anyways, bro.
Cuz I just tell me give me like a
glimpse of what it is cuz I'm not going
to go on it, lad. [snorts] I don't I'm
not subscribed to anyone. I don't go on anyone's channel.
I'll [snorts] tell a lie. I went on
Autumn's the other day because it come
up on a community post even though I'm
not sub to her. And yeah, I saw a load
of simps, load of white knights, self projectors. Yeah,
[sighs and snorts]
they're just [ __ ] too. They're
just [ __ ] lad. That's all they are
is just [ __ ]
And they get away with everything as well.
Why is the weirdo making community post
on me, lad?
That's weird, isn't it?
Cuz he knows I'm right. That's why, bro. That's why. Yeah.
That was a funny today, wasn't it?
>> One sec.
Have they got a number on us?
[ __ ] sake, bro.
This [ __ ] has been pissing me about all day, bro.
I don't know, bro. And I don't really
care to be honest. I've got nothing to say.
I don't know. And I don't care. [clears throat]
I told him he's a biased [ __ ] and that's it.
That's all I had to say, bro. That's all
I needed to say.
I said more than that, but you know.
Yeah. He's not worth it, bro. He's not
even worth talking about or he's not
even worth the time a day. He's not even
worth wasting your breath over, bro.
None of these people are. Why do you
think I'm not on here much? They're just
not worth it. They're not worth anyone's time. Yeah.
I just all I said was that you're just a
biased [ __ ] on the email. Then he
started trying to get rude so I had to
put him in his place. Simple as that.
Yeah. Cuz he was being a dick sucker
defending his boyfriend. So I had to
tell him about it and then that's all I
had to say really. Yeah.
Cuz you know I'm right as well lad. You
know I'm right. everything I said. So,
but yeah, I don't know what this indie
goes telling going on about.
So, yeah, if you can tell me what it is
because I will not be going. I won't be
going on the channel. Yeah.
Yeah. Cuz he was he was he was defending his boyfriend.
Simple as that. Well, I'm not going to
go over it again. Everyone knows the
story, lad. I'm not going to go over it
again cuz it will just give me a
headache again, bro. So, yeah.
Fast, man. What you on about?
It is the truth. Yeah, it is the truth.
I'm sure you already know the story
anyways. I've said it a million times. So,
and then we start the Wii coming again
and then it's the same Joe F sayings.
So, we know he's all he's no different
than these people.
He's no different than these people on here. Simple.
I'm sure you saw the video, didn't you? He jars
while done replying to his email.
It was hilarious, bro. Hilarious. [gasps]
Oh, and then and and the funny thing is,
bro, like he talks about USA, Izzy, but
he's talking about her to me, someone
that knows everything. How does that
make sense? You're talking to someone
that knows more than you about this
person. It's not some idiot on YouTube.
You're you're you're emailing me. That's
what made me laugh about it.
Knowing that you are full of [ __ ] [laughter]
That's the funny thing about it, bro.
That's the thing that made me like, how,
bro? That made me laugh, bro. Cuz it's
like, you're actually emailing me, lad.
You're not talking to anyone else.
You're talking to me. So
he's he's a clown, man. An absolute clown.
Yeah, there's not many normal people on here.
I don't know, man. I had a Chinese today. Um, yeah.
Yeah, I had a Chinese today. >> [snorts] >> Yeah.
Make myself some coke in a minute. Yeah.
I brush my teeth three times a day and it's lush.
That's what it is.
This guy is pissing me off, lad.
No, not yet. Not yet.
I need to get the Jar collection next. It's £135.
pissing me off, bro. Yeah, it's £135.
You're another one that talk [ __ ] behind
my back. So, you're not normal either, are you?
No, it's not comedy, mate. It's immature.
That's what it is. It's immature.
And anyways, if LT's got anything to
say, he can come on this channel, can't
he? Because he's not blocked on this
channel. I'm not going on his little
[ __ ] fanny channel, bro. [ __ ] that.
Right. What is this?
Yeah. [ __ ] me. What's up?
One second. Yeah.
This guy is a [ __ ] [ __ ] He is.
I'm trying to see.
That Joe F's been quiet, isn't it? is
love all uns from
another bullshitting company. More >> [snorts]
>> Oh, I got some popcorn, didn't I? Yeah,
I got some popcorn.
Yeah, lovely yummy popcorn.
I've just been busy doing stuff, bro. I
haven't got time for this shitty
community anymore, lad.
Why not come on here every day?
>> I got my t-shirt on, by the way. My my
Bot Simpson t-shirt.
So nice, bro. And fresh. It's been washed.
It's so nice, bro.
Yeah. I don't have time for this [ __ ]
every day, bro.
To be fair, lad. No.
Yeah, lad. Sorry man,
that football bet I won the other day
should have paid more than 223 in it.
Yeah, nice B Simpson top. >> Yeah,
I know, man.
That's the only thing you can really win
on now the football is it.
What is this [ __ ] doing, bro?
No, this guy just owes me money in it. So
yeah, I borrowed some my money and they
to give me it back.
It's hard money back.
Yeah, the only thing you can win now is
on the football, bro.
Or I guess there's other like sports and
that, but that's about it in it pretty much. Pretty
much, lad. Pretty much.
Been keeping my teeth clean. Steven
Howard, brushing them three times a day.
Nice mouthwash. They're looking nice,
man. My little toothies.
See, I'm normal now. Ever since I quit
dating, I'm normal, bro. No mood swings,
no depression, no nothing.
Ever since I gave up the dating thing, bro,
life's been good. You know uh
I haven't done any football bets since
last week. I won a fivefold last week.
Haven't been back since
I'm going to put £500 on two teams, you
know, at some point, bro. I think I'm
going to do it
at some point. I think maybe.
Do what you want, lad. I could care less.
You haven't emailed me.
I don't answer emails. Well, you haven't
emailed me cuz I check my emails every day.
You don't email ad.
Let me see if it might be on the spam. No.
I haven't got any emails from you, mate.
You must have the wrong email, cuz you definitely don't.
Well, you know my opinion on women, so
what do you think? I haven't got any of your emails.
Nope. I haven't got any of your emails.
Oh, I keep seeing people wear this uh
Canada goose coat. Have anyone seen it?
The themm Canada goose coats. Must be
another copycat trend.
See [ __ ] kids wearing it now. [ __ ] Canada goose.
Must be another copycat trend in it.
Must be copycats. [snorts] Steven Howard in it.
You've seen it. Is it the goose coat?
The Canada goose coats. Yeah.
Just another one where one starts it and
then other people copy.
Pathetic, lad. [ __ ] pathetic.
My email is it tzpjx@yahoo.com. That's it. >> [sighs]
>> Yeah, well, you haven't emailed me, lad,
cuz I check my emails every day. Yeah.
Yeah. You can try again.
Try again, lad. [snorts]
Where is Greasy? Anyways,
has anyone got this LT's channel? [ __ ]
it. Let me go and see what this cunt's posted. Has
anyone got it?
What [ __ ] he's writing?
You [snorts] got to aim. You me or what, lad?
I'm a [ __ ] um Has
anyone got this guy's channel or what?
I'm going to go a minute. >> [sighs]
>> Have a look. Do you have this LT's
channel? Steven Howard.
Oh yeah, I got it now. Yeah, I got it
now. Yeah, it comes up as spam.
Yeah, I got it, bro. I got it. Yeah, man.
Yeah, cuz I'll be making this new
channel soon, isn't it? So you and
Greavvesy can come on it.
Yeah, it comes up on spam like,
"Yeah, I heard this LT is posted about
me, bro." So, I thought, "Fuck it."
And yeah, bro. I got it. I got it. I got
it. Don't worry. I got it.
So, no one knows the channel. I just
wanted to see what's been posted, man.
Why the [ __ ] not in it?
I don't have his channel, bro.
I don't have the channel.
That's what I'm saying.
This is all cuz I told him that he was
being biased. Cuz he was being biased.
Defending white knighting over his
boyfriend being a little white knight
talking [ __ ] [snorts]
That's how it all started, Steven, isn't it?
Cuz he knows I'm [ __ ] right, bro.
He knows I'm right and the truth hurts.
Cuz the truth hurts.
>> [clears throat and snorts]
>> If anyone has a channel, tell me about
it and I'll go on it. Yeah, it's
supposed to be 3D games, but I can't access it.
Yeah, but I can't find it.
No, it's 3D games, but I can't find it. 3D games.
I can't find it, bro.
That's That's the name, but I can't find it.
He was a white knight in his boyfriend.
Did you see it, lad? Stephen Howard. He
was proper white knight in his
boyfriend, in it.
And I told him about it in it. and he
start getting RC and that.
They're so easy to rule out, lad. Is it?
They're so easy to rule out. [gasps]
It's unbelievable, bro. It's so easy, isn't it?
He was white knighting his boyfriend,
isn't it? And he didn't like the truth.
Another Joe F. I say Steven Howard. I'm
not sure about you, lad, but another Jo.
Another Jo, lad. Another Jo.
They're pretty much all the same on
there, lad. Except me, you, Grezy. You
know, there a few others than that. Yeah.
Yeah. Tell you the damnation.
It is to be fair.
Yeah. I'm going to I'm going to link you
my new channel on that one, lad.
I'm going to link you my new um when I
make a new channel, I'll link it to you.
[ __ ] it, bro. Yeah.
Oh, tired, bro. Now I'm tired again.
Going to drink some Coke in a minute.
When this indigo comes back, I'm going
to ask what the channel is,
Yeah, he's another Jo. That LT Steven
Howard, he's another Jo.
Would you agree?
But like I said, they're very easy to
rule out, lad. They're very, very easy
to rule out.
They're very easy to rule out, lad.
Because as soon as they start talking
about the girlfriend and that and
defending a virgin with a girlfriend,
you know straight away, bro. You know
straight away what they're about. Then
we start hearing the m then we start
hearing the we then they then then it
starts leaking in it. The the the oil starts leaking.
You know these people are very very very
very easy bro. very easy.
Then they start coming at you with their
little self-p projection [ __ ] You know
what I mean?
That's so easy, bro. They're so easy.
It's like, you know, that Jo I knew
straight away, bro. Straight away.
You know, they're very easy, bro. They
can't help their bias list. So, you
know, it's very easy to um Yeah.
We'll wait until Indie Go comes back and
um we'll see what um
what he's saying basically. Hey,
you don't need to give me uh you don't
need to give me any advice, lad.
I've been with more women than you, lad.
I don't I don't want your advice, but thank you.
And I've had plenty of success in the
past. Thank you very much.
This is bomb, by the way. Steven Howard. Yeah.
Give it a couple of minutes.
So easy, isn't it? So [ __ ] easy, bro.
Yeah. Okay, bro.
Mhm. Yeah. Okay, bro. Really?
Sounds like bomb to me. [snorts]
>> [clears throat] [snorts]
>> Yeah. Okay, bro. That's
Oh, that Ed Matthews is not live
anymore. What happened, man?
Yeah, he's not live now.
He went offline earlier today. No pick.
Yeah, watch him on kick, bro.
I don't even know why I watch him. I'm
just so bored. That's probably what it
is. Because man, I'm so bored.
That's how bored you are, bro.
If there's nothing in the cinema,
there's nothing good in the cinema,
nothing to do. So
I see loads of people watch wearing
Canada Goose Dusty. That's another
copycat trend where they all copy each
other. You [ __ ] see kids wearing it.
What is it with these bloody trends, man?
You're boring, mate. You're boring. Go away.
You're boring. Very boring.
I don't watch Johnny Sins, lad. That
must be self projection.
I've had more than enough women, lad.
I'm not bothered.
Nothing wrong with being female list.
They're all [ __ ] anyways. [ __ ] him.
Mate, I don't watch Johnny Sins.
Why are you even Why are you talking
about him anyways?
The [ __ ] bro? Why you even talking
about that? It's so random.
No, I haven't tried. I haven't gone back
to it to be honest.
No, I haven't tried. Well, ages, bro.
Can't be asked. No.
You watch Ed You watch Ed Matthews every day, Dusty. >> [snorts]
>> You okay?
You watch Ed Matthews every day? Yeah.
Yeah, I saw that Blackpool one.
Yeah, I saw it.
Stop watching me. I can hear my I can
hear myself. Stop watching me.
Yeah, Laney's watching me. She needs to
stop watching me. It's so annoying, bro.
I can hear myself.
Yeah, I can hear myself in the other
room. Stop [ __ ] watching me. That's
so annoying, bro.
Dusty, do you have this LT channel?
Boy, drop this shadow, bro. [snorts]
I tell you the videos I like the most,
the GTA ones. What happens in this GTA?
What happens in that GTA?
I've got a hobby, lad. I do stuff every day.
I've got a hobby.
I don't need a [ __ ] little part-time
job, mate. That's what [ __ ] virgin boy needs.
He needs a little part-time job and he
needs to get laid.
You need to get a little job and you
need to get laid.
Isn't that right, Steven Howard?
He get himself [ __ ] little 50 pound
a day part-time little job.
The way it would be skin,
he would be skinn would heed.
Do you know this LT channel?
I heard this cunt's been posting about
me in it.
I used to have so much [ __ ] that guy in
it. He chats so much [ __ ] Dusty. It's
not even a joke.
He talks a load of [ __ ] That guy, bro.
[snorts] You should ei bullied out of
school. Bullied out of school. How would
you know if I've been bullied in school
or bullied out of school, bro? You don't
even know me. You don't even know what
school I went to.
How does that even make sense when you
don't know me? You don't even know what
school I went. How does that make sense?
[ __ ] clown, bro. Yeah,
guy's a [ __ ] idiot, bro.
Proper proper idiot.
Why are you talking about Johnny Sins?
Why are you talking about Johnny Sims?
What the [ __ ] bro?
Well, you've seen every video, isn't it,
Dusty? Dusty. Uh, what happens in this
GTA? What happens in that GTA?
You've seen them shorts in it. They're
so addicting. Them GTA shorts are so
What happens in this GTA? What happens
in that GTA? And they do demonstrations. Yeah.
Yeah, you've seen a them shoots. I'm
sure you have.
Yeah. [clears throat] So that guy in
America, um, Ed's friend reckons the
women in England are more stuck up than America.
What do I think?
I can actually judge this cuz I've
actually met loads of Americans. Um,
I don't know, man. Uh,
I don't know which ones are all stuck up.
I think they're both bad in different ways.
What do you think, Dusty? What Who do
you think are worse, American women or
British? I think
I don't know, bro.
I think I've been with more Americans
than I have British, to be fair. So, I
don't know, bro. They're both They're
both They're both bad in different ways.
Like, I can't explain it. Like, um
they're no good in it.
But he reckons it's harder in England.
I think there's nowhere harder than
England, though, to be honest with you.
I know everywhere's western eyes and
that, but like I've said many times, I
think if you stayed somewhere like
America long enough, you'd find someone.
Obviously, not straight away. It could
take months, a year, but I don't think
there's anywhere worse than England. I
think they're just so stuck up here. So,
I don't I don't think anywhere's worse
than here, to be honest.
I'm trying to think of all the Americans
I've met, they were like,
if anything, the Americans were more fake.
Does that make sense? They were more like
I don't know, bro. They come across more
fake, if that makes sense.
I don't know, bro. They're both bad.
They're both [ __ ] anyways, but you know,
he reckons it's harder here. And that
was in Manchester.
When did you last go? Manchester dusty.
I been for like two years.
I think it was not last year. The year
before that. Where we now? No. May maybe
it was last year
I went. Was it last year?
Maybe it was last summer. I don't know.
I know nothing come of it though.
I think it might have been last summer.
No, I think it was the summer before that. that. Yeah.
Been ages, man.
Doesn't matter anyways.
Oh, I love my t-shirt. I'm going to get
my popcorn now. I love my Bart Simpson
t-shirt and my little shorts.
They're so Oh, can't beat it. Dusty
wearing a nice clean t-shirt with some
nice fresh shorts. Oh,
you can't beat it.
Can't beat it.
It's a tiny bit baggy. The t-shirt tiny bit. Oh, well,
according I'm pump now. [ __ ]
Oh my god. You have more microphones
again, you greedy bastard.
You can't beat yourself popcorn. [ __ ] lash.
You don't know.
I don't want much.
I don't rock my teeth at all. Brush my
teeth three times a day. [laughter]
What did you do to fall up the stairs? Huh?
Oh, for God's sake, man.
What you want more? Huh? You're so
greedy. You are.
Ate all my popcorn and my coke. Huh? [clears throat]
>> You most of it.
You didn't buy this one. Anyways,
I'm going there to watch something.
Anyways, I'm going cuz no one's typing
anything. So, yeah, in a bit. Yeah.