madness.
Yeah. Where's the equality? [ __ ] nowhere.
Just making excuses and you and you
expect people to not have an attitude.
What the [ __ ] do you expect people to be like?
You know that they're [ __ ] They're
being [ __ ] and then people are just
defending them because they've got a
[ __ ] in between their legs and and what
do you want people to do? Be all happy
about it. [ __ ] idiot, man. They're
doing it again on Instagram, bro. I've
come across this person. Yeah.
I've come across this person again and
we was talking and they're making
excuses for them again. Bro,
they're making excuses for them again
for women again. This is the second time
in less than 24 hours. I show them a
load of screenshots, they come out with
some mad [ __ ] bro.
Yeah, we hear some [ __ ] Oh, bro. It
took them about half an hour to write
this paragraph saying, "Oh, they felt
pressured." No, no, no, no, no, no,
no, bro. That That's not what happened.
They just make they just make excuses
for him. I don't know why they do it,
honestly. I don't know why they do it, bro.
when it's in black and white and they
still make excuses for him and they say
they're trying to help people. How the
[ __ ] are they helping people by being
biased and sexist?
How is that helping people? I don't
understand how that's [ __ ] helping people.
Madness, is it lad? It's a madness.
the sexism and biasness. Like I said,
that's one of the main reasons why I
stopped, you know, bro, like the whole
um going out and [ __ ] because of the
double standards and that. I didn't
agree with it. I don't agree with it.
So, simple as that.
Making excuses for them again.
I know. I wouldn't mind it if they're
actually defending them because they
actually think that they're right.
That they're defending them because they
actually think that they're right. But
they're not. It's nothing to do with
whether they think that they're right or
wrong. They're defending them because
they're a woman. This is what I'm
saying. That's my whole problem with it.
You know, it's not because they
generally think that they're right.
That's the thing, you know.
[ __ ] that annoys me, bro. It's so annoying, bro.
Oh, this is a woman giving it her
opinion. What? By making excuses about
it didn't look like they were playing
games. It's any excuse for them. Any
single excuse that they will make to to
take that accountability away from them,
they will do it. They will do anything
to take any accountability away from
them. It is madness.
Oh, it looked like they were trying to
not be harsh or rude. What? By leading
people on. Stop sugar coating what they
do. Oh my god. I don't understand why
they do it, lad. [ __ ] me.
If you don't care, if you didn't care,
bro, why you on my channel? If you don't
care, what what are you doing on my channel?
I was on some guy's Instagram who I
follow earlier. Yeah. And I I get what
he's saying. He was on um his video.
What was he saying?
He was saying about like, "Oh, people
that are being monk, like just stop
being monk and just go out there and
like meet people and [ __ ] and whatever."
Well, you didn't need to. Well, bro,
you're on here to tell me that you don't
care. So, you must care to be on my
channel, to be honest.
Yeah. I was talking to this uh woman on
um Instagram, showed us some screenshots um grievy
and yeah, she went straight to the
women's defense again making excuses for them.
It's madness, isn't it, bro? It is actually madness.
It's so mad, bro. It's actually mad. Why
does so many sexist biased people exist?
There should be more impartial people, shouldn't there?
I got a lot I got a big paragraph,
Grezy. I I got a big ass paragraph, bro.
Mate, I've already had enough chicks in
real life. Why don't you apply that? Why
don't you apply that to yourself? That advice?
No, they're literally just doing it
again, Grezy, and making excuses for
him. Why is it that 90% of people are
like this, Grezy?
Why are Why is 90% of people sexist and
biased? I just I just want that answer.
Maybe you'll have the answer. You would
have thought that more people or at
least half the people would be
impartial, but nope.
Nope. That's not the case, is it?
They will literally find any excuse to
take any accountability away from them.
It's like you're you're What do you
think about it, Grezy? It's like you're
It's like you're literally treading on eggshells.
You can't do right and you can't do
wrong. Anything that you do, they will
make it into it's your fault. They just
love blaming the po [ __ ] man. It seems
in this day and age, they love defending
them. They love making excuses for them.
Even when they're clearly wrong on even
when when there's black and white
evidence that they're wrong, they will
still sit there and defend them. I don't
get that, bro. I seriously seriously don't.
Why can't they just say Greavvesy, oh uh
yeah, this one was a bit shitty. This
one done this. They won't have that.
Why? Why, man? They want to be equal.
Remember, Grezy, these people want to be
equal. How can How can you be equal?
And I'm not shut off from hearing
another woman's opinion. I'm shut off
for you keep making excuses, which is
what you done in them 10 screenshots.
You made excuses. You know,
madness, bro. We're never going to be
equal. So people need to stop saying it
now. You know, blatant sexism and blatant biasness.
It's not happening, lad. You know,
madness. And yeah, that's one of the
reason that's one of the reasons I gave up Grezy.
Pointless. It's a mugs game, bro. It's a
[ __ ] mugs game. [ __ ] that [ __ ] bro.
Piss me off, lad.
Yeah, I don't I am normal every day. I
thought you didn't care. Why you still
on my channel? You just come on here.
You said you don't care, but you still
typing to me, bro. Which one is it? Do
you care or do you not care?
No. Why would I be normal? I'm normal
every day, mate. Women are the ones that aren't normal. Anyways, lad. Yeah.
Just pisses me off when people do it,
Grezy. It pisses me off when people do
it. I don't know why. It just does. You know,
and what makes me laugh, right, Greasy,
is then when you say something like,
"Oh, you you you only see them as like,
okay, for example, on something else."
Yeah. Say you say you only you only use
them um for collections, Greavvesy, or
you only use them for like satisfaction
or whatever. People start having the ump
with you, Greavvesy. People start
saying, "Oh, well that's not right. Oh,
that's so what what so what do you what
do you want people to do? Uh put their
eggs into one put all their eggs into
one basket to get [ __ ] over by people
that are all the same. I mean, I'm not I
don't follow what what are you expecting
people to do?
treat people that are not normal normal
act. It just it just don't make sense,
lad. It just doesn't make any sense.
They just take any blame away from them.
It's mad. It's It's It just doesn't make
sense, bro. It don't make sense.
>> What What else are you supposed to do,
bro? The [ __ ] What? Madness.
Yeah, but for some reason this this day
and age just love making excuses for them.
I don't know why they do, bro. And I
don't think I'll ever get the answers,
so I won't talk about them much longer.
But yeah, that's it.
Bad Gourmet Burger Kitchen today, Grezy.
It was a lush burger. Yeah.
Then and another thing they try to do
grievy is they try to um
they try to also critique your
approaches. So for example I had someone
here say oh uh you should say oh I like
your coat. I like your this. I like your that.
Um to basically approach in a different
way. So again what they're trying to do
is they're trying to bl take the blame
off of them. Again, this is what they
like doing in this society. They like
taking the blame off of them. They will
find anything to uh they will do
anything to um blame you and take the
blame off them. It can never be, oh,
they've got unrealistic standards. It
can never be that they're just sick in
the head or they're just, you know,
whatever. They can't um
It can never ever be them. It can never
be them, you know, ever.
I know. That's what that's what I was
saying. You can't do right for doing
wrong. It's like you're literally It's
like you're literally, bro, it's like
you're you're [ __ ] you're you're
treading on eggshells
every time you're you're in a texting
stage. You're literally you're literally
on eggshells. Anything you'll do,
they'll just blame you for it and stick
up for them. Well, most people anyways.
You you get like um
see you later.
Yeah, we're not entertaining these self-reflectives anyways.
We stopped that a long time ago. We
stopped that when it become 2026, didn't we, Grezy?
Yeah, I'm going to order some new Lego
soon anyway, Grezy. Yeah, that stuff is
like, bro, you you know, one of the
reasons, bro, I I don't like react to
these people go on their channels
anymore, lad. It's because this is 2026.
Um, and I left all that [ __ ] in the
past. And if they're still doing this in
2026, well, then there's something wrong
with them. Well, we know there's
something wrong with them, but yeah,
they don't. They're not going to bother
me with their little self-reflecting comments.
Stupid me though. Ain't giving them the
[ __ ] benefit of the doubt
cuz like I said, the more they do it,
the more I'm right about them.
You know, the more they do this greasy
and the less I do it, which I don't do
it, it shows everything I say is right
about them and their jealousy. So that's
why I leave them to it, bro. I unsubed
from all the channels. I unsubed from
Joe F about two and a half weeks ago.
Never went back on that channel. will
never go back on that channel.
So that's that lad.
Mate, I'm not on YouTube much. This is
my first time on YouTube today. I'm
going to be live for about 20 minutes
maybe and then I'm gone. Depends if Steven comes.
No, it's not groundhog for me every day,
mate. It's groundhog day for you people.
How many days have you been covered on
here? How many years have you be people
been coming on here calling people skin,
calling people what you are yourselves?
Come on, bro. It's not It's not
groundhog day for me. Yeah,
it's definitely definitely definitely
not definitely not ground all day for me, lad. Yeah.
Yeah. Okay, whatever. All right, another
thing, bro. Um,
yeah, that's that. Yeah. So, we'll wait.
Steven Howard emails me, by the way. So,
I'll be doing this uh um channel soon.
Yeah, they do make excuses for them. Defo, lad.
I will use the words how I want when I
want. See you later, buddy. Get kicked.
See you later, lad. You get kicked for that. Um, where's this
[ __ ] thing, bro?
They're telling you to [ __ ]
compliment someone's [ __ ] coat,
Grezy, when you approach someone.
So what? That's going to change them.
That's going to change their attitude.
Madness, bro. Absolutely madness.
They've took double standards to the um
you don't know what I've done today or not.
But yeah, I I suppose you have done
nothing again. I do something every day,
bro. Don't Don't self project your life onto me.
Don't self- project um your life onto
me, lad. You don't know me. You don't
know what I do. You don't know what I've
done today. You don't know what I've
done yesterday. Don't self-reflect your
life onto me, lad.
Leave me alone, bro. What are you
talking about? Leave me alone. We're not
talking about these people. We're
talking about people making excuses for women.
The [ __ ] They're just They're never
ever ever Bro, even if I left YouTube
for 10 years, they're never going to
leave me alone.
Why the [ __ ] you talking about that?
Yeah, of course you did, PC. Of course you did.
Of course you did, mate.
You could you could leave YouTube for 10
years, bro, and and never you could be
in prison for 10 years and you could
come back and people would still be
doing the same thing every day, bro. You know,
got nothing to do with people leaving
you alone, bro. The [ __ ]
I don't even react to these people
anyways because I know them. I know
them. I know what they look like.
No, I haven't I haven't tried I haven't
been at the Lego for ages. I haven't
tried for ages.
Or speaking to this woman on Instagram
and she's making excuses for women again
just cuz they're women.
They love making excuses for women.
Whether it be the [ __ ] they do, whether
it be approaches,
mate. Listen. See you later. Bye-bye.
See you later, lad. Seen you on Lord J
before. Bye-bye now. So, yeah. Hold
on one second.
Yeah. Okay, bro. Whatever.
You still there, Grezy?
Like I said, I left all this [ __ ] in 2026, bro.
These little jealous self projectors.
That's why they don't bother me, bro.
Like they bother other people. They
don't get to me, bro. Because
we know what a lot of these people look like.
So, I got all the answers I wanted.
Simple as that.
So, what did you watch in the cinema?
She's literally saying
she literally said you should approach people um
you should approach people and
compliment their coats.
Seems like they're taking the blame away
from women again. They're trying to make
you greasy. They're trying to get you to
change them. That doesn't make sense.
They're trying to get you to change
them. You're not going to change them,
bro. You're not going to change
westernized stuck up women. Doesn't
matter what you do, what you say. You're
not going to change them, bro. The [ __ ]
No. It was Instagram. No, Instagram.
Yeah, I know about him anyways.
Not good, is it, bro? Not good.
should be getting George soon. Uh Greasy.
Yeah. Yeah. I'll be doing a football bet tomorrow. Yeah.
10 or 20 pound. Yeah.
I don't know what I'm going to do though.
Yeah, I won one last week in it.
I won a fivefold. Was good.
What the [ __ ] Um, the double both teams
to score, but you got to lump you got to
lump money on it.
You got to lump money on it. That's the only thing.
But that's a pretty I would say, yeah,
any I'd say the best chance of winning
at gambling yet is a double. Both teams
to score. No roulette, no slots, no
fivefolds, no team to win. Just double
both teams to score. That's it.
I'm talking to this woman in India. She
said, "I don't know, man. I don't
understand these people at all." I said,
"What do you mean the women taken side?"
I mean, yeah, I don't get it either.
It's got to be some kind of condition.
Cuz they do. They are just defending
them because they're women. There was no
[ __ ] other reason, bro. Um,
yeah. That's that's what I find it
easiest to win on. Still skin. Never
been skinned like you. That's self
projecting and you can get banned for
that cuz that's repeating. So, bye-bye.
The only skin people use on YouTube
24/7, lad. Not me. So, anyways. Yeah,
that's the best uh way to win on the football. Yeah.
Obviously risk easy. Obviously you risk
losing like 120 150 but get to like 400
lb quite easy.
You get me? Yeah.
I like that both seems to score.
What's What are you saying,
bro? I leave my house every day again.
That self projecting, lad.
I should go out and touch grass,
brother. I'm outside every single day.
You don't know me and what I do.
Would you ever do both teams to score on
the team to win? I was going to do that
last week. I did do that uh last week,
but all the games got postponed.
Yeah, I done a treble both teams to
score and the team to win. Yeah, I did.
But the all the games got postponed. So
now I just put £10 on two teams and I
lost. Oh yeah, that was last No, what
was it? That was Tuesday and I won the
bet on Saturday. That's what I done on
Tuesday. But they got uh the the all the
games got postponed
>> be the ones I done. So they gave the I
had£10 on a free both teams to score and
it returned 1,400 and something pound. I
did have that.
Yeah, I had that, bro.
See you later. You get yourself kicked.
Yeah, I did do that, bro. I done a free um Yeah,
I might do that tomorrow. Probably like
a double a double both teams to score
with the teams to win.
Yeah, I might do that tomorrow. Put 20
pound on it. I don't know about three.
Three is quite hard, isn't it?
Your best bet is just to put like 120
130 on two teams to get like 400 back.
Easy, bro. Easy money.
Yeah, man. See you later, lad.
So, yeah, I'll probably do two tomorrow.
>> Yeah, I've won so many of them, you
know. 120 on two teams,
one 380 back, 360. I've won quite a few of them.
I'm not going on that roulette again.
[ __ ] that [ __ ] No [ __ ] way, bro. I
think I just went through a little phase
again, Dusty. But never again, bro. I
ain't played that for now. What has it
been a week?
No, not a week. Almost.
I do the South League and sometimes the
Northern League. Yeah.
It's my Okay.
I like the South League and the Northern League. Yeah.
How much do you put on the football? I see.
How much do you put on a football?
Yeah. I'm going to put 20 on.
It's so bad now cuz the odds are so [ __ ] in it.
The thing is the odds are so [ __ ]
I'm probably going to do to win
tomorrow. I'm going to probably do to
win and both to score. Yeah, man.
I can't I can't believe I won a fivefold
[ __ ] last week, but it paid [ __ ] £220.
I always said my dream was to get three
and I got five, but I wouldn't I would
do five again, I don't think.
Nah, I think any more than two is a Mugs
game to be fair. So, I'll check the
games for tomorrow and yeah.
So yeah, three was £1,400. Dusty
both team to score and win £1,400. It
was from 20.
I think it was £10. No, I No, it was
£10. No, it was£10. It was 144 to1.
So it was good odds, bro. But they all got postponed.
So they [ __ ] me.
I'll probably Yeah, probably.
I'll probably just put 20 pound on two games.
You can see who's playing tomorrow, can't you?
We have a look.
So, um, Dusty, when do they start asking
you for ID then on these on these bookie sites?
So, when do they start asking you for
proof of wealth?
Cuz I withdrew £220. It went in instantly.
So, when do they start asking you for
proof of wealth?
when they start asking that.
That's why a lot of people play uh sites
that are not in the UK now, but then
they charge for deposits.
So, but I heard that they ask for uh welfare.
That's what I heard.
Let's look at this lineup for tomorrow.
No, hasn't come up yet, has it?
Nope. Hasn't come up yet.
[ __ ] hungry again, man.
hungry again, bro.
What did I get? I'm starving. Anyway,
as I'm in a minute. Yeah.
Burger, burger, burger. Anyways, I'm
gone. Yeah, see you later, lads. I might
post my football bet up tomorrow.
Who knows? So, yeah, in a bit. Yeah. Peace.