I want to try that roulette, bro.
One second, bro.
Oh, not that noise. That noise is horrible, bro.
This is bad, lad.
Oh, here we go, bro. 18.
That one's a [ __ ] one, [snorts] bro. Come on.
25. [ __ ] off, man. Nope. Nothing.
Nope. Same zero section.
Same zero section again. Boring as [ __ ]
Bors me. Same thing again.
Yeah, nothing happened, bro.
Just attack the same area. What was all
the other numbers? Didn't even let me see it.
Nope. Just attacking the same numbers
again. The same rig numbers that it loves.
I got one win which was 21 and I done
about four spins. Okay. Yeah. Okay, bro.
It's just random in it.
Should they say but I don't know, bro.
You seem to lose a lot on this, isn't it?
And next auto five,
same story again.
How they keep blaming the house edge. I
shall never ever know. Another load of
load of misses.
I'm not so sure, Steven Hour, that it's
just house edge, bro. But keep our
opinions to ourselves.
Yep. Same story again where it misses everything.
Even though you have 80 90 numbers
covered. Shocker in it. [gasps]
Shocker in it, bro. Shocker how it just misses continuously
and continuously keep missing the same
area over and over and over and over again.
that number, don't it? It loves that
area. It was It was a 20 It was a 20p
boost roulette spin. No, it was a boost
roulette. It loves that zero section and
them losing numbers on it. Even when
you've got 80, 90 numbers covered, it
loves that area. And people still blame
House Edge. It's a madness, bro. It is
an absolute [ __ ] madness considering
you have all of them numbers covered.
How does it continuously miss that many
times, bro? It's so [ __ ] fixed. It's
unbelievable, bro. You You really don't
realize how fixed it is until you
actually play it again. Yeah.
So, so fixed. How they can blame House
Edge? They're [ __ ] They've got
something wrong with them, bro. It's
nothing to do with House Edge.
Yeah, it doesn't matter anyways, bro.
I'm not playing no more anyways. I just
My curio My curiosity is satisfied and
it's still fixed.
My My curios My curiosity is satisfied
and it is still fixed.
It is still rigged.
>> It does the same numbers every time,
bro. You can cover 80 90 numbers and it
will still continuously mislad.
You aren't a money person.
I don't have money to gamble.
Bro, you don't know how much money I
have. One second. One second. I'm not
going to block you. Hold on. I need to
calculate something. Just chill.
No, it it definitely No, no, no. It
definitely definitely It definitely
definitely is fixed. Roulette is
definitely definitely fixed. Uh, it
definitely definitely is fixed. You
can't cover 18 19 numbers and missed
four, five, six sessions. That's common
sense, bro. That's not even being a sore
loser. It's common sense. It is fixed.
And I'm not a money person. You don't
know how much money I have. And no one's
saying that you're taking a piss. You
don't know how much money I have. I
could be a millionaire for all you know.
You don't know me. This is what I'm
saying, bro. Don't talk about people
that you don't know.
I know. Roulette is definitely
definitely definitely fixed. I'm just
going to tell Ant-Man about that as well.
You'd be winning sometimes. Trust me, if
it if it wasn't fixed, you would be winning sometimes.
Trust me, Steven Howard, you would be
winning sometimes. If it wasn't fixed,
you'd be winning sometimes on that roulette.
But as you can see, this bis miss cuz it
loves missing everything. It's such a
losing number seeker, isn't it?
It loves that losing [ __ ] number,
don't it? [ __ ] rigged as [ __ ] It is
It is so fixed. It's unbelievable.
Like, which is stupid because the odds
are against you to begin with.
You don't know how much money I get and
you don't know how much money I have.
Again, stop talking about people that
you don't know.
You don't know how much money I get and
you don't know how much money I have.
Again, stop talking about people that
you don't know. Stop basing your life on
on Stop basing other people on your
life. Stop basing your life on other people.
Stop thinking that everyone's got the
same [ __ ] life as you, man. [ __ ]
that's that's what you call immature,
thinking someone's got the same [ __ ]
life as you. But no, that is definitely
definitely fixed at roulette. 100
[ __ ] percent, bro. So fixed. Even
Ant-Man says it as well, bro.
It is so fixed. They should. They should
literally, bro, like, man, if [ __ ]
Yeah, bro. Listen again. You're self projecting.
All of these comments are self- projecting.
You people are sat on YouTube 24/7.
You're [ __ ] wasters. No one cares
what you think, bro. No one cares what
[ __ ] sad, pathetic wasters on YouTube
24/7 think. No one gives a [ __ ] Like
you're w you're wasting your time, bro.
We've already been over this.
Yeah. No one cares what you wasters
think. You're irrelevant to everything
and anyone. No one cares. Stop wasting
your time, lad. But stop talking about
people that you don't know. That's the
only thing I've got to say. It's never
got you anywhere in the past, so stop
doing it now.
And you're banned. See you later. Yeah.
Miss, miss, miss, miss miss, miss miss
miss miss miss miss miss miss miss miss
miss miss Steven Howard as the cookie
crumbles. Miss miss miss miss miss miss
miss miss miss miss miss miss miss miss
that's all it ever seems to do is just
miss it loves them losing numbers don't
it bro conversation every time it loves
them [ __ ] loser numbers you might as
well just took all of them numbers off
the [ __ ] board
I'm telling you bro if this was my own
house I'd be smashing this house up bro
if this was my house I'd be smashing the
I really really will start getting them
dirty mood swings again. But because
it's not my house, bro, like I can't.
And you know what I mean? I I have to
respect people and that.
But it's seriously giving me them mood
swings again, bro. It's giving me them
dirty, stinky mood swings again, bro. For real.
them dirty, dirty, disgusting vile ones. Bro,
I'm not going to tell you any more than
that cuz we got grasses on here. But yeah, Anyways,
bro, why does it love the loser numbers?
Why does it love the losing area so
much? It might as well get married to it, bro.
Anytime. Like, bro, there's you you
might as well just call it money
laundering at this point, bro. Whenever
whenever you play this roulette, this
[ __ ] fixed ass [ __ ] bro. You
seriously seriously might as well just
class it as money laundering. That's
what I'm going to class it as. Now, I'm
not even going to class it as gambling
because you can't win on it. So, if you
can't win on something,
then it's money laundering. If you don't
get a fair game of anything, then it's
money laundering. It's as simple as
that. It's money laundering. It's not
gambling. Because if it was actually
gambling with the amount of money you
put in, you would win. You would win sometimes. You know,
you would actually win sometimes. You
actually would. You actually would. You
would actually win sometimes. You don't
win. It just goes on any number that you
ain't got. It's [ __ ] fixed. How
people can say that that it isn't is mad, bro.
It's annoying, bro. Stephen, it's really
really annoying, lad.
Really, really, really [ __ ] annoying, bro.
It's so [ __ ] annoying, bro. It's
worse than It's worse than football.
It's [ __ ] annoying, bro.
Steven Howard, lad.
You still there, lad?
I don't even know why I even played that
100 pound, bro. To be honest. [ __ ]
fix roulette. Yeah.
I don't even know why even bothering, lad.
Bro, I would say it's probably
everywhere now. I I just thought I'd
just try 100, bro. I don't even know why.
But yeah, we definitely do know the
score. We do know the score.
Yeah. 100 pound loss, bro. Yeah,
I don't like losing, bro. I don't know
how you used to act when you used to
play roulette and that.
I don't like losing, bro. Like with me.
Yeah, when I lose, I think, oh, [ __ ]
them, bro. [ __ ] the managers. They're
feeding their kids with my money and
[ __ ] I go mad, bro. I really, really,
really take it personal, bro. Very,
very, very, very personal.
You know, it's actually a good thing
that B got me banned, you know, from um
that casino, lad, you know, like all because
Yeah. I'm not going to say anymore, but yeah.
Yeah. It doesn't matter, bro.
How are you like when you lose, bro? H.
So depressing, is it, bro? Losing
So fixing it, Steven Howard. cheating [ __ ] Mhm.
I don't know how people are so calm with
losing Steven Howard.
I'd love to know the trick. I'd love to
know the hack. how they can just lose
and be all right with it.
They will lose and just be okay with it. You know,
I think no, the managers feeding their
kids with my money. They're laughing at
me. They're taking a [ __ ] piss, mate.
Why do you think I've spat on all of
them machines and made a scene, bro,
every single time in the bookies?
And I've made a [ __ ] scene. A good
old A good scene, bro. Why do you think, bro? [ __ ] hunt.
Yeah, bro. People
just lose and they're okay with it, bro.
It's like people in this community, they
think that just because you've got
money, it's okay losing. It's not okay
losing. Losing is not an option. You are
playing to win, you are not playing to lose.
You're playing to win. You're not
playing to lose. Losing is not an
option. Simple. Because you're not
playing because you want to lose. Yeah.
I'm not going to tell you everything I
I'm going to say on here, bro, cuz we
got grasses on here. David Howard. Yeah.
People seem to think that just because
it's like only £100 or you've still got
money, they think it's fine. They think
it's okay. Me, I'll just be depressed
the whole day, bro. But if I lose 20
pound,£50, 100 pound,
it affects you that badly. You don't
even want to get out of bed. So I don't
understand. And you before this, you
have no problems. There's no underlying
problems. Only when you gamble,
you know? Only when you gamble, it
causes this, bro. Every single time. You know,
it's like a demon in your head laughing
at you, mocking you, bro. It's like
you've got a demon in your in your body,
bro. I'm mad, bro. Oh, seriously. I'm
mad. Seriously. Seriously. Seriously, bro.
I don't take it on the chin. I don't
give a [ __ ] Simple as that, bro. I don't care.
It is annoying. I don't care if I can
afford to lose the money. I don't care
if I've got money left over. I simply
don't care. I don't care. Losing is not
an option, bro.
You know, simple.
You You actually start feeling like
you've lost your mind, Steven Howard.
You actually start feeling like you've
actually lost your mind.
You remember that time I ditched that
19y old cuz I lost £150 gambling Steven Howard.
Do you remember?
So I've lost £130 today football bets
and roulette. What a joke, lad.
>> [clears throat]
>> I don't know how people are okay with losing. losing, bro.
No, it went before your time, bro. It
was when I was with that when I was
[ __ ] that 19year-old and that
I was that close to throwing a glass in
someone's face. It was in a casino, bro.
I lost £150 and I was so close to
throwing a glass in someone's face. It's
not even a joke, bro. It's really bad.
It was really, really bad. Why do you
think I gave up for 9 months?
The one, bro. the one the mad one that
used to come and give me [ __ ] and
that and this is when I was [ __ ]
getting sex and [ __ ] Doesn't matter.
Yeah, I just lost 100 pounds on the roulette.
Yeah, still fixed.
It's so fixed, lad.
Akmid is so fixed. It's unbelievable.
It's giving me mood swings, bro. It's
giving me really, really bad mood swings.
The 19year-old one, bro. The one I was
went in the hotel rooms with. But it
doesn't matter anyways, bro. The point
is it was giving me mood swings and I
was that close to throwing a [ __ ]
glass in someone's [ __ ] face, bro.
You know, that was 150 like a couple of
years ago. I don't like losing, bro.
Losing ain't an option. Simple as that.
That's it. I lost 130 today just on
roulette and football bets.
should have like a thousand and something left.
Pretty [ __ ] eye.
See, bro, even if you got over £1,000,5
grand, 10 grand, whatever man money you
have, bro. Yeah, it doesn't matter.
It's all you're thinking about. If you
lose on roulette, it's all you think about.
It's all I think about, bro. It would
ruin the whole day out, the whole
everything. It ruins everything, bro.
It's annoying as [ __ ]
You get me, bro? I'd rather much just
lose the£100 falling out my wallet.
It's that bad. And this is how you know
it's not about the money, Stephen H.
Because if if you dropped £100 out your
wallet, yeah, say you had loads of
money, you was missing 100,
you wouldn't be pissed off. You get on
with your day, you know? You think,
"What the fuck?" at first and like, "Oh,
I dropped £100." But if you lose it on
roulette, it's bad, bro. Bad, bad, bad, bad, bad.
brings out the devil in people.
It brings out It's like a monster has been created.
It's [ __ ] annoying, bro. So annoying, ain't it?
It's so [ __ ] rigged and so annoying, bro.
And I start thinking of all the bad [ __ ]
that's happened to me in my life and
that and make up stuff. It's bad, bro.
It's really, really bad. It really,
really, really, really is bad, bro.
Really bad. How people can just get on
with it, I shall never know.
They lose and they just seem to get on
with it. [ __ ] that [ __ ] bro. You You've
seen how I've been in bookies.
And that's gambling responsibly, Steven
Howard. And that's gambling money you
can afford to lose. That's gambling
money you can afford to lose. Yeah.
You don't need to lose
you don't need to lose all your money
for it to affect you.
Um, and I don't know why people seem to
think that they need to lose all their
money or a lot of money.
I don't like losing. Simple as that.
It'd be all right if you won and then
you lost. Yeah. Like say you won
sometimes then you lost and you could be
like, "Oh, well, you know, it is what it is. Yeah,
it's so fixed, bro. So fixed. [cough]
They're cheating [ __ ]
Cheating little [ __ ]
It's so fixed, bro.
People seem to lose and they seem to be
fine with it. With me, it lingers for
like seven hours, bro. It's annoying.
And I used to be the same even if I when
I had more money. I just don't like
losing. Simple. I don't like losing on a
rigged table. Simple as that.
Yeah, they can't fix football, bro. They
can't fix. So, I lost 130 today on
[ __ ] ru football bats.
[clears throat] I'm supposed to be
changing, bro, and saving money. What the [ __ ]
I remember when I was with that Somalian
before, bro, and I lost £600 and I
literally had to hold it in. Could you
imagine how hard that was having to hold that in?
Losing that money, having to hold it in. Mad.
And there's no underlying problems
because I don't get depressed. I brush
my teeth three times a day. I shower.
Um, I'm hygienic. I don't have any of
these problems until I start playing
that roulette again.
I swear to God, bro. Or slots.
You know what I mean, bro?
Yeah. Well, I lost 130 today on the
football and the [ __ ] gou that. So,
I got one winning spin. 21 out of four
spins. Four, five spins, bro.
I think it was five spins.
Not a [ __ ] sausage. Only a money back number.
You've got to laugh in it, bro. You've
got to laugh.
You have to laugh at it, lad.
It's bad, isn't it, bro?
Have you watched that secular sloth? He
says, "Oh, make sure you gamble
responsibly. Make sure it's money you
can throw away, ret."
And that's what we just did. And it
still doesn't make a difference. It's
still annoying losing.
It's still annoying losing, bro.
Doesn't matter if you can afford it or
you can't afford it. That's got nothing
to do with anything,
how much it is.
Just losing is enough. Losing is enough.
I never laughed. I thought it was depressing.
I don't like losing.
I don't like losing, bro.
I think of all the bad [ __ ] that's
happened in my life and I think people
are laughing at me and that, bro. I
don't like losing.