That's crazy as [ __ ] man.
I still got mood swings this morning
when I woke up, bro. >> Yeah,
>> gamble responsible responsibly. My [ __ ] ass.
My ass, bro. My [ __ ] smelly [ __ ] Yeah, right. Yeah.
That's depressing, bro. That is
depressing as [ __ ] bro. Yeah.
Yeah. See, they're saying the same thing again, bro.
They seem to think that because you
don't lose a big amount of money or
because you still have money left, they
still they seem to think it's okay losing.
They seem to think it's okay losing
because it's not a big amount of money
or you still got money left. They seem
to think that it makes any difference. I
would love to know who come up with this
[ __ ] you know.
I'd love to know who come up with this
[ __ ] I woke up. I'm still in a bad mood.
Still in a stinky, dirty, bad mood.
Stinky, dirty mood.
So, what the [ __ ] bro?
So, they seem to think that if you don't
gamble all of your money and you only
gamble a little bit of money, then
that's all right then. No, it'll put you
off anything completely. That's enough
to put anything off any Well, me
anyways. Don't know about anyone else.
It's [ __ ] depressing, bro.
Depressing as [ __ ]
First thing I thought about today when I
woke up was that roulette and [ __ ] me
over yesterday. What the [ __ ] bro? rigged joke.
But because you still got money, it's
all right. It's okay. No. What the [ __ ]
It's enough to make anyone [ __ ] depressed,
you know? That's it.
And I'm still in a bad mood. Still in a
[ __ ] bad mood.
Probably last for about 24 hours.
It's so [ __ ] annoying.
Don't know how people lose and they all
right with it. They must have some
serious serious serious self-control, bro.
at all. None of these people do. That's
why they don't bother anymore. And then
they just get ignored, just get kicked.
You know, as long as you've still got
money, so they say, as long as it's not
a lot of money, so they say, then you
should be able you should be acting normal.
You should be acting normal, apparently. [ __ ] off.
Yeah, bro. [ __ ] off. Yeah.
[ __ ] that [ __ ]
You need to lose all your money for it
to affect you. How does that work then?
How does that work? So, you need to
gamble all your money or a lot of money
in order for it to wind you the [ __ ] up.
Like, it was winding me up yesterday cuz
it's so [ __ ] fixed. And you didn't
hear a number in five spins. No. What
the [ __ ] bro?
Yeah, he's playing that boost do that.
Yeah, that be that I can't. Dirty bastard.
That's what it is. Dirty [ __ ] stinky bastard.
So just because people have money left
that's fine. No bro that's not how it
works. Could be £1,50 million.
It could be any amount of money. You
could have any amount of money left as well.
There's enough to ru It's enough to
actually ruin someone's whole day, isn't
it? What's the time now? 8:00. It's
enough to ruin anyone's whole day.
Yeah, it's enough to ruin someone's whole day.
with for years with them [ __ ]
them stinky [ __ ] women and I still went
out two three [ __ ] times a [ __ ] week.
So I don't think it's to do with people
being weak either.
No, I don't think it's that. Otherwise,
I should have gave up a long time ago.
I just don't like losing. Simple as
that. You are playing to win. You're not
playing to [ __ ] lose. Whether it's
£50 or whether it's £100. And and you
never win either. That's another thing.
It's not like you ever really do win.
Cuz it's money laundering. It's not
gambling because if it was gambling,
you'd win. If it was gambling, you'd win
sometimes. So, it's not gambling, it's
money laundering. That's another thing
we spoke about yesterday as well. I'm
not calling it gambling. I'm calling it money laundering.
Cuz if it was gambling, you'd actually
win at least one out of five times. But
you don't. You lose all the time because
it's fixed. So that's why we call it
money laundering now. Yeah.
[ __ ] madness, bro.
We'll watch this guy's stream back in a bit.
Whenever I used to lose in the casino
and I used to go out drinking, it used
to take me like an hour to calm down,
but obviously I was drinking as well, so
kind of helped in it.
That's enough to trigger anyone's mental health.
That [ __ ] rigged ass shitty roulette. Yeah.
Wouldn't mind if you won sometimes. But
you don't you don't even win when you
play. You don't even win. Madness. Yeah.
Oh, bless you. And we looking at gardening wheels, but bro
was really nice.
It was nice, man. I have to try the chicken one. Mhm.
I don't understand these white knights, bro.
I seriously don't understand these white
knights. It's just another thing you'll never get.
They'll they'll sit there. They'll sit
there, bro, being [ __ ] They'll sit
there being [ __ ] um
virgins in their 40s. Virgin in their
30s, 40s, and still be defending women.
madness. That's That is autism to the
next level, bro.
I don't get white knights. Women don't
like them. They don't get women, but
they they still defend them.
Like a certain person we know. It's madness, bro.
Definitely some disorder. I don't know
why I just thought that. It's definitely
definitely some disorder.
Why they they'd continuously stick up
for something that don't like them
more than a million times. It's madness, isn't it?
You would have thought they'd learn from
other people's mistakes, but clearly not. Anyways,
I'm going in a minute as no one's typing. So, and yeah.
Yeah, pull it off in a minute.
I'm going anyway. See you.