[Music] Hold
up. Just start having some [ __ ]
nuggets. You're not Oh
[ __ ] Just dip it into these
nuggets. Oh, lovely. [Music] H
Nice. All right, mate. I'm just having
some 20 chicken nuggets. My
fat one [ __ ]
version, you know what I
mean? Nothing much, man. Just chilling. Sat
here. Look at you, mate. I had a curry
the other day. [ __ ] B. It
was I love curry. It's my favorite
food. Curry. I love curry. I love beef
curry from the
Chinese. I love curry. It's [ __ ]
banging. Can't beat a nice com
mate. You want £1,000? That's
nice. I'm done with the gambling now. I
don't do it
anymore. Except football bets. 20 a
week. I don't touch
it. That's good to hear though,
mate. Don't touch it. It's unnecessary
stress. People don't
need this ring too.
Yeah, I don't have my shoes anymore,
mate. Anybody back?
Yeah, man. [ __ ] I just I cut my foot as well.
Yeah. I'm YouTube,
man. But you know, I come off YouTube
for a while cuz it's boring, bro. Same
self-reflectors. Nothing nothing ever
changes. It's a dead community, bro. Dead community. [Music]
He got me. He got me. He got me a
suit. Yeah, I don't smoke weed, mate.
Don't smoke at all.
I'm on a detox as well. I want to be
drinking for a few
weeks, which is
good. All I'm focused on now is saving
money and getting out the
country. I'm at that stage, lad. I'm at
stage. At least I look young. At least
I'm 27 and not 35,
36 before you realize like this country's
dead. This country is actually dead. I mean,
um, yeah, bro. [ __ ] it I hate this
country. I hate this country and
everything about it. The women, the
weather, the government, the gambs everywhere.
I everything about England. Yeah,
buddy. That's how I feel about it. The
version the version has got a passport in it. version. YouTube
versions the YouTube versions YouTube [Music]
Whoa. There's nothing left. I'm stopped. I like
man. It was all night
long. It was [ __ ] all night long.
That was all I know.
What a [ __ ]