Yeah, just having a nice uh beef charge today.
a [ __ ] you
know. [ __ ] I'm stuck. What? Blood.
Five. [ __ ] it up. Yeah. My
quick people in this community need some really life.
[ __ ] all the [ __ ] car.
That's why the top boy [Music] I'm
stuck. What are you going to do? Put me
in the oven now,
mother. Oh, they don't. That's
right. That's right. [Music]
Right. What's going
on? Yeah, I told you, man. Give it a whirl.
Oh, so you will hook up with me, eh?
Well, mate, if you if you [ __ ] with me
there before you know it.
Yeah, you're not proving no point.
[ __ ] hell, woman. [ __ ]
sake. I matter if you go to New York
City. They're westernized. They've got
money. They're not interested. It
doesn't matter. Bro, listen. If you
turned around and said to me, "Yeah, oh
yeah, go to [ __ ] Kentucky." Then I'd
be like, "Okay, or but you're telling
somebody to go to New York City where
they've all got money." Doesn't matter
if you got an accent, mate. They they
probably hear it enough because it's a
westernized country. It's a westernized place. Jesus. The
only the only place it will be different is
[ __ ] South America or [ __ ]
Asia. [ __ ] I can't believe she's even
suggesting. She's got to be She's got to be trolling,
bro. You get Americans
here and Yeah. Okay. They might
obviously hear the accent a lot here,
but they're not going to be surprised
about British accent in [ __ ] New York
City. There's [ __ ] millions of
people. They hear it all the time. Like
I said, unless you go to some hot part
of [ __ ] America, some hillbilly land,
it's not going to
work. It's one of the worst countries to do it. worst places.
Well, it could be that he but just
not just not New York. It would never
work, bro. It would never
work. It would never
work. How would that
work when they're all [ __ ]
westernized? That's cuz you might
not hear a [ __ ] You know what I'm saying?
that. No, I was just saying I was just
talking to this American woman, right?
She's from New York and she Oh, yeah. If
you go to New York, you'll kill it. No,
because they're westernized. It's a rich
place. You get Americans here. You know,
they're they're all the same. Americans,
Canadians, English, Scottish, Welsh,
Australian, Hwies, they're all the same. Westernized
It's New York is I I even said this to
my friend months ago. I said if I was to
put money on the worst place we're
trying to get a woman, I would say New
York. I honestly would. It's like a
bigger London with more money. You're
never getting anything
there. Yeah. No, not not New York. And
they would care about the accent because
they hear it all the time over there.
You want to talk? Come and come and talk
to my face. You little virgin. Come and
talk to my face. You little rat
virgin. Depends how much money you're
talking. Sean, why do you keep calling
me skint when I prove time and time
again? I've got more money than you.
Time and time and time and time again, I
have proven that I've got more money
than you will ever have. You've never
left the country. You have no assets.
You've never traveled. You literally
have nothing. And you're calling me ski.
Well, mate, for somebody that's got as
much money as you claim, you've
literally never been abroad. Never been
abroad. Your passport's about to expire.
You have nothing to 30 years of age, not
even a bed. And I've proven time and
time and time again, I have more money
than you. Yeah. Projection. projection.
Um, I've been abroad. Hold on a minute.
One sec. One
sec. How the [ __ ] is am I projecting?
I've been abroad. I've traveled all over
the country. I've got assets. You don't.
I'm talking about you, Virgin boy. I'm
talking about the little Kent virgin
that's scared to meet anyone. I'm not
talking about myself. I'm talking about
blankie little Kent virgin on a grand a
month. That's who I'm talking about. I'm
not talking about anyone else. I'm
talking about [ __ ] you. You're
telling me I've not been abroad. I can
show my passport stamps. I can literally
show you my passport stamps again. How
is it projection? You've literally never
left the country. You've never been on a
plane. How is that projection? That's me
talking about yourself and you're not
getting attention on my channel. So, you
can get blocked. Bye-bye now. Nah, I
don't let little keyboard warriors on my channel. Sorry. [ __ ] B.
Now you want to talk to me, you can come
and talk to me face to
face. Anyways, moving on. We're not
entertaining these weirdos. So, but
yeah, if you want to talk to me, come
and talk to me to my face.
Simple. You don't need to react to these
idiots. And that's what um ruins the
channel, you know.
And you're blocked as well cuz I know
what you're trying to do. And you're blocked. You're
blocked cuz I know what you're trying to
do. And it's not going to work again.
I'm not want you
man. One second. But he's righteous. Hold on.
Sorry, but I had to speak to someone
there. Yeah, of course it is,
bro. 27, never had a girlfriend. Stop
self projecting. You're in your 40s and
you've never been laid, you skin little
loser. Stop talking about yourself. And
yes, I have actually had a girlfriend.
So, try again. You're 47 and you've
never been touched, you little virgin.
Go self-reflect on another channel, you
[ __ ] loser. Bye-bye. Hey, I was just
at the Chinese for I met somebody from
Newcastle. We was having a good old
chat. We was having a good old chat. No
mother, no dog, no money. You're talking
about yourself. Stop self-
projecting. Oh, these self-p projectors of such
losers. They're such losers, man. Any
anytime you go live, have you noticed
your breaks? You you see the same
self-projected fat ugly people that
ain't got nothing in their lives. They
literally Bro, I know I said I was going
to come off here for a few weeks, bro,
but these people are literally something
to laugh at. They are literally
something to laugh at. They're what you
don't want to be when you're older.
These people are what you don't want to
be when you're older. fat, ugly, no
money, sat on YouTube projecting all
day, every day. This is what I don't
want to be like when I'm their age. So,
in a way, it's it's actually good to
have them on the community because it
reminds you what you don't want to be
like. These [ __ ]
losers. They're absolute losers. They literally
are. They are absolute losers. [Music]
Bye-bye. So many idiots. Anyways, met
this person from uh I was speaking to
him. Triple H. He's from He's from Jordi
Land. He's from Jordi
Land. Yeah. Red Star is either bomb or
that [ __ ] virgin.
Yeah. He said he wants to talk to me.
Come and talk to me through my
face. Yeah. It is sad to be honest.
Yeah, bro. I see that. [Music]
Yeah. And show, bro. It's the same
[ __ ] It's the same spastics every
day. Every day.
They asked that they
bro all they do is self
project. They killed it. And you know
what? And the other thing is Yeah. Put gambling videos
up, you know. No one puts gambling
videos up. They just killed it. They
actually kill it, bro. They killed the community.
But the repeating of that, they kill it,
lad. They kill
it. I want to see if I can go into
America and see this woman. Bro, she let
me stay with
her. You're offering,
mate. See what I'm
saying? Imagine that trip 8 starting a new life.
Oh, I get your point what you're saying.
But what I'm trying to say to you is if
you go to New York City, there's loads
of English people there. I'm guessing
there's loads of English people there
because it's a attraction. [Music]
So, you know what I'm
saying? You know what I'm saying,
brother? Like, so they're not really
going to be like, "Oh, you're from
England." Because they hear it all the
time. Just like when I hear I hear
Americans all the time now. I see
now. So when it's not surprising, you
need to go somewhere where they've never
heard it before. like never heard it
before. Like Texas or [ __ ] even if
you went to
like [ __ ] I don't [ __ ] know, bro.
[ __ ] Philadelphia somewhere like
that, you know, chances are they
probably never heard that accent. But
you go to New York City, they probably
have heard it
obviously. Yeah, I was temped to play
fish and frenzy today. trip rates. But
nah, I'm done with the gambling now,
bro. I've been off it for a while. I am
done with it. I just do 20 pound a week
on football and that's it. Yep. Yep. That's
me. That's me, dog. I don't do it anymore,
bro. I can't see your [ __ ] I do, mate. [ __ ] bro. [ __ ] Crazy it.
Yeah. Have a nice bathroom chill.
So, I am done drinking for two weeks
minimum. Yeah, I got stuff to do this
week. I just go to the mall
Friday. I'm going to be the first one
seeing that. I think you call that like
[ __ ] 7 [ __ ]
p.m. Maybe I might go on a Monday when
no one's there. I'm not sure.
I believe it someday. Good
What's happening to Joe anyways? Oops. Yeah. What? It's a [Music]
Yeah. I think I'll be live later, man. I think we're
probably these [ __ ] mongos now. These
repeaters, you know what I mean?
the [ __ ] virgin as
well. [ __ ] 2D in with that [ __ ] virgin as
me. Yeah, he owned me. What? You You
really think being a keyboard warrior is owning someone?
That's embarrassing to be 30 years of
age and be a keyboard warrior and to be
proud of it. That's that's how I know
you people really really are backwards.
Like you take pride in being a keyboard warrior. That's
crazy. I'd be embarrassed. If I was 30
years of age and I had a channel
dedicated to someone that I was scared
to meet, I would actually be
embarrassed. I I would leave the internet forever.
I would leave the internet forever. I
honestly to God would leave the internet
forever. That is embarrassing,
man. You need to get a life. Do you
live? I who when did I say everybody is
skin and everybody's a virgin? I say
that the people that come on here and
call me skin or skin themselves. They're self-projecting.
That's why I said because you're self
projectors. I Where the [ __ ] did I say
every single person I'd say most of most
of the people on this community asking
yes because you're on YouTube every day.
If you had all this money, you'd be
traveling the world, man. You'd be
[ __ ] you'd be loving you'd be loving
life, living life. But you're on YouTube
every day. So that implies that I don't
have that much money. You know what I'm
saying? I just put the links together to
be honest with you, man. And I never
said everyone on this community is a
virgin. I said Sean's a virgin, Bomb's a
virgin, and Timmy's a virgin. That's what I
said. You're just [ __ ] idiots. One
second. Just sad idiots really.
fake Monty Man accounts. Look, they're
making fake Monty Man accounts. That's a
account. That's a fake Monty Man
account. That's not I'm an
idiot. They make fake accounts of
people. It's sad.
Um, well, I guarantee you that they
don't. And you want to know why I can
guarantee you that they don't? Because
as it stands, I have shown the most
money on this community. I have done
more things than most people what most
people have shown and they're sat on
YouTube every single day. If these
people have got more money than me, why
are they sat on YouTube every day they
talking to each other? Should they be
out traveling the world, doing their
hobbies, meeting with their friends? So,
they've got all this money, but they'd
rather sit on YouTube all day. The links
are not adding up, buddy. It doesn't
make any sense. I can guarantee you most
of these people on this I've caught
these people on here saying that they're
skinn as well. I've gone on law JS
before, right? And I've I've seen people
say, "Oh, I'm
skinn." Like, no, bro. Most people in
this community have not a pot to piss in
because you wouldn't be on here all day
every day if you had something in your
life. That's the fact. Yeah. Okay. Well,
I haven't gambled for two weeks, so
that's wrong. And most people in here
work. Most people here don't work
because you're on YouTube every day, so
you can't work. Most people in this
community absolutely do not work because
you're sat on YouTube every single day.
How can you work and be sat on YouTube
all day? It doesn't make
sense. You don't make no sense. You've
got all this money. You wouldn't be on
here. It would make it would make sense,
right? It would make right more sense
that people are on here because they
have no money, because they have no
life, because they've got crippling
anxiety. Not they don't have anxiety,
they've got all this money. It wouldn't
make sense being on here. Why would they
be on here? Think about it. Just think
about it. Doesn't matter what I've got.
Think about that for one second. It
makes no sense, you
know? And that's it. These people near
on this community don't have money
because they wouldn't be on
here. They wouldn't be on
here. Do the math, mate. Okay, so what
about when you people on YouTube every
single day and I'm not your [ __ ]
mate. Don't call me your mate cuz I'll
never be your mate. But anyways, so
okay, it's Sunday today. So what about
right what about when I see the same
people on YouTube all day every single
day? What about that time? It don't make
sense. They lit They literally don't
make no sense, bro. Honestly, if these
people had money, they wouldn't be on
here. If these people had friends, they
wouldn't be on here as they are. I'm
telling you, bro. I swear to God. I'm
you. Yeah. I've got zero mates. Yep.
Self projection gets banned. Yeah. This
is all That's all they do is
project. Yeah. Yeah, I need to stop I
need to stop replying to these idiots.
You're right, man. I need to stop
replying to these idiots. These
self-reflectives, literally. Yeah, it's stupid,
man. 100%, bro. 100% word, bro. Yeah, I
need to stop
[ __ ] engaging with these little
mongos. They're [ __ ] self
projectors. Just like Sean, he says I'm
a skin big. I've got more money than he
would ever have. I've shown more money
than he would ever have. But I'm scared apparently.
Okay. Yeah. They're just self projectors
like you said, bro. They're not even
worth entertaining. They're just little
projectors that talk about their own
lives for a living.
Yeah, exactly, bro. Exactly. They're proper proper
losers. Cuz how would they know what
you've got in your bank account? They
don't know you on that level. They only talk about
themselves. They're literally just
self-reflectives. Exactly. That's all
they are, bro. That's literally all they
are. That is literally all they are,
bro. They got a pot to piss in as well.
And if you go on L J's, right? If you go
on L J's, lad,
um, if you go on L J's, you'll also notice
N. No, I didn't, bro. I just got
Chinese. Um, if you go on L J, you'll
actually catch some of them saying how they're skint
sometimes. Anyways, I'm going for a
bath. Anyways, I'll see you later, bud.