Yo, madness, bro. Madness, bro. Yeah,
that's funny, bro.
That is a madness, bro.
What the [ __ ] is that?
>> Yeah, I just playing a bit of roulette
with 60 pound. Not a winning spin even
though I covered 18 numbers. Just
gambling, they say.
Yeah, it's just gambling, by the way.
You just continuously keep missing
anything, any number that you bet on.
Just gambling. That's the spirit. Yeah, right, bro.
Yeah, [ __ ] right. Is it just gambling, bro?
[ __ ] 18 numbers. I covered 18 [ __ ]
numbers. You could you couldn't even see
the [ __ ] wheel.
[ __ ] hilarious, bro.
Yeah, I think I'm going to close this
site down, bro. 100.
I reckon I'm going to close it down, bro.
This is the only site I had left.
How does it continuously keep missing 18
19 numbers? What's the chances you can
miss four or five times in a row just
like you wouldn't hit four or five times
in a row?
Yeah, it's [ __ ] bro. [ __ ] bollocks.
No, it didn't win. It was a both teams
to score in the first half, so it never Yeah.
No, cuz I done it in the first half and
the the one I had the both teams to go
and win. I got a cash out of £36 from
from6. I didn't take it and now it's
losing. If only I had 50 on it. Then I
put 60 on the roulette. I didn't even
get a winning spin. Yeah. I covid-19 numbers.
Yeah, they're losing now. Yeah. So
that's [ __ ] me up, bro.
Yeah, bro. But it's not rigged, Dusty,
man. No damn. No.
No, it's not rigged, bro. You just
continuously just keep missing any
number that you bet on. But no, it's not
fixed yet. You cover 189 numbers and you
missed about five times.
Yeah. Okay, bro. You missed five times
just like you would hit five times,
right? Yeah. [ __ ] off, bro.
Yeah, of course you did.
Yeah, I know. I can see it, lad. madness, bro.
How people say that roulette ain't
rigged, lad, is [ __ ] beyond me.
How they say that [ __ ] ain't rigged when
you cover 80 90 numbers and you can't
even get a winning spin. I was playing
the Lad Brooks roulette, bro. The Lad Brooks one.
Yeah, I think I'm just going to have to
pack up gambling, bro. Like all of it.
The football and everything. I'm just
going to I feel like I'm just going to
pack it all up, bro. I think not even
just the roulette. Just like everything,
I reckon, bro.
Yeah. If I had £50 at the start, that
cash out would have been about over £300.
So, it would have been Yeah. Right.
Yeah. I'm going to have to stop all of
it, I reckon. Yeah.
Yeah. I'll just get used to not doing it, bro.
Cuz there's no way, bro, you can you can
spin five spins, right? I deposited £60.
There's no way you can spin five times
and not hit a number, bro. There's
literally no way anyone's going to
justify to me. Based on maths, bro, you
would hit a number. Even if it was a
loser number, you can't continuously
keep missing, bro. You would hit shitty
numbers. Even if you was to lose
eventually, there's no way you can keep
continuously missing, bro.
Yeah. It was live roulette. Yeah.
Yeah, it was live roulette.
I could have cast out 36 from
uh6, but I just left it. Yeah, bro.
Well, they definitely definitely do,
bro. Because the past few times I've
played it, I've won nothing.
I have won absolutely not a jack and
[ __ ] all none of it. So, I'm done with
all gambling, I think, after this, bro.
Even the football. I'm going to close
the account down, I reckon.
Simple as that.
and then be done with it. Done, bro.
Nah. Well, it's got to be fixed because
you can't covid-19 numbers and miss five
times. So, it's got to be fixed because
there's no way you can. I've played
roulette the past couple of times, lad.
Well, it must Well, it's got to be fixed
because you can't covid-19 numbers and
keep continuously missing.
There's no way, bro. Mathematically, you
can't. I've played it a couple of times the past
yeah recently and I've not won nothing.
I haven't hit anything. So there's no
way, bro. It's it's
there's no way it's random. It can't be.
You would win eventually. You would
actually hit numbers.
It is possible cuz it is fixed. It
doesn't matter if it's live with a few
hundred people. It's fixed. Simple as
that. It doesn't matter. It's fixed.
It's got to be fixed. If I'm covering
right more than half the board and it's
missed five times, it's fixed. If you
have not hit a number, I will safely say
anyone that covers 90 numbers and you
have not hit a number in five spins,
it's fixed. Doesn't matter what the
number is. If you have not hit any
number, doesn't matter what the number
is, it's fixed. It's got to be.
So that's that.
But yeah, I'm closing this lad's account
down anyways after this football, which
is probably not going to win. And I'm
not even going to do the football
anymore. No, [ __ ] that.
Yeah, I take it. Uh, yeah, they both
lost. So, yeah, man. But no, it's got to
be fixed. It's got to be got to be got
to be fixed.
And you I couldn't even see the [ __ ]
wheel spinning either.
It has to be fixed. It's got to be
fixed. There's no other There's no other alternative.
There's nothing else it can be but fixed.
Cuz what's the chances of missing five
times in a row? What is the chance of missing?
There's like literally no chance.
There's like literally no [ __ ] chance.
So, what is it? What is it? Uh,
people will defend them and say they're
not fixed, but they are fixed. No, I
don't need to gambling. I don't need to
contact them. I'm done with it, bro. I
don't care. I don't need to do all that
extra [ __ ] I'm just done with it. I
don't care and I don't care what they
say. I'm just done with it. Simple as that.
I don't need to do extra stuff, bro. I'm
done with it. Simple. It's my choice to
do it and it's my chance to quit it just
like I did for a year. So, it's simple
as that. Because there's no way you have
put that kind of money in and you have
not hit any numbers. There's no way.
There's no house heads. There's no
nothing. Simple as that. So,
well, it's not a form of entertainment
for me, especially when you can't even
get a fair game. You can't even get a
fair [ __ ] game.
If I had 50 on the football, I would
have got like a 300 cash out.
Yeah, would have lost.
Yeah. So that's that. Yep.
Yeah. I just put 60 on the brouette.
It's madness, isn't it?
No goals. No.
Another losing session, eh?
be done with all of it, I reckon.
Even the football. I didn't even I
didn't say the football before, did I?
Yeah, I didn't I didn't say the
football, did I, Greasy, last time?
But no, I'm doing I'm quitting the
football as well. I'm closing this
account down as soon as these bets um
bets loses. [ __ ] that.
Yeah, [ __ ] that, bro.
There's no way you can you can play
roulette that many times and not hit and
no one's going to justify to me. So, at
the end of the day, bro.
Yeah. No, with roulette, bro, I put 60
on roulette. Five spins covering 90
numbers. didn't hit nothing.
And I'm sat here wondering why you
haven't hit any numbers in five spins.
So, I'm just going to close the account now.
I got £25 in bets and 60 in um on roulette.
I'm done done, bro. 100% I'm done done
closing this account down. And you can
actually close it down as well. I'm done
with the football. I'm done with
everything. Simple as that.
Well, even the other team didn't score.
Yeah, simple as that. I'm done.
Simple as that, bro. No.
Yeah, I think that bet lost.
Yeah. Okay, I can close this account down.
See, I can go cold turkey on it, but I
know something's fixed in my mind, bro.
I can I can go I can go cold turkey on
it. Simple as that. Um, yeah.
I don't think I I just want to know why
it's fixed. I don't know why they need
to cheat on something that they're going
to win on anyways, but I'd love to know
why they feel the need to cheat on
something that's already rigged against
the player. And they are cheating
because you can't miss that many [ __ ] times.
You literally [ __ ] well can't. It's
as simple as that. There's no way you
[ __ ] well can. So,
see you later.
One second. The game's finished.
How people can sit there and say that
ain't fixed. It [ __ ] well is.
How they can sit there and say that [ __ ]
ain't fixed, bro. Well, I I'm not here
to I'm not here to um I don't want people
100% I've given up, bro.
What? Let this football match end and
I'm just closing this countdown, bro.
>> Yeah, 100%. I'm done with gambling, bro.
Even the football.
>> Yeah, [ __ ] that, bro. Absolutely [ __ ] that [ __ ] 100%.
Just want waiting for this football finishes.
It's as simple as that, bro. As simple as that.
I don't like to call it gambling. I like
to call it money laundering,
if you understand what I mean. I like to
call this money laundering because if it
was gambling, you'd actually be able to
win. If it was gambling, you'd be
winning some of the time. So, I call it
money laundering. That's what I call it.
Don't know about you, but I call it money laundering.
Well, it seems to be money laundering
because you can't win. So, it's
definitely not gambling because if it
was gambling, you'd be able to win.
No, it's called it's called money
laundering. That's what it's called.
All right. And I'm done. Simple as that. Thank you.
Simple as that, bro.
So, it is as simple as that. Closed it.
Simple as that.
Not a problem at all. So, I have to tell
people on this on this gambling on this
uh well gambling on this channel now,
there's not going to be no more football
bets. There's not going to be no
nothing. So, yeah, it's going to take
them time to get used to, but yeah, that's it.
I'm not giving money on something that
cheats. It's as simple as that.
And people that can't even provide a fair game. Pointless, bro.
Yeah. It was
I was on the phone to my friend as well. Yeah. Nope.
I'm done with it, lad.
I'm done, lad. Simple.
How was that L11 that I missed five
times in a row?
Five times in a row when I covid-19
numbers and I didn't hit any number.
Seems to be a seems to be a trend now,
don't it, lad?
Yeah, I'm done, bro.
Definitely done. [ __ ] that [ __ ]
It's not about luck. It's fixed.
It's not about luck. If it's not about
luck, cuz eventually you would win.
Eventually, you literally would win.
It's not about luck.
It's that they're cheating. They're
rigging the tables. That's exactly why
I've closed this account, man. I'm not
even going to bet on football anymore,
bro. I don't give a [ __ ] about it, me,
bro. I really don't.
It's not about luck. It's just plain
cheating. It's as simple as that.
Oh, just £60 on the roulette, bro. And
£25 on football bets. I got a cash out
of £36 on a six bet, but I let it keep going.
I don't win gambling. I can't remember
the last time I've won on roulette.
You don't win because it's fixed. That's
the whole point. You don't win. That's
why that's literally why I closed the account down.
It's not about the percentage. They're
making it go on losing numbers.
That's not enough for them. They are
literally making it go on losing
numbers. It's not gambling. I don't like
calling it gambling because if it was
gambling, you'd be winning sometimes.
So, I'm not call I don't call it
gambling. I call it fraud or money
laundering because you literally would
be winning sometimes.
You'd be you'd be getting above your
balance some of the time. So,
oh well, at least that one didn't even score.
But yeah, I'm done with it all anyways. So, yeah,
I am completely done with it all.
And it's as simple as that. Yeah, it is
as simply as that.
No better, no football, no nothing.
There's no point on betting on something
that's fixed. There's literally no point
on betting on something that's fixed.
It literally is fixed as [ __ ]
I'll just find other hobbies, bro. I'm
going to go to the gym on Monday and
I'll do other stuff. I don't mind, bro.
It's as simple as that.
I'm done done, bro. And I feel like
football is bad as well. I mean, like
any form of gambling's bad, so I just
close the account now. Not a problem.
Yeah, no problem. I've got some money
coming in anyways that someone owes me.
So we'll have a fresh start. Complete
fresh start now. So simple, bro. I don't
give a [ __ ]
Yeah, that's that, lad.
Yeah, cuz it's fixed. I've been losing
cuz it's fixed. And there's no point in
playing something that's fixed. It's as
simple as that.
I don't want to hear about it. I don't
give a [ __ ] if it's only money. It's
fixed. I don't give a [ __ ] It's fixed.
Simple as that. You know, I don't give a
[ __ ] if it's only money.
It's fixed. It's as simple as that. So,
why am I going to play something that's
fixed? Luckily, with this account, it
let you let let you actually close close
the account down.
It definitely definitely is fixed.
You're telling me you didn't you didn't
hit any numbers in them? You didn't hit
any numbers in five spins when you
covered 90 numbers? Really, mate?
Really? The whole tier and other numbers
on top? Really, mate? Really? [ __ ] off,
mate. They saw the white man coming.
They saw the white man coming, mate.
That's what they done. They saw the
white man coming.
[ __ ] off. Simple as that.
We're not talking about properties.
We're talking about live roulette.
Sorry, I quote live quotation live roulette.
Yeah, they must have sold a [ __ ]
white man coming
or some [ __ ] They saw a white man
coming with 60 quid. Get [ __ ] Yeah.
So, I'm going to have to explain to
Ant-Man as well like there's not going
to be no football no more. There's not
going to be no nothing.
There's going to be no nothing now. So
simple as that, bro. Yeah, I done £25 on
football bets and£60 on roulette.
I done 19 spin uh 19 numbers, five
spins. Didn't hit nothing. Not a jack and nothing.
They must have saw the white man coming.
Echo, they saw the white man coming, mate.
Yeah, it might be all right for you, but
I won't be there. Your mom,
I closed the account down anyways, bro.
I'm done with it. That's the only site I
used. I'm done with it, bro. Simple.
There's no way you've missed that many
times. And there's no way anyone's going
to justify to me. Simple. So, that's the
end of it.
There's going to be no football, no nothing. Done.
Sorry, but that's the way it's got to be.
I bet on a nil nil as well. Correct.
Score nil nil.
I was betting on the live nil nil. N nothing
[ __ ] started scoring on the 60th
minute. [ __ ] off. Darn it. Simple as that.
The reason I'm not going mad is because
I've already I've already gone bad a
million times. I don't have the energy
for it anymore.
I don't have the energy for it.
I've spoke about the manager. I spoke
about the manager's [ __ ] kids. I've
done it all, bro, you know. So, it's
there's nothing else to say
that I haven't already said. It's fixed
and that's it. Simple. So, yeah. Yeah.
I don't know why they cheat, but they
do. They love cheating. I don't know why,
but yeah, we're having a fresh start
anyways, bro. Got this, like I said, got
this money coming in as well. So, done.
Lovely fresh start.
Been there, done it. We can safely say
in 2026, gambling still fixed. They're
still using magnets under the tables and that's that.
And then the football bets are just not
even worth doing. So yeah.
Yeah. Simple as that.
I don't know what I'm doing soon. Don't
know. Don't care.
Simple as that. Don't know. Don't care.
See you later. No self projected on this channel, lad.
That's self projecting, lad.
I don't entertain you little sad self-p
projecting fat lossers. So, I don't know
why you still come back for more, you
losers. But yeah, your life losers,
mate. That's why no one reacts to you. Anyways,
yeah, Roulette's fix though. That's the thing.
No, I'm done with it, lad.
No, I'm done with it. I'm done with any
kind of gambling now. Football,
anything. Everything. There's no point
betting on [ __ ] you can't win on.
See, look, I'm [ __ ] pissed off here
and these people are still not bothering
me. Like, these people that are writing
this stuff on YouTube, they're still not
getting to me. And I'm like pissed off.
Like I'm at my worst and they still
don't get to me. That tells you
everything, bro. Cuz I know what these
people are. So they can't annoy me even
when I'm annoyed. I know they're sat on
YouTube 24/7. I know they're fat and
ugly. I know they've got no life. So the
moment someone like that is able to
judge you and get to you, bro, you've
already lost. You've literally already
That's You're [ __ ] lad.
Yeah. Well, not me, mate, because I'm
out of the game. It's as simple as that.
I'm out of the game. I'm going to tell
Antman as well.
I'm going to tell Antman as well. I'm
done with it.
I'm going to have to tell him because
obviously we talk about football bets
and [ __ ] I'm out of it, bro. [ __ ] that.
Yeah, I quit gambling for a year, but I
didn't lose everything.
It was just pissing me off.
No, I'm not keeping my chin up, bro.
It's enough to put anyone into a
depression. I don't understand how
people lose and they're fine with it. If
I I if I if I told you what I wanted to
do, bro, you my whole channel would get
banned. Like, it's not it's not even a joke.
Yeah, I was gambling it. I was I lost 60
on roulette and £25 on football bets.
And now I'm completely done with it,
bro. Like, I'm not even doing football anymore now.
I won't be doing football anymore now.
sometime this year, bro.
So, you would have thought these people
could trigger me, bro. But they can't
even trigger me even when I'm pissed off.
Do you think some fat ugly middlewage
losers that ain't got nothing in life
could trigger me? Lad
could trigger me? Are you [ __ ] mad,
bro? Come on now. You've already you've
already lost the game if you're letting
people like that get to you.
YouTube depending morons.
Come on, bro. You're [ __ ] mad.
No, I'm not a bad gambler, bro. I just
gone through a phase of it. I'm done
with it now anyways. So, I won't be
going back to it.
So, I'll be going back to the gym soon
anyways. So, I'm done with it now.
No football bets, no nothing.
No, no, nothing, bro. I thought, oh
yeah, put 60 on roulette. You You're
going to win this time surely. N
no no no nothing. [ __ ] that [ __ ] No, no chance.
I have to hold in what I really want to
say and what I really want to do. Trust
me, bro. Yeah. [ __ ] idiot.
Nah, bro. I can't do that on YouTube,
unfortunately. Too many grasses.
Can't be doing that, lad.
Should have just bought drugs. No thanks.
Yeah, I've only started again recently.
I stopped for a year, bro, because of
the mood swings.
I stopped for a year because of the mood
swings. It wasn't cuz I'm running out of
money. It was because of the mood
swings. Mine's different to you and uh
probably mo probably probably most people.
Yeah. If I lose, I want to literally do
some serious damage
like abnormal to someone, bro. Like the
other day, bro, I was going to drag
someone out the [ __ ] car, bro. And I
weren't going to stop.
It was when I was coming back from the
dentist, bro. No, it weren't the
dentist. I come back from the police to
go to the police and that and I lost
£50, bro. And this [ __ ] was uh I think
they were beeping me and I said, "You
[ __ ] what?" I spat on their car, bro.
And I was I was I went to go in the door
and open the [ __ ] door, bro. And then
I drove off. I was chasing that car
down, bro. They're so They're lucky I
didn't catch up with them, bro. I would
have dragged him out the [ __ ] I was
going to drag him out the car, bro. It
was some old woman. Yeah, I'm not even
joking. I don't give a [ __ ] And I done
it in front of men as well. Yeah.
Serious. Seriously, bro. That's why I
had to stop for like a year.
Well, I feel like I I feel like doing the um
Nope. Didn't win. I lost. And I lost on
roulette as well.
Yeah, it is. And people say that if you
gamble responsibly, John, it's okay. But
it isn't okay. It isn't okay. It's never
ever ever ever okay. Trust me.
No, it was online.
No, I done both teams to score in the
first half and then the other one was a
both teams to score and win. So, I
didn't win. I got a cash out £36, but I
didn't didn't do it.
Didn't take it. So, yeah.
No, I'm not banned online. My gam run
out. I closed the account down anyways.
I'm done with the gambling now. Anyways,
bro, football and everything. I'm
completely done with it. So, that's that.
Yeah, bro. Whenever I used to lose
gambling, I felt like overdosing
and it was always money I could afford
to lose as well. Sick of repeating that
as well. I'm so sick of repeating that
same line, bro. I've said it so many
times because people think, yeah, oh,
they seem to think, oh well, oh, if
you're if you're doing that, it's money
that you can't afford to lose.
Or they seem to think that you got a
problem because you react like that.
What are you supposed to be happy, bro?
It doesn't matter if it was what? It
doesn't matter. It doesn't matter if it
wasn't very much. I don't give a [ __ ]
It could be£10. Losing is not an option.
This is what I mean. People like this
guy right here, they seem to think
because it's not a lot of money, it
shouldn't affect you. It does. It does
affect you. It does. It doesn't matter
what the amount of money is. I don't
know why people seem to think it's to do
with how much money you lose. Losing is
just annoying. Period.
It doesn't matter how much it is, how
much you've got. It doesn't matter.
That's exactly why I closed this account down.
So, and I'm done now. Not even no
football, no nothing.
Doesn't matter how much you lose or how
much you've got left.
I used to go when I used to go Lester
Square, John. Yeah. I used to always
start off in a casino and if I lost And
if I lost, it would ruin the whole night
out. Well, it it went it would take like
two hours to calm down because I was drinking.
But obviously that's probably because
the drinking in it. It might have calmed
me down, but it would literally ruin the
whole night out, bro.
Like it would ruin everything. Like I've
actually ditched people I was with
because of it. It just ruins everything.
It's not about the money. And I can tell
you another thing, John. Yeah. I two
months ago I was I was playing this FBI.
Yeah. I put 50 in. Up down up down up
down. I was up down up down up down,
bro. I took the £50 back and it was
still annoying me and I didn't even lose any money.
So it doesn't matter how much. I just
think people like me can't gamble on
anything. So I won't. So that's it.
Closed the countdown. I stopped for a
year anyways. So that's it, bro.
Yeah. Self projecting, lad. You're not
going to get a reaction out of me.
Yeah, I know about house edge, but
that's not the house edge.
Yeah, I know about the house edge and
it's nothing to do with the house edge
self projectors. Sorry, lads. We get a
lot of them, man. We get a lot of these
wasters. These waste low lives.
Yeah, low lives. Excuse Excuse them.
No, I'm done, bro. It's 2.7. It's not
2.8. It's actually 2.7.
But I'm done anyways. There's not going
to be no treble. There's that. I'm done.
Probably is that virgin. Oh, that loser
Jo. Oh, I was saying this earlier. I'm
going to Nottingham soon anyways. So,
I'm going to put it on my community post.
I'm going to bully me. Nah, you people
don't bully me at all, man.
You people bully yourselves. That's why
That's why you don't bother me. That's
why the stuff that you say literally
don't bother me because I know what you
people look like. I know what you people
are and it's you the ones that have been
bullied by life your whole life. That's
why you don't get to me. Even now I'm
mad. I'm [ __ ] wanting to smash stuff
up over roulette. But bro, it doesn't
bother me because we know that deep down
ugly skin, no money, nothing ain't got,
bro. That's why it doesn't bother me.
You can't even it can't even get me mad
when I'm [ __ ] mad.
Like, you just you just And then I've
noticed as well, people are using my
[ __ ] words now, bro. They're actually
using my words. Like, I said that you
are the wasters. Yeah, you haters are
the wasters. Now you're using my [ __ ] words.
I lost all my benefits, money. No, bro.
I'm not you. Stop comparing your life to me.
Yeah, stop comparing your life to me.
Weird community, bro. Proper weirdo community.
No, I don't need to go to meetings, bro.
I can stop. I haven't lost all my money.
I've got money, bro.
I can stop, bro. I'm done. I'm literally done, lad.
I'm done, bro. I can stop, bro. I
stopped for a year anyways, bro. I've
only just recently gone back to it. I'm done, bro.
Don't worry about me, bro.
I've got good money, bro. I've never
done Just Eat in my life. So, you might
want to get your facts right, cuz I've
never done Just eat in my right in my
life. So, if you're going to if you're
going to tell people that they've done
stuff, you might want to get your facts right.
And maybe I've got good money now. You
don't know that. You'll never know
because it's none of your business. And
no one tells you jealous people anything.
I don't need beans and toast, mate. I've
got plenty of money to get whatever I want.
Had a nice curry today.
I will never be on beans and toast,
mate. I've got plenty of money. You
don't need to know about that, though, do you?
No, I'm not doing football bets. I'm
just dumb, bro. I'm dumb. Simple. Simple as that.
Yeah, I'm done, bro. It's all good, man.
Yeah. Well, it depends what you Well, obviously. Yeah,
obviously I'm in control, bro. Obviously,
I'd say so. Well, obviously. Yeah. I
don't go broke. I've got my bit. Yeah. Obviously, bro,
cuz obviously I had an online account
and I feel like if I wasn't, I'd be skinn.
I'd be broke. So, I I still think Yeah,
I I I do, bro. I kind of do
cuz I'd be broke right now if not
I said I never said I had someone to
change the passcode. You know,
bro, why are you so obsessed with my
life and what money I have as well?
That's another thing you weirdos do.
You're so obsessed with what other people have.
people have. It's so weird. Worry about
your own lives. It's [ __ ] weird, man.
Yeah, I know, bro. Yeah.
Yeah, I'm done anyways, bro.
Yeah, I'm done, lad.
See, if I lose, I just spit on the machines.
No, it's nothing to do with luck. It's
just It's just blatantly fixed. It's as
simple as that.
Yeah, I I spat on a machine. Um,
when was it a week and a half ago?
She was like, "Oh, mate, can you calm
down? Can you calm down?" I said, "Don't
call me your [ __ ] mate." And then we
was arguing, arguing, arguing. Just left
the shop and I thought, "Nah, no, no. I
I want to come back. I want to go back
for some more, mate." Just spat all over
the machine. Simple as that, bro.
No hurting hands, no smashing. I've done
it many times.
Just a nice big lovely spit all over the machine. Lovely. You know,
yeah, simple as that. Lovely bit of
spit. Lovely bit of flem all over it.
Yeah, about a week and a half ago on it,
bro. In the betting shop.
No, I don't have a problem because I've
still got money. I still eat. So, how
can I have a problem? I've got a problem
with uh machines being fixed. Yeah.
See you later. Madness.
Yeah, I know. I just don't like rigged
things. cuz I just don't like rigged
machines. Simple as that. Yeah.
Let's see if thingy email me back.
But yeah, I'm done anyways.
Trevor Dawson, you're another one that's
not going to get to me, lad. I went all
the way to Middles, bro, and you never
come out again. You literally
You can't get to me. You're another
coward. Just like Jo, just like the rest
of them. You're another coward, lad.
You're just a little fat ugly loser
coward. Ain't got no life. Would never
say anything to anyone's face. You
couldn't come out when I went to your
No, I didn't upload videos after. No, I
didn't, Trevor. And stop trying to use
that as an excuse because you would have
just went there with another video. Stop
making excuses. I was in Newcastle live
after Middlesbrough. You did not come
out. Yeah. Come on now. We know the
story. Everyone knows the story and I
don't need anyone to back me up. So, no.
If if I uploaded videos after I left,
you would have literally done a video to
prove I was wrong. Middlesbrough is is
is a small place, but you couldn't
because you knew if you went out, you
knew what would have happened. So,
simple as that. So, you can make all of
the excuses you want, lad. That's it.
And I want to know what's the excuse
going to be when I go to Nottingham.
Oh, yeah. Yeah, I went to Middlesbrough
a couple of years ago and this little
[ __ ] didn't come out and he was on
YouTube and he's from Middlesbrough.
Yeah, now he makes excuses that oh, I
done videos but I went home. The same
usual excuses that you make. Oh, [ __ ]
hell. It's boring, bro. I'm I'm going to
love to hear what the the excuses. I was
in B for 2 hours, brother. I was in B I
was in Middlesbrough for 24 hours. I
stayed over there, mate. I've still got
the video of the place that I was
staying in. No, I know he doesn't live
in Nottingham. I'm going to meet him
halfway. It's as simple as that. And
there's a reason why I'm going to
Nottingham. There's there's a there's a
reason why I'm going to Nottingham. No,
he doesn't live there. Uh Trevor Dawson,
I stayed in Middlesbrough for 24 hours.
Yeah, bro. I I literally was I literally
stayed over there. So, nice try, Trevor.
You're full of excuses, mate. Everyone
knew that I was staying in Middles, bro.
Right. Stop talking [ __ ] mate. Stop
talking [ __ ] Right. I still got the
booking on here and the video as well.
Stop talking [ __ ] You did not come out.
Stop it. You're a keyboard warrior.
You're not the only one, bro. Cory Dak
didn't come out that day either. Just
own it, bro. You're a [ __ ] house. Like,
bro, just own it. You're a [ __ ] house.
You're not the only one. You didn't come
out. Sh didn't come out. Cory, that
didn't come out. You're all shitous,
bro. You're not the only one. I don't
know why you Bro, you know what I'm saying?
Bubba, listen. He I would be letting him
know when I'm in Nottingham.
Yeah. Simple as that. And if he does not
come out, he's a [ __ ] house. And I'm
going to give him more than enough uh
time in advance.
Um and the reason and there's a reason
why I didn't go where he told me to go
because I knew exactly what he was going
to do. Yeah. All they're going to do is
say, "Oh, I've made you go all that
way." H I control you. I know the game,
bro. I know what happens. So this way,
I'm going to Nottingham. I want to go
there anyways. It's halfway. So, he's
just going to look like an idiot when he
doesn't turn up. Well, Nottingham's not
even halfway. It's more nearer to him
than it is me.
But yeah, I live I live miles away from
Nottingham as well. 150 mi to be exact.
That's no excuse, lad. If you're about
it, you'll meet halfway. Simple. If
you're about it, you'll meet halfway.
Yeah. If you're about it, you will meet
halfway. Simple as that.
And if you don't, you're a [ __ ] house.
Which he is a [ __ ] house, you know.
Yeah. It makes me look stupid. Really? Does it? really? Okay, Trevor.
Okay, Trevor, you keep telling yourself
that. Oh, [ __ ] Like you got out, bro.
Yeah. Okay, bro.
Yeah, you come up with so many excuses
when I was in mles, bro. It was embarrassing, bro. So embarrassing.
Oh, you done videos when you went home.
No, that's not what happened. I was
literally staying in Middlesbr, bro. But
you always you're always going to have
your little excuses, bro. Like, we know
all of this [ __ ]
Did he Did he turn up to the place, Jake?
Did he turn up to the place? It It was
the pub, wasn't it? It was to meet at
the pub, wasn't it? He said to meet at
the pub. Well, as far as I can remember,
he didn't even turn up himself. So, it's
not a win cuz he didn't turn up. So, if
you want to go down that if you want to
go down that avenue, mate, we'll go down
that avenue, won't we?
Because he didn't turn up. He literally
did not turn up. So, how could there be
a victory when, bro, he didn't even turn up himself.
So, you know, we'll move on from that.
No one won on that one. I will be
letting him know when I'm in Nottingham. Yeah,
I will be. Okay, forget all of that.
Anyways, I will be letting him know when
I'm in Nottingham. But well, before I
go, obviously I'm going to tell him in
in advance and we'll see what this guy
is all about. Yeah, simple. Like,
there's no point going back and forth
about that. That's disabled, bro. I will
be letting everyone know when I'm in
Nottingham. Straight up.
Yeah. And and and and and we'll see what
kind of man he is. Yeah.
But like the thing is Trevor Dawson, did
you not learn anything from this? Like
don't piss people off because I would
back in the day I would just travel 5
hours to you. I'm not like you. See, you
seem to think right. This was your
mistake. Yeah. It was the same thing
with um Triple H and um Cory, but they
were it was a different way for them.
And you you how many times was you not
saying, "Oh, come to the Northeast. Come
to the Northeast." Because you didn't
think that anyone was uh you didn't
think anyone was actually going to come
because you would never come to London.
You didn't think anyone was going to
come from London to you. And then when
they do come to you, you come out with
all of these excuses. Yes, I did stay in
Middlesbrough. Yes, I did. Everybody
knew I stayed in Middlesbrough. Stop
making excuses. The only one that's
lying is yourself. Yeah. The only one
that's lying is yourself. Stop
embarrassing yourself. Everybody know
that I Everyone knows I went to
Middlesbrough. Everybody knows that I
was staying there. And that's it. Stop
making excuses. Literally, what do you
think? Someone just went all the way to
Middlesbrough to call you out for 2
seconds and and go back home. Stop it
now. Stop it. We all heard the excuses
that you made right when I was there.
And at the end of the day, bro, you
could have easily went where I was and
showed me up.
Stop making excuses. You're not about
it. Yeah. [ __ ] me, bro.
I won't even meet people in my own city. Really?
Really, bro? I won't meet people in my
own city. Really, bro?
You You know you're talking to me, bro.
Someone that's met more people than
anyone. You You know you're talking to
me in it. This is what I had to tell LT
when he was like bringing up the whole
USA thing. I said, "You do realize
you're talking to me, bro. Someone that
knows more than you.
Someone that actually knows more than
you. You actually talking to me now? Not
some idiot on YouTube that doesn't know
anything. You're talking to me, bro. How
are you even going to try that?
I think sometimes these people forget
who they're actually [ __ ] talking to.
Oh, bro, not this again. We're not
having the same conversation again, are
we? Bro, like I told you, I'm going to
be in Nottingham soon within the next
couple weeks. So, what why are you
bringing all of that [ __ ] up?
We'll see who the running man is then,
won't we? That's it. We'll see who the
running man is then. That's nice, bro.
I've been in Oh, of course I have. I
know what these people are like, bro. I
know what these people are like.
Yeah. I know what they're like. That's
why they don't get me mad, bro.
These people don't even get me mad when I'm mad.
It's impossible. you. They're more funny
than anything to be honest. Well, I say
they're funny, but
I don't know, bro.
I don't know, bro. I mean, they're kind
of funny, but then they're kind of
someone to just feel sorry for
to drive all that way. Well, I mean,
they can get the train.
Well, they can Well, then it doesn't
matter then. If they don't turn up, then
they don't turn up. Simple. I'll be
going to Nottingham and that's it.
So, I'm sure you'll have no problem
jumping on a train that's 80 miles. If
I'm traveling 150 mi, why can't you travel?
You know, I mean, I'm going to give you
more than enough time in advance. I
mean, if I can travel 150 mi, why can't
you travel 90 mi?
What's stopping you? Come on.
Yeah, it's jealousy, bro. That's what it
is with these people like Jo L1. They're
just jealous, bro. They're just jealous
fat, ugly people that ain't got a life.
I don't even I just laugh at them now.
Yeah. Well, at least I'm not afraid of
meeting someone in my own city like you,
Trevor. I'd rather be afraid of a
motorway than be afraid to [ __ ] meet
someone in my own city like you.
You're so embarrassing, lad.
So embarrassing. That is embarrassing,
bro. And then you come out with these
excuses when everyone knew I was staying
in the middles. Bro, I've got the
booking right here. You [ __ ] idiot.
You're mad. Um, I don't know what I'm
doing tomorrow, bro. I don't really make plans.
Probably go get some food or something.
Yeah, I was in B for a few hours. You
keep telling yourself that, bro. Yeah,
you keep telling yourself that. Yeah. Okay, bro.
You keep telling yourself that.
If I show you the booking.
Okay, I can I can I I can show you the booking.
Do you want to see the booking, Grezy?
Well, here's here's what we're going to
do because I don't feel like I need to
prove myself to these losers. Grievesy,
do you believe I stay in Middlesbr, bro,
or do you not? If you don't, I'll show
the booking right now. If you do, then I
won't. It's all up to Grezy,
you know, because I can't have genuine
people not believing me, you know. If
you don't, I'll show it right now, mate.
It's simple, mate. Oh, you know that
time I went to Middlesbrough, Trevor
Dawson is trying to say that I didn't
stay there and I was only there for a
couple of hours. Even though I showed a
video of me in the place I was staying,
he's trying to say that I was there for
a couple of hours.
I mean, what do you think, Greavves? Do
you reckon I stayed over there? We're
talking like two and a half years ago, bro.
When I was in the Northeast, you
remember that time?
Okay. Show right now.
Yeah, why not?
Cuz I need to jog some people's memory.
One second. Go on booking.com.
I've traveled to a lot of places, bro.
Right. One second.
One second, bro.
Look at that right now. Two seconds.
I think I need to log in.
One second, bro. So, now
you're going to look really stupid now, lad.
You're going to look really, really stupid.
Oh, so now you're saying Oh, you're just
talking [ __ ] now. Oh, he's just he's
just completely talking [ __ ] So, you're
saying that even if I showed the book in
I I didn't stay there. So, okay, now
you're just talking [ __ ] Okay, now I I
was actually expecting like people to be
genuine now. You're just You're just
talking [ __ ] now. But I'm going to show
it. I'm going to show it anyways cuz
Grezy wants me to.
>> Okay. Okay. Okay. I'm going to put it up
anyways, Grezy. Yeah. But this guy's
always going to talk [ __ ] just like the
rest do. Yeah. Yeah. I'm going to I'm
going to show it anyways. Yeah. One second.
Yeah, he's talking [ __ ] bro.
This guy is talking [ __ ] One second.
Bookings and trips. Two sex.
Here we go.
It will show you when I checked in.
Checked out. There you go.
There you go. You want to see the
booking? It's right here.
Sorry about that, Captain Log on. It
been a long time.
Where is it? How do you zoom in?
[ __ ] [ __ ] [ __ ]
Why is it not working?
One second, bro.
I'll just put it up.
And what you'll find is the only one
that's got anxiety to is you.
There we go.
Now look at that. That was in middle,
bro. Where I was staying.
There you go. It's right there. Right in
the middle. That's my booking.
Yeah. And you're still going to talk
[ __ ] and still make excuses. And that's
why I don't go and meet anyone anymore.
And Gregy, this is exactly why, bro.
Yeah, fake bookings. Okay, bro. Fake
bookings. Okay. Yeah. Okay, bro. The
bookings right there along with my other
bookings. And Grezy, this is exactly why
I don't waste my time trying to meet
these people anymore.
Uh because they just come out with a
load of [ __ ] excuses, bro. And it's
just like completely pointless.
They just completely make excuses. It's
right there in the middle. You can see
it. You can literally see it. You can
literally see it right there. And then
you still come out with bogus excuses.
That's why no one waste their time
anymore, bro. That's why literally no
one actually wastes their time anymore
cuz you just come out with the most
ridiculous [ __ ] excuses when someone
It means Yeah. It means I It means I
checked in. Checked in and out. Yeah.
It's right there in the middle. Yeah.
It's not evidence. Okay. Trevor Dawson,
we all know that I was in Middlesbrough
and we all know you did not come out.
So, keep coming out with it. It's right
there. You can see it. It's right there.
It says completed.
Yeah, it's right there in the middle.
What? What? What? What the [ __ ] bro?
It's right there.
You can literally look it up, bro.
Look it up. Look up where it is. Look up
the date as well.
You talk [ __ ] mad [ __ ] bro. Just own
it, bro. Someone come to your to to your
um city and you didn't show up. Stop the
excuses. It's embarrassing.
Yeah, that's what it means. Look,
there's other bookings as well where
I've been. Look, there's Nottingham.
Look, there's other ones. He's He's a
He's a bullshitter, bro.
Simple. I don't need you. H, bro. It's
right there, brother. It's right there.
It's in black and white. Black and white
paper where I was staying, mate. You're
a [ __ ] house. You're an absolute [ __ ]
house. If you really believe that
somebody wasn't in Middles, bro, you
would have just walked out and and shown
me up. Come on. You knew I was there.
You was never going to leave your gaff
cuz you're a fat ugly old man. Just like
a lot of these people on here. And look,
even when you're shown evidence that
someone stayed over in your city, you
still make excuses. [ __ ] off, man.
You're an idiot. You're a clown, bro.
But the lesson lesson learned. Don't
stop thinking everyone's like you.
Stop thinking that because you wouldn't travel. Uh um
uh explain to us why you didn't come
out. Explain to us why you didn't come Simple.
Why didn't you come out? And don't say
because I wasn't there cuz it's right
there. I stayed in your city. So you
can't even use that anymore. Well, you
know it's [ __ ] anyways. You just
want to use that excuse. Why didn't you
come out? If I really wasn't there, why
didn't you just come out? It's in your [ __ ] city.
No, I knew I was in middle as well.
Okay, bro. Yeah, you're you're an idiot,
man. You're an absolute You're a
bullshitter. You're a bullshitter. Stop
calling out people that you don't know.
Yeah, that's that's a lesson learned.
Just because you won't travel 5 hours
away, that doesn't mean someone else
won't travel 5 hours away. You know
that that's a problem with a lot of you
people on here. You seem to think
everyone's like you. And that's the
biggest mistake that you um that you
make. You seem to think everyone's like
you. And you would have thought you
would have learned your [ __ ] lesson
by now. But nah. Yeah.
You're an idiot, bro. Yeah, bro.
Yeah, it is. So, what happened, bro? I
tell you what happened, Grezy. So, um
I stayed over in Middlesbr, bro. I left
all my [ __ ] in Middlesbr, bro. I was in
Middlesbr, bro. And then I went to
Newcastle around 9:00 at night. I got
the train to Newcastle at 9:00 at night.
Yeah. And so, I was clubbing. I was
drinking. I'll tell you exactly what
happened cuz I remember this and I
couldn't get back. I couldn't get back
to Middlesbrough because the trains
wasn't running at past 12 and the cabs
was asking too much. So I was like, "Oh,
[ __ ] Let me book a hotel in Newcastle."
Booked a hotel in Newcastle. Tried to go
to the hotel, but it was on a curfew. It
was on a curfew and so I couldn't even I
couldn't even get in it. Like it was one
of them curfew ones and bro it was
pissing down with rain. I got soaked. I
literally had to stay out until 8:00 in
the morning. Went to a calf at 5:00 in
the morning. Had to wait till 8:00 in
the morning. Go back to Middlesber, get
my [ __ ] and then I went back home. I
remember that. I can actually remember
that. Stop the lies, bro. No one lies
like you and LJ. There's no lying on this channel.
You know, you're the one that's lying.
You are the one that's lying. There's
proof that I've been to Middlesbrough.
There's proof that you didn't show up.
So the only one that's lies is you and
your boyfriend, Lord Jay. Not me, bro.
There's no lying on this channel. I say
when I've won money. I say when I've
lost money. I don't lie like you and your boyfriend.
Nah, there's no line on this channel, lad.
Oh, you know when I went to Middlesburg,
Dusty, uh Trevor Dawson's making up all
of these excuses why he didn't come, so
I had to show the booking. Yeah, I got
caught in I got caught in uh Rain, bro.
I was [ __ ] cuz I couldn't get in the
hotel cuz it was on curfew.
So, I just got soaked. I remember I
forget what month it was. I think it was
I think it was January as well.
I can't remember the month, but I
remember exactly what happened. I
couldn't even stay in the hotel. So,
it was bad, bro. Bad.
But yeah, rest be assured, Trevor Dawson
just [ __ ] out. You will never meet anyone.
You will never ever ever ever meet anyone. Yeah.
Oh, is it February? Is it? I knew it was
even January. I thought it was January.
Bro, this was years ago, by the way.
Greavves. It was about three years ago.
If it it was when I was still grieving,
if you get what I mean, grievy. I
thought it was January, bro.
Yeah, I thought it was January. It's close enough.
it was years. It was a few years ago.
I'm sure it was three years ago.
Yeah. No, nothing. I just it's just
funny when Trevor Dawson tries to give
it the big on YouTube when when you
actually travels when you actually
travel 5 hours he doesn't come out. I
just found it funny cuz cuz you come in
the chat you see. So yeah. So what do
you think's going to happen when I go to
um Nottingham Greasy? Do you reckon this
Jo's going to meet me?
Bro, I'm going to Nottingham for a
reason. Do you not understand? There was
there was an actual reason why I'm going to Nottingham.
I'm like, "Oh, you're it's killing two
birds with one stone." You not understand?
Cuz I know the game. I've been on here
for years whilst living my life. I know
what these people do.
It makes sense. It might not make sense
to you, but it does make sense
because he didn't turn up last time. He
didn't turn up last time. And I already
told you why I didn't turn up last time.
And he didn't turn up either. He didn't
turn up either. So
yeah. And why should he why should he
meet me? Because he's got a lot of [ __ ]
to say on YouTube. He's got a big mouth
and he's got a lot to say. So, I want to
see if he's got the same energy in person.
So, that's why he should meet up because
he keeps running his [ __ ] mouth on
YouTube 247. So, let's see what this big man's about.
Simple. No, I'm not doing that, Trusty.
I'm just saying when I'm going to
Nottingham. And if he does not turn up,
he does not turn up.
Simple. He's still going on YouTube.
Someone told me he made a post earlier.
When did his post? That's fine. So, you
can say all of this stuff to my face. Simple.
You know, you're still acting big on
YouTube. You're still mentioning me. So,
[ __ ] off. I'm going to tell you. Yeah.
I'm going to tell you where I'm going to
be, when I'm going to be. And if you
don't turn up, that's on you. Simple. Yeah.
He's a freak, lad. He's a freak, bro. A proper freak.
I already knew about him anyways. Hu
Jars I I know, bro. I can tell these
people from a mile off, bro. There's
things that they do. It's like LT.
There's things that they do and you
start then they start spilling the
beans. Bro, I know all of this, bro. I
know when they start doing certain
things. Yeah. You know it's all coming
out. Bro, how do you think I pulled his
trigger so easy, bro? LT. cuz I already
knew, bro, what what what he was saying
when I had to put him in his place as
well. You know, it's easy, bro. I'll
just say where I'm going, when I'm going.
You know, they don't show up. And I'm
going to I'm not doing this back and
forth where I'm going all the way to
them because I want to go to Nottingham
because I want to go to Nottingham. I'm
not going to waste my time and waste my
money on a jealous person.
[ __ ] that, bro. On someone that deep
down is jealous. It doesn't make sense.
So, by going to Nottingham, I want to go
there anyways. And it's as simple as
that. I've got stuff to do there. So, if
they don't turn up, they don't turn up.
Simple. I'm not going to waste my time,
bro, going all the way to leads only for
him to come up with some [ __ ]
excuse, right? For him to come out with
some [ __ ] excuse to say, "Oh, I
control you and oh, I made you." Bro, I
already know the excuses that are going
to come out. So, it's I'm not doing
that, bro. There's no way I'm doing that.
So that's it.
Yeah. No one cares about him. He's irrelevant, lad.
It's not nice to call yourself a
[ __ ] lad. It's not nice to talk
about yourself like that.
It's not nice to talk about yourself
like that, lad.
See you later, lad. You get kicked.
You like Jo's post? Why? He's a [ __ ] weasel.
He's a [ __ ] weasel, bro.
He's an absolute weasel.
He's another one that's obsessed with
me, bro. I got a lot of middle-wage
people obsessed with me on here. Huge ass.
A lot of middle age people obsessed with
me, bro. It's kind of Sometimes it's
freaky, but then sometimes it's nice cuz
I don't know, man. Like, you're doing
something right in it. It is weird.
I got a lot of middle-aged people
obsessed with me. Who? Jos. No, he
definitely definitely wasn't spot on.
No, he definitely definitely was not
spot on. I read what he wrote cuz people
kept going on about it.
No, no, no. He's definitely definitely
definitely definitely definitely 100%
not spot on on anything that he says.
And I read it earlier, bro. I literally
read it earlier. Yeah, they all want my
ass, bro. Yeah, they love me, bro. I'm
better looking than them. I got more
money than them, bro.
I mean, do you want me to go over what he's wrote?
because they're obsessed with me, lad.
Now, bro, you know when you're trying to
say this Joe F is is spot on, bro. What
is this Jo then?
What is he in his 40s, fat, ugly,
obsessed with a 28-year-old
and and he's right about me, bro?
Someone that's middle-aged, someone
that's obese. He was trying to call,
bro. I unsubed from him like three weeks
ago. Yeah. When he was trying to call me
Porky. An obese man is trying to call me
Porky when I'm not even fat. And you're
obese. Seriously, bro. Seriously. Now.
And you're trying to talk about me.
Like, bro, just stop talking about
yourself. It's unhealthy.
He doesn't bully. None of you people
bully me, lad. You bully yourselves. Literally, lad.
You you you lit you literally bully
yourselves. You do not bully no one. You
bully yourselves, bro. You can't even
make people mad when they're [ __ ] mad.
You bully yourselves. You're living your
worst lives. Sat on YouTube obsessed
with a 28-year-old every day. You're
living your worst lives, lad.
You're living your [ __ ] worst lives.
Um, you're calling someone fat and ugly,
but you've never seen him. Bro, bro,
bro. I have seen the people on here that
have shown their face. Bro, bro, bro br
bro. I know the people on here that
shown their face. Yeah, I have seen
people on here that shown their face and
they're all uglier than me. Yeah, funny
that, isn't it?
They're all uglier than me. Isn't that
funny, mate? That's another thing that I
was I I was thinking of as well. That's
why I also don't react to you people
anymore cuz every single person that
does this is [ __ ] ugly,
which is where the jealousy comes from
as well along with other things. So that's it.
I think that's Timmy, you know.
Anyways, I'm going to stop banning these
sad self projectors now. Anyways, yeah,
it is 2026. These people need to get a life.
But that Jo is not spot on.
Yeah. And he was like, and these people
are jealous as well. They are jealous of
me. That's why I don't I don't want to
waste my time on people that are jealous of me.
It's jealousy where they're ugly and
they're fat. They don't like you cuz
you're better than them. You're better
looking than them. And they'll never
admit to themselves. They'll be in
denial for the rest of their lives. But
they are jealous because believe it or
not, just believe it or not, they are
uglier than you. They are skint and they
are in a worse position in life than
you. And this is what you're always
going to have over them. Do you
understand? None of these people are
good-looking. None of them are
good-looking. None of them look normal.
None of them have got nothing. Not any
of these people.
Am I lying? Am I am I lying right now? I
don't even need to mention any names.
And stop saying that I'm a waster when
I'm calling you a waster, bro. Like,
you know what I mean? But like I said,
he can say all of this stuff to my face
when I'm in Nottingham. Simple.
You know what I mean?
You can say all of this stuff to my
face. So, what do you reckon the chances
are he's going to show up? Um, Rezy. Mhm.
What's the chance you think he's going
to show up,
bro? Like, either way, if he does or he
doesn't, it's just going to be
pointless. You know what I mean?
Cuz you're not winning a fight against
me, bro. You're literally not winning a
fight against me.
Four years later, mate, come on. It ain't happening.
You know what I mean?
No, I can't be bothered to listen to Timmy, bro.
[ __ ] it, bro. I can't be bothered to
listen to that.
No, I'm not changing. I'm not changing.
If he does not come to Nottingham, I'm
not going I'm not I'm not going back and forth.
I'm not going I'm not going back and forth, lad.
There will be no going back and forth.
There's no back and forth, lad. self projected out.
Simple as that. Yeah.
Yeah. I'm not going back and forth with
these little jealous weirdos here. And Yeah.
You liked it earlier, didn't you agree
with you when I was saying he's very
touchy about his boyfriend.
He's very, very, very touchy about his
boyfriend, is he?
Know what I mean?
Nope. I never said I got my hair and
beard done today, bro. I don't know why
you're asking me that.
Why would I? I never said I was. I never
said I did. Why are you asking that, bro? Yeah,
bro. I think I'm just going to end up
going to Nottingham very soon, bro.
I'm really just going to end up going to
Nottingham very soon.
Honestly, Grievy, bro, I want to
actually I want to quickly like end
this, bro. There's not going to be no
back and forth. There's not going to be
no nothing. Yeah.
I'm just going to end up going there,
lad. Like the good old Peter Belly days.
Fill someone in. There's not going to be
no filling someone in because no one's
going to turn up.
No one's going to turn up, lad. Yeah.
Why don't you do something?
Well, mate, if he doesn't go to
Nottingham, then I'm not going to him.
It's as simple as that. If you cannot
meet halfway, then that's it. That is
it, bro. And look, you've already got
your excuses. You've already got your
excuses. What happens if Joe is working
at Nottingham or MC? You've already got
your little excuses planned out. And
this is exactly why I'm going to
Nottingham. This is exactly why I am
Okay. Do you know what? Yeah.
Do you know what? Right.
I'm going to go I'm going to go to Sheffield.
And then you got no excuses. Simple as
that. Right. Then you've literally got no excuses.
Simple. Simple as that. I'm not going
Leeds. I'm going She Sheffield. Simple
as that. cuz you can get to Sheffield on
the same train station. I'll be going
She Sheffield. Simple as that. And then
you've got literally no excuses. You
have literally then got no [ __ ] excuses.
I'm biased. Yeah, I'll give him plenty
of notice, bro. I'll give him plenty of notice.
I'll go Sheffield. So then the cunt's
got no excuses. Yeah, bro. I'm biased.
How am I biased?
You're the one defending a [ __ ]
virgin that shows a fat ugly girlfriend
squit crying when every time I call him
a virgin. I'm not biased. You are the
ones that are biased. You think a fat
ugly girlfriend means someone's had sex?
Oh, no it isn't, mate. A [ __ ] [ __ ]
and being naked in women's bed like me
is proved you've had sex, you [ __ ]
[ __ ] Not someone showed a fat ugly
girlfriend that can't consent to sex.
You [ __ ] [ __ ] You understand?
No, no, no, no, no, no. I'm I'll be
given notice, Dusty. I will be given notice. Obviously,
I'll be given notice. Duh. [ __ ] hell.
You are you are definitely definitely biased.
Every time I call him a virgin, you're
straight saying, "Oh, he's got a
girlfriend, bro. Don't say that about
him." And a girlfriend is not proof that
someone has had sex. However, a [ __ ]
and being naked in women's beds is proof
that someone's had sex, not a
girlfriend. Two different things, you
understand? So, yeah, man.
That's it, lad.
Yeah. So, I'm going to I'll be going to
um I'll be going to I'll be going to
Sheffield. No, I can't be I can't be
bothered listening to Timmy. He's a
[ __ ] [ __ ] bro.
He's another biased [ __ ] I can't be
I can't be annoyed listening to him. Nah,
I'm not a copycat, lad.
Nah. [ __ ] off, bro. I can't be bother
listening to this [ __ ] idiot. Nah.
No, bro. Not even.
No, I'm not letting him on, bro.
But I already knew about Joe when he
started defending his boyfriend and his
girlfriend. They give themselves away.
They literally gives them They literally
give themselves away, bro.
They literally give themselves away, bro.
They literally give themselves a [ __ ] way. Yeah.
As soon as they start saying he's got a
girlfriend, don't say that about him.
They start sucking their boyfriend's
dick. You know what time it is, bro? You
literally know what time it is.
You start hearing the we and the mant
and all of this [ __ ]
I don't Well, he's definitely not happy.
If he can sit on YouTube stalking me
every day, bro, you can't be that happy
in your relationship to have that much
free time on your hand stalking someone
just cuz they're better looking than you
and you're jealous of them. I mean, I
don't know, man. I beg to differ. Maybe
we've got different um opinions on what happy is.
But mate, if I was happy, I wouldn't be
stalking and hating someone every day on
YouTube. But hey, that's just me, lad.
Is it? Everyone's different.
I would say that's probably the opposite
of happy. But each to their own, eh?
What is he jealous about? Um,
you need to ask him that because only he
will know what he's jealous of.
Yeah. Well, I've already explained this
multiple multiple multiple multiple
multiple times. Not any of the people
that hate on me
is better looking at me than is better
looking than me.
Not one person that does this is better
They're not young as young as me. They
haven't got as much money as me. Go
figure, bro. You really get it with the
looks, though. You really, really get it
with the looks. I mean, I showed you one person earlier.
I showed you one person earlier that
stalks me every day. You saw him on the channel.
You are some bad looking people on this community, bro.
There's a lot of bad looking [ __ ] on
this community, Grezy.
Strange, isn't it? Why don't any of them
look [ __ ] normal?
Weird, isn't it?
Not one of them look normal.
Not one of them. M up.
Yes, I am very very happy.
Yeah, very happy I don't need to hate on
people every day. I don't know. Yeah, very happy.
Yeah, I'm very happy.
I can tell you people on YouTube are not happy.
I can't believe you're still doing this in 2026. Scary, bro.
You are scary, lad.
You're very scary, bro.
You [ __ ] made me look a [ __ ] These
people made me look a [ __ ] you know,
Grezy cuz I was giving them the benefit
of the doubt to Laney. Nah, they're
going to get a life in like 2026. Surely
2026, they're going to stop this. And
now look, you prove Laney [ __ ] right.
Same [ __ ] people every day, huh?
It's not good, bro.
Oh yeah, but Grey, I'll just wait in it. You'll wait.
Yes. Until they get alive.
I'll just literally be sat there at the
screen just waiting until they all get alive.
Yes, until they get alive.
Yes, until they get alive. Uh, son. Yeah.
Greavves. I want some uh I'm fancying some digestives.
I want some digestives.
I'm fancying some digestive biscuits, lad.
What will I do? I'll I'll give them a
round of applause. Oh,
no. I didn't. I didn't cash any bet in. What bet?
What bet? I didn't cash any bet in. My bet's lost.
Okay, Greasy. Well, I think Chev Cole's fit.
Let me see.
What bet was it?
Nope. I've already achieved all my goals.
No, one second. What's that channel called?
Oh yeah, that's just a little bit. Yeah.
Oh, that's nothing though. I would have
got much back for it anyways. I don't
really give a [ __ ] You don't need to
know what my goals were. You need to
worry about your own life, lad. No, you
can ask. You can ask, but I won't be answering.
you know. Oh, a double both teams to
score. Yeah. So, so what, bro? Only had
15 pound in the balance. Who gives a [ __ ] Grezy,
have you seen that Shel Cole? She's so
attractive, man. I was looking her up earlier,
but I don't give a [ __ ] about 50.
That V is a definite definite virgin.
He is a deaf e defro is a virgin. Davio,
have you seen him around Autumn Rose?
He's a proper proper self-p projecting virgin.
Yeah, he's a proper virgin that need to
get a life. But anyways, Greavvesy,
I like Shel Cole Greavvesy.
What's your opinion on that?
I think she's hot.
She's fit, Grezy.
And if you don't like her, you're gay.
What's your opinion on that?
Well, if you don't like her, you're gay. Greasy.
No, she's so fit.
She's so so fit.
Yeah. If you don't like her, you're gay, lad.
What's your opinion on that?
So, so was the people in the community
post being copycats on that forum? Grezy,
were they being copycats?
So, on the forum they were being copycats now.
L11. I got called I I said I got called
gay. They Someone said if I don't find
Shel Co attractive, I'm gay.
They said if I don't find her
attractive, I'm gay.
Not nice, is it?
So not liking one person make means you like dick.
Sounds like sounds like a trend if you ask me.
Why do people say that? Dusty,
I don't know, bro. I just Well, I never
got the answers, did I?
Go away to me.
I I don't know. It was a long time ago.
I just want to know why people copy each other.
Weird, isn't it?
And the Skint virgin boy tries to say
that he never said that, Dusty. Yeah.
Yeah. The skint virgin tries to deny it.
Have you noticed no one's ever going to
bring up the girlfriend anymore, Dusty? Um,
Grezy, because if they bring up the
girlfriend anymore, they're just going
to I'm just going to shut them all down,
bro. So they don't even try to bring up
this girlfriend anymore, you know,
cuz I've got a bigger I've got a bigger evidence pack.
You understand? I've got a big evidence pack. Greasy.
I don't know. I just want to know why
people copy Dr. Eko.
I just want to know why people copy.
Copy the crowd. Little copycats.
But yeah, I've shut my account down and
no more nothing. No roulette, no
football. Even quit the football now.
The way it had to be, dude.
Yeah, that's the way it had to be in the end, lad.
Bad, isn't it?
So Dusty, why did Nons go to Amsterdam
after I went?
That seems a bit weird, isn't it?
Weird, isn't it, lad?
L11. Why did Nons go to Amsterdam after I went?
It seemed a bit strange, isn't it?
I can't I can't do anything anymore. I
can't put [ __ ] any I can't do
anything with you copycat [ __ ] anymore.
I can't do anything anymore.
That's why I don't like put too much out
there because anything I do, you
copycats [ __ ] copy.
You know, you [ __ ] copycats in it.
No, I don't think he would copy them
places cuz he's scared of flying.
Nah, he's scared of flying.
He would have copied my copy approach.
He would have copied my cold approaches
if he wasn't scared of women, which he
is. He's scared of women. That's why he can't approach.
That's why he's still a virgin.
That's why he's still a [ __ ] virgin, mate.
Yeah, mate. Happens.
What [ __ ] happens, mate?
Yeah. A disabled woman that can't
consent to sex. Do you want a medal, bro?
Brown, silver, gold. Give me your
address and I'll send you a medal if you want, lad.
Yeah, he's asleep. He's He's asleep next
to a disabled woman that can't even talk
properly and can't consent to sex. Yeah,
he hasn't shown him getting a [ __ ]
like me. He hasn't shown him in bed with
women naked like me. He hasn't [ __ ]
hold women's hands and [ __ ] had women
admitted to sleeping with him. [ __ ]
has he [ __ ] mate. So come back when
you can show that bit like what Peter
Belly showed. Oh, you just got told,
didn't you, mate? You just got told. Oh,
got him, mate.
What can you say, bro? What literally
can you say, mate? I would rather have
no one than have somebody that's got disabilities.
I would never target a vulnerable person
with additional needs. I'd rather have
no one. I literally rather a [ __ ] no one, mate.
You know, I'd rather have [ __ ] no
one, mate. [ __ ] no, mate. Yeah.
Did he show Did he show a [ __ ]
Grezy? Did he show him naked in bed?
No. Didn't think so, mate. Didn't think
so, mate. Didn't think so, mate. Not Not
like Peter Belly. Not like Peter Belly,
mate. Peter Belly show.
Did he, mate? I [ __ ] showed more with
women that I didn't sleep with, like the
ones that I'd kissed in the clubs.
Crazy. Do you like them little voices? Yeah.
Oh, itchy leg.
Itchy leg, mate.
I just think he needs to get [ __ ] laid.
Yeah, good for him, bro. A disabled
girl. Yeah, good for him.
Yeah. Yeah. What a way to [ __ ] show
you're having a good time
by copying someone else's holiday. Boo.
What a copycat. Boo.
Yeah. By copying another person.
Do you know what? I would I would love
to be a police officer, Greezy, cuz I I
I would I would I would nick him.
And do you know what I would nick him
for? I would nick him on two different offenses.
Do you know Do you know what them
offenses are for?
Do Do you want to know? I can tell you
if you want. I I would just I would just
I would just abuse my powers.
I really really would.
Nope. Well, that is Well, I would say
that you're under arrest on suspicion of
being a dirty, stinky virgin copycat
with no mind of your own. You do not
have to say anything. And then the
second one and then the second one.
And then the second one
like nick people for just things that I
say. Then I'd say, "Bro,"
Then I would say, "You're under arrest
for for having a [ __ ] guitar."
Bro, you need to stop with that whole
girlfriend thing, bro. Most of you
people that are saying that I've not had
a girlfriend are [ __ ] virgins.
That's literally why I don't I don't I
don't react to it, bro. Because like
most of the people that are saying this
have never even had sex with a woman,
let alone had a relationship. So, you're
just self- projecting, bro. That's why
it doesn't bother me.
Would L be able to say no. And do you
know why? I could answer you uh why
because um that was not the first place
that they went. I went to Amsterdam
and then literally
when I went after I went to Amsterdam,
he went to Amsterdam straight after.
Straight after, mate. Straight after.
That's a copycat them. That That's a bit
different. That was not their first
holiday, mate. That's a copycat.
Um, did I sleep with her? You know I
slept with her.
Mate, you you know I slept with her. So
why are you asking that when you when you know
that I've slept with her? Oh, look who's
just gone live. Grezy,
what do you mean? Did I sleep with her?
You know I slept with her, bro.
Yeah, Timmy's live.
I don't know, bro. I don't know.
Why are you asking me if I set with that
New Zealand one when you know I did?
What the [ __ ] lad?
>> Why are you asking that?
Why you asking that, bro?
You're under arrest for playing a [ __ ] guitar.
I don't have a [ __ ] picture of her anymore.
Wish I should have cuz she's part of the collection.
Yeah, I'm I need to start a new woman
collection now. John, starting to collect women.
Like I collect my little Lego. Cute, isn't it? Yeah.
[ __ ] hell. You go on Timmy's chat yet
and it's been the same people for like 15 years.
Regy, it's been the same people for like
15 years, lad. Yeah,
women are evil, John Gold.
You should just collect them
and compare experiences.
That's the only thing you can really do
cuz they're quite evil. You see, women
are evil, John.
They're out to get people and hurt them.
Isn't that right, Greasy? Yeah.
Nope. It's not true. It's completely made up.
I don't gamble all my money away.
You seem to be getting yourself mixed up
with me, bro.
Why do you people talk about money every
day on this community? Can I ask you that?
What is your obsession with skin and
money and people losing all their money?
I think it's time now to ask this
question years later. What is your obsession, bro? Huh?
You're you seem to be very obsessed with money.
Must be part of the autism.
Yeah. Very weird.
So strange, man.
Why do you do that?
That is so weird.
I laugh at it most of the time though.
People are sat there. I've seen like
posting that like ages ago like, "Oh, PJ
gets his money on the ETH." And it's
like, "You literally don't know nothing."
That's why like it's hard not to laugh
at it because it's like, "If only you
knew. You don't know nothing.
You're obsessed with other people's
lives so much, you get everything wrong, mad." So weird.
love to see me lose. But I don't lose
though because I've got plenty of money.
But I don't lose though because I'm
better looking than them. I've got more
money than them. I've been with more
women than them. I've got life more life
experience than them. I'm not losing.
It's like it's not even losing. I've got
more money than them. I've got I'm
better looking than them. I've got
family unlike them.
So, the only people that are losing is
these losers sat on YouTube 24/7
obsessed. They're the only ones that Well, bro,
stop asking me if what people say on
this community is true because, you
know, everything that they say is [ __ ]
Who's telling you this on YouTube?
People that are sat on here 24/7.
Fat, ugly people that ain't got a life.
Yeah, they would say that cuz that's
probably what they do. Do you not
understand? They're self projectors.
But yeah, man,
you hate people on here because you're
jealous of them.
That's why you do what you do. It's
jealousy with you people. So obvious. So
obvious. We've seen what a lot of you
people look like, you know.
Yeah, but it's not even just about that.
You literally spend all your lives
stalking me, bro.
That is so batty. That is so weird.
Like, you literally sit on YouTube for
four or five years stalking someone that
you've never met. What a loser. I was
talking to my mom about this earlier and
I was saying like it's so weird how like
they've been on here for years and years
trying to [ __ ] with people that they
don't know all cuz you're better looking
than them and you've got what they wish
they had. It was so weird it come up in
I can't remember why it come up but it's
like all cuz you're better looking than
them and they wish they were you.
And I was saying to her like it's
concerning like that they've been doing
it for like four or five years.
No, but we're not talking about losses.
No, no, no. We're not even talking about
that. We're talking about everything.
We're not even talking about that.
It's the [ __ ] that you do and the extent
that you go to. We're not talking about losses.
Ah, bro. I'm not answering it again.
I've already answered it multiple
multiple multiple multiple multiple
times. I'm not answering it again. All
I'm saying is is every single person on
here that's done this has been ugly.
That was the evidence that I needed as
well. That's when it started not looking
right. You know, Jamie Thompson ugly as
[ __ ] Nons legs ugly as [ __ ] Terry
ugly as [ __ ] Even people that show
their faces and then you look at you and
you're like, "Oh, wait. You actually
look better than them. You actually got
more family than them. you've actually
got more money than them. And then it
started making sense. Okay.
You know, okay.
Yeah. But you people have always lost in life though.
Yeah. Yeah. But you people have always
lost. Like you're actual wasters. Why do
you think people are actually saying now
that I'm the waster? Because they're
actually copying what I'm saying.
Like you people are actual wasters.
You're an embarrassment.
Like you you are on YouTube from the
time you wake up to the time you go to
bed. You're an embarrassment. And the
only reason people don't say anything
about this stuff uh is because Yeah, I
know, bro. He's obsessed with me. He's
You know, I I know why, bro. It's
because I'm better looking than them.
It's what Ronald Pump said to me before.
You're better looking than them. You got
more money than them. And he was right.
And it's the truth. He was so right.
Whoever that account was, he was so
right. You're better looking than them.
You got more money than them. And it
kills them. He was so right. I agree
with him. It's so so right. Cuz look at
all of these people that do this. You're
better looking than them. He was right
all along. You are literally better
looking than them. You got You're better
looking. You got more money than them.
You got more family than them. Look at
these people. They can't have anything,
man. To be sat on the earth every day
for 24/7. They can't have a better life
than no one. They've got to be life's losers.
They've got to be life's losers to be
sat on YouTube 24/7. They've got to be
the life's losers.
They've got to be one of life's losers,
if not all life's losers. That's why
they don't bother me. I'm saying it now
because you want the answers. That's why
I don't give a [ __ ] They say this,
whatever. They say that whatever. Simple
as that. Why are all these people ugly?
Because they're jealous of you. Multiple
multiple people have said this. People
that don't even [ __ ] you know,
people are not even related to my
family. They're like, they're jealous of
you. They're fat and ugly people. And
they're right. They are literally right.
They are literally [ __ ] right.
I've done a lot in my life as well the
past couple of years as well.
And we're not even just talking about
looks, bro. We're not even just talking about looks.
It doesn't matter what my life is for
not ending up like you people.
It's weird. You're just [ __ ] weird.
You're weird, bro. You're weirdos, man.
Proper weirdos. Why are you so obsessed
with other people's lives?
You don't come in here and say, "Oh,
what are you doing? What are you doing?"
You don't. You are actually obsessed
with other people's lives. You're not
even starting conversation. You're not
even being normal. You actually obsess
over other people's lives. You know,
it's actually an obsession.
So weird, bro.
You don't say, "Oh, have you gambled?
Oh, have you done this? Oh, have you
done that?" You kind of share your life
and you are actually obsessed.
You are actually obsessed with with people's lives.
It's so [ __ ] weird, man. You You
people are older than me, man.
You are older than me, bro.
You are literally older than me.
You should act your age, not your shoe size.
It doesn't matter what I want to do in
the next 5 years. What's that got to do with you?
Yeah, I do. I do. I do.
Yeah, I do. Yeah,
but you're talking about benefits.
You're talking about money every day. No
one's talking about money. No one's
showing money. But you're still obsessed
with money. You're still guessing when
people get their benefits and you don't
know anything. You literally don't know
what people have and what people don't
have. That's the weird part about it.
It's so weird. Why don't you worry about
your own lives? It's so [ __ ] weird, man.
Yeah, I am leaving YouTube, bro. John, I
am leaving YouTube. I should have left
ages ago to be fair. Do you know what?
Yeah, I haven't gone out drinking for
ages cuz I said I weren't going to go
out drinking until March. But yeah, bro,
I I do need to leave to be honest with
you. I was off here for two weeks, bro.
I've only just come back to be fair.
Yeah, it's a weird obsession, bro. It's
it's it is a very very weird obsession.
I don't know what it is, bro, with them.
But I don't know why they do it, bro. It's strange.
Yeah, I've got a lot of people obsessed
with me, bro.
It's [ __ ] weird, isn't it, lad?
It is [ __ ] weird. E,
but have you seen what you've seen what
that Jamie Thompson looks like, isn't
it? Let me put him up again.
I'll show you what he looks like again,
bro. Well, I don't know if you saw him.
I lost it, lad. I'm sure you've seen
them in it.
Yeah, they've been doing it for years,
John. They've been doing it for years, lad.
They've been doing it for years, man.
But they're not jealous, bro. They've
got nothing to be jealous of. They just
waste their life every day for years doing this.
But they're not jealous though, even
though they're uglier than you. And it's
been established that they're uglier
than you. Um they've got less family
than you. They've got less money than
you. But they're not jealous. No. No.
Cuz cuz like if I'm So if someone if I'm
better than someone and I'm not jealous
of someone, I waste my life on them.
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. cuz that's the way
that's that that makes sense, isn't it?
So, the best way to show that you're not
jealous of someone is wasting your whole
life on them. That that shows that
you're not jealous of someone. Apparently,
I'm sure you would do the opposite.
I'm sure you would do the opposite, but apparently not.
Do you know what's so mad, John, is that
you It's not even what they do. It's
It's how long they've been doing it for.
Um, it's actually how long they've been
doing it for. It's not even like it was
like over co or a month or six months or
whatever the [ __ ] They have been doing
it for years,
bro. And and I'm and I'm stubborn and I'
I've you know, like I've got a lot of
dedication, bro. But I could I I
couldn't do that, bro. I don't
understand how they can I was saying
this to my mom earlier, bro. how they
can be so bitter and hateful to someone
that they don't even know for years that
they've never met. It's madness.
Like it is actually it's mad.
It is mad.
No, they are obsessed with me. They've
been doing it for years, bro.
Jealousy is a horrible thing, bro.
Jealousy is a horrible thing. You won't
find another man on my devices, bro. You
won't find [ __ ] [ __ ] on me, bro.
Yeah. Yeah. See, look. Yeah. They're
obsessed, bro. Very, very obsessed.
They don't leave me alone. Yeah, bro.
It's not It's weird, isn't it, John?
How they can stalk someone and do this
every day for years
is I don't even know what it is, John. I
can't even I don't know what it is with
these people, bro.
I don't know what it is.
How they how they can't get bored of it.
Like, it's so bad now that they don't
even they don't even bother me, bro.
Like, I don't get mad. Even when I'm mad
at gambling, they they don't bother me,
bro. It's that it's it's to that point
now, bro, where it's just like it is
what it is, bro. They're just mad [ __ ] losers. Yeah.
Yeah. So he says, bro. So he says.
It's madness, isn't it?
Who knows, bro? Who knows?
They're stalkers, lad. Stalkers, bro.
I'm sure this guy's in a wheelchair.
John Gold. I'm sure I'm sure this guy's
in a wheelchair, bro.
[ __ ] weirdos, bro. Yeah,
I don't know. But there's not going to
be I closed my account now. I'm not even
betting on the football anymore.
And I don't know when I'm going to be out drinking.
Probably neither to be fair.
I've closed my account, man. I'm not
even betting on the football anymore. So
yeah, that's that's that's the that's the virgin.
I like to call him virgin boy. Virgin boy.
Another skin virgin. Peter Belly's got a
lot of people obsessed with him, bro.
kind of best to leave YouTube in it, bro. Yeah.
Yeah. That's the virgin, lad.
That's the virgin boy.
Why do you think they're so obsessed
with me, John?
Maybe they just want my ass, isn't it?
They're [ __ ] weirdos, is it, lad?
Why is that bad thing? Well,
do you go on wrong and central's
channel, Mr. Fella?
No, he never had a job in his life. Okay.
Have you have you gone on his channel?
Have you Have you gone on his channel
before? Have you seen the stuff he's
wrote and stuff?
Have you gone on the You've Oh, you've
gone on his channel.
One second, John. I need to deal with
something here. So, you have gone on his
channel, I'm guessing, right? Because
he's shown he said he's shown girlfriend. Um,
you've forgotten each other, right?
Have you got any shadow?
I just don't know how these middle-aged
people can sit here and do this every
day for years.
Blows my [ __ ] mind, bro. Takes a lot
to blow my mind as well.
So anyway, since you've been on his
channel, why have you never said to him um
um why being why is being a bad a virgin
a bad thing? Cuz I'm sure he's called me
a virgin before.
Pretty sure. So why didn't you ask him that question?
Is it cuz you've got a agenda?
Is that why, mate? You knew where I was
going with that, is it? You do it every
time, bro. You literally, you people do
this every time.
Surely to God, you would be asking him
the same question.
You lot seem to love up this nonslegs,
isn't it? It's the same as LT. You seem
to love this nonslegs. I don't know what
it is, bro, with like sucking his dick
every time someone calls him a virgin
and [ __ ] You people seriously need to
get married to him, bro. You love
Yeah, you're [ __ ] You're weirdos,
man. Proper proper weirdos.
Yeah, proper weirdos, man.
You have never asked that. No, you
haven't. No, you [ __ ] have not, mate.
Now you ain't [ __ ] am not. You have
never asked him that cuz I've been on
these channels several times. No, you
have never asked him that. Don't even lie, bro.
See, this is self projectoring. No car,
job, wife, kids, house, ambition,
skills. All of these people that are saying this
um are 40year-old virgins that don't
have any of these things themselves.
Basically, this community, John, is just
full of a bunch of middle-aged wasters
that failed at everything in life that
they tried. So, they're trying to put
their misery onto other people.
Yeah, it's it is the same people, bro.
That's their life, is it, lad?
Oh, just some account. Just on account
that I was reading.
Yeah, just on account I was reading. Why
do you think these people are obsessed
with me, John?
Why is being a virgin a bad thing?
Because it's because it's bad to be
almost [ __ ] 31 and you're still a [ __ ] virgin.
Never had [ __ ] in your [ __ ] life.
You're going to be [ __ ] 31 in
February and you're still a [ __ ]
virgin. That's [ __ ] embarrassing,
mate. Step your game up.
Yeah, bro. Literally,
what they do is they just spend all day
calling people what they are themselves. Um, skin
[ __ ] [ __ ] It's just everything that
they are themselves they project on to you. Yeah.
Yeah. They're losers, bro. Absolute life's losers.
Yeah. No prospects, bro. I'm 28 and I've
got more money than you and I've and I
have more life experience than you and
I'd rather live at home than live in a
shitty bedit owned by the council. No prospects,
bro. You're in your 40s and you have no
one. Look, look a bit more closer to
home and you'll find your answer.
I would rather live at home than live in
a bed beds owned by the council. I've
stated this many times. I've never ever
tried to hide it. Like, bro, with no
prospects, bro, you 40 year olds don't
have no prospects.
You're actual in your 40s. You got
nothing going for yourselves. You're
actual wasters. Like, bro, what you're
saying is literally about yourselves.
You are literally talking about your 40y
old selves. Huh? Like, you would
literally, bro, you're not you're not
talking about someone like me. You're
talking about yourselves.
You know what I'm saying?
Yeah, bro. But you know the thing is
John with them with these people there
yet instead of owning what they are they
then start talking about people that are
better than them. So it's not like no no
but bro you know the thing is bro the
[ __ ] I can actually expect it bro I can
sorry I could actually respect it if
they're just that way but what it is is
they are literally
bro they are literally life's losers and
then they try to talk about other people
that are better than them.
That's the thing that makes me [ __ ] die, bro.
It's hilarious. Like, they they're literally life's
losers. And that's one thing, bro.
That's one That's That's one thing. But
then they come and try to talk about
other people that are better than them. [ __ ] weird.
No, no, no. Have I said that everyone
that comes on here has got nothing in life?
What? I've said that.
Well, I have literally said that, bro.
I've never said everyone on here that.
No, I've never said every single person.
I said every single person. I never said Nah.
Well, of course, bro. Of course I get
brought up, lad.
Because I'm better than them, bro. I'm
younger than them. I'm better looking Yeah,
I'm just better than them, bro. Not even
just the looks. I'm just better than them, bro. you know. So, yeah.
Yeah. And Yeah. Like Red Star. I'm
talking about Red Star. I'm talking
about V. I'm talking about some of these
accounts. Yeah. If they generally had
something in their life, they wouldn't
be sat on YouTube for years hating
someone they don't know. Yeah.
Yeah. It's the truth. It is literally
the truth. You would not be on here
hating all day, every day if you had
anything in your lives. Yeah. I own it.
There people that do that ain't got nothing.
N Red Star is a gay boy just like you.
Just like you and your boyfriend
nonslegs. You're all little gay boys
that ain't got nothing in life.
Sad, jealous, pathetic people. Wasters.
Oh, you didn't like that word, did you
when I called you that?
Nah, you're just losers. Absolute
And I put myself in your shoes as well.
How long has it been going? Uh, they've
been doing it for years.
They've been doing it for about 15
years, these people. Yeah, about 15 years.
I've been on here about 8 years and
they've been doing it they've been doing
the same [ __ ] for 8 years.
They've been doing it every day for
years. But I I've spoke to people and
they've been they've been doing this since 2012.
I come on here in 2019,
2020, something like that, bro. But
yeah, they've been doing it for a very,
very, very long time, bro.
Yeah, they've been doing it for a long time.
Nope. I wish I was, bro. It's been the same people.
>> So, you're basically talking about yourselves then.
Bro, that's literally you you're talking
about. You people don't have a job. You
people claim benefits. You people ain't
got a life. So the definition is
yourselves you're talking about. Stop
talking about yourself.
If you had anything good going for
yourselves, you wouldn't be on here
doing what you do every day. It's simple
as that. So it's like that's it.
You are literally life's losers and you
try to put it on to other people. It's madness.
You are the definition of a loser. Look
at what you people do every day. And
yes, it has been going on for eight
years with these people. They got [ __ ]
all going for themselves. Literally
nothing. No life, no nothing. Trust me,
bro. I've I was off here for weeks. I've
only just kind of come back.
I was off it for two weeks, bro. Yeah.
Um, they tried to ruin people's
Christmas as well, John. They tried
ruining people's Christmas.
Something you'll find if you stay on here. Yeah.
They're jealous. They're jealous of
something. They're very, very jealous.
Hateful people in here, bro.
They don't like anyone better than them,
better looking than them. They don't
like anyone that's better than them,
bro. Because where they're wasters and
they have failed at everything in life.
They don't like anyone that's got hope.
That's what it is with these people. You
look, you look at the people in this
community that most of them are old, [ __ ] wrinkly,
[ __ ] they look horrible. Look at
them, bro. It's It's not rocket science. Yeah, man. Yeah.
So like when it was so like every every
year near Christmas they start self-p
projecting more and more and more like
you ain't got this you ain't got that
like proper they will try to like put
you in a bad mood over Christmas which
is what they try doing with me because
obviously they've got no one Christmas
they got no mom they got no family so
they were trying to project their [ __ ]
onto me and do you know what I done on
Christmas, John. Yeah, I done this
little test, right? Um where I went live
for 5 minutes before going to my
sisters, right? Um I literally uh put
the live stream on. I walked down the
stairs. I left the phone upstairs just
to see who was on Christmas and I walked
up walked up the stairs and it was the
same people on YouTube Christmas Day.
Same [ __ ] people. Um, and
yeah, and then it was the same people on
Christmas [ __ ] day, bro. And I ended
it and I'm thinking these were the
people that was self projecting onto me.
No, there was only a Christmas day, bro. Yeah. Projecting.
So, but then they want to try and talk
about other people. This is what I'm
trying to say, you know.
No, they were on their Christmas, bro. Yeah.
And before Christmas they were No,
they've been doing it years, bro.
They've been doing it years.
It has been the same [ __ ] for years with
these people, lad.
Do you know what I think it is? I think
they just gamble all of their money away
and then they just come on here cuz they're skint.
That's what I think, bro.
That I think that I think that's what
they do as well.
I think they lose all their money
gambling and then they come on here
angry and [ __ ] as well. You know, a lot
of them gamble, bro. So
It is weird. Yep.
It's madness, isn't it?
Yeah. They don't make my life a misery,
bro. They I just laugh at them. Me, bro.
I actually just laugh at them.
I just laugh at them, bro. To be fair. I
don't really They don't make my life a
misery. I just laugh at them. Cuz think
about it, bro. How could they make
anyone's life a misery? They're sat on YouTube 24/7.
These people are ugly as [ __ ] So, think
about it, bro. Anything that they're
trying to do to anyone else, like, just
look at the life that they're already living.
like they're they're living their worst life,
you know, that's it, bro. They don't
even, you know, I would say, bro, you
know, a lot of these people,
they don't even leave their house, bro.
They don't even leave their [ __ ] house. Yep.
But yeah, Mr. Fella, you people have
never had prospects.
That's why you talk about other people
not having prospects and stuff cuz
you're talking about yourselves.
It's funny how you middle-aged losers
all say exactly the same things. That's
that applies to yourselves.
Everything is literally about your own
lives. I would have thought in 2026 you
would have realized that you're talking
about yourself, but nah, clearly not.
How can you try to pick on people that
are better than you is is beyond me.
Literally no life whatsoever. Literally
no life. I don't care whether you've got
friends or you don't have friends. I
don't give a [ __ ] to be honest. I just
find it you literally have got no life.
What's your excuse for having no life? I
don't care if people have friends or
they don't have friends. I mean, most
people are fake nowadays anyways.
Yeah, but you people don't have a job.
Maybe, bro. Maybe.
Maybe, bro. Maybe. I mean, maybe every
single person in the world that has a
job is better than me, but none of you
people have a job cuz you're on YouTube 24/7.
Well, sorry. Okay. 95% of you don't have
a job. Sorry, mate. I mean, there is
some people that work.
I mean, none of you's work. You're sat
on YouTube 24/7.
You can never survive on benefits.
You're already surviving on benefits.
You already are, you silly ghost.
That's another thing. You people used to
be obsessed with Seaside Mark because he
was claiming benefits.
I never really got that, you know.
I never really got the Seaside Mark
thing, the the obsession with Seaside
Mark cuz like I I remember when that
went on, you know, like everyone used to
hate him because he was claiming
benefits. I remember that, you know. I
really do remember that.
I do remember that. And it's kind of
like it's weird to be honest because
it's like don't watch the guy. If it
really annoys you that much, don't watch
him. They I remember when that all went
on. If that guy is annoying you for
being on benefits, yeah, why do you keep
watching him? Why do you literally keep
If if him being on benefits is annoying,
why do you keep watching him? I never I
never understood the the the the hate
for the benefit thing.
I never I never understood that. I
really never understood that, you know.
Yeah, John, man. Yeah, I never I never
did. I always saw it as if he don't [ __ ]
the system over, someone else is going
to [ __ ] the system over.
So, I don't I never really understood
the obsession. If you're not happy with
your life working, that's on you.
I thought I found a lot of people that
were saying that also weren't happy with their life.
I feel like they just weren't happy.
Bro, no one cares what I've said about
children. Have you show Have you heard
Have you heard what people have said
about my dead relatives? I spoke about
people's children because they spoke
about my dead relatives. Yeah, no one
cares. It's 2026.
Stop using that same excuse.
Yeah, people's putting my dead relatives
up, so I spoke about their kids. Yeah, simple.
Well, he can't work cuz he's disabled.
Yeah, well, he can't work because he's disabled.
you're still obsessed with what people
have said about children in 2026.
You really have got some bad autism. You
know that, bro?
You really really have got some bad
autism. You're still bringing that up.
You're still asked about that,
bro. You have got you've really got bad
autism, bro. Like, seriously. Seriously.
You have really, bro, you've really got
bad autism. You really really need to seek help.
That is You've got some bad autism. So
anyways, he signed Mark couldn't work
because he's disabled. Why should he
look for work if he can't work,
you know, just because you're not happy
with your job, you know? That's your
problem. That's literally your problem,
bro. That is your problem.
That is your [ __ ] problem.
You know, no one else's, bro. Your problem. Yeah. [ __ ] madness.
Oh, I just used to say stuff about these
people's uh children because they used
to talk about my dead relatives. Yeah, man. Yeah.
No, no, no, no, no. These people do not
give people spit because of what they've
said about kids. The people that this
guy defends is an actual pedophile that
says that they will date a 15year-old.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no,
no, no. You're not you're not even going
to try and say that. You're not even
going to try and use kids as an excuse
to try to justify your jealousy and why
you've been stalking someone for [ __ ]
four or five years. You're not even
going to try to use kids. Yeah, you're
not even try to use kids. You people
have spoke about people's dead
relatives. You people have put people's
kids all over YouTube. You're not even
going to try and use kids as a weapon.
You're not even going to try and do
that. You put my sister's kids up. You
put Monty Man's kids up. Shut the [ __ ]
up. So, don't cry about it. It's simple
as that. Yeah.
Simple as [ __ ] that, bro. Simple as
[ __ ] that. Yeah. Did you say anything
when Pat Mustard was putting people's
kids up all over YouTube? No, you
didn't. So, shut the [ __ ] up.
You've got an obsession with kids.
You've literally got an obsession with kids.
Stop trying to use kids to try to
justify your jealousy every day. Yeah.
Yeah. I don't need to answer your
questions cuz I know what you're trying
to do and it's not going to work again.
You're talking to me. Yeah.
If you're still obsessed with kids in
2026, that's your [ __ ] problem. That
ain't my problem. That's your problem, lad.
That's your problem.
Yeah, that's your problem. That's not my Simple, [ __ ] idiot.
I'm not answering your questions.
Oh, I used to just say mad stuff, bro.
When I used to lose money. Yeah. I just
used to say mad stuff.
Yeah, I used to just say mad stuff. Yeah. Yeah, man.
So, why did you never used to say
anything about Mustard when he used to
put people's kids all over YouTube? Do
you want to answer that one? Now I've
answered your question.
Okay. Now I've answered your question.
Do you want to answer my question?
Why didn't you say anything? These are
These people, by the way, John, right,
used to defend people that used to put
people's kids all over YouTube. They're
not going to tell you about that.
They're not going to tell you that they
used to support a man that used to go on
people's Facebooks, right? Take people's
um kids photos and put them all over
YouTube. They're not going to tell you
that. That's the bit that they don't
tell you about. They'll tell you about
the stuff that you've said. They'll tell
you. They'll tell you about the stuff
that you've said, but they won't tell
you about the stuff that they've done
and said. That's what they like to do on this community,
mate. You've seen pe You've seen Pat
Mustard put kids all over his YouTube.
Don't you even try to defend that. That
is even worse than saying that. He saved
people's pictures. He's saved people's
kids and he's put them all over YouTube.
Yeah, that's worse. That's literally
And he's threatened my mom as well.
That's another thing as well. Oh yeah,
another thing. Do you know what they
said about my mom as well? Um John, they
said that they were going to beat my mom
up. They said that they were going to
beat my mom up and uh what was it? They
was going to uh go to the hospital and
beat my mom up. Yeah. [ __ ] you people,
bro. And what people have said about
you, you [ __ ] deserve it. What you've
said about people's moms and you've put
people's kids all over YouTube. Tell
tell them what you've done to Monty
Man's kids, my sister's kids, and what
you've said about my mom. Yeah, you
should you should tell you should tell
them that as well. Tell them that bit
about how you're going to [ __ ] You
said some mad sick [ __ ] about my mom as
well. [ __ ] off, bro. Don't come on here
and try to play the mole high ground.
Don't you dare try and [ __ ] play the
[ __ ] mole high ground, you [ __ ]
Mongs. Don't you even dare try to play
the mole high ground just because you've
got a newcomer on here.
Just you got got a newcomer on here.
You're not going to try and brainwash
him like you didn't say and do stuff,
bro. [ __ ] out of here, man.
You know, idiots. Simple, bro.
Simple. I don't give a [ __ ] what the
casino manager. I don't give a [ __ ] No.
The guy was called Pat Mustard. No, no,
no, no. He he his account was called Pat Mustard.
No, no, no. His account was called Pat Mustard. Yeah.
No, no. Obviously. Yeah.
Yeah. Why don't you Why don't you say
what you've all of the stuff that you've
done and said?
Yeah. Yeah. Why don't you Why don't you
tell them all the stuff that you people
have done and said whilst you're at it?
Yeah. Yeah, he's a fictional milkman.
Yeah, but there's there was an account
of him and he used to come in hangouts
and [ __ ] obviously. Yeah, [ __ ] you people, bro.
Yeah, [ __ ] you people. Yeah, no one
cares what's all there, bro. No one
cares what's all there. No one You can
You can look it up.
>> No, but you supported a man that spoke
about kids. You supported a man that
threatened an old woman. And you
supported a man that puts people's kids
all over YouTube.
No, but you supported all of that,
didn't you? So, yeah.
Yeah. So, that's it. You done the same
thing with Monty as well.
Yeah, that's fine, bro. But all of the
things I've done and said is in retaliation.
That's nice, bro. All of the things that
I've done and said is in retaliation.
So that's it. And you clearly don't have
a problem because if you had a problem,
you would have come and done something about it.
If you people really had a problem, why
didn't you come and done something about
it? You can't be that bothered, can you?
Simple. So, oh, just these same
repeating people talking about things
that I've said in the past in
retaliation to them.
Just obsessed in 2026.
That's mad, bro. Like I've Oh, bro. Bro,
that is actually mad.
That is mad, bro.
You know, it was one person. It was one
person. It was one person.
Yeah, bro. These people have done a lot
of [ __ ] on here, bro. Do not let them
try and take the mole high ground.
Trust me, they've done a lot of [ __ ] A
lot of [ __ ] bro. Yeah,
I can tell you a court case that I've
got coming up in a couple of years of
this [ __ ] trying to play the victim. Yeah.
So, wait, hold on. So, Mr. Fella, yeah.
So, you're you're still bitter about
[ __ ] that people said years ago. Wow.
You need to get a life, man. Look at all
the [ __ ] Seaside Mark has done and all
the all the [ __ ] other people have done.
You think I would sit on here being
obsessed for years over them? I'm just
trying to put myself in your situation.
So wait, if someone So if someone comes
on here right now, right, and says the
maddest [ __ ] so does that mean I'm
going to be obsessed with them for four
years like you're obsessed with me or am
I going to move on with my life? Because
the thing is, right, this is what
doesn't make any sense. If someone's a wrongin,
you distance yourself away from
wrongins. This is where the whole
disabledness comes into it again. If you
really thought somebody was a wrongin,
you wouldn't have anything to do with
them. Whereas you seem to keep being
obsessed with me every single day
despite claiming that I [ __ ] wrong.
It doesn't make sense.
It really does not make sense, man.
Yeah, man. see that you would literally
do the complete and utter opposite to
what you're doing if you thought someone
wasn't wrong. And you literally you
actually would you actually would do ex
you would do the opposite.
That's how you know you're obsessed,
bro. You literally would do the complete
and utter opposite.
You you're mad, bro. You're you're
you're [ __ ] You're really [ __ ] in
your head, bro.
Yeah, man. I can never give my life away
to someone because they've said stuff
about kids or whatever. I can never give
my life away like you people give your
life to me.
Yeah, but I don't lose though because I
live a better life than you. I'm better
looking than you. So, the only ones that
are losing are you losers. I'm younger
than you. I'm better looking than you.
and I've got more money than you. I
don't know how many times I've had to
say this to you, but you still don't
understand it. You losers giving me your
life proves I'm better than you. You sat
on here from the time that you that you
wake up to the time you go to bed, not
leaving your house proves I'm better
than you. It's the evidence that I need.
Younger, better looking. Are you sure
it's not you guys that are losing? Think
about it, bro. Think about in the in the
past four or five years what I've done
and what you've done, bro. I've been
beating you. I've been beating you losers.
I've been beating you. Well, you've been
giving me your time, bro. I've been
beating you, bro.
So, you people have been losers your
whole life, and you continue to be losers. Simple.
You couldn't even get a life in 202 [ __ ] six.
You couldn't even get a life in 2026.
It's [ __ ] madness. In 2026, you
couldn't even get a life. It's mad.
It's [ __ ] madness.
Yeah. Yeah. I also go out drinking. I've
also got friends. I've also traveled a
lot more than you people. I've also got
family unlike you people.
Oh, the casino manager. I ain't got no
sympathy for the casino manager.
Nah, bro. You You got sympathy for casino manager.
Nah, bro. I lost 60 on roulette as well,
so I closed my account.
I'm done with all the gambling now, bro.
Anyways, no, not even any football bets anymore.
You think I give a [ __ ] about that, bro?
About a casino manager? Oh, [ __ ] them. I
don't give a [ __ ] about them.
[ __ ] them, bro.
They rigged the roulette tables.
I won a football bet last week, lad.
So, yeah, I'm done with it, Mr. B, bro.
giving the football bets.
I haven't lost all my money,
bro. I haven't lost all my money. What
the [ __ ] I haven't lost nowhere near
all my money.
How much did he lose?
No, bro. But I I am stopping because
Yeah. No, even not even football bets.
Yeah. And what about the po [ __ ] that
they're conning out of people? They're
calling out They're calling people out of money.
Bro, I haven't lost all my money, bro.
You know what's so bad, Mr. B is they
gave me a cash out. Yeah, I put £6 in on
the bet and it and it let me cash out £36.
Um, but obviously I didn't take it. So,
could you imagine I had £50 on it? The
cash out would have been sick, bro.
Yeah, they gave me a£36 cash out, but I
I didn't I didn't take it.
I don't care, bro. I'm done with it.
It's as simple as that. I've closed the
account and I'm done with it. So, I'm
not even doing football bets anymore. [ __ ] that.
Yeah, done with it, bro.
Even the Well, even the football bets.
Yeah, man. I was going to do the
football bets, but I'm done with them
now, bro. I clos your account down.
It's not good, lad.
But yeah, if I had like 50 60 pound on
the bet, the cash out would have been
good, isn't it?
My bet got [ __ ]
Yeah, I'm done with gambling, bro. I'm
done with gambling.
I am going to miss like the both teams
to score the double where you can put
big money on the doubles and that, but oh well.
Yeah, it would have offered 5300. Yeah,
I know. I know. I would have cashed it
out if id put 50 on it, but I weren't
going to cash out £36.
Yeah, [ __ ] in it, bro.
But was I really going to put £50 on it
on a bet like that? Come on. You know, so
I bet on a game to stay nil nil, Mr. B.
The first half it was nil nil.
I bet I bet on it to stay nil nil,
didn't I? And then the second half they
scored the bastards.
I wish it stayed nil nil.
Damn's too addicting, bro.
Yeah, he wanted to come into me, but I
can't be dealing with him, bro.
I'm done with [ __ ] Yeah.
[ __ ] gambling, bro, is bad.
Yeah. You people are biased. Yeah.
You are biased. Yeah.
Yeah, you are biased, lad. You're biased.
Why are you so biased?
L, no one knows when I get f No one
knows when I get paid and no one knows
how much money I have either or get.
People say a lot of things, but they
don't know nothing. Apparently, I get
money on the ETH. I've I never know I
got money on the ETH.
Yeah, that's self projecting, bro. I
think what they really mean is they get
money on Thursday and they get money on the ETH.
Yeah, it's just self projecting. Yeah. Of
course he does.
You don't gamble, do you? UK Asylum, you
Yeah, my G days are finished.
No, my gambling days are finished, bro.
Yeah, it's [ __ ] it gambling.
Oh, that [ __ ] roulette is fixed, Mr. Bean.
All right, it's fixed that roulette, lad. Let's
try fix that roulette.
You lost 600. One roulette.
[ __ ] hell, bro.
Oh, [ __ ] roulette madness. What?
Yeah, they can stay some good games
Saturday. They can stay some good games, lad. Yeah. I'm mad.
So, Dusty, are you ever going to Amsterdam again?
You reckon you'll ever go again?
Oh, don't be a [ __ ]
Don't be a [ __ ] stinking copycat, bro.
Don't be a copycat, lad.
Never be a copycat.
You need to get laid. I know who that
is, mate. And you need to get laid.
You got l mate. You got a ding.
Running out of time.
You'll be You'll be 31 this month and
you still have never had sex.
You pathetic [ __ ]
You seriously need to get laid, man.
[ __ ] hell. I'm running out of time.
You're going to die of virgin.
You [ __ ] virgin.
M you're a little copycat. You're
nothing but a little copycat.
You're you're a little copycat.
You said shovel car was good-looking.
That's what everyone else said.
Mustard chances, eh? She's not ugly, you
can't deny she's ugly.
If you say she's ugly, you must be gay.
You little copycat.
You need to be arrested for being a copycat.
Trying to fit in with the crowd.
You literally need to be arrested,
mate. You need to you need to be arrested.
You said that she You can't deny she's
attractive. Oh, I watched your live
stream, by the way. No, you never said
that she was hot.
You You said that you can't deny that
she's attractive. And if you don't find
her attractive, you're gay. You little copycat virgin.
Because Because you're insecure about
your sexuality. You're trying to And
guess what, mate? She is [ __ ] ugly.
And I've had more women than you.
And she is [ __ ] ugly and I'm not
insecure about my sexuality.
Nah, mate. You went to Amsterdam because
I went to Amsterdam.
You're a copycat.
Just cuz I went, you thought you was
missing out on something
because you never went. Always
always have the coffee, don't you?
Always have the coffee.
What be the crowd
copying another person?
Can you explain to me where
the desire comes from to want to copy another person?
Why copy? No one likes a copycat.
You little copycat.
You a little copycat.
Are you a little copycat?
So why was you talking about Cheryl Cole
then? If you're not a copycat,
why why was you talking about Cheryl Co
being attractive? Then that's what
everyone else used to say.
She want to fit in. Do want to feel left out.
Might must be tough, you know, being
being a new kid in college.
He They [ __ ] you up, didn't they,
mate? Miles and Jackie,
they [ __ ] you up, mate. Them glass region lads.
The Scottish lads [ __ ] your [ __ ] up, didn't they?
They used to pick on you for the way
that you dressed.
And they also said, "If you don't stop,
they're going to give you a Glasggo smile."
And you don't want one of them, mate.
You're two Scottish lads.
They used to pick on you, didn't they, at school?
Do you know what? I was actually
speaking to Hannah Aris
uh on on Facebook.
You remember Hannah Harris?
You know Hannah, the the the the
one from Kent,
the one that rejected you.
You don't remember?
Do you not remember?
No, no. You said that chem was
attractive to fit in.
You saw my community post where they was
all talking about her. What's the chances?
They're they're talking about her and
you was talking about her.
What's the chances?
You copy each other. You copy each
other. And you was aware of the trend.
You're not stupid.
You're aware you're aware of the trend.
You even knew about the trend
yourself. You was copying, you know,
you don't smoke weed.
You never [ __ ] an escal. You can't get
your dick up. You go down your fing. So
why the [ __ ] what the [ __ ] were you
doing in Amsterdam?
What the [ __ ] were you doing there?
You [ __ ] absolute virgin. What the
[ __ ] were you doing there? You [ __ ] virgin [ __ ]
Yeah, he's a s. Um
V's a s.
They're too ugly to get a woman's number in person.
That's why they simp. It's a bit like
virgin boy above you up pip. He's an absolute virgin.
He's a [ __ ] virgin. He's a [ __ ]
virgin, mate. He's a [ __ ] virgin,
mate. You're [ __ ] virgin.
What do you think, Pip Smoker?
Why don't you like virgin boy?
Why don't you like Virgin Boy?
What's Virgin Boy done to you?
There was a red flag. Yeah,
Virgin Boy is very strange.
Yeah, he's very strange. Very strange.
Very strange that
I know a lot of stories about him. Pip,
his dad's got a very dark past. His
dad's got a very very dark past.
How did I uh originally meet him? Um so
basically I went in a chat and um
yeah, we was talking about places in
London and stuff. There was only three
of us in the chat. I can't even remember
who the other person was. And then we um
was talking and yeah, we spoke about
meeting um you know for for a while. We
didn't meet until ages and yeah, we kind
of just met up from there
and everything was good.
But then he started telling me stories
about his dad and oh the Indian the
Indian restaurant, bro, you don't even
Oh, mate. The Indian restaurant. What
happened in that Indian restaurant? So embarrassing, bro.
I was getting bullied. Nope. No one's
ever bullied me on PlayStation, bro.
People was bullying you. Aaron Cox used
to bully you. Uh, literally, people used
to bully you for the way that you dress.
No one ever bullied me. I hadn't I I got
into arguments with with people.
Yes, there was drama. But no, no one
bullied me on PlayStation. They bullied you.
You couldn't even stand up for yourself.
>> No, no, no, no, no, no. One ever bullied me, lad.
No one ever bullied me.
I told you not to have that vindaloo in
the Indian. You [ __ ] shack yourself
the next day. I told you nods legs.
The first time I met him. Yeah. The
Indian. Do you remember that story I
told you about the Indian? I told him
multiple times, don't have a vindaloo.
Don't have a vindaloo. I want to try it,
man. I want to try it. I want to try it.
So, he tried it. He [ __ ] shat his
pants the next day. [ __ ] virgin.
No. No virgins.
Virgins don't get links, lad. Sorry. I
don't allow virgins in my channel, mate.
You can't handle You can't handle a
Vindeloo, mate. They're not for little
virgins like you. They're for big strong
Turkish men that can pull American women
and get blown jobs in alleyways and and
stuff like that. They're not for little
virgins like you.
Socially awkward virgins like you, mate.
Sorry, I don't make the rules.
I really don't make the rules, mate.
It's what I'm told.
No. Look at that beard. You reckon you
could ever grow a beard like that? Look,
I've actually got teeth. Something that you're missing. Look,
I'm lovely, mate.
See you later. Oh, you're not get you're
not getting the link. You're not getting
the link. No virgins, mate. No [ __ ] virgins.
No virgins. I don't make the rules. Sorry, mate.
I'm the coward that you went to the old
bill. Dusty, he's calling me a coward
when he went running to the police
crying. No, I'm the coward. I'm the
[ __ ] coward, am I?
I'm the coward. says the [ __ ] virgin
that let me go to his area three times
and he didn't come out once but instead
ran to the [ __ ] police. Don't you
ever try and [ __ ] call me a [ __ ]
girl with you [ __ ] virgin.
Oh [ __ ] body cing mate.
Top up the Yeah,
mate. I went to your [ __ ] virgin area three times.
You let me go to your virgin area three
times and you didn't come out.
You made me go all that way to that
virgin area for you to not do nothing.
Trying to act the big trying out the big
[ __ ] Do you remember mate? I stopped
you going to them little events.
I stopped it. I put a stop to it for a
couple of weeks. I also stopped you
going on YouTube for a couple of weeks.
I stopped you going on YouTube for a
couple of weeks.
Yes, I did stop you going somewhere and
I stopped you going YouTube for a couple of weeks.
You stopped going on YouTube for a
couple of weeks, mate.
Nope. You You did stop. Don't try out to
the big man now. You You did stop, mate.
You stopped going to the little event
tonight because of me. I closed it.
No, you never. Duck. Duck.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Dusty, why was he talking about Cheryl Carl?
He said that you can't deny she's
attractive, Dusty. You can't deny it.
You can't deny she's attractive.
You can't deny it. That's what he was
saying. You can't deny it. He was being
a little [ __ ] weirdo.
If you don't like Cher Cole, you're gay.
As we used to say,
he literally said that if you don't find
her attractive, you're gay. No, I
brought her up. I brought her up. Yeah.
And I'm saying what you said in response
to it. You literally said that you can't
deny that she's attractive.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
You you you you literally said that you
can't deny that she's attractive. And if
you don't find her attractive, you're gay,
you little copycat. I'll tickle you.
I'll tickle you, you little copycat.
You used to And you told me that you uh
you told me that you pretended to like
football to fit in or something. Yeah.
No. No. No. Yeah.
You said you're you said that you you
pretended to like football to fit in or something. Yeah.
You said your you said your dad was born
on the 1st of September
and they used to go to different
countries to work or something
or something like that. Yeah. I don't I
don't know. I can't I can't remember exactly. [ __ ] knows. Yeah,
that's that's what you started off
saying. You started off saying normal stuff,
then it got really, really dark.
You told me that you was put into care
at a very young age because of your childhood
and then your dad [ __ ] going to
Australia and [ __ ] And I was like, "No,
that's [ __ ] weird.
You was put into care at a very young age
because of your upbringing.
That's why you're so [ __ ] up.
You was put into care. You was put into
You was put into care since you was till
you was 18. And then you lived with your
dad for a year and then you got your own
place when you was 19. I remember that.
You told me.
You told me you got your own place when
you was 19.
And we met that freak from Birmingham, Luke Lambbeath.
You met him first and then I met him after.
Luke Lambeath. Yeah. You got your own
place when you was 19 something.
But yeah, you was you was in care until
you was 18. Yeah.
Your mom your mom your mom used to throw
the dog on you. That's where your phobia
dogs come from
because your your mom used to throw
throw the dog at you. Chilly the Dalmatian.
That's why you said you preferred cats after that.
Yeah. Tilly the Dalmatian.
I know a lot about you, kid. A lot about you.
a lot about you, mate. How do I know
your dad's birthday?
No, no, no.
You told me that your dad went on a
plane before and he had a panic attack
and they had to stop the plane or
something. You told me so much [ __ ] cuz
I couldn't believe what the [ __ ] I was hearing.
I couldn't believe the [ __ ] I was I was [ __ ] hearing.
And you told me you told me that your
[ __ ] dad met your your dad was 42 and
your mom was [ __ ] 12
and he [ __ ] he met her at after
school or some [ __ ] He he was one of the teachers. Um
um he was one of the teachers at the
school and um yeah your mom was 12
and that's how they met. Yeah.
Yeah. It's true. It's true. Pip
is [ __ ] Mick has got a very very dark
past lad. Why do you think I stopped
beating this [ __ ]
Well, yeah, we we was literally friends.
We met like 30 times. I met you 30
Yeah. 30 times.
You you told me that your did the the
dad was a teacher at the school in it. Uh Pip
and he was [ __ ] he he he was grooming
um his mom
and that's how they met. Bro, it's just
it's disgusting. It's vile, bro. [ __ ]
vile. Why do you think I don't waste my
time with this [ __ ] prick, you know? Yeah. [ __ ] vile. Absolutely vile.
No, it hasn't taken all of these years.
I always said that your dad was 42 and
your [ __ ] mom was 12.
I just never told people how they [ __ ] met.
How's it taking me all of these years?
I've been saying that for [ __ ] years.
one was 12. His dad was 42.
Yeah. Apparently he used to prefer them longer younger.
The younger the better apparently
he used to say. Yeah.
Weird. [ __ ] weird.
So [ __ ] weird, man.
No. No. No. No. No. No. No. No. No. No.
No. No. No. N no no no no no no.
And you said that you would get you said
that you'd get with a 16y old.
No, he [ __ ] would not, mate. I'll
meet your [ __ ] dad tomorrow. And you, you [ __ ]
I love both of you. I love [ __ ] both
of you little [ __ ] virgins.
Little [ __ ] bed me like you. You sure
about that, mate? You want to do it,
You want to do it right now?
Meet me. Meet me right now. Meet me Yeah.
And you told me that you wanted to get
into Izzy's knickers or something.
Weird. You said you jerked off to her uh
you said that you you jerk you jerked
off to her photos.
Yeah. You said that you jerked off to her photos or something.
You're [ __ ] vile. You are [ __ ]
You're vile. You really vile.
[ __ ] weird. You're [ __ ] vile, mate.
So why so why did you want 16 year olds?
I always I always used to tell you that
you know 18 and above.
It's always been 18 and above.
It's 18 and above.
Why you not
Aisha? Aisha was 17.
Aisha was 17 and you was 21.
Yep, I remember that.
Aisha was 17 and you was 21. Yeah,
I think I got that right.
And you went absolutely nowhere near
that girl sexually. You you done
absolutely nothing with her.
Absolutely nothing with that girl. And
I' and I've spoke to her. I've spoke to
spoke to Aisha. Aisha boot. You don't
you absolutely nowhere near that girl.
Nowhere near her.
She rejected your advances. Advances
went nowhere near that girl sexually.
You went nowhere near that girl. Aa
I've spoken to her
when you got a hug.
Yeah. You got a hug for her, but you you
[ __ ] her. You do nothing nothing
sexually, mate. You [ __ ] You [ __ ]
You [ __ ] mate. Yeah.
Anyways, I'm gone. I'll see you.