There we go. Open it.
Do you know what? Right.
I should have a think.
How nice is it to um
be able to
Do you know what song that is? Dusty.
Do you know what? Right. I just went to
um I just went to Lakers, Dusty.
Do you know what Lakers is?
You know what Lakers is?
You [ __ ] should do, Sam.
I was just thinking I had a long walk
got a bit of exercise and this is what a
lot of these people need to do. Lakers
is a chicken shop. And I'm thinking, you
know, if people like Red Star and
Poverty Eye Joe with a 200 pound phone,
um, Non Legs and all these people come
out as gay, it they would it would open
up a lot of doors. you know, obviously I
can't um you know
um I can't relate because I'm not I'm
not gay, but you know, I mean, I feel
like the the day they actually come out
as being gay that the it would help a
lot of their problems,
Dusty, it would help a lot of their
problems if they just come out as gay.
What do you think, lad?
Yeah, I went to Lakers. I just got some
chicken. I got a chicken burger and a
piece of chicken
and it was and it was delicious.
I haven't done I haven't even started
the Lego. I just done the characters.
Do you remember these? Look.
Nice to be able to chew them again.
Yeah. He changes claves.
Um, so yeah, if they come out as gay,
they might get a lot further in life. Dusty
just admitting that they're [ __ ] gay.
I bet you can't wait until I'm in
Nottingham, can you, Dusty? I will be
going. I've got a friend to see. And
it's not unworthy, mate. It's not unworthy.
It's not unworthy. clock. Someone have
known for years.
It's not nice.
This guy talks about people's family. Dusty.
No, it's not tit for tat because I am
going to Nottingham, lad. So, he's got
one more chance and I will I will give I
will give notice. I will give notice obviously, bro.
Hello, Greavves. Are you all right?
Why didn't I go for a haircut? Because I
didn't. Why didn't you go for a haircut?
All right, Darcy. What do you mean give
it rest? I am going to Nottingham. I'm
going to Nottingham to see a friend, bro.
Yeah, man. It's been going on for years,
lad. And I've actually traveled to places.
Yeah. So what, bro? I'm not I'm not
doing this anymore. I'm going to
Nottingham cuz I'm going anyways, lad.
All I'm doing is killing two birds with one stone.
Obviously, bro, do you actually think
I'm going to Wait, you actually think
I'm I'm going all the way to where he lives?
That's embarrassing, bro. That is
embarrassing, bro. I couldn't even
imagine telling your mom that. That's so
embarrassing, bro. Like, paying all that
money, traveling all that way to try to
meet someone off of YouTube that's
jealous of you. [ __ ] that, bro. You're
just You're just embarrassing yourself
doing that. I'm I need to go to
Nottingham cuz I'm meeting a friend.
But I like I I'll tell people where I am
um when I am and if they want to if he
wants to come, he can come and if he
doesn't, he doesn't. So,
Nope. I don't I don't look You don't
look like you're just off a boat from Syria. Not nice.
Oh, did you see what I done to Yoda? Uh, Graves. Oh [ __ ]
Look, he's got a he's got a red lightsaber now.
He's a baddie.
Look, I changed his clothes.
That's nice, bro. Thank you for that.
Let's see your face.
I reckon a lot of people on here look
like Jamie Thompson.
I've just come back from the chicken
shop. Greavvesy, don't mind me, lad. I
reckon a lot of these people look like
Yeah. Jamie Thompson.
I got a feeling a lot of them do. Dusty.
That's why they don't come on camera.
Not starting anything. Not starting any
any [ __ ] or anything, you know.
Not starting anything.
Don't want to start a fight here, lads.
But I've got a feeling that a lot of you
uh you look like that Jamie, mate.
That's why you don't come on camera. I
could be wrong. Could be wrong, mate.
Could be wrong. I don't know. I don't actually know. [clears throat]
I could could be wrong, lad. Could be wrong. Who knows?
That happened for chicken. I just come back.
But yeah, honestly, man. But um yeah, Greasy.
Nope. I went for a walk. We're not all
housebound like you, lad.
Not everyone's housebound like you.
I might go to Waxy soon. Um Dusty,
I really might be going to um Waxy soon.
Are you all right, Pip Smoker? You know what?
I went to the chicken shop and I walked
back. It was about a mile and a half
there, a mile and a half back. Had a
long walk. And I was thinking to myself,
right, how better these people's lives
would be if they come out as gay.
Jo, Virgin Boy, Red Star, all these
people, if they actually came out as gay,
their lives would would be a lot better.
You know, I don't know how they would
come out or who they'd come out to.
That's nice, bro. My eyes look disabled.
Really? Really? Thank you, mate. Thank
you. Well, at least I'm not scared to
show my face like you.
You people look like Jamie Thompson, don't you?
Do you want to see Jamie Thompson again, Bipmoker?
Do you want to see Do you want to see Jamie Thompson?
But no, seriously though, like honestly,
bro, if they actually come out as gay,
they're obviously it might be a bit hard
because I think one's got a wife or says
he does and then the other one's got a
disabled girlfriend, but obviously he
hasn't [ __ ] the girlfriend. So, I
mean, it's going to be very hard to come
out. You reckon you can help them, Greavvesy?
Could you do that, boss? you know, be a
good citizen and maybe help them come
out as gay,
you know, reckon you could maybe give
them a bit of advice.
Yeah, there's a lot of people on here
that are gay, man.
Definitely, definitely. Definitely.
How they can sit on YouTube stalking
people all day, every day, bro? They got
seriously wrong with him, lad. I could
even do that to a woman for years and
years and years that I met. I couldn't do it. Um,
yeah, he is. No, I
I think Timmy's bisexual.
I think Timmy's bisexual, bro.
I think he's by
um Virgin Boy is gay. Uh DF's gay. Um
Red gay. All gay.
You couldn't even act that way over a
woman, bro. But they act like it over
men every day. So they should just come out, bro. No.
Yeah, man. Should come out as gay.
That is crazy.
See you later, self dog.
See you later, lad. Get kicked. No self
projectors on my channel.
Proper proper wasters on this. Do you
people actually leave your house? Let me
ask you this. Yeah. Do you people
actually leave your house?
I don't think they do, bro.
I don't think these people leave their house, man.
sat on YouTube all day, every day being
wasters. They don't like that word.
You can tell they didn't like that word
when I use that. Cuz why? Cuz cuz Peter
B hit a nerve.
>> Yeah, man.
Oh, UK asylum. What do you think?
Do you think Jo needs to come out as
gay? I do.
Proper proper gay, bro. proper proper.
But then again,
he is a lavry mong. So yeah. Um, Weird, bro.
Sad what you people do on here, man.
I love how you can be so jealous of
someone that you don't know. I wish
there was a normal person on that could
explain it to me.
All you write is hate every day, man.
You write so much hateful [ __ ]
They write a lot of hateful, but it's
how they feel about their own selves.
You know what I mean, Gregy? It's how
they feel about their own lives. You know,
that's why they do this.
You know, I start going out again, bro.
thinking I'll be off here, lad.
I'll be off here.
I don't think I'll come back, man. I've
got Steven Howard's email. Sorry. Yeah, [snorts]
I got Stephen Howard's email.
Oh yeah, Jo's on here, man. Come on my
channel. Let's arrange this meet up. Come on.
You little lavy mong.
Come on, you little lavy mong.
I knew he was a lavy mong. Little porky
obese [ __ ] Look, I'm saying all of
this [ __ ] bro, and he won't come on my channel.
[ __ ] obese. [ __ ] fat ugly [ __ ]
Trying to call me [ __ ] porky when
you're [ __ ] obese.
You [ __ ] fat [ __ ] You can't even
talk. You're talking about me, mate.
You're talking about me. Come Joe with a
200lb phone. Can't even face me [ __ ]
oneonone. You [ __ ]
Don't be [ __ ] mad. These people
Joe with a 200 phone. I made it rhyme. [ __ ] hell.
Come on, mate.
Come on, mate. So, Dusty, if I turn up
tonight again, do you think he's going
to turn up?
Do you think he's going to turn up, bro?
Oh, I wish I could have a bath, bro. We
don't have a bath here. Shame.
Do you reckon he's going to show up? Dusty
probably with a 200 pound phone. What do you think?
Never, bro. Bro, do you know Do you know
why they wouldn't sign up there, bro?
It's not cuz obviously they are scared.
They're [ __ ] houses. They're more
They've got anxiety. Yeah. Like they've
got anxiety. Um just like generally. The
reason that they won't as well, another
big reason is because the thing is, bro,
like if they if they meet you, then
they're going to show what they look
like. And then if they show if you could
if you show them what they look like,
then what can they ever say about you
anymore? Because we know that these
people are very bad looking people. So
if they was to actually meet you, bro,
that's it. That's the end. You know,
bomb never came back. All of this [ __ ]
that they've been doing online, it's over.
It's finished because obviously we know
what they look like. I know what this
guy looks like.
I know what he looks like, bro. I know
what this guy looks like, but obviously
I don't have 100% proof. Even though I
know. And even if it takes 10 years,
I'll be right. But you know what I'm
saying? Like, but if when they when they
meet you, if they meet you, you're going
to know what they look like. So, they
can't say anything about you anymore
because they'll just get roasted in the
chat. That's why they will never meet you, bro.
That's one of the main reasons. And
obviously, they've got anxiety as well.
So, I don't think they're necessarily
just scared of fighting. I think that's
what the the main thing is.
So, yeah. No, I'm just going to
Nottingham uh soon. Paul Key.
Yeah, man. I'll be announcing it soon.
Yeah, I'll be going to Nottingham
[clears throat] cuz I want to go and um
see a friend. So yeah,
that's that, bro.
Ah, my head.
This community's hurt my head again.
Nah, the only one that's got a list is
you, lad. No self projectors on my
channel. See you later. >> [gasps]
>> [ __ ] bog. But yeah, no, I agree with
you. The the thing is right is because I
I'll explain it to you. If I go to
leads, the thing is, bro, if I go to
leads, then I'm wasting that money. I'm
wasting my time and it's making me look
bad because I know in the end what these
people are. I know the excuses they're
going to make. I know what they do. I
know what they are. So, I will give you
the option to meet me in Nottingham,
which is more than halfway for me and
it's less than halfway for you. That way
you can't come out with these excuses.
That why you you can't you will have
nothing to say. Um and I'm just getting
on with what I'm doing anyways.
It's embarrassing as well. If I if I
actually do go all the way there and
that's embarrassing because this is 2026
and we know what these people are. So
it's actually making us look bad as well.
We know that they're fat. We know that
they're ugly. We know they ain't got a
life. We we know that they're wasters.
And that's what's going to come out in
the end. So, you know, it's Yeah,
Lottingham is perfect. It's perfect. Perfect. Greeny
cuz it's embarrassing. It's embarrassing
if you're if you tell your mom or
someone, oh, I've spent this money to go
all the way. They're going, "What over
YouTube again? This is 2026."
Embarrassing, bro. Very embarrassing.
See you later, self-reflector. [gasps]
>> [clears throat] >> Yeah.
That's that, lad.
What? Who's your money going to be on?
Bezy, who's your money going to be on, lad?
It's going to be me, bro. It's not going
to be me winning. It's going to be me
showing up and that [ __ ] not showing up. Simple.
Trust me, bro. I've been on here years.
Done stuff in my life, but I've been on
the years to know to know exactly what
these people are like. See?
Okay. Put it this way. Right. So,
If I announce that I'm going there
and the [ __ ] doesn't want to meet, then
he's a [ __ ] in it.
He's a [ __ ] then. Cuz I'm traveling 150 mi, right?
Which is long for me. Well, to me it's
not far, but technically it's far
because I've traveled everywhere. So,
I'm used to these
distances. But if he's not willing to
travel 90 miles and I'm willing to
travel 150 mi, it's the same northeast.
uh north uh yeah northeast. So it's not
like it's completely different
direction. Then he's a [ __ ]
As simple as that, bro. He's a complete [ __ ] That's that.
And that's the end of it. Simple.
That is literally the end of it, bro.
Nottingham's nowhere near me, but
obviously I'm going to arrange it obviously.
[ __ ] phone froze, bro.
I think this this phone's almost packed up, Greezy. Yeah.
[snorts] Yeah, lad.
Probably Joe with 200 pound phone.
You like that, Grezy?
No one's going to be able to take down.
And you know what, Grezy? I'm going to
be wearing my little Bart Simpson
t-shirt as well.
I'm going to wear my Bart Simpson t-shirt.
Okay with you, boss. Some people like
[ __ ] taking a piss out of my little top.
[ __ ] hell, man. S bastards
need to come out the closet.
Know you on YouTube. Come on my live
stream. Know you in YouTube.
My [ __ ] phone's almost bloody packed up.
It's all right.
All right. with you.
Is that all right with you, Bet?
Make it so
you're not the new boss anymore, Grezy.
Is that okay with you, Virgin? [laughter]
Is that okay with you, Virgin boy? [snorts] Oh gosh. Oh bless. Bless. Pleasure.
I'm going to speak to my friend in a bit.
I feel uncomfortable. I've got so many
people that want my ass. And I don't
swing that way. I don't swing that way.
Leave me alone.
Jealous ass people want my my backside.
I wonder if I didn't show my face, would
I still have the same amount of people
obsessed with me? Who knows?
So, what what you going to do, Greavves?
You just wait for the Nottingham uh
video to be made
or you just be sat there with a cup of [ __ ]
waiting until it's been made. Poor [ __ ] Yeah.
What uh what community is this again? Grezy,
what would you call this community again?
You said it, but I forgot. [laughter] [clears throat]
Yeah. Cuz look, look, Grezy, did you
see? Yeah, I I [laughter] [snorts]
unboxed my Lego. I unboxed the Lego. Did
I, Grezy? Yeah,
I un [laughter]
I unbox the Lego and then Lord J done an
unboxing video. What's the chances?
What's the chances, eh?
Oh, look. He's done another one.
Yeah, he's done another one. An air fryer.
He's a little copycat.
Everyone go over in his channel and call
him a copycat. Copycat.
You're a big fat stinking copycat.
That's twice you've done it now. He's copying.
He's [ __ ] copying, man. He's copying.
He showed the unboxing the trailers. Now
he's showing an air fryer which is in
the same box. You stink your
Oh, a Bigfoot stinking coffee. [laughter]
What's What's LJ being? Grezy,
what's he been lately? DJ,
sorry, man. I'm going to have to put it
up again, bro. I'm sorry. [laughter] >> [snorts]
>> There we go.
Yeah, he's copy him.
Leave me alone. One second.
See, look. I like that new picture.
You like that new picture?
Yeah, I like that. That's cool.
I need to start eating inside Grezy, but
I just can't be bothered to cook, you know.
You know how it is, eh? Dennis
is the copycat community.
How long am I live for? Um,
until the new Scream comes out.
Yeah. Scream seven.
Yeah. And I I'll be live until that comes out.
Uh when is it coming out? Wednesday.
When's it coming out? I just stay live.
Well, you're going to be waiting a long
time cuz I don't think it's been made yet.
It's okay. I'll just wait.
You You wait?
Yes. Until it's been made. [snorts] Yeah.
I was speaking to my friend from
Amsterdam. I said we should stay up here
and try to break the record for staying
up the longest. Greasy,
I think the longest is 10 days, isn't
it? Someone stayed up for Oh, man.
I think you would just pass out of
exhaustion, wouldn't you? [snorts]
I want some digestive biscuits.
I forgot digestive biscuits. Grezy,
I'll be going to Dust Dusty. Trust me,
bro. I will be going to Waxy soon.
I'll be going to find a new mama.
What's your opinion on that, Grezy?
Finding a new mama.
Um, I'm not sure. I've not seen him for
a little while. [snorts]
Yeah, but I don't know where. What is he
commenting on? I haven't seen him
comment or anything.
I don't know why Joe tells people
they're living in poverty when he is
literally the most poverty ridden wanker
I've come across. 200 pound phone
pretending that he's winning at gambling.
Everything screams poverty about him,
but nothing screams poverty about me.
Not one thing,
but this community is no stranger to
self projecting. Are they Grezy?
Are they lad?
Yeah, LJ is being a copycat.
He's proper proper copying, bro.
Look at his channel, bro.
Look at his channel. He is a copycat.
All right, agrees. Look at his channel,
bro. There's not one other video where
he's unboxing something until yesterday and today.
See, he's copying, bro.
Nope. Just food. He's a copycat.
Oo, a stinking copycat. Yo, I'm going
through the videos now.
So a big fat stinking dirty copycat.
You think he looks better like this, Grezy?
Do you think Yoda looks better like that?
He's got a red lightsaber.
cuz he wanted to sit down and he
couldn't sit down on his other body.
Hey John Street, you okay?
How you doing today? >> [sighs] >> No.
And I lost 60 pound on roulette
yesterday. I've given it all up. The
football, the roulette. I'm done with it
all now. [ __ ] had enough. I've had
That's funny. Grievy, you saw that
video, is it in Manchester of that Indian guy.
They said I don't do Indians. That's so
weird. You saw that, is it? Yeah.
Now everyone's going to start doing
unboxing [ __ ] videos. [ __ ] sake. I
can't do anything.
I can't [laughter] do anything without
someone [ __ ] copying.
The only thing that ain't copied is
approaching women because they ain't got
the balls to do it. But [ __ ] they
everything I do that suck. I find
another person copies.
What's the [ __ ] point?
I [ __ ] unbox someone copies. I go to
Amsterdam. Someone else copies and goes
to Amsterdam. What the [ __ ] can I do? I
do a [ __ ] um I have hot curry.
Someone's doing a [ __ ] curry challenge.
What the [ __ ] can I do without someone bloody copying?
I might have to have LJ in the hangouts
and ask him why he's being such a copycat. You know,
being such a [ __ ] copycat. I call
these people wasters. Now Jo's calling
me a waster.
So what what is the what are the cats on
this community waiting for Greavves?
What are they waiting for?
Yeah, but who who who's going to be the
one to do it? [laughter]
Who's going to be the one to do it?
Who's going to make the statement? I
guess I'm going to have to [ __ ] make it again.
Hear that? [snorts] coffee.
That made me laugh, bro.
How's things with your um How's things
with your narcissist, Grezy? Absolutely skin. [sighs] [snorts] Nice. Nice.
Skin. Skin. Skin. Ah,
my brain hurts.
These people are so boring. Repeating bastards. Peter [ __ ]
What the [ __ ]
See this? He nearly put me off my lunch.
I would I would take looking like
crossbow to walk then have his life. He
claims he went looking no respect.
These people really need to come out as gay, bro.
Their lives would be so much better.
Instead of talking about people's looks
every day that's better looking than
them, they need to literally come out as gay.
And like I was saying, that's why none
of them will ever meet you cuz they get exposed. Yeah,
I do need to go to the barber soon though.
Maybe Saturday. But the thing is, when I
go to the barbers, Grezy, then it means
it's my time to go to waxies.
And I don't really want to go out
drinking yet, Grezy.
So, I'm not going to just get a haircut.
I not go out.
It's just like I will go out. If I get
if I get a haircut, I'll be going out.
Why wouldn't I? You know, you have to
sit on the chair for a [ __ ] hour. I'm
not just going to have a haircut and not
go out. You know what I mean?
Cuz this is kind of like my way of, you
know, I know I'm not going to go out if
I don't get a haircut. Does that make sense?
Go to waxies, you know, find a new mama
to the collection.
Can I show you who I've collected when I
go out again, Grezy? Can I show you my little collection? Yeah.
Imagine Imagine I just put them in a
dungeon. I do like a video quy showing
you. They're all like sat at a table eating [laughter]
like my little collection. Imagine >> [laughter]
>> Oh gosh, [clears throat]
your skin. Your skin. Oh my god. 2026. No.
What's wrong with wearing a Spider-Man
t-shirt and a Simpsons t-shirt
greasy for lounging around in? What?
What? What is What is wrong with that?
What's wrong with wearing a a Simpsons
and Spider-Man t-shirt
just to lounge around in? I think they
look all right.
I think they look quite cool.
What the [ __ ]
I think they look all right, mate.
I'm going to put my Spider-Man one on
later after I have a shower, Grezy.
But the thing is, Dusty, they're made for adults.
They're made for adults, lad.
These are adults t-shirts. They're not
for kids. They're for adults.
You understand? Look, I was reading uh
Jo's post. He was like,
"Honestly, in 10 days, you have declined
fast. What the hell was all the kids
clothes you're wearing? Kids toys you're
playing with. A, they're not kids toys.
And B, they're not kids clothes either.
And I'd rather be wearing a Spider-Man
t-shirt than be a [ __ ] middle-aged
man on YouTube obsessed with a 28-year-old
showing [ __ ] fake gambling wins. Any
day of the week. Any day of the [ __ ] week, bro.
You're the one that's obsessed with
someone you don't know every day on
YouTube cuz you're closeted gay. So,
bro, like what the [ __ ] Clo children's
t-shirts. How are they children's
t-shirts when they're made for adults?
What the [ __ ]
No, bro. No. No. I mean, there's 40 year
olds that love [ __ ] Marvel for [ __ ]
sake. What? Spider-Man. Marvel.
Yeah, you're right, Cory. I'm just
wearing my little Bart Simpson top. I
need to go to the barber soon, but I'm
not going out um drinking anytime soon.
So, I've just kind of let my beard grow
and my hair grow, so you know. And I got
myself a Bart Simpson t-shirt. And I've
also got myself um Spider-Man.
Yeah, people on YouTube are being
jealous of my clothes.
And oh, I didn't show you. Bori
started collecting Lego. Look,
I got Yoda.
I got Judger.
I got Mr. Robot.
I got Darth Vader, the white one.
I got him. Yeah, bro.
Sorry. Like um
they're not kids toys. Lego is not for
kids and Spider-Man is definitely not for kids.
All right, this Joe F is saying that
Lego's for kids and my t-shirts are for
kids, but they're not. Cory, he's just
jealous cuz he's a middle-aged closeted homosexual.
A lot of these people on here, Cory,
believe it or not, lad, they're [ __ ]
They're [ __ ] They're closeted gays,
bro. For 100%, bro. 100%.
Um, yeah, the set before it. There's progress.
Um, the other one I haven't even started it yet.
I don't know when I will, to be honest.
I'll probably go for a night out and
then after that I will. But yeah, a lot
of these people on here are closeted gay, bro.
Jo, nonslegs, Red Star, they're all
closeted gays. They need to come out the
closet, man. Their life will be better
if they when as soon as they come out
the closet. 100%, lad.
Saying that I've got [ __ ] kids toys
when they're not even kids toys. And I'm
wearing kids clothes. How the [ __ ] is
Spider-Man How's a Spider-Man t-shirt
kids clothes when literally there's 50y
olds, 40y olds that that like Marvel?
What the [ __ ] bro?
coming from a middle-aged closeted gay Cory. Cory, lad.
[ __ ] hell, mate.
I do. I need to go to the barbers, bro.
I do. I know I do. I know I do, mate. Yeah. I know.
Yeah, I know, man.
No, Cory, I I Yeah, well, I need to I
need to collect some women. Um Cory, I'm
starting women collecting soon again.
So, yeah, I'm just going to have like a little collection.
Okay with you, boss.
No, I don't have a razor, bro. I don't
have a razor.
I don't have a razor, lad. No.
>> [clears throat] [laughter]
>> I haven't shaved for years, bro. I would
always just go to the barbers and get it
trimmed. You know what I mean? Yeah.
The the thing is, Cory, yeah, lad, this
is a copycat community, bro. That's why
I don't really like this community.
Like, I done I done an unboxing Lego
video, bro. Um, yesterday and then I
deleted it, bro. I deleted it and then
all of a sudden Lord J started doing
like unboxing and stuff and he done
another one today.
He's a copycat, bro. It's a copycat community. Yeah. >> [snorts]
>> Yeah, there's a copycat community, lad.
I just think a lot of these people need
to come out the closet, lad.
Be much happier in life, won't they? I'm sorry. No, no.
I need to go for some Guinnesses. Cory, boo. Boo.
>> Yeah, [snorts] man. Yeah, you're better
off not watching them, lad. They're [ __ ] retards.
They're [ __ ] retards, lad.
You still got my number, don't you, Cory?
Still got my little number, don't you, lad? Yeah, bro.
Oh, [ __ ] sake.
[clears throat] Yeah.
Going to start going to the gym soon, Cory. Lad, no. No.
Yeah. You'd end up like [ __ ] the
you'd end up like these people. [ __ ]
Joseph Ferrar [ __ ] obese
Cory. You'd end up like these [ __ ] people.
Yeah, like these [ __ ] mate. Obese. Yeah. Yeah, lad.
[ __ ] these [ __ ]
obese bastards in it. Do you know these
people on here, Cory? Yeah. You know
they're not even fat, bro. They're
actually obese. They're not even fat.
They are actually obese.
That's why they don't come on camera. Ah,
that's why they don't come on camera, lad.
Oh, I'm in my little nesticles. Cory.
Oh gosh, look who I've got next to me. Cory,
I've got Crash.
I've got Crash Bandicut.
You like him?
He's a good little friend.
>> He's good. Crash Bandicut, bro.
I won him in the arcade. Yeah.
Anyways, I'm going. Yeah. See you in a
bit, bro. Text me if you need me.