[ __ ] sake, bro. Right. I'm doing this
one more time, bro. One more. One more.
One more time.
Again. Consider yourself lucky, bro. Yeah.
Consider yourself lucky, lad.
Yeah. I've just been scrolling, bro,
whilst eating a bit of a Chinese food,
as you do.
This is very, very, very concerning.
Like I like I said earlier, man. And so
I had a nap. So yeah, I've just just
just had a nap. Um
like I said, bro, um you come out the
closet, you'll be a you'll be a much
better person. A lot of these people on
here generally need to um need to come
out the closet. Yeah, I'm going to talk
about these two in a bit. Yeah, when
more people join.
Don't forget, I don't live in [ __ ] um
London anymore, bro. I see this Smokeoky
B talking [ __ ] again, bro. I will meet
this guy tomorrow. If he really wants to
meet me tomorrow, bro, I will meet this
[ __ ] Yeah, we'll start with him. Yeah,
even though this Jo is more obsessed,
bro, just just go live anywhere tomorrow
in London and I will meet you anywhere
you want, bro. Yeah. And we will we will
see what you're really really really
about. And if you're not going to do it,
if you're not going to give me the
chance to humiliate humiliate you in
person, then stop going on about me.
It's as simple as that. Because that's
that's the end of that. If you're not
going to give me a chance to humiliate
you in your face and on camera, then
bro, just just just just stop it. You're
embarrassing yourself. Only [ __ ]
[ __ ] people, bro, would think that
you're that you're winning.
Do you know what I'm saying? Did you Did
you not go in Laur's pip? Did you not go
in it, bro? [ __ ] everybody. It wasn't
Smokey. Not Not every comment was Smokey
We bro, but this Jo, every single
comment was about me. The guy is gay,
bro. He's a batty man. When I was saying
this yesterday, bro, earlier some, bro,
I was being deadly serious. He's gay,
bro. I'm not even using it as an insult.
The guy is a [ __ ] He is a big [ __ ]
bro. Every single comment. Yeah. You see
people commenting normally. Yeah. And
then you see this guy comment, "He's a
[ __ ] All he does is talk about me.
He's Bro, he's got to be jealous of me
or something, bro. This poverty eyed
[ __ ] with a 200 pound phone. This
obesity [ __ ] He's got to be jealous of
me or something. He He wants my ass,
bro. I swear to God. And I see that
Smokey B talking [ __ ] I'm I ain't block
Smokey B. I don't think if I have, I'm
going to unblock him, man. We'll arrange
it, bro. Like, if you've got something
to say, I will meet you anywhere in
London tomorrow. It's not a problem.
I will meet you anywhere in London
tomorrow. And if you're not going to do
that, bro, then stop embarrassing
yourself. It's as simple as that,
you [ __ ] stupid little [ __ ]
Don't [ __ ] go talking [ __ ] behind my
back, bro. If you're not going to meet
me, it's as simple as that.
And don't forget, bro, London, you you
live near London. You know what I'm
saying? I don't live near them parts
anymore. You speak to LT, so you can get
LT involved if you want, bro. You're not
you're not banned for my channel,
you know? And I'll make an example out
of you before I get to Joe. It's as
simple as that, bro. And if you're not
going to do it, just stop. Simple.
It's simple, bro. Like, if you're not
going to give me the chance to humiliate
you, then what the [ __ ] bro? What's the point?
Every, bro, you didn't see him. It It
was every comment, bro. It was literally
every comment with the obese poverty
[ __ ] with the fat hands. It was every single comment.
Every single comment.
It was every comment, bro. Every single
one. So anyway, Smokey B, get your ass
here, bro. I know you're watching me.
Yeah, let's arrange this, bro. Good and
proper tomorrow. Come on. Let's arrange
this good and proper. You can go cry to
LT if you want as well. If that makes
you feel better, you know?
Then if you're not going to do it, bro,
like, yeah, stop embarrassing yourself.
I'll [ __ ] send you back to [ __ ]
island where you [ __ ] come from.
You weirdo, bro. And they'll deal with
that joke next week. It's as simple as
that, bro. So, let's let's have it, bro.
Come on. We've got a lot to say on the
internet. Well, you've got a lot to say
on the internet, right? I don't even
bring these clowns up. You've got a lot
to say. So, let's do it, bro. Come on.
What you What you waiting for? What you scared of?
Come on, bro.
[ __ ] What the [ __ ] are you talking
about Charlie for, bro? Why are you
talking about Charlie anyways?
I'm not going to Nottingham to meet
Charlie. You don't know who I know in
Nottingham. You don't know anything. You
don't know anything about me. Why the
[ __ ] would I be meeting Charlie?
Why the [ __ ] you even bringing Charlie
up? You're the one sucking a virgin's
dick every day every time he gets called
a virgin. You're the one with a
boyfriend. You're the one that keeps
going on about someone all day every day
because you ain't got no life.
You know what I'm saying?
So, it's as simple as that, bro. Like,
the [ __ ] man? None of them are banned
on this channel, by the way. Simple,
you know? That's it. And I'm not
annoyed. I'm not triggered. I'm I'm just
saying, bro, like you you know you got a
lot of [ __ ] to say, then say it to my face. Simple.
Copy my words. [ __ ] everything, bro.
You know what I'm saying?
And that's it.
Meet me tomorrow, smoke me. I'll put you
all over my channel, bro.
Simple. Not a problem. You go live
anywhere in London. Can you wait for me
and I'll come? It's as simple as that.
It is as simple as that, bro. Not a
problem. Yeah, that's fair now cuz I I
live out the area. So, come on, man.
Come on. Come on.
Simple. You could go crying to LT as well.
I don't have boyfriends, but I'm not gay
like you. I don't have a channel
dedicated to someone like you. Nah,
we're not gay like you, Poverty Eye Joe,
with a 200lb phone and a chubby fat ugly
fingers cuz you're obese. You can't even
be called fat, bro. You're actually
obese. Look at them [ __ ] hands. And
you tried to talk about other people.
Nah, bro. That's you, bro. You lavy
mong. That's you.
And yes, that is hands of a fat man. You
[ __ ] poverty obese [ __ ] >> [laughter]
>> And when you meet me in Nottingham, and
if you do meet me at Nottingham, bro, if
you've got any if you actually grow a
pair of balls from now until then, bro,
I will I will show everyone what you
look like. I will show everybody what
you look like. And that's one of the
reasons why you will not come out
because of your looks. You're ashamed of
what you look like. Yeah. Same as Smokey
B. Same as the rest of these little
wasters. I know you like to, you know,
copy my [ __ ] words, you know,
wasters. Yeah, that's it, bro. You know,
you're a copycat as well.
If you don't rep, if you don't come on
here, I'm just going to make a video to
you and that's it. I'll happily meet
Smokey Be tomorrow. It's not a problem.
It's not a problem. And then we're going
to do Joe, bro. It's as simple as that.
So, I'm just going to I'm just going to
show everyone what happens when when
people when you're act when your bluff
is actually called. Yeah. You didn't you
didn't show up last time, did you? You
know, and I'm doing this one more time,
bro. One last time. Yeah. The Nottingham
thing I don't even need to worry about
because when I'm going, I'm I'm letting
everyone know where I'm when I'm going.
I'm going there anyways. So, I'm not
wasting my time and money on these
people. Do you get me? But obviously
London, bro. Like, yeah, man. Just
anywhere in London tomorrow, bro. It's
Thursday. I'll just have a drink. It's
not a problem, you know?
And that's that, bro.
And I and I'll teach you a good old
lesson. I'll teach you a valuable
[ __ ] lesson, bro. Yeah.
And that's it. Let's see what you're all
about, Smokey B. Come on. Let's see what
you're all about. Yeah.
Sorry, I have to mention this LT, bro, cuz
you know, he he he will somehow get
involved now. You see, cuz he's always
watching. Don't believe he's not cuz he
he always [ __ ] is.
Come on, bro. What the [ __ ] No one's
blocked. You got a lot of [ __ ] to say on
other people's channel. Let's meet up.
Come on. We're not too far from each other.
Simple. What are you waiting for?
Jesus Christ, man.
>> [snorts and gasps]
>> They will never meet anyone, bro. Never.
Never meet anyone cuz they're ashamed of
what they look like. It was the same as
the bomb, bro. They're ashamed of the
way that they look. So, they would never
meet anyone purely solely based on that
reason. You understand?
None of them look good. They're all
weird looking [ __ ]
and that's it, bro. And they got anxiety
as well. And I don't even think it's
just anxiety about like meeting for
fight. They've just got anxiety, bro.
These people. So
So you got a lot to say.
You got a lot to say, but now you you
got nothing to say on my channel.
Come on, man. I'll put you both in your place.
What are you waiting for?
So lucky you're getting a response, you
know. So lucky.
Yeah. I will meet you tomorrow, Smokey
B. And I'll meet the [ __ ] obese
Joseph Ferrar, the poverty Joe with a
200lb phone next week. It's as simple as that. Simple, bro.
And yeah, Jo, no one's got a boyfriend.
The only one that's got a boyfriend is
you. How many times was you sucking
someone's dick when I was calling them a
virgin? You [ __ ] obese fat bastard.
And that's one of the reasons you're not
going to meet me in Nottingham cuz
you're ashamed of what your fat ass
looks like. Every single bro, I'll put
you in your place on a video, bro. If if
they don't come on this channel, bro,
I'm going to make it so to the whole of
this community, bro, what these people
are about. Yeah. Simple. I'm going to
talk about Smokeoky. I'm going to call
them both out, bro. It's as simple as
that. I'll go and see Joe next week. So,
he's got more than And I've looked up
the exact distance as well. So, you've
got no excuse when I'm in Nottingham.
Yeah. You've got literally no excuse to not come.
You have literally got no excuse because
I'm traveling 150 mi away. So, you've
got no excuse. Yeah. And I and I will be
holding that as an L if you don't show
up. Yeah, bro. I'm literally, bro, I'm
eating my Chinese. Yeah. I'm sat here
chilling. I thought, "Oh, let me just
scroll on this." Yeah. I see this guy,
these these people talking a load of
[ __ ] again. This Smokeoky B. Every, bro,
it's so bad. Yeah. Every Joe F's comment
is about me. I said, "Bro, you need to
come out the closet. You honestly at
this point, bro, you need to come out as
what you are gay." Yeah. So, I was like,
and then the Smokeoky Bee's talking
[ __ ] He's talking [ __ ] I'm reading it.
They're talking [ __ ] again. I was like,
"Okay, bro. Um, you know, I'll meet
Smokey B tomorrow then. You know, it's
not a problem. You go live anywhere in
London and I will meet you anywhere you
want and I'll go for a drink. Yeah, this
has got to stop, man. You know, and I
don't I don't mind making an example out
of you. You can cry to LT. You can call
LT. I don't care because we know he's
going to try and get involved anyways.
Yeah. So, bro, like we might as well
just say it now, is it? If you've got a
lot of [ __ ] to say, that's fine. We've
all said a lot of [ __ ] Let's meet
tomorrow. Yeah. Just go live anywhere in
London. Anywhere. And I and I will be out. Simple.
you know, and I will humiliate you in
front of this whole community and you'll
think twice before being an obsessed
keyboard warrior every single day.
Simple. If they don't come on here, bro,
I'm going to do a video and it's going
to be it's going to be my last video to
them, bro. Simple. Simple, bro.
Just [ __ ] moeyed Joe with a 200lb
phone with his [ __ ] obese [ __ ] gay
self. Know what I'm saying, bro? Come
out of the closet, bro. You're gay. You
claim that you got this wife and that.
Yeah. Every single comment, bro, has
been about me, lad.
Yeah. Everyone has seen me try to meet
people multiple times, lad. And we don't
care about we. You are the losers. No
one cares what ugly fat people laugh at.
You laugh at yourselves, bro. You are
fat, ugly people that don't leave your
house. You do not go. You do not count
for the population, bro. No one cares
about fat, ugly virgins like you. and
what you laugh at. I laugh at you every
day, bro. I laugh at the fact that I'm
younger, better looking, more money. I'm
not fat and old like you, bro. I get
more laughs out of you than you will
ever get out of me. I will get I get
more laughs out of you ugly people than
you will ever get out of me, bro. Yeah,
trust me. I laugh tfold at you ugly
people than you will ever laugh at me.
Yeah, let that sink in your head, bro.
You are all fat. You're all old. You're
all ugly. You're all loners. You've got
no life outside of YouTube. Literally,
not a single one of you have got a life
out of this community, bro. You are on
here 24/7 with no one. No one cares what
rejects laugh at, bro. You You do not,
bro. This is so bad. Yeah. You do not
even fit into society. Yeah, bro. By the
rejected ugly losers. Of course they're
going to laugh at me, bro. Someone
younger and better looking than news. Of
course, you're gonna laugh at me. You're
jealous. You're jealous, bro. We have
seen what you people here look like. And
you're some bad looking people, bro.
You're some bad looking people. And it
explains why you do what you do. You're
ugly. You got no one. You're ugly.
That's why you do this, bro. Not one of
you people could turn your cameras on
due to embarrassment of your looks. No
one cares about you people. I laugh at
you. I come in here and I laugh at you.
I don't want to be like you when I'm 40
odd. Yeah. fat ugly on YouTube. You're
what I don't want to become. Use an
example, right, are such wasters. Yeah.
That you should be showed in schools not
to grow up like when you're older, 40,
no money, no life, sat on YouTube.
You're not what someone wants to become,
bro. You They should put you in [ __ ]
in secondary school. What you people
don't want to end up like. [ __ ]
boggers on YouTube, bro. It's so bad
then. I bet you not one of you leave
your houses, bro. Not one of you leave
your house. You're all fat and ugly.
That's why you're on here every day,
bro. You know what? It's so bad. Yeah.
You can't even take one day off of
YouTube because you've got [ __ ] all in life.
Simple, bro. [ __ ] all in life, lad.
Bro. Yeah, bro. You're in your 40s and
you're still a virgin, lad.
Bro, you're you're literally in your 40s
and you're still a virgin. Don't even
try and come at me, bro. Don't even try
and project your [ __ ] onto me. You are
in your 40s and you've never even been
with a woman. Don't you even try and
project your virgin life onto me, bro.
Like I said to you, bro. And also, a lot
of you people on here are actually
virgins as well. And I'm talking about
the haters, by the way. I'm not talking
about every single person on this
community, bro. You've shown what you're
about when a new woman comes on this
community. Bro, most of you are virgins
in your 40s and you're talking about me.
Bro, this is a tip that you need to
learn. Yeah. Don't talk about someone
that's better than you in every way. It
makes you look a fool. If you didn't
suffer suffer from Yeah. severe
disabilities, you would know that
talking about someone that's better than
you in every way makes you look like an idiot.
Yeah. Simple, bro. That's that.
You know what I'm saying?
Yeah. Okay, bro. Okay. Okay, bro. Okay.
Well, why don't you meet me tomorrow
then with Smokeoky B? How about this
then? Right. How about Oh, bro. This is
[ __ ] hilarious, bro. Why don't you
meet me tomorrow with Smokeoky B and
we'll see who'll be running away. Come
on. Why don't you Why don't you meet me
tomorrow with Smokey B?
Huh? Why don't you meet me tomorrow with
Smokey B and we'll see who's running
away? Or are you going to just keep
making excuses and keep bringing up the
past? Meet me tomorrow with Smokey Be
and I'll show you exactly who runs away.
Yeah. And if you're not going to do that
or you change the subject, shut the [ __ ]
up cuz you've come on my channel. Yeah.
I've asked someone to come on my channel
to meet me tomorrow. You're getting
yourself involved. But why don't you
come tomorrow as well then? Yeah. It's
as simple as that. Yeah. Simple as that.
Simple, bro. Simple. Simple,
bro. Yeah, you'll meet me after work.
Yeah. Okay. Right.
Let me sub to your channel.
I know you're not going to beat me, but
anyways, I'll sub to your channel. Yeah,
bro. Meet me. Meet me after work
tomorrow. Yeah. Yeah, bro. Yeah. Yeah.
Yeah, bro. One second. Let me sub to
your channel. [gasps] Yeah, man. Yeah.
You and Smokey B, bro. I'll meet both of
you, bro. I'll meet both of you. One second.
Let me sub to your channel.
Yeah. And I'm going to show what you
people look like as well. If I'm brave
enough to meet you. Yeah. Which I am
brave enough to. I'm not scared of
anyone, especially anyone on this
community. Then I'm also going to show
everyone what you look like when I'm
done with you. Just to show everyone
that I was right all along about what
the way the way that you people look
like cuz obviously it's a big part of
this. So I'll be doing that tomorrow as
well. Yeah. when I'm done with you. This
is why these people talk about other
people when I put the camera in your
face. And I've never been wrong, lad.
Never been wrong.
Yeah. Meet me tomorrow, bro. Yeah. Meet
me tomorrow, bro. 100%. Yeah.
Yeah, bro. Why don't Jo come on this
channel, bro? We'll sort it, man. Come on. Yeah.
Low, I've just won £100 on a bet. I
might post it. Bro, no one cares about
your£100 poverty Joe. Poverty eyed Joe
with a 200lb phone. You literally need
it more than me, bro.
Poverty eyed Joe with a 200 pound phone.
You need it more than me. I don't live
on I don't live under poverty. So 100
pound doesn't bother me. Your little
fake wins, your little fake videos don't
bother me, fatty. Go lose some weight.
You're obese. before I talk trying to
talk about other other people. Lad, you
are [ __ ] obese and that's one of the
reasons you're not gonna meet me. He's
another Jamie Thompson, lad. Yeah, bro.
Why do you keep talking about LT?
Why Why do you keep talking about LT,
bro? Do you want Do you want to bum the
guy or something?
LT? Why do you keep talking about LT?
Don't worry, bro. I'm meeting you after
work tomorrow. Stop talking about LT.
Why are you talking about LT? Is LT on
here now? Is LT on here now mentioning
my name? No. No, he's not. You are, and
so are you. So, I will meet you tomorrow
after work. Stop talking about LT, bro.
No one's talking about LT. Yeah,
you. I'm We're talking about you
wasters. You ugly old men. You fatties.
We're talking about you, the fatties.
The rejects of society. Why are you
talking about LT?
If LT comes back on it, I'll tell him
about himself as well. We're Stop
changing the subject. Stop changing the
subject. You're meeting me tomorrow
after work. Yeah. And I'm going to try
and get Smokey B to meet me as well.
Simple. Yeah. Simple. I've sub to your
channel, you stupid little [ __ ]
idiot. So, go and do a video tomorrow
and that's it.
And then it will be poverty Joe with a
200 phone. Yeah. Simple as that, bro.
Simple as that.
You're meeting me after work. Don't
worry about LT.
Don't worry about LT, man.
And I've already explained everything
about LT in the video to when I've done
the email. I'm not explaining it again.
He's not on it. He's not talking about
me. Don't worry about him. Yeah. Simple.
You idiot. Yeah, bro. Like I said,
you're going to meet me tomorrow. Bro,
you said I'm the runaway man. So, we'll
see who meets who tomorrow, won't we?
Come on, big man. Come on, big man. And
I'll And I will literally laugh in your
face and pull it on camera, bro. I will
meet both of you tomorrow. I've said
this. I've literally said this, bro. I
have gone live to say this, lad. I will
get up in your face and I'll laugh in
your face and put it all over YouTube.
Yeah. So, you get taught a lesson. Do
you understand? I will grab you and
laugh in your face and it's not going to
be behind the keyboard. It's as simple
as that. Stop backtracking. Stop talking
about LT. Yeah, you're coming on here
[ __ ] Stering. I've subbed to your
channel. Yeah, we'll see what you're
about tomorrow. Simple. Don't worry
about that. Don't worry about LT.
Worry about yourself, big man. Make sure
you meet me off to work tomorrow, big man. Yeah. Simple. That's that.
You [ __ ] loser.
You [ __ ] absolute loser. Yeah.
And like I said, bro, you're not going
to meet me for the same reason as a lot
of other people's not going to meet me.
Because you're ashamed of what you look
like. Because of your looks. It's as
simple as that.
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. I will do. I will do.
I will do. Yeah. I will do. And
nothing's going to happen. Nothing's
going to happen, bro. Nothing's going to
happen. Not one thing's going to happen.
Simple as that, lad.
And there we go. LJ's followers calling
me a M. Yet I'm better looking than all
of them. And I don't have to s over a
woman on YouTube. Bro, it's a madness.
Fat, obese, ugly single people calling
me a m. What the [ __ ] is the world
coming to, bro? It's a madness.
[ __ ] obese, fat, ugly people. That's
That's probably still virgins. You've
all seen the way they [ __ ] go at that
autumn [ __ ] rose. It's a madness.
Yeah, bro. Tomorrow. Yeah, 100%.
And bro, yeah, 100 100%.
And you know the reason you keep talking
about LT because you know that LT is the
only one that's got got a chance of
meeting me. Yeah. Do a video tomorrow as
well. Show me you're there as well. Show
me you're there. Or join the live. No,
no, no. Just do a video and I'll be there.
Yeah. Cuz you're not going to make me go
somewhere that you're not going to be.
Simple as that. I'll do the same thing
with Smokey Be tomorrow. Actually, I'll
go live. Do you know what? No, no, no,
no, no. What I'm going to do tomorrow is
I'm going to go live. I'm going to go
live tomorrow, bro. Out and about.
That's No, no. That's exactly what I'm
going to do. So, you're not going to
talk your way out of it? Yeah. You're
not going to talk your way out of it?
No. I'm going live tomorrow and I'm out
actually. No. So, yeah. You're not going
to talk your way out of it? [snorts]
Yeah. You two are not going to talk your
way out of it if he agrees to it. Yeah.
[ __ ] this [ __ ] bro. And I'm literally
going to laugh in your face. Laugh right
up in your face. Yeah, that's what I'm
going to do, bro. That's what exactly
what I'm going to do.
Yeah, I'm going to laugh in your face
and I'm not going to stop. And we'll see
what you're about, bro. We see what
you're about. Yeah. This isn't no four,
five years ago, bro. Stop living in the
past. Yeah, bro. I will be live
tomorrow. I will be live tomorrow, lad.
Simple. I will be live tomorrow. All
right. Can someone get this smokey be on
this channel, please? Yeah, I'm going to
be going live tomorrow, bro. Yeah, I'll
be going live tomorrow anyways, lad.
Yeah, can someone get this smokey be on
this channel as well? I don't want this
little [ __ ] getting out of it, right?
Because I'm going to deal with these two
tomorrow, bro. And then I'm going to
deal with Joe next week. Simple, bro.
Bro, I literally went on Bro, listen.
Yeah. No, I'm not Jo. Like, listen.
Stephen Hour, bro. I literally ordered
some food. Yeah. I went on Lord Jay's
and bro this [ __ ] bro listen Smokey B
come and meet me tomorrow and I'll show
you the special needs one I will show
you the special Irishman I will show
everyone what you're all about listen
bro listen to what I'm saying bro I went
on their I went on the channel Steven
Howard this guy is talking about me non-stop
this [ __ ] Joe he needs to come out as
gay bro he's a gay boy I told you he's
gay he's just like his friend. Bro,
everyone's commenting normally, bro.
Everybody is commenting normally. Yeah,
every single person is commenting
normally. And then you see this gay boy
talking about me.
What the [ __ ] bro? Every single comment
was about me, lad.
Simple. Every single comment was about
me, bro. He is a gay boy. He's just like
his boyfriend that he sucks off. I told
you, bro. He is just like his boyfriend
that he sucks off every day. And then
you know what he was trying to say, Mr.
B? Yeah. I'm going to Nottingham to meet
Charlie. I'm not meeting Charlie. I
don't even talk to Charlie. And Charlie
is not my boyfriend. I don't suck
someone's dick every time they get
called a virgin like you. You're the one
with a boyfriend. You're com you're
constantly liking these comments cuz
you're both a pair of gay boys. And
trust me, bro, Nottingham's going to be
even worse. Um, Grezy, it's going to be
even worse, bro. Yeah. Yeah. Simple,
bro. Yeah, it's as simple as that. This
I'm going to, bro. Steven Alvin, listen,
bro. Yeah, I'm telling you exactly why.
And and you're going to make me right on
this thing. I've I've I've looked up the
distance. Yeah. I'm traveling more than
he is traveling. So when I go to
Nottingham, bro, I'm 150 mi away. He's
73 miles away. That's fair, bro. That is
literally literally fair. Yeah, that is
fair, bro. And the thing is, he's not
going to meet me, bro. Trust me, he's
not. And he's not going to meet you me
not because of why you think he's not
going to meet he's not going to meet me
you know just like Jimmy Jazz is never
going to meet anyone but they're not
going to meet you not because the
reasons why it's because they're ugly
they're ugly fat people that are on here
Steven Howard that's why they're not
going to meet you not because well they
are probably scared as well but that's
not the main reason think about it bro
these people turn up to a fight yeah
their face gets shown up what are they
going to do come here and talk about
people every day again after their face
has been out there. No way, bro.
That's one of the reasons. No, but bro,
I'm going to Nottingham. No, no, no. I'm
going to Nottingham. I am going to Nottingham, bro.
Because I am going to Nottingham. I've
said this and I am going tomorrow to
meet the Smokeoky B if he says. And
that's it, bro. I'm not doing it
anymore. Simple. No way, bro.
I want to meet poverty Joe with a 200lb
phone. I want to show everyone how obese
he is, bro. He's a He's another Jamie Thompson.
He's another Jamie Thompson, bro. No one
cares about Prime. This is 2026, lad.
Jimmy, this is 2026. No one cares about
four or five years ago, lad. You're a
[ __ ] waster that will never beat no
one, you little gay boy. And I heard
that you live in West London as well.
Hey, bro. Hey, Steven Howard. odds on
poverty eyed Joe with the 200 pound
phone showing up. I don't think so, lad.
I don't think so. I don't think the
obese poverty man is going to and the
balls to turn up, mate. What do you
think? He's like his boyfriend. They
resemble each other so much,
don't they, bro? He's just like his boyfriend.
Oh, he's like his boyfriend. He's not
going to show up, bro.
These wasters are never going to [ __ ]
listen. Tell this guy to meet to to to
meet me anywhere in London tomorrow,
bro. Smokey, you didn't tell me nothing.
Join the I'm I'm on his chat as I'm live
now. Come and join the hangouts. Yeah.
And let's arrange it. Come on.
He will not show up, bro. Because
they're ashamed of what they look like.
Steven, bro, do not re Bro, listen. Do
you not realize Yeah. why they do this?
It's cuz they're ugly. They're fat. They
got no one. This is all they've got in
this YouTube. Jo is a closeted gay,
right? He has to make up stories that
he's got a wife and better. But in all
fairness, he is a closeted homosexual.
That's why he talks about me every
single day because he's a little gay
boy. And the sooner he comes out, bro,
the better. You know, if a lot of these
I said this to my mom earlier, if a lot
of these people in this community come
out, it would be uh it would be it would
literally be Yeah. The world would be a
better place. Yeah. You're trying to
join, but it's not letting me add you.
Yeah. Here you are, bro.
Right. Can you hear me? Yeah. >> Hello.
>> Can't hear the [ __ ]
>> Yeah. No self projectors. Bye-bye.
>> I can't hear this [ __ ] bro. my [ __ ] phone.
>> Can anyone hear? I can't hear him, lad.
>> I can't hear him. One second. Stay.
Don't leave. One second. I'm coming
back. Don't leave.
>> What do you mean? Yeah. Yeah. I can't
[ __ ] hear the [ __ ] you stupid
bastard. One second. Don't leave. I'm coming back. Hello. Nah,
>> I can't hear, bro.
>> One second. Let me reset my phone. Don't
leave, bro. Do not leave. I'm not
letting you get away with this buff. No
way. One second. One second. Let me
reset my phone. 2 seconds. Don't leave.
Do not leave.
>> [clears throat]
>> Right. Can you hear me? Yeah. Hello.
I can't hear, bro. What the [ __ ] man?
One second. Maybe it's my settings or something. Nah.
Why is this not working? He's not talking.
What the [ __ ] bro?
[sighs and gasps]
Seriously, bro. I can't hear anything. Is it? No.
Why is this not working, bro? Right.
Try and join join again.
Try and join. Okay. Yeah. You can hear
me now. Yeah.
Yeah. I can hear your mic now. What you saying? Come on. Yo,
>> we know you're there cuz I can hear your mic crackling. >> Hello.
>> Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah. Can you hear me? Yeah.
>> Oh, you idiot.
Come on. Nah, he's not going to p me, I don't think.
Come on. We know you're there, man. We
Oh, you little fanny. Oh, you little
fanny. What you going to do? Start going
crying to [ __ ] LT now. Come on, man.
All I'm all I want you to do is come and
meet me tomorrow in London, bro. You
know, all I want you to do is come and
meet me tomorrow in London.
I just want you to come and meet me in
London tomorrow, man, and see what
you've got to say face to face. Come on.
You know what's so hard? You got a lot
to say, bro. Come on now, man. Don't
start backing out. You want Peter
Belly's Oh, you know what I'm saying?
You know, you want you want some
attention, bro. Come on. You got some
attention. You got Peter Belly's attention now.
A shame Joe It's a shame Joe F can't
come in, but he's scared of talking, so
I mean, he's scared to talk, so you know.
Oh, why is he not letting me put the link up?
Yeah. What the [ __ ] Why are you leaving?
Sad bastard, bro.
I was getting excited, man. No.
Two poverty Joe with a 200 phone.
[sighs and gasps]
Don't you worry about the past, Jake.
You'll be meeting me tomorrow, won't
you? You don't need to worry about the past.
>> Yeah. Really, uncle?
Really? That's not nice, man. To call me that, lad.
Because I'm pretty sure you are the ones
that are handicapped. You are the ones
that are sat on YouTube for 10 years
repeating the same [ __ ]
I don't know, man. I'd say that you
people are pretty disabled.
You are the ones that are sat on YouTube
every day repeating yourself for 10
years. I don't know, man. I'd say that
you are the disabled ones, but I don't
know, man. Who
who knows, eh? I would say for people in
their 30s and 40s to sit on a community
for 10 years being wasters every day,
I'd say they got some mad disability. To
be fair, lad. Yeah, I will be. I will
be. Why is this guy not joining?
[ __ ] bro. Absolute [ __ ] Jake can't
stay away from here. Jimmy Jazz, you're
on here literally every day. You can't
take a day off of YouTube. Yeah.
Yeah. You're you're literally on it
every day more than probably most people.
And you people don't bully when you
bully yourselves, which is probably why
people keep coming on YouTube because it
shows how bad your bullying attempts
actually are, lad.
Well, this Smokey B join and he backed out.
You people are such wasters, man. It's
it's it's it's so bad.
You're actually such wasters. Madness.
Yeah. Am I, bro? Like I said, this is
not four or five years ago, lad. You're
living in the past, not me. You're
living in the past, not me, lad.
Oh, here we go. Trying to join it. One second.
One second. It takes Okay, here we go. Hello.
>> Yeah. Can you hear me?
>> Yeah, I can hear you.
>> Yeah. Let's meet up tomorrow, man.
You've got a lot of [ __ ] to say on this
large, bro. I was I was watching what
you were saying.
>> Listen, you want to meet tomorrow? What
day is tomorrow?
>> What day is tomorrow? Thursday.
>> Yeah, exactly. People like me work.
>> Okay. So, okay. Let's Let's Okay, I'll
meet you on Sunday then. Is that better for you?
>> Yeah. Yeah. Perfect.
>> Yeah. Meet me. We'll meet anywhere in London. Yeah.
>> Why London? You come on. Why London?
Because Because that's it's fair that
way. [clears throat]
>> No, he's fair,
>> bro. I will knock the [ __ ] out of you.
>> Meet me anywhere in London, bro. And you
know what I'm going to do, bro? I'm tell
I'm tell you what I'm going to do. I'm
going to humiliate you in your face. I'm
going to show everyone what you look
like. That's what I'm going to do. I'm
going to show everyone what you look like.
>> I will, bro. I'm going to show everyone
how fat and ugly you are. Look, he's
left. [laughter] He knows, bro. He's a
[ __ ] He's a [ __ ] [ __ ] bro.
He is a [ __ ] [ __ ] Why are you
leaving? What the [ __ ]
bro? Come on now. Yeah. Is your phone
[ __ ] up or something? You know, you
talk about people being skinn, but how
many times have you lagged out? Come on, bro.
One second. Let me put the lip back. Why
are you leaving, bro? Come on. People
like me work. Okay. Yeah, fair enough.
I'll meet you Sunday then. I didn't kick
you out, you [ __ ] [ __ ] Why would I
kick you out when I'm [ __ ] trying to
meet you? Don't start this [ __ ]
again. No one kicked you out. Come on.
No, it's your stupid [ __ ] phone that
[ __ ] kicked you out. Get a decent
phone, you [ __ ] [ __ ]
>> Here we go. No one kicked you out, you [ __ ] idiot.
>> You kicked me out, you tramping
16 Pro Max, you dirty Trump [ __ ] What a
>> So why do you keep [ __ ]
disconnecting, you [ __ ] stupid bastard, huh?
>> You must be a [ __ ] piss signal. And you're [ __ ]
>> Bro, I've got Wi-Fi. I've got a better
phone than you. Look, he's left again.
Look, he's left again. Why you keep
leaving, you [ __ ] [ __ ] Stop leaving.
Come on, bro. Stop leaving. And don't
try and say I'm kicking you cuz no one's
kicking you. I'm trying to meet So, you
want to meet Sunday? Yeah. >> Yo.
>> Yeah. Look, look. Now he's playing
stupid again, bro. Let's meet Sunday.
Come on. [clears throat]
>> Come on, man.
>> Come on. Meet meet me. Meet me Sunday. Come on,
>> PJ that [ __ ]
>> Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
>> Yeah. Yeah. One.
>> Yeah. I got him here on the on the voice
call. He said he wanted to meet me for a
fight on Sunday.
>> You have to speak to him. >> Yeah.
>> Yeah. Come anywhere in London, man.
Anywhere in London. Come on. And you can
go cry to LT as well. You can go crying
to LT as well because we know you like doing that.
>> Really ugly.
>> Go say
>> fat [ __ ] ugly. [laughter]
>> No one cares about your fat ugly business, bro.
>> Bro, you just told her to say that. Oh,
how about this, Smokey? How about this?
Is that Is that your wife? Is that your
>> I'll knock you and your wife out. How
about that one?
>> What you say? Say it to him.
>> Get a life.
>> Bro, I'm better looking than your Bro,
I've got a life. Your ugly [ __ ] ass
keeps talking about me every day. You ugly slag.
>> He really does, man. He buys Lego,
>> mate. I'm better looking than your ugly
gay. I've got something to say about
your husband as well. He's a closeted
gay, by the way. He's not telling
[laughter] you cuz he doesn't know how
to come out. You stupid little slag.
>> What' you say?
>> You stupid little [ __ ] slag. It's a
good thing you don't have kids to be
honest, Smokeoky Bee, because two uglies
make ugly. So your kids would be ugly
and I'm meeting you Sunday and I'll say
it to your face.
>> I will say it to your face. You stupid
Irish bastard. Bro, you can listen. On
Sunday, I'm going to send you back to
where you come from.
>> And I got one of your birds and I
married her. Hey,
>> you say what?
>> I said I come to your country and I
stole one of your birds and I
>> stole one of my birds. You stole a fat
ugly bun that no one else wants. A
little slag that can't have kids. Why do
you think you ain't got kids, bro? Cuz
she can't have kids. No one wants to
wash up. Bro, listen. How about this?
You and your wife. You remember you said
that he was going to be your wife. Do
you know how many Irish women I've been
with? [laughter] Do you know how many
Listen, do you remember I told you
before when I mentioned
>> I've had more Irish women than you've
had actual women? You [ __ ] stupid fat
[ __ ] Backing out and meeting me, bro.
Backing out of meeting me. Come on, man.
>> Come on. Let's meet Sunday then. Come
on. I will meet you. Bring your ugly
wife as well. I'll shove a camera in her
face as well. I'll shove a camera in her face.
>> Simple, bro. I want to meet you. I've
been trying to meet you.
>> You have not been trying to meet me, PJ.
>> I've been trying to meet you, you fat
bastard. How many times now?
>> Never ever once came to me.
>> I've never You were supposed to come on
my door, you stupid bastard. And then
you started editing the [ __ ] post.
>> You haven't got [ __ ] the bus fair to
get to the end. You edited the post, you
stupid skint [ __ ] dirty bastard.
Everyone knows that you [ __ ] edited
the post. Anyways, I'll meet you Sunday,
man. It's not a problem. Fine.
>> Okay, so between the middle between me
and you would be Watford.
>> Watford? No, you come to London.
>> Why can't you come to London?
>> I'm I'm not I'm not near anywhere in
London anymore. Why can't you meet me in London?
>> The middle between me and
>> you're half an hour away from London.
>> No, I'm not. You [ __ ]
>> I'm going to wear the Spider-Man
t-shirt. Not the Simpsons t-shirt. I'm
going to I'm going to wear the
Spider-Man t-shirt. No, it isn't. What?
Big stupid bastard. Just come to London.
>> Where do you live?
>> Why don't you just come to London?
Watford's 20 minutes away from London.
Why do you come to London?
>> You live in Rumford
>> and you can call anywhere near that.
>> Huh? Yeah, that's why I said London, you stupid bastard.
>> I don't live anywhere.
>> It's going to take me about half an hour
to get into London, you stupid [ __ ]
>> Yeah, it would take me about 1 hour to
get to London.
>> No, how is it going to take you 1 hour?
You said you lived near Milton Kees.
It's half an hour on a train. You
[ __ ] idiot. Mate, are you forgetting?
I'm I'm more well traveled than you. I
know these things.
>> Mitch, you are a [ __ ] [ __ ] You,
>> bro. I'm more wellraveled than you. I
know these things. Do you know how many
times I've been to [ __ ] this place,
that place, this place, that place? Come on, man.
>> You're more wellraveled than someone
who's from [ __ ] Northern Ireland and
lives in England. Yeah, suck my dick, BJ.
>> Northern Ireland, man. [laughter] What
is that? What's that supposed to mean,
you [ __ ] idiot,
>> man? Just meet me Sunday and bring your
wife. Come on.
>> You got the [ __ ] plane to Scotland,
you [ __ ] [ __ ]
>> Yeah, I got a plane to Scotland and that
makes me a [ __ ]
>> Meet me Sunday. I want to show everyone
how ugly you are as well. I want to make an example.
>> I want to show what you dregs look like.
I already done it with Jamie Thompson,
bro. I'm going to do it with you as well.
>> You can try. You [ __ ] [ __ ] Everyone's
already seen my face on here is worth anything.
>> I've not seen your face, bro. Yeah,
because you're a
>> I'm pretty sure most of the people on my
channel ain't seen your face.
>> Yeah, cuz they're all [ __ ] trolls, you [ __ ]
>> So So who's seen your face? What? Two,
three people from L J's. You said most
people have seen your face. Who?
>> Yeah, people who [ __ ] matter, PJ.
People on here who I wouldn't give two
shits to show my face to because people
on here who are decent folk.
>> People on your [ __ ] channel are trolls.
>> Well, well, my channel could be the
judge. It would be Sunday.
>> Yeah. Greavvy. Have you seen Greavves face? >> No.
>> Is Grezy on here? Is Is Grevy on here
trolling people for fights like you are?
>> No. You're the pulling people for fights
and you're going to get your head [ __ ] killed.
>> You You're not even Bro, it's not even
going to be a fight. It's It's not even >> Exactly.
>> It's not even going to be a fight, bro.
You're not even going to be able to even
go anywhere near me. That's how bad it
is. Well, we'll see what you're up about
Sunday then. Is it
>> [ __ ] homeless?
>> Yeah, I know. I I haven't shaved for two
months and guess what? I'm still better
looking than you. So, WHAT DOES THAT SAY
ABOUT YOUR LOOK?
>> YEAH, EXACTLY. Have you Have you seen me?
>> Am I Bro, I will be seeing you on Sunday.
>> Yeah, there you go. Suck my dick.
>> And And you're going to be uglier than
me. I bet. I'm going to put a bet on it
as well. I'm going to put a bet on it as
well. I'm going to put a bet on your fat ugly.
>> I'm going to put a bet on your fat and
ugly just like your boyfriend. You're
all the same, bro. You're all the same.
>> You are one [ __ ] serious. you something.
>> Yeah, you can say to my face on Sunday,
bring your [ __ ] stupid wife as well
and I tell her about herself in front of
you. I'll do it in front.
>> I'll do it in front of you. Like, it's
going to be that bad that I only want to
do it in front of you. No one else. >> Yeah.
>> Okay. Yeah. Okay. So, that's Yeah, I
will. I will.
>> Yeah. Okay. Okay. So, no worries.
>> Sunday. Yeah. Sunday.
>> So, you got to you're going to come to
London Sunday? Yeah. >> 100%.
>> You're coming to London? Yeah.
>> I'll be in North London on Sunday.
>> Just go. Yeah. Fine. That's fine.
Anywhere in London. Yeah. Fine. I know
exactly where. Okay.
>> And you can cry to your little boyfriend
LT as well because I'm not scared of him
either like you are. So you can also cry
to your boyfriend LT whilst you're at it.
>> I don't give a [ __ ] mate. You understand?
>> Anything? I won't post anything until afterwards.
>> You won't what?
>> I won't post anything until afterwards.
>> Okay, that's fine. That's fine.
>> I won't post before and let you know
exactly where I'm going to be.
>> That's fine. That's completely fine.
That's completely fine. And don't
forget, I'm going to be live as well. So
when you do that, I'm also going to be live. [laughter]
>> So you're not going to get out of it, mate.
>> Then why why would I get two [ __ ] what
you're going to do,
>> bro? You're just You're just simply not
going to show up. Simple. It's just not
going to happen.
>> That's fine. That's fine. I'll go live.
You go live. I'll tell
>> That's fine. That is fine. I'm I'm all
for it. I'm literally all for it.
>> I'll be there on Sunday. You better be
there. If you're not there, delete your YouTube.
>> Yeah, man. I mean, you should have
deleted your YouTube and you didn't come
on my door and you pussied out, but you know,
>> you're still on there talking [ __ ]
>> So, it's funny you should mention people.
This This one's off the cards. The last one.
>> No, it's not off the cards. You You
edited your post. You said that you was
going to come on my door. Anyways, it
doesn't matter because I'll be seeing
you Sunday. [clears throat]
>> Doesn't matter. Yeah, exactly. Sunday.
You don't need to go to Nottingham. You
don't need to go [ __ ] trying to meet.
>> No, I'm going to Nottingham for Joanne.
That's not Oh, that's another thing,
right? You say that you're well traveled. Yeah. >> Yeah.
>> Listen, you said that you're well
traveled. I saw a comment of yours.
Yeah. You said that. Oh, um, so I'm
going to go I can go to Nottingham, but
I can't stop off at Milton Ke. Uh,
Notting Milton Kees ain't on the way to
[ __ ] Nottingham. You stupid [ __ ] idiot.
>> How much you know? It's because Milton
Kees is the most [ __ ] idiot. Milton
is about 100 miles away, you [ __ ]
stupid bastard. It's a complete different way.
>> No, it's because [ __ ] Milton Kees is
30 odd miles away from you, you
[ __ ] And 100 miles away from you.
>> It's a complete different [ __ ] route,
you [ __ ] idiot. So, how about you?
>> You are. You are a complete [ __ ]
aren't you, PJ?
>> That's nice, bro. You can say it to my
face on Sunday, can't you?
>> I won't say anything to your [ __ ]
face and keep your head in your smell.
>> Yeah. Yeah. No chance some [ __ ] dirty
Irish [ __ ] is going to [ __ ] beat me,
bro. Not a chance in [clears throat] [ __ ] hell.
>> Not a [ __ ] chance in hell, bro.
>> Ain't no [ __ ] man like you ever had a
[ __ ] fight with me.
>> Yeah. Well, well, we'll see in it.
>> Think about it, bro. You're the one that
knows where I live and you ain't done [ __ ]
>> Think about it. How much talking have
you done here? How much talking have you
>> You would be leaving in a [ __ ]
ambulance, mate. So, just how
>> How much talking have you done?
>> Show up. Make sure you show up.
>> I will be showing up. I will be showing
Yeah, I will be showing up, lad.
>> You do a lot of talking, but we know
you're not about that life. We know that
you're not about that life, bro.
>> That's absolutely fine
>> because you talk a lot of [ __ ] You said
that you was coming on my door. So, do
you think that anyone's going to believe
that you're going to show up? I'll be
live on Sunday. I'll be there.
>> Do you think I give a [ __ ] what anybody says?
>> I give a [ __ ] what anybody thinks. I'm
not on here desperate for attention like
you. But if you want,
>> you're just sat on YouTube all day,
every day. It
>> Yeah, every every day. Have you seen you
on here every day? You smelly camp.
>> You're on here every day, mate. We saw
you every day on the Christmas period
>> on Oh, on the Christmas period when I
wasn't on here for about a month.
>> You was on here, man. You was on here.
>> You [ __ ] full of [ __ ] Don't try to
call me [ __ ] man, you [ __ ]
>> So, look, there's two of them and you
still can't beat me. Two [ __ ] Irish
mons and they still can't beat me.
>> PJ, if you fill this guy in tomorrow
while we are on Sunday as well.
>> We're not [clears throat] meeting
tomorrow. We're meeting Sunday.
>> No. Oh, this guy on YouTube. Yeah. Oh,
LJ, you're not going to go anywhere,
bro. Shut up. If you fill this guy in
tomorrow, I'll be here on Sunday as well.
>> You're not going anywhere Sunday. You're
not about that life.
>> So, we'll see this guy on tomorrow.
>> That life6,
>> bro. It's 2026 now. Who are you trying to fool?
>> Are you fating this guy tomorrow or now?
>> Yeah, I'm meeting him tomorrow. Yes.
>> I'm telling you now. Yeah. If you fail
this guy in tomorrow, I'll come on
Sunday as well. You're not going anywhere.
>> Yeah, I'll be on Sunday.
>> It's 2026, LJ. You're not falling nowhere.
>> They weren't for you. Wait, you're on
here calling people out and it's 2026. >> 2026.
>> Yeah. And you're calling people out
>> and you're not about that life. [laughter]
>> And PJ's going to get filled in about 3 days.
>> It's 26 and PJ's calling people out.
Well, again, PJ, if you fill this guy in tomorrow,
>> I'm calling people [ __ ] 24/7 to prove
that I'll be there on Sunday. Yeah, I've
been talking [ __ ] about you for years
about nothing again. How long have you
been saying to come back here? It's
giving everyone a headache.
>> DJ, you told me last month that if you
had my address, you would come to it.
>> You're giving everyone a headache.
You're not allowed.
>> I give you the address and you didn't come.
>> Listen, listen, listen, listen. Why
don't you come tomorrow?
>> Okay. Okay. Why don't you come tomorrow then?
>> PJ, you No. One second. One second. One
second. Why can't you come tomorrow?
>> Cuz I'm I have plans tomorrow.
>> No, no, no. Okay. Why don't you come Friday then?
>> No. again. If you fill this guy in
tomorrow, I'll be doing something.
>> You're just playing stupid games again.
Oh my god.
>> What games? You're meeting this guy
tomorrow for a fight, aren't you?
>> No, you're not going anywhere. You're
scared of flying. You're scared of
London. You're scared of London. You're
not going anywhere.
>> What games? You're fighting a guy
tomorrow. If you win, I'll be there on Sunday.
>> [ __ ] God. You're not about anything.
>> What? What do you mean? Nobody's about
anything. You have to fight this guy
tomorrow anyway. I'm telling you and I'm doing that
when I'll be there on Sunday.
>> Okay. Okay. Yeah. And what? Okay. And
what if he What if he doesn't turn up?
>> Well, what do you mean?
>> I'll knock you in.
>> One second. One second. If he doesn't
turn up on Sunday, are you going to come Sunday then?
>> No. But you have to f you have to beat
the guy tomorrow.
>> No. No. That's not fair because he might
not turn up.
>> Well, then if I if either way, Smoke is
turning up on Sunday. >> Exactly. >> Okay.
>> No, no, no, no. So if you go on Saturday
Wait, if you go and fight this guy
tomorrow or don't turn up [laughter]
one second, one second. Are you free on Saturday?
>> Wait, who mean?
>> Oh, so you're only free on Sundays?
>> Yeah. No, I'm only going if you
>> I mean I mean you can still come on Sunday.
>> Where? Wait, where are you meeting this guy tomorrow?
>> I'm meeting him in um Hibbury Park.
>> Right. So you'll be live in Hibbury Park. >> Yeah.
>> Right. Okay. So, if you go live tomorrow
and he's not there, then Smokey Bale
will still fight you on Sunday. If you
fight this guy tomorrow and win, then
I'll come. I'll tell you what, if you
fight this guy tomorrow and win, I'll
come on Saturday.
>> Okay. But but if he doesn't show up, you
won't come on Saturday.
>> No. If he doesn't turn up, he doesn't
turn up. [laughter]
>> Cuz I don't think I don't think it
doesn't even make sense.
>> I think that you had that account set
up. That was someone set up to make you look
>> You're giving me a headache. You're so
[ __ ] You're making me lose brain cells.
>> Okay. That's all right.
And another thing and another thing.
Another thing as well. Can you stop
copying my videos as well?
>> What videos?
>> When I was doing the unboxing, you
[ __ ] started unboxing trainers and
[ __ ] showing the [ __ ] air fryer.
You copycat. Stop copying me. That's
another thing I had to say.
>> Here comes your autism again.
>> No, I'm just here autism again. Yeah.
>> Yeah. Here comes Here comes your autism
again. I went I went through all of your
videos and you don't have any other unboxing video.
>> I thought you weren't subbed to my channel.
>> You don't have any [laughter]
>> I thought you weren't sub to my channel.
Why are you looking for it?
>> This is a
nice See, just a little bit of pressure
put on and now his autism.
>> Yeah, bro. I'm so nervous. I know, man.
>> What time are you meeting this guy tomorrow?
>> Panic attack.
>> Well, you have we know you have I'm
going to have a really bad panic attack.
I'm going to start biting my teeth in
the airport, bro. Like the one on the
put my hood over my head.
>> Like like the one on the shelves or the
one outside the airport when you're
supposed to go to Switzerland, you know. >> Yeah.
>> There. What time you meeting this guy tomorrow?
>> Uh we're meeting at 6.
>> 6 tomorrow night. >> Yeah.
>> In a dark part. >> Yeah.
>> Part of whistle.
>> Won't have no toenails left by Sunday.
What the [ __ ]
>> Yeah. Yeah, I am. I'm going to be your
>> You going to leave at 6 p.m. or you're
going to be at the park at 6 p.m.?
>> I'm I'm going to go live in Hibbury Park. Yeah.
>> At 6:00 p.m. >> Yeah.
>> And it's going to be another no show
because nothing will ever change with
this community and you people
then you're no tomorrow's going to
change you people here.
>> Well, again, that's okay. If no one
shows, then Smokey B fills you in Sunday.
>> If the guy turns up,
>> you're not going to feel me. If the guy
turns up and you fill this guy in, then
I'm going to then I'll turn up and I'll
fill you in.
>> I'll give you an elbow.
>> Yeah. Here comes his autism again. I'll give you
>> You can ask Banger here. He's seen me
and he's seen my misses. So ask questions. [laughter]
>> That's good, bro. And I'll be seeing you
in your Mes another another person who
has a misses and PJ's never had a girlfriend.
>> But guess what? But guess what? We've
never seen you with a bird. We've never
>> Why the [ __ ] would I bring women on? You
should tell everyone on YouTube that
would happen on so
>> Yeah, of course I was.
>> Yeah, because you don't get women, bro.
You got no women and you're trying to
talk about me. At least I've been with women, bro.
>> You want to talk? You want to talk about
your What about when me and Axel used to
laugh at the video on the train?
>> You can't get women. You have to beg with
>> What about me? Coldroach.
>> You used to laugh at the
>> Why have we never seen approach? Why the
[ __ ] would they do a call the Bronx on
YouTube? Anxiety doesn't allow it.
That's why you have And why do you keep that? [laughter]
>> Why would they do a calls
>> on YouTube? If you get all If you get
all of these women, why do you beg women
on the internet? Tell us all.
>> Who do I beg? >> Autumn Ox.
Never begged on him.
>> What did you say?
>> Me and him. Nobody.
>> I'm not talking about you, Smoker. I'm
talking about L. Nobody. When did I beg
>> Autumn? Bro, we have seen you on
Autumn's channel along with like Money
Mike. You You all do it.
>> [ __ ] do it.
>> PJ. Okay. There's your autism again.
>> Yeah. Autism again. Yeah. Okay.
>> PJ. PJ. Here you go. Autism again. Yeah. Okay, mate.
>> PJ laughs when I put pictures up of you
on my channel. Autumn laughs at you,
>> bro. I don't give a [ __ ] about that ugly
woman that you
giving you a terrible name. And you know
why, Logic? Because I've got a life like
you. I don't need to s like you. So you
know you respons on YouTube. I couldn't care less.
>> You're on YouTube.
>> I couldn't care less about
you have a leg. Tell her tell her to
come out and show her face without Spider-Man t-shirts.
>> No no listen listen. Tell her to come on the camera.
>> Listen. Yeah.
>> He's absolutely [ __ ] fleeced. >> Yes.
>> Auto is fat and her pictures don't. Yes,
she does use filters. Of course she uses filters, man.
>> Remember the woman? Listen, she uses
filters, bro. Remember the woman? She uses filters.
>> Yeah, Smokey. A woman a while back, he
was talking to her on WhatsApp or
something and he was using an old
picture of him and then she seen him in real life.
>> Have you seen self rejection, bro?
Listen, you're foureyed ginger that
can't get women. No self rejection on
this channel recently,
>> bro. I've never I've never had to beg a
woman on YouTube like you, bro. I can
safely say that.
>> Sending actual videos of you crying.
>> I've never had to beg a woman like you.
>> Crying over a woman.
>> That says a lot about She
>> That says a lot about you.
>> He was crying over a woman that he never slept with.
>> CJ, it's not triggering you. It's true.
It's not It's not
phone sex with women.
>> PJ, you cried, bro. You cried on. You
cried on the phone. You sent actual
video of you in tears on a train laughing.
>> Just stop it, Lord J. Embarrassing now.
You're You're embarrassing yourself now.
>> TJ, you were crying.
Ever seen L J with a with a woman?
>> Why would I bring a woman on here? It's mom.
>> Oh, one second. One second. One second.
Oh, here we go. The Mongs are coming.
Sorry, I've got to kick these two cuz I
need to talk to this guy now. One sec.
Prime, how we doing, man?
Long time. Long time.
It's nice. It's good to have you back.
Sorry, man. I've had to kick them
because this guy wants to come in. It's
It's good to have you back, man.
How we doing?
Come on. It's good. It's good to have
you back. Oh, and now he's left. Oh,
gosh darn it. What is it with these bloody people?
Now he's left. Right, we'll let this
[ __ ] wanker back in.
I'll be wearing my Spider-Man t-shirt on
Sunday. How's it feel that you're going
to lose a fight against someone wearing
a Spider-Man t-shirt?
>> Well, I won't be losing a fight against
[laughter] you. [ __ ]
>> How's that going to make you feel?
It's like one joined and then the other
the others follow. You you joined and
then LJ joined and then Prime joined. If
I if I didn't know any better, I'd say
you're a bunch of copycats.
>> Three people that have absolutely owned you.
>> I'd say that you're a bunch of copycats.
>> Three people that have absolutely owned
you in life.
>> Own. Really, bro? Really? Really? That's That's nice.
>> Being bullied and getting the attention.
>> So So he had to kick you for a sexy sympos
Oh, I know another woman that you beg.
That Sarah like a horse.
>> Calm down.
>> You begging her to suck your [ __ ]
>> Yours autism was bad. Like PJ was you
was begging you begging her to suck your [ __ ]
>> Yeah. I' never begged women. I've never
begged a woman in my life. L's been on
YouTube. We've never seen him with a
woman with you. PJ doesn't know PJ
doesn't know how to interact with women
and he doesn't understand men and women
talk like that before.
He doesn't understand that. So he
doesn't cuz he's never had a woman
communicate with you. We've never seen
you with a woman. PJ's
with women, but we've never seen you
with a woman.
>> PJ, you want to deal again? Listen, I
know you're autist
or your man is going to be watching you.
Listen, relax. PJ says he's going to
throw Smokey Bean in a Spider-Man
t-shirt. I think that's because that's
the only bit of clothing he has now that
fits him. If PJ puts on a stone,
>> if PJ puts on one of his Stone Island
jumpers right now and it fits him, I'll come tomorrow.
>> Lj, you're obese. Do not talk about you
arely obese. Do not even try to talk
about you cannot lose weight to save
your life. You're not even
with you and other obese.
PJ 100. You're not even fat.
>> Put a jumper on. PJ,
>> you're not even fat. Obese.
>> Okay. Well, PJ, put one of your obese.
>> Are you going to put on diets are you
going to keep going on before you get
the point? You're meant to be a fat
[ __ ] It's in your genetics. You lost
the genetic lottery. Four eyes, ginger
beard, disabled bat. Relax.
>> [ __ ] fat as you just lost the genetic
lottery. Calm down.
>> How many diets are you going to go on,
>> PJ? Are you going to ignore what I said?
Are you going to put How many diets are
you going to go on,
>> PJ? It doesn't matter. Are you going to
put a jumper on? Then I'll come.
>> I don't need to put any jumper on. I
don't need to prove anything to some morbidly obese.
>> Don't fit your morbidly obese.
>> You obese.
>> You want me You You want What the [ __ ]
Why did you leave?
>> What the [ __ ] Stick one of your
>> So would you would you say that you're
overweight, Smokeoky B?
>> Nope. Stick one of your Stone Island
jumpers on. Take a photo.
>> I don't I don't Bro, listen. You people
are fat. You're not going to even
project your weight onto me, bro. That's
not what's going to happen. You're going
to see me. You're going to see me on
Sunday, aren't you?
>> Exactly. And you'll see.
>> And we're going to see who the fat one
is. We're going to see who the obese one
is. And it's going to be you people.
>> Well, we'll see.
>> Yeah, we will see. Bro, you you I bet
you look like that Jamie Thompson, don't you?
>> You reckon?
>> Yeah, 100%. >> Okay.
>> Have you seen him? What he looks like?
>> Of course I've seen him.
>> What do you think of him? Does he look a
bit like you?
>> He still He still has a better life than you. [laughter]
>> He has a better life than me. Yeah. Sat
on YouTube stalking someone every day
for 4 years. I'm well jealous, mate. I'm
well jealous. I'm so jealous, bro. You got me.
>> He has that You do realize he has that
account on you which is set up by a bot
that all I'm jealous, bro. You got me.
Damn. You got You caught me, bro. You
caught me. I'm so jealous. and he works
and he lives in a different country and
he has a
>> Bro, he he Bro, he's got he's in a
wheelchair, bro. I think he's in a wheelchair.
>> No, I think you should be in a wheelchair,
>> bro. That he is You're telling me that
[ __ ] is not in a wheelchair? >> Hello?
>> You're telling me that [ __ ] is not in a wheelchair?
>> You should be in a [ __ ] wheelchair, PJ.
>> He is in a [ __ ] wheelchair, bro. What
the [ __ ] And you're telling me that he
works? No [ __ ] way, man. If you show
up on Sunday, I'll put you in a
wheelchair. How about that?
>> Okay. Well, you won't. And I'm going to
be wearing my Spider-Man t-shirt.
>> [ __ ] There you go. You're absolutely
primed for the wheelchair.
>> I'm going to I'm going to wear the Spider-Man t-shirt.
>> Spider-Man t-shirt. Look. Face looks
like an absolute [ __ ] I'll put you
in a wheelchair.
>> Good to be all the way.
>> Yeah, bro. You can come. Yeah.
You're good to come if you want. I'm
eating this. I'm I'm eating this. Um,
I'm eating this uh
>> meeting on Sunday. So, you're more than
welcome to come. As they say, the more the merrier.
>> Exactly. You're meeting
>> because I know you're going to try and
get involved anyway. So, yeah, you can
come, man. That's fine, man. I don't mind.
>> Right, you [ __ ] I'm away here cuz
the MS wants me. I'll be back.
>> Yeah, I'll see you Sunday.
There we go, man.
No, I wasn't calling him a black. That
this guy's lying to you, mate.
No, I've said everything I'm about to
say about you being a biased [ __ ]
No, definitely definitely wasn't. Yeah,
you're welcome, man. You're welcome.
You're welcome. No one called you a
black anything earlier, mate. You can
you can rewatch everything. You're not
let these people try to uh Yeah.
Anyways, why didn't you reply back to my email? Anyways, yeah.
Anyways, why didn't you reply to my email?
Huh? Cuz you know I'm right. Cuz what
could you say? There's nothing you could
say. There's [ __ ] nothing you could
say. Cuz you know I'm right. You know
you're touchy about your boyfriend being
called a virgin. Like you say that you
got this degree and all of this [ __ ]
bro. Then how comes I'm more intelligent
than you, bro? How comes I'm way more in
Bro, you couldn't even say nothing. The
only thing you could do was resort to
insulting me because you was touchy
about your boyfriend with being called a
virgin. Very touchy about your
boyfriend. Like I was saying this
earlier, bro, and I weren't even saying
this to annoy people. Some of you
generally need to come out the closet.
It will be better for your mental
health, bro. It will be better. It will
be much better for your [ __ ] mental
health. How can he be a virgin? Because
there's no proof that he's had sex and a
fat, disabled, ugly girlfriend is not
proof that someone's had sex. A [ __ ]
and being in women's beds naked is
proof. A ugly girlfriend is not proof
that someone's had sex. Someone could
suffer from erectile dysfunction.
Someone could not have a dick. You don't
know their sex life. You've never seen
them have sex. However, you've seen me
have sex, but you don't say anything
about that. So, get the [ __ ] out of
here, you biased [ __ ] A fat ugly
girlfriend is not proof. If a [ __ ] is
not proof, then a fat ugly girlfriend
that can't consent is not proof.
No, I'm saying some fat ugly girlfriend
is definitely not proof. If paying and a
blowjob's not proof, then that's not
proof. And there's nothing you can say,
LT. Simple, bro. Simple. You are touchy
about your boyfriend being called names.
You're touchy, bro. You How many times
have you come on here, LT, and you've
complained about biased people? How many
times have you complained about people
being biased? Come on. Let's have it
right here, right now. Uh, she is fat
and she definitely can't consent. And he
has not proven that he stuck his dick in
her. He has not shown no proof. I have
put a porno out there. I have shown my
dick getting sucked. I have shown proof
that can't be denied.
Come on, bro. Yeah, like I said, I'll
see you tomorrow anyways, bro. I'll see you tomorrow.
[ __ ] go mad.
You You moan about people that are
biased. Yeah. Oh, someone this person's
biased. And come on, man. Let's have it
out now. You say that you're intelligent
and you've got this degree. Yeah. A
[ __ ] isn't sex and and and a and a
disabled girlfriend isn't sex. And a
disabled girlfriend, that's not sex.
That's not sex either. A [ __ ] leads
to sex 99% of the time. Now, a fat ugly
girlfriend ain't sex. That's not sex,
though. You understand what I'm saying?
That's more sex than showing a girl that
can't consent. You understand?
You live for this [ __ ] toxicity,
mate. Well, yes it does. Yes, it [ __ ]
You can come Sunday all you want, bro.
You can come Sunday all you want.
Simple. I don't give a [ __ ] Simple as that, matey.
Sick of you biased bastards.
LT, why do you moan about biased people
when you're biased yourself?
Nah, a disabled girl that that that
can't consent is definitely not sex.
That's no proof that someone's had sex. Family,
what I've shown is proof. Being in
women's beds naked, kissing [ __ ]
that's proof. Not a disabled girlfriend.
Actual proof. I have put up actual
proof. Just like I've shown more money
than you people. Actual proof. Not a
disabled girlfriend. Actual proof. Yeah.
So that's that.
Come on LT. Where you going, bro? You
said that you've got this degree. You've
got this degree and ret.
Okay. So let's have it out, bro. Come on.
Come on. And you say that you've got
this degree and stuff.
Ah, my head's hurting, bro.
Oh, my head's hurting me. My head's
hurting me, Grezy. Ah, this is what
happens, bro. The longer you stay on this community,
the long, you know, the more you lose
brain cells. My [ __ ] poor head.
My poor [ __ ] head. >> [screaming] [snorts] >> Mhm.
Oh, Steven Howard. Oh my god, my head,
bro. Can you come here and rob my head?
Yeah, he's run away because he knows I'm
right what I'm saying about him being
biased, bro. He moans. What this guy
does? He moans about people being
biased. Oh, he hasn't turned up here.
But, bro, you're the biggest biased [ __ ] going, lad.
You know, there's literally you are you
are literally being biased. You can't
answer any of the [ __ ] I'm asking you.
You know what I'm saying? Um,
I didn't win anything. I lost both of
them and I lost 60 on roulette.
Oh, I'm done. Oh, Steven Howard, bro. I
got to say this to you now, man. Um, I'm
done with the gambling now, bro. I'm
done with even the football bets, the
ruler. I'm done with all of it. I closed
the account down.
Yeah. So, what I said yesterday was I
had a football bet and it it offered me
£36 for six. Uh6 bet returned 36. Uh,
they offered me a cash out at 36. So,
could you imagine I had 50 on it? It
would have been decent.
I'll be live tomorrow, lad.
I'll be live tomorrow, laddyy.
So, yeah, you can't moan about any of
these people, LT, bro. You're just the
same as them, Joe F, all of these
people. You deserve everything that you
got, man, about these people being
biased. And you're more than welcome to
come Sunday. I don't give a [ __ ]
Don't ever moan about these people to me
ever again, bro. You're the biggest
biased [ __ ] going.
Yeah. Come on, bro. Anything you want to
say, you can say it. We We'll have it
out, bro. I don't mind. I don't give a
[ __ ] We'll talk about the M thing. I
don't give a [ __ ] bro. Come on, bro.
Let's go. Come on. You know, simple, lad.
What's more ridiculous is saying
someone's a virgin that's literally
being in women's beds naked, shown them
having a [ __ ] having women admitted
to sleeping with them. That's more
ridic. That's more ridiculous calling
someone like that a virgin than somebody
with a girl that can't consent. I mean,
I'm pretty sure it's more ridiculous
calling someone like me a virgin. But
biased people be biased people. I mean,
you're calling someone a virgin that's
shown they're getting their dick sucked,
shown them in beds with women naked,
shown their friends with benefits
multiple times, had women admitted to
sleeping with me, and you're calling me a virgin?
I don't think so, mate. I don't think so. Yeah.
Didn't pay anything. And even if I did
pay, mate, that's more proof than
someone showing a girlfriend. That's why
you can't say anything. Cuz you know I'm
right. That's why you literally can't
[ __ ] say anything. Cuz you know I'm
[ __ ] right, bro.
You know I'm right, man. You know I'm [ __ ] right.
You know I'm bloody right, lad.
You know I'm right about that. That's
why That's why you stopped emailing me.
No, he won't be arrested because he
ain't slept with her. Cuz that's not Oh,
well, obviously he's not going to be
arrested because he's not slept with
her. He's still a virgin. He's still a
big virgin. So, obviously he hasn't been arrested
cuz he's still a virgin. He's never had
sex ever. He's literally never There's
nothing that's proved that he has ever
stuck his dick up any woman. There's no proof.
cuz he's living because that's his
carer. He's not [ __ ] her, is he?
[ __ ] hell. She can't consent to sex.
That's why he's still a virgin. And he
ain't slept with her. That's my whole
point. Because they're not [ __ ] You
went nowhere near that girl. I'm telling
you, mate. The authorities would have a
lot to say about that. The authorities
would have a lot to say about that, mate. So, yeah.
you know. No. Oh my god. She's got a
mind of a child. For [ __ ] sake. She's
got a mind of a child.
Jesus. Bloody Christ,
bro. I've already had a girlfriend and
I've had more women than you. And what
you And what you people can't stand is
people that are better looking than you,
that's got a better life than you. Oh,
I've got all my evidence to prove it.
Bro, I've already had a girlfriend and
they've never been disabled. I'm
answering every single question that
you're answering, bro.
You can't stand people that are younger
and better looking than you and had more
women than you. Better looking. That's
what you people can't stand. Listen,
Jake. Okay, let's put it this way,
right? You lame me one person that shows
their face that comes on here doing this
that's better looking than me.
Come on, bro. Tell me one person that's
better looking than me. Come on, Stephen
Howard. You tell you name me one person
on here that's more confident than me
than better looking than me. You can't.
Why is that? Why is that, lad?
I've had a girlfriend and she's never
been disabled. And bro, you're not going
to meet me now. Now Rick Mace is not
better looking than me. The guy's
[ __ ] bored. Try again. Oh [ __ ]
That's another thing. What? One sec. One
sec. You've you Oh, you do realize now
you're saying this, bro. You're you're
losing all credibility now. You're actually
Now you're actually um you're it's
actually proven that you're not going to
meet anyone now,
bro. You're losing credibility, bro.
Yeah, you're saying that we all laugh at
you. This guy's definitely not meeting
me tomorrow. I'm I'm Bro, I am sure this
guy is not meeting me tomorrow. I'm I'm
I'm putting all my money on this guy's
not meeting me tomorrow. He's not even
going to be seen tomorrow, bro. And you
know how I know he's not going to be um
Do you know how I know he's not going to meet me?
No, no, no. Rick Space is definitely not
better looking than me, bro. That guy
looks like Mr. Beams because you're
talking about you're talking about
people laughing at people. You're like
Mongey Joe. You're the same little
waster. You're not going to beat no one,
bro. People like Primeier, you actually
believe. But people like you saying we
laugh at you and this you're not meeting
no one. You're making it too obvious. O
Steven Alvin, he's making it too obvious
now, lad. When he's talking about people
not having a girlfriend and projection,
they're losing all credibility. You just
know they're not going to meet you, bro.
Who cares about what you people laugh
at? You're old, ugly wasters. Who cares
what wasters laugh at? Who cares what
little virgins that that have no life
laugh at? Bro, look at the whole world,
bro. Look, the world is mad. Look at
what's going on in the world. Do we care
about a bunch of life's rejects with
nobody laughing at anyone?
Do you think we care about a bunch of
reject fat ugly people what they laugh
at that's got no life? You think anyone
cares what a bunch of fat ugly people
laugh at? We laugh. I laugh at you. I
laugh right back at the ugly middle-ag wasters.
I laugh at I laugh at the obsessed gay
wasters. I laugh right back at you ugly
people. You little low lives with
nothing. I laugh straight back at you.
You know what I'm saying?
Simple. I look like Jamie Thompson. I
laugh at the fact that he looks like
Peter Griffin. Peter Griffin in a
wheelchair. I laugh at you ugly people.
It's not one-sided, is it, Steven Howard?
I laugh at the fact that you're on
YouTube 24/7. You beg women. You've all
got terrible looks. I laugh at you. I
laugh at you more than you could ever
laugh at me.
Trust me, bro. I laugh like Father
Christmas at you people every day. [laughter]
You know what I'm saying? I laugh at you
wasters on YouTube 24/7 obsessed with a
28-year-old. I love it, lad. I love it. I'm saying Yeah, man.
Yeah, bro. Like I said, like I said,
bro, you can write all of the comments.
It's not going to bother me because we
know what you people are. Fat, ugly
virgins. That's why it's not going to
get to me. What fat ugly virgin wasters
say has no effect to me. We know what
you are. We know your looks. We know
your life on YouTube 24/7. We can't get annoyed.
We can't get annoyed at virgins like
Uncle Andy. You're all wasters. That's
why you start talking about me every day, bro.
You're [ __ ] wasters. You're so
irrelevant to life, bro. That your
opinion doesn't even mean anything.
Think about you people. You're you're
middle-aged. You're bold. You're fat.
You're ugly. Ugly ass people.
[ __ ] middleage. No girlfriend, no
life, no money. No one cares what the
losers laugh at. No one cares what a
bunch of losers laugh at that have got
no life. Cuz I laugh right back at him.
You know what I'm saying? It's a madness.
You're actually starting to hurt my
[ __ ] brain now. Simple. Oh, Steven Howard.
My brain, lad. Oh,
these people are hurting my brain, bro.
Yeah, it doesn't matter. Do you know
what makes my day? That I'm better
looking than you and I'm not middle-aged
like you. It makes me laugh that I'm
better looking. I'm not fat. I'm not
old. I'm not ugly. I'm not virgins like
most of you people. That makes my life,
not my day. You people make me feel
better about myself. My myself. You
people make me feel better about myself.
I'm not old. I'm not bored. I'm not
ugly. I don't have to sip over women on
YouTube. You make my whole life. You
wasters make my life. And that's that's
probably why I come on here so much.
Steven Howard, to laugh at the losers
that never made it, the failures in life.
You know what I mean?
So, I'm I'm basically middle-aged.
What? 28 is middle-aged?
Really? I don't think so. I'm not sure that's true.
What the [ __ ] bro? 28 is middle age.
I love it as well, mate. I love it as well.
Yeah, you people. It It Yeah, man. You
people show what you really are, man. Honestly,
it's bad, bro. It's really, really bad.
If I'm Okay, if I'm doing So, I'm self projecting.
so why don't you come and hang out and
prove me wrong? One second, Steven
Howard. One second, mate. Everyone shout
for a second. All right, we're getting
down to business here, sad. If I'm wrong
and I'm self projecting,
come on here and put your cameras on.
One second. Oh, what is it doing?
If I'm wrong about you and I'm really
wrong about you, then you'll come on
here and put your cameras on.
Everybody shut the [ __ ] up for a minute.
Grievy, shut it. Steven Howard, shut it.
If I'm self projecting about you and
your looks and what you are, come in and
put your comers on. Stop talking. Shut
up and join. Shut up and [ __ ] join.
Shush, Grezy, Steven Howard. Shush.
If If I'm If I'm self projecting, come
on. Come on. Prove it.
Exactly. Cuz you know I'm right. You
know that you're middle-aged. You know
that you're fat. You know that you're
wasted. You know I'm better looking than
you. And that's where the jealousy comes
from. Thank you.
Thank you, mate.
Thank you, matey.
Thank you. I'll see you tomorrow, lad.
We'll see what you got to say to my
face. Why are these people so jealous of
me, Steven Howard? Every time I come on.
Yeah. I've got all of these bids people
obsessed with me. It makes my skin
crawl. Makes me feel famous.
I got a lot of people obsessed with me,
bro. Why are so many middle-aged people
obsessed with me? They need to come out the closet.
No, honestly though, bro, do you know
why I think it is with these people?
Seriously, I think Yeah. I think that
I think that they're jealous. I think
that they're um they're closeted
homosexuals. I'm being serious now. I'm
not even joking. And I also think that
they also hate themselves as well. I
think there's three reasons why they do it.
They definitely They need to come out
the closet though. Serious, bro. I I was
They seriously need to come out the closet.
Yeah. Laugh at you. What? Laugh at
someone that's younger and better
looking than you in life. I don't think
so. No, Dusty though. Seriously, bro. I
think that they're they're homosexuals.
I'm not even joking. I'm deadly serious, bro. Homosexuals.
Uh they're jealous. Um and they hate themselves.
But I think more of it is that they're
homosexuals because, bro, you know that
USA Izzy thing, bro. Let me tell you,
bro. Let me let me just bring this up
again, bro. I stopped after like a year
and I didn't do it consistently every
single day, right? I done it like
whenever I could be bothered and then I
was just like, "Oh, [ __ ] it. Just leave
them." spoke to a friend and leave them.
This is someone I met. This is someone
I've done the business with. Now, these
people haven't met me. They certainly
haven't done the business with me
because I'm not gay. But they seem to be
on here every day doing this. So, you
have to question these people's
sexualities, mate. You really really do.
Like, you really really [ __ ] do,
mate. They have been doing this for
[ __ ] years. And for someone that they
haven't met, you've got to be gay, bro.
You've literally got to be a homosexual.
Well, what what else can it be, bro?
You've got If you're if you're swearing
that you're blue in the face that you're
not jealous, then you're homosexual. So,
it's one or the other. You either love
the person or you're jealous of the
person. I still think it's a bit of both
with these people. Only because Steven
Howard, only because
um of what they've ended up looking
like, Steven Howard. It's only It's only
No, I wasn't stalking anyone for three
years. How can it be three years when I
didn't even meet her three years ago?
No, bro. How can How can it be 3 years
when I didn't even meet her 3 years ago?
It's going to be 3 years in April and I
haven't done anything for over a year.
So, how can you say I've been stalking
someone for 3 years when I haven't even
met them three years ago? Come on.
It will be three years in April.
Yeah, it's not going to be four years in
April. It's got to be three years.
Bro, bro, you people are jealous of
being in pip living with your mom.
Brother, brother, brother, brother,
brother, brother, brother, brother,
brother. And what are you people?
Middle-aged, ugly as [ __ ] don't leave
your house, ain't got no family. Yeah, I
think you are jealous of someone being
on PIP living with their mom. Yeah.
Yeah. I think middle-aged ugly bastards
that don't leave their house is jealous
of that. Yeah. Yeah. And what's your
point, bro? You are You do you not
understand what the point I'm trying to
make? You are worse than anyone you're
trying to call
you. My family hate me. My family hate
me today. Self projection, bro. You're
you're you're calling people that are
better than you. I'm going to have to do
a video on this Jo one more time. Um
Steven Howard, I'm really going to have
to put this [ __ ] Oh, you don't need to
feel sorry for me, bro. Don't need to
feel, bro. My My life could be worse. I
could be you.
I could be ugly. I could be middle-aged.
I could sat on YouTube being a waster,
bro. I could be you. I could literally
be you. Like, my life could be worse, lad.
I literally could be a middle-aged
waster with no life like you, bro. Don't
feel too sorry for me, bro.
So, um, but no, you're definitely
jealous and a homosexual. Definitely.
Definitely. I'm going to title the
video, um, uh, Steven Howard, it's time
to come out the closet.
Are you going to give it a watch,
Greavvesy? Are you going to give it a watch, lad?
You know, never had a misses, brother. I
have had a misses. Use are in your 40s
and you're still a virgin. Stop self-p
projecting. It's not going to change
what you 40year-old losers are. You can
keep projecting your life onto a
younger, better-l looking person than
you. It isn't going to ch It's not going
to change what you virgins are, lad.
It's not going to change what you
wasters are. You can say it a million
times and I'm going to title it. It's
time to come out of the closet.
Obviously, I don't need to do one to
smoke. I was going to add Smokey B in
with it, but obviously he said that he's
going to meet me and I think he's a lot
worse than Smokey B, but Smokey B said
that he's meeting me Sunday, so I don't
need to I don't need to talk about him.
And he's nowhere near as bad as this Jo.
And he's going to be seeing me Sunday,
mate. This [ __ ] is going to be seeing me
on Sunday, Greezy. And we'll see we'll
see what he's got, mate. Do you know
what? [ __ ] it. Going to pick out my
outfit now. [laughter]
I'm so mad, you know, mate. Oh, I can't
even find the light. What's going on
with me, mate?
There we go.
Oh, I got a really sore [ __ ] head, lad.
There we go. That's the top I'm going to
wear. And I'm going to wear shorts.
Okay, with you, boss.
Oh, and I'm also going to bring a judger.
Like, this is how bad it's going to be,
bro. You you you literally, man, that's
how bad it's going to be that you're
going to get defeated by someone in a
[ __ ] Spider-Man t-shirt. I'm wearing
B Simpson right now. You know,
you can't get beat by someone in a
[ __ ] Spider-Man t-shirt,
you know, with a with a figure, can you?
You can never hold it down.
I'll give you a tour when you show us
your face and you prove that you're not
fat and ugly.
You show me that you're not fat and ugly
like I know you are and then I'll start
showing you stuff.
When you show me that you're not fat,
ugly, and middle age, which you are,
then start coming to me, mate. That's
why I've got you by the gonads. We know
what you people look like. You're
[ __ ] You're so bad looking. Bad
looking people. That's why you're jealous.
You're still there, Steven Howard.
You're still there, Steven, mate.
That's not nice of you to talk about Charlie, mate.
Unworthy clock's a decent guy.
Why the [ __ ] Why is Charlie Charlie's
not my boyfriend? I haven't spoke to
Charlie in bloody ages.
What do you think it is with these
people near Steven Alberta? Do you think
it's more homosexuality
um that they hate themselves or do you
think it's jealousy or I think it's
I'm going to give a percentage. Let me
give this percentage. I think that
Nah, I think it's 50% jealousy and 50% homosexuality.
I think it's 50/50, bro. defo.
I think it's 50/50, bro. I don't think
it's full on jealousy. I also think it's
because they are they are they're
definitely homosexuals. They can't deny that, bro.
Cuz if they can stalk a man that they've
never met more than someone could stalk
a woman uh that they've done the
business with, you got to start
questioning this stuff. It's not good. It's unhealthy, you know. Yeah.
And I only say I only say it's jealousy
because of what they end up looking like
uh when they get out there when they get
you know put out there and stuff lad.
And I'm also going to say I'm also going
to put in a video to this joke. If you
are going to accuse someone of being
jealous um if you are going to um if you
are going to um tell somebody that
they're jealous at least put up real
gambling videos and stop putting money
in machines and then taking them out.
then you're liable to then start
accusing people of being jealous. Um,
which no one's jealous. We are simply
telling you what you do. Actually, at
the at the end of the day, Stephen
Howard, I gamble, bro. Well, I you know,
I've only just stopped, but I bet on the
football one in the football, played the
roulette. I know about these things,
bro. I know about these things about
what what pays out and what doesn't pay
out and stuff. And it's just it's not
believable. And I said I gave him the
chance so many times, Stephen Howard, go
live. I'm going to completely wreck this
guy in this video, bro. He's not even
going to be able to say anything back to
me. Um, so yeah, if if you if if you if
you're as good-looking as you say, why
can't you even get a date? I have had
dates. I've slept with plenty of plenty
of women. Again, self projecting.
It's not going to change what you are.
Why can't you people show your faces?
Why do you beg women on the internet?
Oh, here's another thing as well. Yeah.
So, and I said to him multiple times,
just go live.
Just go live. And he can't do it. Shut
up, Trevor Dawson. Don't make me come to Middlesborough again.
Don't make me come to borrow again and
make you come offline, you [ __ ] bastard,
you little [ __ ] house. And then you come
out with all of these excuses.
Okay. Okay. Well, I care, mate. I care.
And like I said, you can say all of this
tomorrow. You can say all of this stuff
tomorrow. No, he don't oppose to me, so
I've got to respond back to him.
Um, Megan, I've literally been with more
women than most of the people in this community.
Literally way more women. And I've never
had to beg. Stop selfjecting, you know.
Oh, you want the link? Okay, one second.
And what was the excuse? Do you remember
what the excuse was for not going live
in the bookies?
Hobby Joe with a 200 pound phone. Do you
remember what the excuse was?
What was the excuse? Do you remember the
excuse? Oh, you can't go live in the bookies.
You can't go live in the bookies.
One second. You can't go live in the bookies.
And I proved that to be [ __ ] didn't
I? This guy's going to get [ __ ]
Trevor Dawson. Trevor Dawson. Trevor
Dawson, you don't have a girlfriend. You
don't have a woman. You don't even leave
your house, lad. You're just like
poverty Joe with the 200 pound phone.
That's what I'm going to say. Uh, you
don't have a girlfriend and you've never
had a girlfriend. Stop self-projecting.
You're not going to bring me down to
your level. I'm not fat. I'm not
middle-aged. I'm not ugly. Like, I know
you're a [ __ ] Trevor Dawson. I I know
one thing about you that I went to
Middlesbrough and you didn't show up. I
know that I went to your city and you
didn't show up. [laughter]
O Steven, do you remember when I went to
Middlesbrough and this little [ __ ] house
didn't show up and he started coming out
with all these excuses and I had to show
the booking. I know exactly what you
lying bongs are all about. I know
exactly what you're all about, mate.
Exactly. With a big G. I know exactly
what you're all about. No one uploaded
the videos after I left. Nope. Nope.
Nope. Nope. That excuse does not wash.
Everybody saw me in Middlesbr, bro. And
if I really really uploaded the videos
after I left, you would have went there.
And you wouldn't have went quiet. You
literally went quiet. Shut up. If I
literally literally, bro, literally
literally, bro, if I if I went there, if
I done a video when I'd come back, you
would have just went there and showed me up.
You didn't show up, you little lavry
mog. Just like Joe. Poverty eyed Joe.
Poverty eyed Joe with a 200 pound phone.
Porky Pete, mate. Nothing's porky about
me, lad. You are the ones now obese.
You're the obese munters. There's
nothing pulky about me, bro. I am more
in shape than you will ever be. You are
[ __ ] obese. You people. Obese people
trying to call me Porky, bro. Did are
these people so skinned that they don't
even have a mirror? Bro, you people are [ __ ] obese.
You're morbidly obese, fat, and ugly.
You are no room to talk about someone
that's better looking than you. Yeah,
bro. I'll put my camera on because I'm
not obese like you people. I'll happily
put my camera on, lad. Someone that's
better looking than you.
I'll happily One second, mate. I'm not
ashamed of my looks like you people.
Where's this [ __ ] camera, mate?
Yeah, but you people are [ __ ] obese.
You fat people are obese. You're more
than porky. You're pulky obese. And I'm
going to say all of that stuff to um Joe
F in the video. Steven Howard. I'm going
to say it all in the video. You're
[ __ ] obese. You're more You're not
even fat. you obese? How the [ __ ] are
obese people that are in wheelchairs
going to call me porky?
How the [ __ ] are a bunch of fat ugly
people well overweight that don't even
leave the house talking about someone
better looking than them? I want answers
going [ __ ] mad.
Bro, you're calling yourself Porky. You're obese.
You're calling yourself PY as well as a
bun. That's you. That's yourself,
bro. Trevor. Trevor, you're obese.
Listen to me when I'm saying this stuff, bro. [ __ ]
Listen. You are obese. Open your ears.
You people are obese.
You're more than fat. You're [ __ ]
obese. Look at yourselves. You would
have thought in 2026.
Lit. Literally Steven Howard, everything
that these people say is literally about
themselves. They've not ever said one
thing that does not apply to themselves.
I don't know what what line of work you do.
Especially that [ __ ] poppy eyed Joe
with a 200 pound phone. Jesus Christ,
mate. I'm not in tears. I'm going bloody mad.
It's funny, bro. It is funny, man.
Where's poverty eye Joe with the 200
pound phone? You like that one? That's
why I'm going to start calling him now.
Poverty beast obesity Joe with a 200lb phone.
Bro, you people are [ __ ] obese.
You're more than puly. You're [ __ ]
fat. You're flat out flat fat. You are
flat out obese. You're not going to talk
about me, bro.
Bro, they're trying to fat shame when
they're [ __ ] obese.
Obese people calling other people pulky.
They need to look in that mirror,
bro. I'm sure they've got a mirror, bro.
All of the people in Most of the people
in this community are obese.
Yeah, Pete the Plumper, bro. I'm I'm
more in shape than you will ever be. You
need to invest in a mirror. Look at yourself, lad.
I know, bro. I I I Well, do you know
what, Uncle? Well, do you know what I do
know? Do you know what I do know? You
don't know. You know everything about my
life. What color boxes am I wearing,
bro? That there's nothing porker about
me, bro. You people are obese. She saw
you fat ugly people and thought, "Fuck
this. I don't want to be obese like
these fat ugly cunts."
Bro, you people are overweight. Stop self projecting.
You people are [ __ ] obese. Look in
that mirror. Your skin, you're boring.
You got no life. Look in that mirror.
Listen, Richard, you need that mirror
and look at yourself. You need to look
at You are all of them things. [ __ ]
You're all fat. You're all lonely. It's
all you. You need to get that mirror self projector.
That's That mirror is is calling you,
bro. Everything you say is about
yourselves. Get that mirror. It'll be
the best money you'll ever spend. You
need a mirror, lad. You're porky. You're
obese. You're skinny. You're ugly.
Everything is you. It's your own life.
It's literally you ugly people. I mean,
look at Trevor Dawson for example.
Doesn't leave the house. Sat on YouTube 24/7.
Do you know what I'm saying? Literally
got nothing in life. Been on there for
10 years. We know what you Ley Bongs are.
We know what you are.
No, bro. I'm just joking, man. You know,
I was just acting up, lad. I was just
acting up, bro. I'm just acting up, bro.
I was just acting up, man. Jesus Christ.
No, I was just actually acting up, bro.
You didn't think that was really real,
did you, Greasy?
like someone going mad and stuff, did
you? Sorry to disappoint, Grezy. I
baited you, didn't I? No.
Are Are you not going to ask me why? Of
course it wasn't real, bro.
Nah, bro. It wasn't real, man.
Are you not going to ask me why?
Steven Howard, are you not going to ask me why?
Are you not going to ask me why? Are you
not going to care to ask why, lad?
I can't really get mad at these people, bro. [snorts]
Because I can't get mad at them, lad. I
really can't get mad, man. I was only
joking, bro. [snorts]
I was only joking. [snorts] Uh,
I was only joking, bro. I can't get mad, lad.
Yeah, I am going. Of course I'm going
tomorrow, bro. Of course I'm going tomorrow.
Of course I'm [ __ ] going tomorrow.
What the [ __ ] I'm talking about like
the reacting to them and stuff, bro. I
was only joking, man. You think a bunch
of fat, ugly little morons could could
make me rage? Obese morons. They ain't
got a life. Come on, bro.
>> Yeah, of course I'm going tomorrow, bro.
And that's just to prove a point, bro.
Because like I said, if they've got a
lot of [ __ ] to say on YouTube, then
yeah, of course I'm going tomorrow, bro.
I'm going Sunday as well. All of that
[ __ ] going mad and [ __ ] that's just
part of my uh this is part of a
condition that I've got, you know?
Yeah, Trevor Dawson, you live in
Middlesbr, bro. Hold that L down
forever, lad. You're forgetting that
I've been to Middlesbr, bro.
Bro, you if you want to laugh, Trevor
Dawson, all you got to do is look in the
mirror. You'll get the biggest laugh,
brother. You don't need to look at a
t-shirt. You need to look in the mirror.
Look at your life. You'll get the
biggest laugh for a good couple of days. [laughter]
Did you like that one, Steven Howard?
Trevor Dawson, if you want a laugh, all
you got to do is look in the mirror.
Look at your life living in
Middlesbrough. And I've been to
Middlesbrough as well, so I know exactly
what it's like, mate. So, you need to
look in the mirror. Don't look at a
t-shirt. Look at your face. Look at your
life. You get the biggest laugh, bro.
You don't need to look at someone better
looking than you and fake a laugh. Just
look at yourself.
I'm still going to do this video um to
Jo, by the way.
Okay, you keep telling yourself, Trevor
Dawson, we've already been over this,
lad. We've already been over this. Uh,
we went over this yesterday.
We went over this yesterday, lad. Yeah,
bro. Do you know the reason why these
people get mad at me living with my mom,
Steven, is because they what it is with
these people is they don't have no mom.
They ain't got no family.
Um, so that's why they talk about me
living with my mom. Why the [ __ ] do
these people care who I live with and
who I don't live with? It's because
they're jealous. They ain't got no mom.
They ain't got no They ain't got no dad
either, to be honest with you, bro. They
[snorts] ain't got no family. That's why
they're so obsessed with my mom. How
many times do these people talk about
people's moms, lads? [clears throat]
Yeah, bro. I get bullied every day.
Yeah, man. No one wants to live with
their mom at 28. Why not? Save money.
Get to get to Why Why would you want to
live with your mom at 28?
Hey, and uncle, my life's not as bad as
yours either. I could be fat,
middle-aged, and ugly like you, bro.
Respect. My life could also be like yours, lad.
Can you imagine my life was like yours?
Some ugly little wobbler?
[ __ ] hell. At least my life ain't as
bad as yours. effect fist bump.
I could be like you, some [ __ ] ugly
wobbler. So that's to think about every
day, is it, lad?
Is it, lad, mate?
Yeah, they ain't got no mom. They got no
family. Bro, Steven Allen, honestly,
bro. Yeah, these people are just life's
rejects. They they they bro, they It's
so bad, bro, that they don't even fit
into any normal community. They're just
fat, ugly little wobblers.
They're fat, ugly little low lives.
You got nothing going for themselves and
they know that I'm correct. Ask yourself
this question, Steven Howard. Yeah. Why
are they on YouTube 24/7?
Ask yourself this. No, just just one
second, bro. Just hold on. Why are they
on YouTube 24/7? If they've got a life,
just just stop. No name calling. No,
you're there. Forget all that, bro. We
have We have proved
we've proved more than enough times that
these people are sat on YouTube all day.
Now, they say they've got a better life
than you, mate. So, we can kind of build
a picture of what these people [ __ ]
do, mate. You know what I'm saying?
On YouTube 24/7. They're obsessed with
my mom, bro. Steven Albert.
It's weird, bro.
Bro, I've told you this, man. Be Dawson,
you've got a mirror.
All you need to All you people need to
do is look in the mirror and look at yourselves.
All you people need to do is look at
your fat, ugly selves. You get the biggest laugh.
Why the [ __ ] are you going to waste your
time waiting for me to show a t-shirt
when you can just look in the mirror?
Look at your fat, ugly selves. You'll
get the biggest laughs ever. Trevor
Dawson, if you want to laugh. What? One
second, lad. If you want to laugh, just
think of the time that I went to
Middlesborough and you didn't show up. [laughter]
That gives me a laugh. That gives me a
Just think of the time that I went to
Middlesbor. You shut your pants. Sorry,
I just had to say that, Grevy. I'm a bit
cheeky. I'm a bit cheeky. I'm a bit
Sorry, mate. That's That just made me
laugh. Sorry. Sorry. I could help myself
there. You're thinking the time I
traveled 5 hours and you didn't show up.
That That always gets me going sometimes.
What about you, Grezy? Did that get you going?
I've done the same with bomb in Manchester. [laughter]
Okay, bro. You keep telling yourself
that. Yeah, bro. You keep telling
yourself. Well, like I said, Trevor
Dawson, you northerners have all got the
same excuses, so keep making them. But
we know that's not what happened.
Yeah, you keep telling yourself that,
Trevor. That's not what happened.
Everyone saw what happened in Manchester
and Middlesbrough. It's not going to
work. Them Northern excuses are not
going to work.
Everyone Everyone saw what happened,
lad. Yeah. Everyone saw what happened.
And your northern excuses don't wash.
Even with L J. L J is not even going to
lie for you. That's how bad it is.
No. No. No. No. No. No. No. No. No.
Bomb will forever own me.
What? What? Bomb.
Bomb will own me. Who's Bomb?
Bro, who's that? Is that the one that
got doxed and ran off of YouTube and
never come back?
Yeah, bro. He owns me so bad.
Oh, he owns me so bad, bro.
Oh, yeah. Yeah, yeah. He owns me so
badly, bro. I know, man. It's a pity he
wasn't here to say himself.
Yeah, bro. The one that got doxed and
ran off of YouTube due to his ugliness.
Yeah, bro. I got owned hard, man. Don't
tell anyone though, bro. Don't ruin my
reputation, bro. Please don't. Please don't, mate. Don't um Oh, really?
Yeah. No, that's not you, bro. You don't
have a mom.
You don't have a mom, lad. You ain't got
no family. You ain't got no family, lad.
You're you're you're you're right about
all the other things, but you ain't got
you don't live with your mom because you
ain't got a mom. You ain't got family, lad.
Yeah, bro. You I I'm going to do this
video to Jo as well. I'm going to put
this [ __ ] in his place. I want money for
this, by the way, mate. Greavves. I want
some money for this, mate, cuz I'm going
to be I'm going to be doing a lot of people in
I'm going to be doing a lot of [ __ ] in,
mate. So, you know. Yeah, man.
Yeah. Yeah. Who thinks that this guy is
in a wheelchair? Come on.
I'm an orer to you. H
Yeah. Yeah. We'll see about that, won't
we? And I'm going to I'm going to ask
Joe, would he kindly stop talking about
[ __ ] Charlie, you're the one sucking
your boyfriend's dick.
Um, but yeah, it's going to be titled,
"It's time to come out of the closet,
Joseph Fra." And I'm not trolling when
I'm saying this. Um, I'm not trolling
when I'm uh saying this stuff. 100%,
bro. I'm being deadly serious. Like,
there's there is a time to be serious. I
do think you are gay. Like, I'm not
joking, bro. I swear on my [ __ ] mom's
life, bro. My life and everything, I'm
not saying this. You generally have got
to be gay. You have got to be a closeted
homosexual. So, whenever all of this uh
ends, whatever, do try to I I I can't advise you
um because I'm not gay, so I've never
had to come out. I don't know. Maybe go
on Reddit, see what their advice is. But
you do need to definitely definitely
come out. Um looking on your channel,
you've got some serious issues, bro. Um
you Jamie Thompson, Red Star, a lot a
few of you, a few of you are. Um, you
know, it's uh there's there's there's a
there's obviously trying to wipe people
up and then there's uh I mean, yeah, I
mean, I don't uh I don't think L J's
gay. Um, so it's there's a wind up and
there's No, bro. You've got to come out
the closet, bro.
Nah, it's not true, bro. It's not true.
They don't know anything. They just say
that to try to get a reaction, lad.
Maybe he is gay. I don't know that he's
gay, bro. I know that Joe F is
definitely gay. Um, so we'll be doing a
video on him later. Nah, bro. They just
say they just talk [ __ ] for [ __ ]
react. I think he's maybe he's bisexual.
Maybe he's bisexual. Maybe, lad. Yeah. Right.
Let me see. Right. Your dress and mine
is like 1 hour apart.
No, we're meeting in London. Don't try
and change the time that Don't try and
change the place now. You said that
we're meeting in in North London.
Yeah, because it's going to take me
about 30 40 minutes to get into London
to the place where we're meeting. No,
no, we're meeting in North London. Don't
try and change [ __ ] now cuz the anxiety
is getting the better of you, lad.
I'm not going to be mentioning you in
this video, Smokey B. I'm meeting you.
I'm meeting you. Yeah. And that's it.
I'm meeting you Sunday. North scared to travel.
Am I scared to travel?
No, you don't bully me. Bomb Jo, you're
all jealous of me. Jealous of me for
being better looking. That's why you're
obsessed with me. You give your lives
away to me for nothing. Think of it.
Bomb Joe LJ, you're obsessed with me
because I'm better looking than you. I
love it. Keep going. I love it. And no,
bro. Am I scared to travel?
You're asking me, Smokey. Am I Am I
scared to travel? How long have you been
on this community now?
How long have you been on this community now?
You should know that I'm not scared to
travel. You You're talking to me, man. So, [snorts]
yeah. And I'm still Yeah. And And I've
seen you people as well, Rufo.
And I've se And I've seen you people as
well. Yeah. And I've seen you people, [laughter]
haven't we, Steven Howard? We've seen
them people, mate. Yeah. Yeah.
Tottenham. Yeah. Yeah, bro. That's fine.
I'll meet you in Yeah. Okay. Yeah. That's fine.
That's fine, bro. That is absolutely
fine. Yeah. Cool. That's that. Yeah.
And you can go crying to LT all you
want. I don't care. Simple. That's it.
Yeah. We'll see if you've got the same
energy in person on Sunday. Yeah.
But yeah, I'm going to do this video to
Jo. I won't be mentioning you, Smokey B.
I'll meet you Sunday. Yeah, I will meet
you Sunday and I and I will tell you
about yourself to your [ __ ] face and
you're never going to talk about me again.
Yeah, simple. Oh, Boris, bro, I just
went on I just went on LJ's live
earlier, bro. And him and Jo just kept
talking about me, talking about me,
talking about me. I'm thinking, what the
[ __ ] bro? I'm trying to eat my Chinese
here now, and we we've got this gay law
talking about me, and then we've got
this smoky bee talking about me. So, I
was like, bro, if you've got anything to
say, let's just have it out. Now, this
has been going out. This has been going
on for years
and I have to address that Jo as well.
Trevor Dawson, I went to Middlesborough
and you didn't turn up. Stop it. Stop embarrassing yourself.
No, I don't know. What do you mean I've
got none with you, brother? You was on
large days continuously talking [ __ ] and
talking [ __ ] and talking [ __ ] and
talking [ __ ] and talking [ __ ] So, let's
meet. Simple. I don't care. I've got
beef with you because you keep talking
[ __ ] [ __ ] time and time and time
again, bro. What? I was watching you do
it for about half an hour. Yeah. So, I
was like, "Okay, you've got a lot to
say. You can come and say to my face."
And trust me, Joe's going to get even
worse, bro. He's getting it worse than
you, bro. Yeah. Don't you worry. He's
getting worse than you, bro. Yeah. Well,
you can say to my face then. Simple.
Simple. Well, you can say it to my face
then, can't you? If you've got something
to say, you can say it to my face.
That's it. Simple as that.
Yeah, you can talk about me as much as
you want, bro. But you can also say it
to my face.
Yeah, simple. And you're not even the
worst one. And the thing is, Smokeoky B,
you're not even the worst one, bro.
Yeah. And I'm not backing out. I am
meeting you Sunday, but I I'm getting
That Joe's getting it as well. Trust me,
that Joe's getting it as well, bro.
Trust me. Yeah, he's the worst one, bro.
And he's talking about unworthy clock.
I'm going to also talk about unworthy
clock as well, bro. The [ __ ] guy
doesn't even come on my [ __ ] channel.
Yeah, bro. We'll see in it. We will see.
We will see. We will see. Yeah.
You're not bringing stuff up. You are
[ __ ] talking. Yeah. You are [ __ ] talking constantly.
Yeah. And I'm tired of it. I'm [ __ ]
tired of it. All right. I'm [ __ ]
And this Jo was also talking about
people's family as well. >> [gasps]
>> Um, so yeah, he is he is definitely
definitely definitely um Yeah, and I'm
going to explain as well why I'm going
to go to Nottingham as well. I'm going
to also explain it. Yeah. Also, there's
a reason Smokeoky B why I don't really
want to leave London for you. But when I
go to Nottingham, I'm meeting my friend
and it's not on WBY Clock. There's a
natural reason for it. There is an
actual reason for it. And I'm not scared
of traveling. Why would I be scared of
traveling, man? Come on. Why would I be
scared of traveling?
It's not about being scared of
traveling, bro. Why do you think I'm
going to Nottingham and not leads?
There's a there's a natural reason for it.
Uh, no, I'm not meeting in Watford. We
said North London.
Nope. We said North London. You know,
I tell you the reason why I'm not going
to lead Steven Howard. Yeah. I I'll tell
you why. Why, bro? Because the thing is,
yeah, if I go all the way to Leeds,
think about it, bro. Yeah. I don't know
anyone in Leeds. Listen, Joe. Listen.
I'll be doing a video to you later.
Yeah. Poverty Joe with a 200 pound
phone, right? And you're going to also
be addressed. Yeah. The reason is I'll
tell you why, Stephen.
Yeah. Yeah. We're meeting in We're
meeting um we're meeting in Tottenham.
Poverty eyed Joe with a 200 pound phone.
Mr. Obese, wait your turn. Poverty eyed
Joe. You can wait your turn. The thing
is Yeah. Yeah. I'll go to Tottenham and
he can call LT if he wants. I don't give
a [ __ ] Simple. Yeah.
I don't give a [ __ ] bro. You're getting
it as well. So that's it.
Yeah. Um, there's a reason why I'm not
I'm not going to lead or har and I'll
explain it. I've got a valid reason. I'm
gonna I'm gonna deconstruct you, right?
And what what's your what's your problem
with Charlie, bro?
What's your problem with Charlie?
What is your problem with Charlie, bro?
What is your problem with Charlie? And
that is not you in the picture, you
[ __ ] idiot, bro. That is not you in
the picture. Shut the [ __ ] up, bro. And
if that really is you in the picture,
which is not, you've literally got no
chance of beating me. That is not you in
the picture, bro. You're the one sucking
off your boyfriend on legs. You [ __ ]
closeted homo. Oh, don't call him a virgin.
Shut up, mate. How many times have you
sucked your boyfriend's dick? He's not
even proved he's had sex. And you're
talking to me. You're talking to me, you
closeted homosexual [ __ ] bastard.
You [ __ ] keep sucking up your
boyfriend's dick all because you showed
a disabled girl and not proved he's had sex.
You [ __ ] defending your boyfriend. I
don't even talk to Charlie.
Oh, he's got a girlfriend. Don't say
that about him. You [ __ ] [ __ ]
Oh, he's got a girlfriend. I can't
understand it. You was crying over your
boyfriend. I can't remember the last
time I spoke to Charlie. I don't talk to [ __ ] Charlie.
I've not spoke to Charlie for a [ __ ]
long time. And I'm not [ __ ] defending my boyfriends
like you. Oh, I can't understand him.
He's a virgin. Oh, Joe, listen. Why do
you think Jo listen? Why do you think LT
LT was in here the other day? Do you
know why he left? Cuz he can't say
nothing to me cuz he knows I'm right.
You're very touchy about your boyfriend.
Now again, when we're done with all of
this, when we're done with all of this,
right? Nah, I won't be sucking his dick.
I'm not like you and legs. You need to
get a room, you pair of gay boys.
You [ __ ] pair of gay boys. Oh, he's
not a virgin. Don't say that about him.
Listen, bro. Why do you think he
insulted me, LT? Because even someone
that claims they've got a degree knows
I'm right. Jo, you're very touchy about
your boyfriend being called a virgin.
Get a room. Get a room, you gay boy.
That is not you, bro. Hey, listen.
Listen, listen, Joe. That's not you in the picture.
Bro, I don't care if you people laugh at
me. I laugh right back at you.
I laugh right back at you, ugly
bastards. I laugh right back at the the
the the life rejects. I laugh right back
at you. I've told you this. Jesus Christ. Yeah, man.
So, anyways, um I'm going to explain to
in the video, Joe, um why I'm not going
to lead and I will meet you in
Nottingham. I've got a valid reason
and I've got a valid reason as well.
There's an actual reason for it as well.
There's an actual reason.
There's an actual reason for it, Steven
Howard. Because you don't understand how
embarrassing it is because we know who's
going to find out. We know who's going
to find out. And then I'm And you know
what people are going to say to me?
They're going to be like, "What the [ __ ]
are you playing at [ __ ] traveling all
of this way, spending all of this money
for these jealous ass people?"
Whereas Nottingham, we can justify it.
Tottenham, we can justify it. I can go
for a drink in London. I can justify
that. But we know the story with these
people. Trevor Dawson seems a [ __ ]
house. Bomb's a [ __ ] house, right?
Bomb's a [ __ ] house, right? Joe F's a
[ __ ] house. The reason you are going to
Nottingham. There's not a reason. Oh,
gosh darn it. Joe, I'm not [ __ ]
defending my boyfriend like you. We saw
you. We saw you um putting thumbs up to
his video. Joe F. You're very touchy
about your boyfriend.
Hey, get a room. You a non legs. No,
don't call him a virgin.
He's got a girlfriend. I can't
understand it. You [ __ ] gay boy.
[ __ ] poverty eyed Joe with a 200
pound phone. We could go We could go for
a beer afterwards, mate. You poverty
eyed Joe sailor with a 200 pound phone.
[ __ ] hell, son.
I'll tickle you. I'll [ __ ] tickle you, mate.
It's a load of bollocks, mate. It's a
load of bollocks.
Yeah, I have an anxiety attack.
Poverty eye Joe with a 200 pound [ __ ]
And bro, why haven't you put up any fake wins recently?
No more fake gambling bins. No more
putting the money in and taking it out.
Oh, come on, bro. Come on. Come on.
[clears throat] That's not you in a
photo, Jo. Stop it now.
Really? Really, really stop it now. Yeah,
you need to. But no, seriously, Joe, you
need to come out the closet. And I'm not
even saying this to be nasty. You
actually are. You need to come out the
closet. You Red Star Nons, you need to
come out. Trust me, bro. your life will
improve once you come out the closet. I
can even help you if you want. Um, you
know, I do think a lot of the people on
here are homosexuals
as well as jealous, but I think they're
homosexuals as well. No, seriously.
Seriously, you are you really really are
a uh a closeted homosexual.
You was on Lord Jay's and there was
nothing else she was talking about but
me. Bro, I'm not giving you my ass. I
don't swing that way. I'm sorry. I'm not
gay. And guess what, bro? If I was gay,
you're not my type.
You are not my type. Nonss is not my
type. And Red Star is not my type. I
don't swing that way.
Literally, bro, I will not I literally
do not swing that way. I'm sorry, bro. I
don't swing that way. I I I respect your
you know, you being gay and stuff. I've
got no problem with gay people, but I
personally don't swing that way.
Sorry mate. Me and you is never
happening. I'm not giving you my ass. So
kindly after this, I'd like you to [ __ ]
off, you know? Right.
Right. And then you're talking about my
kid. A Jesus Christ, bro. I'm going to
do a video to you, man. I'm going to set
the record straight one more [ __ ]
time. Right. And I'm going to And I'm
not going to Nottingham either. Sorry.
I'm not I'm going to Nottingham. I'm not
going to Leeds for [ __ ] sake, bro.
Yeah, I'm going to Nottingham and I'm
not going any further than that. Right.
And Nottingham is 73 miles away from you
and it's 150 mi away from me.
But I am not getting with you because I
do not swing that way.
I'm not gay. Yeah, [ __ ] me. Oh, how are
you doing? UK asylum.
I need to start start my women
collection soon and you bastards are
kind of ruining it for me.
I'll go to waxies on Sunday. I love a
waxy Sunday session. I'll fill this
[ __ ] stupid smoky bean and that's it.
And we'll start my collection. Is that
all right, Grezy?
Yeah, my little collection.
I've got a few friends in Nottingham and
I don't even talk to Charlie. I've got
nothing against Charlie. I got no
problem with him. He's he's he's all
right Charlie. I actually quite like
Charlie, you know.
He doesn't [ __ ] stir. He doesn't do
anything bad. But I just don't talk to
the guy. I got nothing against him,
but I I'm not I'm not meeting Charlie.
Why would I be meeting Charlie? I don't
I don't talk to Charlie.
I got a lot of friends in um Nottingham
Grezy. They talk a bit like this. Like a
bit like Robin Nood. That's how they
talk in not uh that's how they talk in
Nottingham Greasy. A bit like Robin
Nude. Like you know that's how they talk
a bit. They talk a bit like that.
Like Dorby and that
I'm from Derby. That's how they talk.
They talk a bit like that. Yeah. Greasy.
I was watching this. I I was watching
this Andy Marget. Yeah. He's gambling
story and he doesn't he doesn't post anymore.
Do you remember that Andy Marget when he
said he had a gambling addiction
Greavvesy and he said that it went on
for about 18 months and then his wife
found the letter
and he and he got kicked out and he had
to go to his parents and that. It must
have been tough, isn't it? Yeah. Oh,
that's scary, isn't it?
Do you remember that Andy Marget
when he used to do his uh gambling where
we made a quick gambling? I'm sure some
people remember him. Do you remember him, Dusty?
Yeah, I'm sure some people do. Jesus Christ.
Yeah, bro. He was What do you think of
him? He said that he's found he his wife
found a um statement and um kicked him
out of the house and he had to drive
through his parents and that. That's not
good, bro. Is it?
See, with me, bro, it wasn't a case of
like where I owed people money or like I
didn't have enough money. It was more
like it was getting my moods, the moods
and stuff because, you know, if someone
goes to Gamblin Anonymous, uh, Dusty,
they they usually go cuz they've lost
their home, they've lost their business,
they own money, they're their, you know
what I'm saying? like there whereas me
it was just the moods
whereas I still have money and I still
had money you know but but you know what
I'm saying so it's different reasons
even though it's still bad
whereas them they just lost all their
money they were in debt they lost their
house that would never happen to me bro
it would never ever happen to me
to be honest because I would never lose
all my money it's as simple as that look
at what I done bro I I yeah Stephen
Albert I [ __ ]
I um I closed the lad I closed the lad
Brooks account down Stephen Howard.
I'm done with it, bro. The football and
all of that and whatnot.
So I I closed it down, bro.
I'm done done with it, bro. So
I'll be starting my women collection
again soon. So, you know, like I said, I
can't be doing that gambling [ __ ] anymore, bro.
You know what, Dusty? It's such a waste
of life when you think about it. You
know, gambling, bro. You know, you know
about the money, bro. It's not even just
money. It's actually like
it's actually you waste so much of your life.
You know what I'm saying? I mean, not
footballs, but roulette, you actually
waste your life. Um, well, I don't think
in four or five years I wasted my life
cuz I still live my life. But
it's still a waste of life, ain't it,
bro? Think about it.
Do you like Yoda's new clothes?
Can you wait to see my new collection of women? Grezy,
someone on Reddit said, "Well, they're
not people according to you." No,
they're not people.
Oh, look. I'll show you.
I had to change his I had to change this
look. Cuz he couldn't sit down.
UK asylum. Why do you think I'm a troll?
I'm not a troll. Look, look. Look.
Well, here's the thing, Jo. If you're if
you're actually not fat yet and you're
actually not ugly, I will be [ __ ]
very [ __ ] surprised. You know what? I
will be very very very very surprised UK
asylum if this guy is not fat and ugly.
I'll be very very surprised. I would
actually be gobsmacked.
So you go to the gym, you're not fat and
you're not ugly. I'd be very very very very surprised.
I'd be very surprised. Then I would just
simply think that he's gay. Simple as
that. I would just put I would just
person I would just I would just I would
just think that he's uh he's gay.
UK Asylum. Why are you calling Why are
you calling me a troll?
How have I ever trolled?
Because I said that I'm collecting
women. Okay. So, how am I a troll?
Why would I troll anyone, bro?
Why the [ __ ] would I troll, bro? Well,
how have I trolled?
By saying I'm starting a woman a woman collection. Nah.
Never troll me, lad.
I like collecting stuff. What's your problem?
Did you see earlier?
Did you see earlier UK asylum? Did you
see earlier, lad?
Did you see earlier? I was talking to
Smokey B. Then Large A come, then Prime
come. They'll copy each other. They
don't [ __ ] come like like unless the
other one comes. [ __ ] copycat.
Lav the copycat.
Yeah, of course you're doing unboxings
now, aren't you? You little copycat.
UK asylum. Look, go on his channel, bro.
Go on LJ's channel. There's no there's
no unboxing. There's no nothing. There's
no unboxing or anything until I done it.
The only time he done it was when I
started doing it. Look, bro. Look at all
of these shorts and videos.
Reezy, are you still there? No, not this weekend, bro.
Not this weekend. I will announce when I'm going.
But yeah, if this if this Joe if this
Yeah. Look, there's nothing. Greavvesy,
bro. There's no unboxing. There's no
nothing until when I done it. Why is that, Grezy?
No, Dusty. I No, no, no, Dusty. I done
an unboxing video and then literally a
little bit after he done one and then
another one. What's the chances, Greavesy?
What's the chances?
I Bro, I'm looking on all of his [ __ ]
There's no boxes. Nothing.
I'm looking. I'm looking. I'm looking.
Why is there no unboxing? Yeah,
I ain't seen where. I'm looking through
his I'm looking I'm looking at his I'm
looking at his I'm looking at his videos
now. What do you think this is? Yoda,
let Yoda talk. Meow.
What? What do you mean, Yoda? Meow. Meow.
Little copycat. What do What do you
mean, Yoda? Yoda says that he's copying
Do you want to ask Yoda a question or do
you want to ask Ja?
You're under arrest, Grezy, on suspicion
of being a little copycat.
How do you think? I [laughter] love Griezy.
I know Greavvesy trolls, but it is
funny, man. It is funny.
It is funny, isn't it? It is. It is
[ __ ] funny, man.
So, I've got So, on Sunday, I've got uh
I've got to wear the Spider-Man t-shirt.
Don't I Grezy?
So, yeah. Yeah, we are all fat and
obese, aren't we? I'm 40, not been for 20 years.
Nah, I don't believe that's him, bro.
Fair play if it is. If it is, then I'll
take back everything I said. I would
just say that you're simply just a homosexual.
Um, yeah, if you actually are not fat
and you're not ugly, then yeah, I would
attract my um I would track my
statement, but you are still gay. But I
I just can't imagine that being him,
bro. Because the thing is, bro, there's
no way, lad. Because you're saying
because the the thing is, right, what
you're saying is, yeah, you're saying,
"Yeah, we are all fat and obese, aren't
we?" But you got to understand, the
people that have been doxed,
um, the people that have been doxed have
all been fat and ugly. Every single
person that has been doxed. And maybe if
he's not fat, then he's just really
ugly. And I never said everyone on here
is fat and ugly. No, obviously Nods Legs
is a lanky ugly [ __ ] that looks like a
rat. Terry's an ugly [ __ ] I when I
say fat, I mean people from L J's. Yeah,
the the point is they're badl looking
[ __ ] people and most of them are
[ __ ] fat. So none of them are [ __ ]
normal looking. None of them are normal. So So yeah.
So even if he's not fat, he probably is
because there's no way this guy's not
fat and looks normal because he would he
wouldn't be doing this. He would not be
doing it there. No, there's been no one
in the past that's done this that's
looked normal. So I mean LT says he
does, but we've never seen LT.
So we we haven't seen anyone that has,
you know. So
of course I own them. They call me Porky
and I'm not even fat. What the [ __ ]
What do you think of the picture that
Joe F put up?
This Joe F is he's very obsessed with
me, isn't he? Why is he so obsessed with another man?
Do you know the last time I went on USA
Izzy's profile? Greasy.
Ask me when.
I can I can tell you when if you want.
Today. Earlier today had a wank. [laughter]
No, I'm only joking. Long time, bro. No,
seriously. Seriously, a long time.
No, bro. A long time, bro. A very very
very very long time. I can't remember
the last time.
I think when I stopped talking to a friend,
I mean, when I when I spoke to a friend,
I stopped I stopped up before that anyways.
But but I but what it was greasy is I
would go on it like every two weeks and
just look. Whereas these people Whereas
these people do it every day. Like they
will continuously habitatly [ __ ] with
people every day. Whereas I would just
go on her profile every two weeks and if
I stumbled across someone whereas they
are literally every single day. Yeah.
Okay. Do why? Okay. If you if that is
really you, join the link right now and
and and show us show us the same boxes
and show us the same stomach.
Okay, if that's you,
okay, if that's you, then then then show
us the same thing on the on the camera.
[snorts] That's a fair deal, isn't it,
Grezy? If that's really you, Yeah.
then you will come on the stream and
then obviously then it is you. Yeah,
that's the only way. You don't have to
talk cuz I know you're you're scared of
talking. It's a bit much for your anxiety.
But yeah, if you if you want to
if you if you if you show the same thing
on the on the Streamyard camera, then it
is you. Yeah.
You said you've shown money before. Come
on then. Simple.
and you're not strong, bro. Even if that
is you in the photo, you're not strong,
bro. You wouldn't last. Look at me, bro.
Peter Bell is a big Peter Bell is a big [ __ ]
I'm big and strong, Grezy, because of
all the the the curries that I eat and
stuff. Greavvesy, I'm a little curry muncher.
Okay, [snorts] then do a video then. Yeah.
What do you think of Lord J UK asylum?
This is a copycat community. [laughter]
Bezy, you make me laugh. Oh, you done a
video, did you?
Let's have a look.
Right, I've just gone on your channel. Nothing.
Well, bro, even if that is you, you got
no chance against me, mate.
I'm a big [ __ ]
I'm big and strong.
I'm big and strong. Trust me.
Yeah. I've took on [ __ ] bounces
bigger than you, lad. Yeah. You ain't
got no chance with Peter Belly.
I said if it is you, I don't know if
it's you. There's no video. I said even
if it is, you're still not going to win
against me. I never said I said if it is
you. Yeah. We're waiting for this video.
Oh, I'll give him more than enough notice, lad.
That's That's me and Steven Howard's business.
Yeah, we'll see if it is you.
But that could be anyone. That's not
even me being awkward, Greasy. That
generally could be anyone.
It actually could be anyone. I'm not
even trying to be awkward. It could be.
It literally could be anyone.
Because think about it, bro. Joe, you
can't call no one porky. You are morbidly obese.
You can't talk about, bro. Your hands
shows that you are actually fat, bro.
Let me see. Is this a short or [ __ ] video, bro?
I can't see it.
Oh, [ __ ] me, man. >> [snorts] >> Okay.
Let me see. Okay.
Yeah, bro. You're not beating me. No chance,
bro. Look how skinny your arms are, bro.
What the [ __ ]
You You're not going to win against me, bro.
You your your little twig arms. You're
going to win, bro. You're not going to
win against me, bro. Trust me.
You wouldn't win against Big Peter Belly. Trust me.
Oh man. You're fast. You're not faster
than me, lad.
You're not faster than me.
Trust me, you're not faster than me,
mate. I'm very, very fast.
I can always run. I can always run uh
and and catch the bus. You want to see
me? Certainly, Captain.
I'll show you, Captain [ __ ] [snorts]
Oh, what? Why is my camera not working
on here then? One second.
I think my phone's on its way out. Tell
me the truth.
No, my phone's one second. My camera not working.
All right, here we go.
Why is this [ __ ] thing not working, bro?
way bigger than yours, bro.
My My muscles are way bigger than yours.
That's why you don't go to the gym for
two weeks. I gain muscle very fast
cuz Yeah. My muscles are bigger than
yours, bro. you you would get wrecked.
But it's not let me talk about Look. Oh,
here we go. Now it's working.
Bro, you're not going to beat Peter
Belly. You've got [ __ ] twig arms.
Look at me. I've got muscle and I don't
even go gym.
I don't even go to the [ __ ] gym.
You're not [ __ ] beating me, you [ __ ]
And I'm I'm obese myself.
I'm obese. [ __ ] off, mate. I'm a [ __ ]
beast can. I'm going to wear my little Spider-Man top.
I've got bigger muscles than you, mate.
And I don't even go gym.
Look at that. Look at my muscles. Flinch
your arms. You ain't got no chance
against me, mate. [sighs]
I'm going to wear my little Spider-Man
top, Grezy. Okay, boss.
Is that okay with you, boss?
You know what I'm saying?
You're not going to win against me, lad.
I don't need to show you my stomach.
I don't need to show you my stomach,
mate. Even my chest is hard. I don't
even need to show you. I don't need to
show you my stomach.
Looking ahead of me. Thank you, mate.
And I'm better looking than you.
I'm better looking than you, mate. Oh, Joe.
Well, let me tell you something, bro. I
tell you one thing. I bet you look like [ __ ] rice.
We know for a fact, bro, that Be honest,
bro. Be honest about the way that you look now.
No, no, no. Actually, bro, be honest
about the way that you look.
I don't go.
It's all fat. Nope. Nothing's fat about me, mate.
Even my chest is solid.
Oh, Joe. Be honest now, bro. Do you look like Rice?
Yeah, you look Bro, you're not going to
beat me, bro.
No chance. And you're not faster than me either.
I got a right set of tits. No, I don't.
I'm not even fat, bro. What the [ __ ]
No, I'm not even fat, lad. [snorts]
I bet you look like rice.
I bet you look like rice, mate. Yeah.
Yeah, I bet you look like Rice.
But I know you look I know I know you're
not good-look. I know you're not better
looking than me, mate.
I know you're not better looking than me, mate. me.
But no. Well, you do need to come out
the closet, though. You definitely need
to come out the closet.
You definitely do need to come out the closet.
I mean it, bro. You actually do need to
come out the closet. You Your channel is
dedicated to me, bro. Just come out.
There's nothing wrong with being gay.
Just come out, lad.
Bro, if I went to the gym, bro, for
like six weeks, I'd have the best body,
bro. I'm just lazy. I'm not even fat
either, but I'm just saying if I if I
was to go, you know.
Yeah, bro. You really think you're going
to beat me?
You You're not going to beat me, lad.
Trust me, you won't beat me. Just like
Smoky Be is not going to beat me. Just
like Prime's not going to beat me
because I can grab really hard, you know. Yeah.
Bless you, mate. Yeah.
I bet you got a weird looking face,
though. I bet you 100% see now, that
he's got a weird looking face. There's
no way you are not fat and you're normal
looking doing this. There's no way, bro.
Al him. Al him. Al him.
Please. I don't use filters. You do. So
why don't you show yourself not using filters.
There's no way that you are a normal
looking person that's not fat that's
doing this. There's no way. There's no
There's literally no way.
You are homosexual though. You do need
to come out the closet. Definitely need
You really, really, really do need to
come out the closet, lad. You know. Yeah.
Do you like my beard?
It's nice. I like it. Me.
I like it. Me, lad.
Keeps me warm.
Yeah. Keeps me warm, mate. Yeah, man.
I would I do need to go to the gym soon,
though, to be honest.
So, what what's your opinion? Yeah, if
he obviously like he's not fat, then he
definitely has got a weird looking face.
He might just look like Rice.
I'd be very surprised if he's normal
looking and he's not fat. I'd be
surprised, bro. I'd be very surprised.
And if if he is, then he's just a
homosexual. Simple as that. So yeah,
but it doesn't matter, bro. Really,
because I mean, look at Nonlex. Nonlex
is jealous of me and he's not fat. [ __ ]
um there's someone else as well. Terry's
jealous and he's not fat. So he could
just look like a weird looking bastard, you know. Yeah man,
you are looking normal. Yeah, I am
normal looking. Yeah.
Yeah. Do you know why Autumn you know
why you get so many people simp over you
on this is because they don't get women
where they're so ugly as [ __ ] they can't
go and get they can't go out and meet
women. So that's why they that's why
they beg you. Have you noticed I don't
beg you because bro you're not even in
my league, mate. Yeah, you you use
filters and you're not even
good-looking. I can literally go out
right now and approach someone and get
someone's number. I don't need to beg
some [ __ ] woman on YouTube that uses filters.
You know what I'm saying, bro?
Yeah, I am. Yeah.
You're not in my league, mate. Trust me,
you're not in my league. Trust me.
Okay. Okay. So, what what would you say?
What would you rate your looks out of 10, Joe?
No, I'm not wrong. You are actually a
you are actually a homosexual.
No, no, no. You are actually a homosexual.
You are actually No, I I do think you
are a homosexual.
You nonsle legs. I do think you are a homo.
You're definitely a homo. I believe you're homosexual.
Uh well, Nons is a virgin. Nons is ugly. I mean,
you're probably ugly.
Okay. So, would you say that you're ugly then?
And also, bro, it doesn't really matter.
There can be people that aren't fat that
are jealous. Look at Nod's legs.
Look at Nod's legs. He's for I'm way
better looking than him. He's jealous of
me and he's not fat. There's nothing
wrong with being homosexual.
You just need to come out the closet for
your own sake.
You got a channel dedicated to another
man. Bro, what's going on?
That you've never met. What What's the score, lad?
What is the actual score here?
Something's not right with that, bro.
You're definitely a homosexual.
It's not fair in your makebelieve wife.
You better come out sooner rather than later, Joe. Yeah.
Jealous, bro. And guess what? I'm better
looking than Joe. I've got more
confidence than Joe. I've done more than
Joe in 28 years. I'm not jealous of no one.
You don't. Yeah, but Joe, you don't get
women though, do you? You don't get
You don't get women. You said that
you've got a wife and she is fat. So,
you don't get women. Just like your
boyfriend don't get women. That's why he
targets That's why he targets disabled people.
Because you don't get women, do you?
Come on. Come on, mate. Yeah, mom.
It's okay though. It is okay to be gay.
Just Just come out the closet.
I couldn't stalk a woman for full amount
of times that you stalked me.
And And that's [ __ ]
And you're supposed to be normal.
Oh, mate. I don't need sublet money.
I've got plenty of money. And I and you
didn't stop by money either. Hey honey,
guess what? I've got more money than you.
Hey, and you're another one, Red Star.
So, um, anyways, ma'am, you need to come
out. You, Non Legs, and Joe, you all
need to meet up and you all need to find
a way to come out as gay. Um, it will
make your life much uh easier.
[sighs and gasps]
Trust me, bro. You do need to come out
as gay. I'm actually trying to help you.
It's okay to be gay, man.
Man, you do need to definitely come out
um you need to come out as gay. There's
something not right with you, man.
Stalking a man every day on YouTube
from the time you wake up to the time
you go to bed. It's not my fault that
you're gay and that you've not come out.
You're an angry closeted homosexual.
This is what happens. You know, when
they don't come out, when they don't
come out, they start getting angry and stuff.
Just come out as gay, bro.
I can't be that much of a m for you to
be sat there on YouTube being obsessed
with me every day with your boyfriend.
Bro, I got to be doing something right.
You need to come out as gay.
You need You need You need to generally
come out as gay, lad.
It'll help you, man. It will help you.
Nothing wrong with being gay.
If I was really as ugly as you were
making out, you wouldn't be obsessed
with me every day.
You wouldn't be I've got to be doing
something right. Think about it. Think
about it, Steven. Yeah. I've got to be
doing something right. Yeah. For to have
that many people obsessed with me every day.
You didn't stop any of my money. Peter
Betty makes money.
We literally, bro, I literally make
money and I've got money. You didn't
stop my money. [ __ ] all of that stuff.
You I've got to be doing something right
in 2026 for these people to still be
doing this. There's got to be There's
got to be something, mate.
Yeah, Red Star, you are skin, lad. Stop
repeating yourself. You are skin. You
are ugly. We know what you are. Stop
talking about yourself. It's 2026. Get a
life. Come out as gay. Rebuild your
life. And that's it.
Yeah. You never got any of my money stopped.
Stop lying. Stop lying to the community.
You never got a penny of my money stopped.
you, your boyfriend tried to get my
money stopped and I had him go to the
police and stop going to events because of me
and I was over [ __ ] the silly amount
of money. So, do you think some loser
like you could ever stop any of my money?
Do you think some loser like you would
stop two grand of my money? I had your
boyfriend stop going to events because
of me. I had him I I controlled his life
for three years.
I controlled your three years. Three
three um three years, bro. Oh, bro. Bro,
that was worth it. I didn't mind being
in a cell, lad. If it meant me stopping
your boyfriend doing what he loves, I
didn't mind being in a sale, lad.
That's fine. I stopped your boyfriend
doing what he loves for 3 weeks. I don't
mind being in a cell. That's fine, bro.
You get a tea, you get a biscuit, they
look after you. That's fine, bro. to be
in a cell
in exchange for stopping your boyfriend
going through what he loves. That's completely fine.
I didn't go running to the police. I
didn't go crying I weren't a fighter. I
didn't stop going to events. I didn't
stop walking the wrong way. I stopped
your boyfriend doing what he loves
because of me. And I take pride in it.
Is that right, Stephen Howard? And if
you don't know what I look like, it's this mug.
This mug here put a stop to go into certain events.
Imagine that. And then you're trying to
say you've stopped my money. I don't
think so, bro.
I get more money than you will ever
have. And you didn't stop any of my
money. I've got more money than you.
[ __ ] hell. How do you think I still
gamble and stuff? Because you don't know
what people have. You only know about
your own closeted homosexual life.
You only know about your own closeted
homosexual life. That's the only life
that you know about, lad. No one else's.
Yeah, I loved it as well cuz you never
stopped any of my buddy. I also love it.
I also love that I had your boyfriend
stopping going to events for three
[ __ ] weeks cuz of me and nothing
happened. I'm still here. I'm still
alive. I'm still living my life.
Yeah, I'm saving for the barbers. Yeah, man.
Yeah, but no, seriously, you do need to
come you need you do need to come out as gay.
You do need to uh come out as gay, mate. Yeah.
Anyways, see you later.
No, seriously, bro. Um,
you do need to come out as gay.
I love it, bro. I love it. All right,
but Stephen Howard, listen, bro. If
they're If they're generally Yeah. Bro,
if they're generally Yeah. not not
jealous of people. Yeah.
Then like what else could it be? Unless they're gay.
Think about it, bro. If you if you if
you meet a woman, right, and and you're
obsessed with a woman for like a couple
of months or and then you give it up.
Yeah. So, you're done with it. So,
you're done with someone that you had
sex with or you're done with someone
that you met. And I would say that I'm
quite impulsive, then they have got to
be gay. There's there's nothing else
they actually can. If they swear and
they're swearing down, bro, that they're
not jealous, then they have literally
got to be homosexuals
that are closeted. There's nothing else
it can be, that because
what the [ __ ] bro. It's so weird, man.
How they can sit on here for years doing
this? They need to [ __ ] get a life.
And that comes with like um coming out the closet.
I don't know, man. It's weird.
So, yeah. What do you think of Jo's body?
I believe it when I see it in
Nottingham, lad. Let's put it that way.
I believe it when I see it in Nottingham. [snorts]
I'm still going to put him in his place
in this video as well.
Could just look like rice.
Yeah, they are they are they are definitely homosexuals
cuz they have put because think think
about it. Yeah. Dusty, they have put a
hundred times more effort into me than I
put into USA Izzy. And these people have
never even met me, lad.
They've never met me. They've never So,
think about it, bro.
I think they're angry at the fact that
they're homosexuals and they don't know
how to come out. So, obviously, they
take it out on me. But, I don't want to
I don't want to date any of these
people. Thank you, lad.
You're [ __ ] stinking autumn.
You're [ __ ] stinking, son.
>> [sighs and gasps]
>> Oh, this is so annoying, bro.
Why do I have so many people that want
my ass on this community, bro? I don't
swing that way, man. I don't swing that way, bro.
Why do you think, Steven Howard?
I don't swing that way.
He said he's got a strong punch.
You've got a strong punch.
What do you think, Jo?
Sorry. What do you think, Steven Howard?
Do you think this has got any chance of
beating Peter Belly?
Highly highly doubt it, bro.
Highly doubt it, bro. No.
No way, bro. Peter Belly. Nah,
look at Peter Belly, man. He's still
good looking even with this beard and
with this hair.
No, but I'm going No, no, no. Steven
Howard, I'm going to [ __ ] um I want
to go to Nottingham anyways, lad.
I want to go to Nottingham anyways.
I want to go to Nottingham anyways, bro.
So, I'm not going for them. That's the
whole That's what I'm trying to say,
lad. That's the whole reason I'm not
going to leads is cuz I know they're not
going to show and whatnot. So, I know
they're not going to show them, you know.
I know they're not Hey, when I had this
beard and I went to the airport, Grezy,
they started asking me loads of questions. The security
I remember I had my beard like this,
bro. They were asking me
a lot of questions, bro.
They were trying to It's because the
beard. They must have thought I was up
to no good. Yeah, man. Nah. Uh,
why are you obsessed with other men's
looks? Are you another one that needs to
come out the closet, lad?
A lot of these people on here need to
come out the closet. Nah, bro.
Look at my beard.
Look, it Yoda can almost have a little
home in my beard. Look,
imagine he sits like that. [laughter]
Bless you, Yoda. Maybe
you're just jealous. I bet you can't
grow a beard.
My beard is horrible. I bet you can't
grow a beard. Hey,
beard's lovely. Actually,
I like it. Yeah,
I'm not your [ __ ] mate. Yeah. No, no, no.
Yeah, I knew it, lad.
Bro. Joe, I've got nothing to hide. I
don't have a double chin. I'm not fat.
I've had a beard for years, lad.
I've had a beard for [ __ ] years.
All right, Autumn. Why don't you put a
picture up without using filters, you know?
I know. I'm The reason I've got this
beard is because if I if I go to the
barbers, I'm going to be tempted to go
out drinking and approaching and I want
to not do that for um No, I don't like a
woman calling me mate. It sounds
horrible. It sounds masculine. It's
horrible. It's gross.
No, it sounds horrible. I've already had
a girlfriend and I've had more women
than you. We've been over this. Get your
brain tested, lad.
Does my mom call me mate? No.
I don't even like it when men call me
mate. I had to pull up Ant-Man about it
the other day. I said, "I'm not your
mate. Don't call me mate. I'm not your mate."
He doesn't like it when I say, "Oh,
bless you." He says, "Stop saying that.
It's patronizing." And I told him,
"Don't call me mate. I don't like being
called mate by anyone. It's horrible. It's common."
Yeah, I've got no mates, Joe. Okay, bro.
You keep You go back to sucking off your
boyfriend nons legs, lad.
Go back to
go back to um sucking off your n your
boyfriend nons legs. Go cry some more.
When I call him a virgin, Joe, go and
cry some more.
Go cry some more in the corner of the
bathtub at your boyfriend being called a
virgin. Oh, go cry some more.
Go cry some more.
Yeah, man. I don't know why you and LT
have got such problems. You're You're
all the same, man. You're all the same. You, LT,
you're all the [ __ ] same. I don't
know why you you've um got issues. You
all you all love to suck your
boyfriend's dick off. Uh you're all
biased. I mean, what what why do you
have problems? I don't you know, I don't
[gasps] I don't
Well, well, no, Joe. We've literally
been over this.
Well, no, it's not me because me and
Steven would get on, me and Greavesy
gets on. got no problems with how hard
can it be. No, you're just biased, jealous [ __ ]
I mean, I can I can explain it one more
time if you want me to.
I mean, why do you think LT insulted me?
He insulted me because he knows I'm
right. He never answered any of the
questions that I asked because he knows
I'm right. He literally couldn't answer
it. That's why he went to insulting me. Yeah.
Yeah. I mean, I can explain it one more
time if you want, Joe.
I don't really want to cuz it's boring,
but No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no,
no, no. You are.
And yes, it was over the Christmas period.
No, it's definitely you find it weird
when someone calls someone a virgin
because they've got a disabled
girlfriend that can't consent, but yet
you don't find it weird when someone's
calling me a virgin. That literally
makes no sense. Yeah, it definitely
definitely is you being biased. Yeah.
Yeah. I mean, do you want me to ask
people outside like genuine people? I'm
going to ask them, Stephen. Right. Who
has got more chance of being a virgin?
Someone that's got a disabled girl
that's got disabilities that can't
consent or someone that's shown a
[ __ ] someone that's literally been
in bed with women naked, that's been
with multiple different women and have
had women admitted to sleeping with
them. I know what they're going to
choose, mate. It doesn't matter what I
paid. Okay. Okay. I paid every single
woman for sex. Yes. And that was more
than a girlfriend. So again, answer my
question, Joe. Why have we not seen you
on Nlex's channel talking about this
19year-old and talking about this um you
know how you suck your boyfriend's dick?
So when he's calling me a virgin, why
have you not said anything?
You're so far
his girlfriend. His girlfriend sucking
his dick. But then when he's calling me
a virgin, someone that show more than a
girlfriend, you got nothing to say cuz you're biased.
If a [ __ ] ain't sex, then a
girlfriend ain't sex. It's as simple as
that. There's nothing you can say. What
can you literally say? There's nothing
you can say on that one. Even if you're
right of other things, you're fast
enough to defend a virgin that's not
proved they've had sex. But someone like
me that's actually shown sexual acts in
bed with naked women, you got nothing to say. What?
Sucking his dick. So, at the end of the day, listen,
bro. Oh, but you're going to defend
someone that says they like 15y olds, Joe.
Oh. Oh, but Oh, so you don't like the
things that I've said? Oh, but you just
like someone that likes 15y olds. Make
it make sense. Jesus [snorts] Christ.
You said that you don't like him. But
you So, you do like him then. Make up
your [ __ ] mind.
You know, it doesn't matter what I've
said. Facts is facts. I've shown more
than a disabled girlfriend that can't
consent. But [ __ ]
Oh, so you'd rather just defend your
boyfriend? Oh, he got a girlfriend yet
you said that you don't like him and you
think he's a n. Hold on a minute. Didn't
you call this guy a n?
One second. One second. One second. So
So you don't like him cuz he's a na, but
you stick up for him. Make it make
sense. You then you said that you call
him a naunt.
Yeah. He said he likes 15year-old. Yeah.
Yeah. It doesn't matter if they're in a
relationship. That's not sex. If a
blowjob's not sex and a girlfriend's not
sex, there's nothing you can say. And I
said the same thing to LT. I said, "Stop
sucking your boyfriend's dick."
And why do you think he went at me hard?
Cuz he knows he was he was sucking his
boyfriend's dick. You for some reason
you seem to love this nons
you lt you seem to love this nons. I
don't know what it is right but you seem
you seem to love this pedophile but yet
you claim that you don't like pedophiles.
It's so weird. It's so [ __ ] weird, lad. Okay.
Well, so do you not find it hard for
somebody like me that's not had sex
then? Someone that's actually shown
[ __ ] that's actually shown that
they've been in bed with women naked. I
mean, I would find that even harder than
someone showing a disabled girlfriend.
There's no proof they've had sex. It
Listen, listen. We're going This is
going to sound immature to you, but this
is the way it is. If he has not proved
that he has had sex, he has not had sex.
If a [ __ ] is not sex to you and me
being in bed with women naked is not
sex, then a girlfriend is damn sure not
sex. It's as simple as that. You have
made up excuses for me, right? So, I
don't know if he's had sex. There's no
proof. Think about it. The bro job is
not proof. Me being in bed with women
naked is not proof. Then, bro, a
girlfriend ain't proof. It's simple as
that. If it's like calling a porn star a virgin. Yeah.
You You find it hard, bro. Bro, there's
no finding it hard with me. You've seen the business. [ __ ] hell.
You're mad, bro. Just give it up, bro.
You're biased. Simple.
You know, there was way more chance of
him being a virgin than me, but you only
like to suck his dick when he's called a
virgin. And another thing is, what did
you say, Joe? You said that you don't
believe I'm a virgin. Um, one second,
Steven Howard. You said that you don't
believe that I'm a virgin, but you just
won't say anything because I know it.
So, why are you sucking your boyfriend's
dick then? Why don't you Why don't you
keep your opinions to yourself, you and
LT, but nope. You you just want to suck
dick when when I'm when I'm when I'm
talking about their boyfriend
girlfriend. Girlfriend. Isn't that right
though, Steven Howard? They've literally
said before that they they know that I'm
not a virgin, but they're not going to
say anything. So what? You only want to
suck your boyfriend's dick. Only when I
call him a virgin.
Stop sucking dick again when I'm talking
about Oh, I find it hard to believe he
got a girlfriend. Mate, it's probably
because your virgin is just like him.
You know, you hate the truth, to be
honest. But no, you don't let it go when
I call him one. No, you [ __ ] suck his
dick every time. You and LT. And you
know what I said to LT? Do you know what
I said to LT? I said that you've seen
the business, but you don't say anything
when he's calling me a virgin. But me, I
call him a virgin. You [ __ ] sucking
his [ __ ] you biased [ __ ] And at the
end of the day, I'm not scared of LT, so
I can say all of this stuff. Jo, I can
say all of these things. Things [ __ ]
things. [ __ ] am I saying? You suck your
boyfriend's dick. Just come out the closet.
So why don't you keep your opinions to
yourself then, Joe, when I'm talking
about your boyfriend? Let everyone Let
everyone know it.
Why do you Why do you not just let it
play out? Why don't you just let two
people call each other virgins? You
won't have anything said about your
boyfriend. You are LT the little batty man.
You will not say anything have anything
said about your boyfriend, will you Joe?
Am I right, Steven Howard?
It doesn't matter if I paid and No. One
second. One sec. One second. One second.
One second. One second. Hold on. Hold
on. Hold on. Um, actually, I didn't pay
all of them women. And Okay. And even if
I did pay all of them women, then what?
Have you seen him have sex with his girlfriend?
One second. One second. One second. One
second. One second. So, I paid Sig for
sex. I paid a 19-year-old for sex. I
paid the woman on my birthday for sex. I
paid the woman in Nottingham for a
[ __ ] And I paid that woman for sex
on my birthday. So, I paid all of these
women for sex. Okay, bro. Yeah. Yeah, I
did. I paid them all a million pounds.
And what's your point? It's more than a girlfriend.
You're [ __ ] biased [ __ ]
You're a little It's It's the truth. You
got You're touchy about your boyfriend.
And do you know what I said to LT as
well, Jo? I told him, "Do not ever
[ __ ] cry when these people are
telling you that you're white and you
and you didn't go to Scotland. If you're
fast enough to suck your boyfriend's
dick and be biased, you deserve
everything you get.
You deserve everything you get, bro. I
could literally have only been with
Escorts. And And then And what's your
point? At least I've shown me having
sex. I've shown more than a girlfriend.
I've shown way more than a girlfriend.
So, one second. Why do you not let both
play? One second. No one typ.
And if you know he's not a virgin, why
do you butt in and suck dick every time
I call him a virgin?
Why would you button? Oh, don't say that
about him. He's got a girlfriend. Why do
you suck dick?
Why the [ __ ] do you suck dick every time
I call him a virgin? Just Just don't say
anything then. But you won't have
anything said about your boyfriend. Oh,
touchy about your boyfriend, aren't you?
You [ __ ] little [ __ ]
Yeah, bro. I paid four women for sex. [laughter]
Okay, bro. Of course I did, bro. What
does that mean? No, no, no, no, no, no,
no, no. What? It doesn't matter what's
unlikely. I can tell you what's a
definite. I can tell you what's a
definite that I haven't had sex. I have
not had sex. That is It is a definite
that I've had sex. Okay, Dusty. Like,
okay, I'm going to repeat myself again.
Right. So, I have shown me having a
[ __ ] I have shown me in bed with
women naked. I have had women, right,
um, admitted to sleeping with me, right?
He's only shown a girlfriend. So what is
more proof? Think about it like this.
Okay, watch it. Right, let's do the
whole thing now. We have shown me
kissing women. We have shown me getting
my dick sucked. We have seen me naked in
women's beds. We have seen me [ __ ]
having women admit to sleeping with me.
Is that not more evidence than a
girlfriend? Do you not think that maybe,
just maybe, if people was not biased,
they would have a lot more to say about
him calling me a virgin than me calling
him a virgin. There's literally more
chance of him being a virgin than me.
Like, bro, we're having it out right
here. No, no, no, no, no. One second,
bro. One second. Listen to what you're
saying. Listen, listen to what you're
saying. What have I shown? And what have
he What has he shown?
There is 100 million% more chance that
he's a virgin than someone like me.
Someone like me, mate. I've been doing
this for [ __ ] years, right? I've been
doing this for years. So, at the end of
the day, bro, that is definitely
definitely sucking his dick. Because if
you was if you was generally, like I've
said multiple times, I repeat myself. If
you generally was not biased, why has LT
not said anything about him calling me a virgin?
Okay, he's not biased. Okay, he's saying
what's right. Okay. So, by rights then
would we not see people talk about him
calling me a virgin? Someone that's
shown more than a girlfriend. It is
biased. There's no You can't argue
against it, bro. It's It's in black and white. You know,
you're biased. It's the same thing with the money.
Yeah. Exactly, bro. Yeah. And I'm
telling him how he's a virgin. He's a
virgin with a girlfriend. And I've
explained to you how he's a virgin, lad.
Yeah. Yeah. But LT No, but the thing is
with No, no, no, no. But the thing is,
LT, but Dusty, but we're talking about
LT as well. LT says that he doesn't like these people.
So why is he sucking a virgin's dick?
Why is he sucking a virgin's dick just
cuz he's got a disabled girlfriend? I
told him about himself. Why do you
think, bro? Why do you think the guy
does not message me? Cuz I'm right. I'm
right about him. Why do you think he
didn't message me back, bro? I said,
"Stop sucking your boyfriend's dick. Get
a room." Yeah, cuz it's the truth, bro.
It's the truth. Come on, bro.
It is the truth, lad.
So, don't cry about people being biased.
Oh my god. I'm not jealous of somebody
that dates disabled. I'm Bro, no, no,
no. Do you know what it looks like? It
looks like you people are jealous of me
stalking me every day, having me on your
devices. It sounds and looks like you're
jealous of me, bro. Jealous of someone
better looking that can actually get
normal women. I'm not the ones with
channel dedicated to people. It looks
like and is that you're jealous of me.
It does more than sound like, bro, you
are the ones that have got channels
dedicated to me just cuz I'm better
looking. No one's jealous of you people, bro. [snorts]
Bro, bro, bro, bro, bro, bro, bro. No
one cares what any of you believe. He is
100% a virgin. Until you show that dick
inside that vagina, you're a virgin.
Same thing as you said to me, bro. Same
as what you said to me. I don't care
what you believe. Until you prove you've
had sex, you're a virgin. Simple as that, mate.
Until you prove you're a virgin. Simple
as that. I'm saying to them what they're
saying to me now, Steven Howard. Think
of it, bro. A [ __ ] is not proof that
someone's had sex, right? Um being in
women's beds naked is not proof. So, a
girlfriend ain't proof. A girlfriend is
nowhere near proof. Isn't that right, Steven lad?
They're not sleeping together. He's
never been anywhere near her. There's no
proof. Where is the evidence? Where is
the proof, bro? They might not even be
in a relationship. Steven Howard, who we
For all we know. For all we know,
that could be his carer. Think about it,
bro. Like, I'm I'm agreeing with what
these people are saying. I' I I could be
a virgin. We don't know, bro. showing
you getting a [ __ ] showing you in
bed naked with women. That's not proof.
So, a girlfriend can't be proof. It's as
simple as that.
It's weird, bro. Do you know what I'm saying, bro?
It's got a girlfriend can't be proof.
Think about it, bro. Think about it. If
If a [ __ ] isn't proof, if if what I'm
shown is not proof, then I know a
girlfriend ain't proof. That's not
proof. Who knows? We don't know if
they're actually together. Yeah. [snorts]
Yeah. So do you, bro. No one's jealous
of you [ __ ] ugly people. Bro, you are
the ones that are jealous of me. And
listen, I've been with women, Jake, and
none of them were disabled. None of them
were fat. They could all talk, unlike your boyfriends.
Another dick sucker.
If a g if a [ __ ] [ __ ] and and
being in women's bed, then I know a
girlfriend ain't proof. I'm going on
what these people are saying. You want
to try and call me a virgin,
then someone with a girlfriend is
definitely a virgin. 100 million% a
Simple. I know I'm right. I know I'm [ __ ] right.
Sucking on that dick again. Stop sucking
on that dick. No one's [ __ ] jealous
of you and your boyfriend that attacks
vulnerable disabled women. No one's
scared of your boyfriend. I told LT this as well.
Do you remember when LT was doing it as
well? He was sucking dick. LT was
sucking dick. And he's the first one to cry, lad.
He's Of course you hate me. Cuz you're
jealous of me.
All of you people that hate me and
you're just uglier than me. Why is that,
Jake? Why is that? Why is your boyfriend
got missing teeth? Why is your boyfriend
in a bedsit? Why is your boyfriend got a disabled girlfriend?
Why is he jealous of me? I'm going to
start waking people up.
Yeah, stop sucking your boyfriend's
dick. You're going to get a sore throat. [snorts]
Why would why would you upload a video
of yourself? To prove it, obviously. Yeah. [snorts]
Bro, what the [ __ ] man? Yeah, man.
You know the maddest thing is yet if you
got a girlfriend tomorrow, which I've
already had one, they would still talk [ __ ]
You know, they would still talk [ __ ]
You could literally get You could
literally get married, bro. These people
would still talk [ __ ] Even if you got
[ __ ] married, bro. If you got
married, they'd still talk [ __ ]
LT, you always used to say, "Oh, I'm not
going to these places anymore." People
say I don't go there. People are trying
to say that I'm white. People are saying
this. People are saying that. Oh, I
don't like these biased people, bro.
I don't like these biased people, bro.
Hey, do you know what's [ __ ] bro? How
can you hate someone that you don't even know?
That is, you know, it's
you can hate someone that you don't even
know. That's weird.
You can hate someone that you don't even know, lad.
That is weird, bro.
Well, Steven Howard, I did go on
Nonsex's channel and I can't see LT
anywhere, bro. Talking about the 19year-old
Yeah. How we doing, John? Lad, you're
right, man. I can't I can't see him
anywhere talking about the 19year-old
and [ __ ] singing that. [snorts]
Yeah, I went I went to see that maybe,
but not. But best believe if I call him
a virgin, we'll start hearing about this
girlfriend again. Oh, don't say that.
He's got a girlfriend. How's it
possible? You [ __ ] little [ __ ]
Yeah, exactly. Indigo go. Exactly, bro.
Bro, you got to understand, bro. If they
if they really thought you was a
wronging Yeah. they would distance
themselves away from you.
They would actually distance themselves
away from you. Do you know what my
friend in Amsterdam said? Yeah. He said
that these people would stop. Yeah. But
they would only stop if you ignore them
for like a year.
But maybe I don't I don't even think
they would stop then to be honest, bro.
What if you just done videos for like a
year and you didn't respond? Nah, [screaming]
I don't think they would, bro. I I don't
I don't think they would. I don't think
they would ever stop, bro.
I don't think so. Whether you're on air,
you're not. I don't think they would
ever stop. They're actually obsessed.
They are generally generally generally generally obsessed. [snorts]
When you're better looking than these
people, they don't like you. I noticed
this trend years ago. Anyone that's
younger and better looking, they
dislike. You got to understand this is
the waster community. They're all fat.
They're all old. They're all ugly.
They're all full of hate. They see a
newcomer, younger, better looking. They
don't like you, mate. They will find
things to have problems with you, mate,
cuz you're not losers like them. They'll
never tell you this, Steven Allard. This
is the way it is. [snorts]
No, but seriously, man.
Yeah, it is weird, bro. It is very weird.
They got so much hate and um [ __ ] for
someone that they've never met. It's
mad, bro. It is. It is mad.
I can tell you, Indigo. [snorts] I I can
tell you. I can tell you. I can tell
Hands up. I can tell you.
I put my hand up like you put up with the teacher
cuz they're jealous bastards. That's why, bro.
It's cuz they're jealous.
It's think about it. Think about it.
Think about it. Yeah. Think about it.
Indigo. Yeah. What do people tell you to
do? Yeah. You say you meet Okay. Say you
you say you met a woman. Say you met a
woman, bro. And she and she was a
bastard. She was a [ __ ] Yeah. Let's
just say you met a woman. Yeah. and then
she was being shitty or whatever. What
would you do?
Would you obsess over that woman for 6
years or would you find a new [ __ ]
You'd find a new [ __ ]
Yeah, you'd find a new [ __ ]
But these people
Okay. Do you want me to give you an example?
Why do you think I don't respond to the virgin?
Why do you think I don't have a channel
based on the skin one in the shitty
cancel bed? Cuz I know I'm better than
someone that's got no teeth. I'm better
than someone that's a virgin. I'm better
than someone that is on a grand a month.
I'm better than. So I know that if I'm
wasting my life on them, they're better
than me, but I'm better than them.
Do you understand?
We don't know. Like I said, if a
blowjob's not sex, a girlfriend ate sex.
We can guess, but we we don't know.
We don't know, lad. We We generally
generally don't. I don't know if they've
had sex or not. We don't know. A
girlfriend is not enough proof. We need
actual proof. Isn't that right?
We need like we need some porno out there.
LT is LT one of LT one of the Bravesy. Um,
no. He's definitely definitely a virgin.
Definitely definitely definitely a virgin
until he shows. He's a big big virgin.
And a girlfriend with disabilities ain't
proven me wrong. Sorry mate. You
[snorts] can all suck his dick all you
want, but if a [ __ ] ain't sex, a
girlfriend ain't sex in my book. But
they won't have that, will they? Debas bastards.
I know, bro. Of course,
Dusty's on our side.
Dusty's on our side, lad.
Hello, Dusty. You all right?
What in the act of sex?
But what about the virgin? The skin virgin.
Well, when he starts showing some sex,
mate, I'll believe he's not a virgin. Yeah.
You know, LT. Yeah. He proved that he
was one of them because he started
saying B and we.
I said, I knew you was one of them. As
soon as they start the [ __ ] talking
about that girlfriend, they give
themselves away. Don't say that about
it, bro. [ __ ] virgin.
You're nothing but a nasty, stinky virgin.
You [ __ ] nasty virgin.
And a [ __ ] girl with disabilities
ain't proven you ain't one.
So come back when you got the proof,
lad. Last year I proved it, lad. I've
showed me getting a [ __ ] I've shown
me in women's beds naked
several times, bro.
And no one defends me like they defend their boyfriend.
Don't say that about him. He's got a girlfriend.
Don't say that about him. Someone's
touchy about their boyfriend. Steven Howard, you know,
if they were living happily, why why is
he stalking me every day on YouTube?
Happy people don't do that. Nah, none of
these none of these people that do this
are happy because if they were happy,
they literally would leave you the [ __ ] alone.
Dad, you can't even say you're happy.
You know, the thing is these people
literally can't even say they're happy.
Well, you defend your boyfriend about
this girlfriend and he's a nons. I would
have thought you would have just said
what was right. You're not living
happily. Living happily, being jealous
of me on YouTube every day. You're
living happy. You [ __ ] virgin.
You're living happy. I could safely say
for a fact that every single person on
here that [ __ ] with me are not happy, Dad.
They literally are unhappy people. that
I could I could actually say that
[ __ ] living in your council bed [ __ ]
Still a virgin. Didn't go broad until
you was [ __ ] 30. You're nothing but a
little virgin. What could you be happy
about? You being a big virgin.
[ __ ] you [ __ ] mad at No, I'm
making myself a cup of tea.
You used to call me a virgin. I'm a
[ __ ] virgin yourself. You [ __ ]
virgin. You never stuck your [ __ ]
dick up women. That's why you still call
them women that I've been with.
Because you're nothing but a nasty virgin yourself.
He's the virgin. The virgin on sex.
Virgin. You are the virgin.
Thanks for that.
Just myself a cup of tea. D, would you
like a cup of tea?
>> Dusty, you know, you know nonslegs. Do
you know how non You know how Nons's dad
met um his mom?
The [ __ ] he his dad was his mom's teacher. [snorts]
Nah, bro. I can never be cool with LT ever again.
I can never be cool with LT ever again,
lad. Cuz with the thing is with LT,
Dusty. Yeah. I kind of thought we was on
the same level because obviously we had
traveled to places. He dealt with [ __ ]
I dealt with [ __ ] I was willing to
forgive and stuff and I thought we was
on the same level. I actually heard a
guy talk and I thought let bygones be
guy bygones but sorry bro when someone
starts being biased it starts raising red flags.
You can defend who you want. I don't
want you to be a yes man. You can if you
don't want to believe someone's a
virgin, then don't believe that they're a virgin,
you know, but the thing is you have not
said anything about anyone calling me a virgin.
Why have you not said anything? And then
you started using the same excuses. So
mate, I had to swerve you. Simple as
that. I have to swerve bias people. Yeah.
Oh, mate, I'm ready for call. I've got
my little evidence pack.
I've got my little evidence pack. It's
up to 174 pages now. It's called
harassment. I need to I need to rename
it. Peter Belly's evidence pack,
mate. I've got my little evidence pack
ready. I added a couple more things to
it the other day. I got a big evidence pack.
This guy's [ __ ] bro. Trust me. I
spoke to my solicitor the other day as
well, but I had to go to the police
thing about something else. He said,
"Yeah, the guy's [ __ ] As long as
you've got stuff," I said, "I've got
everything that this cunt's been doing,
harassing me, uh, calling me millions of
I've got the [ __ ] lot. So, trust me,
it's not going to go down well with the judge."
Um, so yeah,
you're going downtown, Virgin boy.
Do you know what, mate?
Do you know what mate? You're under
arrest for being a stinky dirty virgin.
That's what I would do if I was a police
officer. I'd find out where you live and
I'd nick you on suspicion of being a
virgin. A stinky dirty copycat virgin, mate.
You're under arrest for being a virgin.
And I look at you with when I say that, mate.
[ __ ] hell. Yeah, leave me alone. I
don't want you.
Leave me alone. I know your girlfriend's
never not given you sex and you're still
a virgin, but I'm not taking your
virginity. It's not my fault you're
still a virgin. You and Jo can maybe
make love. Why don't you just all get
together? I I don't swing that way.
Sorry, I don't want you. I'm not gay.
And to be honest with you, you're not my
type, even if I was gay. So, you know,
leave me alone. I don't want you. Just
like Britney never wanted you. Never
did, never will, never have, never will.
Not interested in you.
Then you tried to compare the me and you
were say Izzy story to you and Britney.
Well, how comes I saw boobies? How comes
I I got some punali? How can I tell you
exactly what the body looks like? I bet
you can't tell me what Britney's body
looks like cuz you never had that
pleasure. You never had that that um
Yeah. You never had the pleasure in
seeing her booby lungs.
Isn't that right, lad?
You're nothing but a [ __ ] That's what
I think. You think I'm taking your
virginity? I'm not doing it, mate. [ __ ] off.
I'm not taking his virginity. Greavvesy,
you come [ __ ] right off, mate. Leave me alone.
Britney weren't into you.
Britney don't want to know.
Then you was trying to um say that, "Oh,
Britney don't exist." You're a bad liar.
You know that. You're a very bad liar.
Just like you done with the Cheryl Cole thing.
Oh, I I never said she was hot. No one
said that. You said So Cole was hot. I
brought her up to you.
Yes. And then you looked her up and I
remember exactly what you said. You was
like, "You can't deny she's attractive.
So attractive. If you don't like her,
you're gay." I said, "I don't find her
attractive." You said, "You're gay." Uh,
and then you also said, "My dick don't
have a mind. When I look at her, my dick goes odd."
You didn't tell anyone on YouTube that
though, did you? You little [ __ ] copycat.
Just like the football thing. You
[ __ ] copy. Yeah. There you little copycat.
You [snorts] can just sit here and just
And you know, it's better than TV,
Grezy. It is actually better than TV,
Grezy. Watching a bunch of people copy
themselves, copy each other. Think about
it, Grezy. It's better than TV. greasy.
Just watching people copy other people,
it's quite entertaining, isn't it?
You wanted to fit in with the crowd, didn't you?
So, why am I Why would I be gay then?
Um, for not liking Cheryl Cole. Can you
please explain? You did say that and you
didn't say it to annoy me. You didn't
say it to annoy me either.
You didn't say it to annoy me either
because you was meeting me at the same
time. So why would you try to annoy me?
You never said it about any other woman.
Is it because her name's Cheryl Cal? No.
Go on, Grevy. I want you to answer me.
Right. Why did he Why was he calling me
gay when I Cuz I didn't find Cheryl Co
attractive. Why am I gay?
Why am I Why Why would I be gay? How How
am I gay, Indigo?
What? Because I don't find this person
attractive. That's not fair, is it? Why
am I not allowed Am I not allowed a different type,
Grezy? Am I not allowed a different preference? Yeah. [snorts]
But I'm not gay, Indigo. I promise you
I'm not gay. Steven Howard, why did Nons
say that I'm I'm gay if I don't like
Sher Cole? I'm not gay.
I promise you I'm not gay. Why did he say that?
He never called me gay before. That Steven Howard.
No, you literally said if you don't find
her attractive, you're gay.
One second. Well, she's a good-looking
woman. All the normal size women you
call fat and the men and things you say
about I say the strong posit you are.
So, what if I Okay. Okay. One second.
Okay. So, what if I like women with
bigger boobs? What if [snorts] I liked
black women only? What if I only liked
blonde women with blue eyes? Would I
still be gay? One second, [ __ ]
Right. Settle down, [ __ ] Greavvesy.
Greavvesy. Indigo. Uh, Steven Howard,
settle down, [ __ ] I'm trying to speak.
Settle down, [ __ ] I'm trying to speak
and when you keep typing, you keep
making me forget. So, if I like black
women only, right, or I like women with
blue eyes and big boobs, but I didn't
like Chev attractive. Do you think maybe
people just have got a different type of
women that they go for? Do you think
maybe, just maybe?
Yeah, she's better than her. Yeah. Do
you think maybe
I've just got a mind of my own and I
don't follow the trend? Don't follow the crowd?
Do you think maybe or just straight to
like a dick? I mean, what's what's the chances?
I don't know
how people could say she's attractive.
She's not attractive. She's like mediocre. Of
course it is.
She's not good-looking at all. She's
like a five or a six. She's not good-look.
Never ever ever. Oh, okay. [snorts]
No, she's not good-looking.
She's definitely definitely not good-looking.
If you don't like Chev Cole, you're gay.
No, you're copying.
Copying the crowd.
Literally copying the crowd.
You wanted to fit in. Yeah.
So, wait, wait, wait, wait. So, so if I
if I don't like Cheryl Cole, but I like
black women and I like women with blue
eyes, I'm still gay. Even though I I've
slept with them women and I've never
been with a man, I'm I'm still gay.
I wonder if their name wasn't Cheryl
Cole, would he still be saying the same
thing? What do you think, Grezy?
Let's ask Griezy for help. He's like I
like Griezy. He's like David Dickinson.
He he butts in when he needs to to give
advice. I mean, what if they they they
uh what if the person's name wasn't
Cheryl Carl? Do you think people would
still be calling you gay?
You know, let's ask for help.
Yeah, I watch David Dickson sometimes.
He uh he butts in um he gives advice
saying, "Oh, you should take it to
auction or not."
What do you think? Rezy
say, okay, let's just say that she come
on YouTube and and and her name weren't Sheble Carl.
So why why wouldn't they say that then?
So what you're saying is that it's the name.
Okay. No, let's just say Okay. Let's
just say Autum had the same H.
Let's just say, let's just say, let's
just say, let's just say, let's just say
that all was Cheryl Cole, but her name
wasn't Shevel Cole. She just looked like Cheryl Cole.
It's the name. Nonsense. It's the name.
You saw a trend and you didn't want to
feel left out cuz of them Scottish lads.
They used to pick on you. Miles and Jackie,
the Glass Region lads. That's why you
started talking about Sher C. Don't lie.
Don't lie, mate. Don't lie.
You didn't want to feel left out.
Yeah. [snorts] No, no, no. They can find
them good-looking, Grevy. No, no, no,
Greavvesy. They can find them
good-looking. They can find them
good-looking. Yeah. Yeah. But if they're
trying to say that you're gay because
you don't find them attractive. Yeah,
that is copying. No. Yeah, that bit's
copying though. Like I like Sydney
Sweeney. I saw the horror film. I didn't
even know who the [ __ ] she was until a
couple of months ago. But would I say
that you're gay if you don't find her attractive?
No. That is copying. I remember before,
bro. Uh back in 2009.
Um I don't know if you remember Beyonce.
I said, "Oh, I don't find Beyonce
attractive to my my um mom." Sorry, not
my mom, my sister. And she looked at me weird, greasy.
She said, "You got a screw loose." I
think Yeah, it was Beyonce. Yeah.
And I said, "Oh, I don't really um Yeah,
she's not really for me." She looked at
me weird and said I had a
said that I had a screw loose. This was
back in 2009.
I don't know, man.
Strange, isn't it?
That Rihanna one was definitely copying
Grezy. Grezy, that was definitely
copying. That Rihanna one.
No, that Rihanna one was definitely
definitely definitely copying
cuz I never saw anything special with
that Rihanna ever.
No, that one was definitely copying as well.
Never ever found. No, bro. What the
[ __ ] They used to talk about Rihanna as well.
Grez, they used to talk about Rihanna. [laughter] Yeah.
Yeah. It's all to do with the name. Greasy.
Yeah. It's all to do with the name, lad. [gasps]
Cuz didn't you see on the student inform
Grezy, weren't they calling each other
gay for not liking Shevil Car?
What's the chances that they're saying
the same thing as Nons said?
What's the chances? [snorts]
Your [ __ ] dad was 42 and your mom was 12.
That's [snorts] disgusting, mate. Absolutely vile.
[ __ ] no wonder he was [ __ ] put
into care at a young age.
[sighs and gasps]
He was [snorts] put to care.
So what Greavvesy when So really was
they actually talking about Sher Co in
school? Really? Grievy, be honest with
me now. Tell me you're not trolling me.
[laughter] What? So waiting to go in the
class, they were talking about her. No,
be serious though. Are you actually
trolling me or were they actually
talking about her? >> [snorts]
>> [ __ ] hell.
How comes you've got missing front teeth?
You absolute virgin.
Why have you got [ __ ] missing front teeth?
See, the thing is, Indigo. Yeah. No, but
seriously. Yeah. Because you talk
normal. They say they say that they do
this every day because you've said stuff
about uh children, people's kids and stuff.
I don't know, man. I don't think that
justifies being obsessed with someone
every day, all day, every day in 2026
because someone said stuff about kids.
Nah, that doesn't justify it, bro. That's
I mean, that is It's like what you said.
Wouldn't they just live their life if
they were better than you?
You would they I would have just thought
they would just
they what they say just doesn't make
sense, bro. They say that they they go
for you because you said stuff about people's kids.
That's what they say. But that's silly,
bro. If you think about it, in 2026,
that is strange, bro. That is like very very very
cuz when they I I just I don't I don't
get them, bro.
Yeah, LT. Yeah, they all do it. [snorts]
Why do you think they do it every day?
Indigo, do you think they're just like
homosexuals or what?
No, nothing's worse than that virgin.
Nothing's worse than that little virgin.
Nothing's [snorts] worse than virgin, boy.
Yeah. Their lives are so good, man.
You remember that Jamie Thompson? Oh, I
got I got to put his picture back up.
I got to put their picture I got to put
his picture back up, bro.
I'm surprised he hasn't took it down yet.
You sure that [ __ ] ain't in a wheelchair, bro? wheelchair? Yeah. Yeah, bro.
No, no, no. Sorry.
Yeah, a lot of people are obsessed with me, bro.
Even virgin boy. Virgin boy.
What the [ __ ] bro?
That is mad. Imagine looking like that, bro. [laughter]
Did you think it was funny when I
started emailing LT Greavvesy? Was you
rubbing your hands? [snorts]
Yeah. I wonder what happened to Ricky Millington.
Maybe he's just taking a break from YouTube, Dusty. Yeah.
How could this Joe F say,
"Yeah, I'm not gambling anymore." Steven Howard
No, I've never had trouble with him. Uh, Grezy,
I've never had trouble with Maf. I
remember who he is, though. Hey guys,
Math's Heart here.
Yeah, he was a weirdo, bro. I've never
had problems with him.
Yeah, I'd remember who he is though.
Hey guys, maths aren't here. What do you
think of Andy Marget being a compulsive
gambling? Compulsive gambler. He he he
he gambled through the roof, Greavvesy.
And he's and his wife found the letter
and kicked him out. It's not funny, is
it? What gambling does to people, Greavves?
It's not funny what it does, is it to people.
Good old Andy Marget.
Imagine that Greavesy dying over a roulette table.
dying over a roulette table. Grezy,
no more gambling anymore. Um,
Steven Hour lad, sorry, bro. I've I've
packed it in
I call I call London Taylor Taylor Swift.
Yeah, I like J Blinks. He's cute.
Oh gosh. Busy. Taylor Swift.
Do you like Taylor Swift? Look, Scriezy. Taylor Swift.
She'd go nice in the collection,
wouldn't she, Greavesy?
Well, they're a lot of people according to you. Greasy.
Someone on Reddit said, "Well, women
aren't people according to you, is it?"
I said, "I want to collect women." They
was like, "What are you even talking about?
No, I haven't seen him for a little
while. I need to buy the game cuz I can
cancel the membership. My membership.
What? Franklin and his little dog chop.
You remember when I used to go women
hunting every week, Greavesy,
to get my little nutrients? Is that cute?
Um, I'm 28.
You make me laugh. You know, Greavvesy,
when you said, "Oh, women, there's some
women that just go to work and stuff."
They shouldn't be going to work,
Greavvesy. It should be satisfying Peter Belly's needs,
not going to work to pay rent and stuff.
That's cute, isn't it, Grezy?
They need to satisfy Peter Belly's
needs. What's wrong with them? You know,
cuz you do realize, Grezy, that you're
eventually going to get [ __ ] over.
You're alone, lad. You're alone right
now. You're self projecting.
You need to [ __ ] them over before they
[ __ ] you over.
Grezy, you know that.
Yep. Yep. Yep. Yep. Yep. Yep. Yep. Yep.
You know they're going to [ __ ] you over.
These women, Greavvesy, if you get with one,
look at what my mama done to me, Greavvesy.
Did you felt Did you feel sorry for me
when that happened?
You bloody should have done. [snorts]
Yeah, I love Crash Crash Bandicut.
I got Yoda. I got Crash Bandicut. I
don't need anyone else,
you know. [snorts]
What do you think of this women woman I
was speaking to on Instagram when I
showed her my little evidence and she
ignored it? Why did she ignore it, do
you think, Griezy? I showed her the
screenshots of what the woman was doing
and she was kind of dismissing it.
Any reasons why Indigo or Grey or
any idea? She said um
I don't know what did she say?
She was making excuses. She said okay so
granted not being vegetated. Why did I
get that? That one girl that met someone
literally two days later is crazy. How
are they leading you on and stuff?
Strange. Why are they making excuses?
Greasy Indigo, do you know why they're
making excuses or
I wonder what what what do you reckon
they're making excuses for, lad?
No, no. What I meant is I showed her
like uh the screenshots of like the
women leading me on and [ __ ] and playing games
and she was kind of like making excuses for them.
Any idea why or
Indigo? Any any idea why?
Is there any reason why?
Why do you reckon that she making excuses? Greasy. Cuz
obviously none of the people in the
messages were men, were they? They were all women. Any ideas?
Don't laugh at me, lad.
Wonder what they were making excuses for. Grezy,
she's like, "Oh yeah, one woman met
someone two." Yeah, but she obviously
didn't meet someone two days.
What do you reckon?
Any ideas, Greavesy?
So, what's the point of me dating then,
Greavvesy? If the whole world's against
me, why would I be bothering dating when
when the whole world is against men?
What's the point in them dating? You
can't do right for doing wrong.
So, is there any point of Peter Benny
even trying to date any more grievy? You know, [snorts]
No. Why are you not answering my
question, Greavvesy? Why are they making
excuses for them?
Please don't tell me it's a gender thing. Grey
Grey, it's not Grezy.
Greasy, can I moan up? Can I complain
about men? Grezy and see if I get the same reaction. We
Steven Howard, what's your opinion on it?
Grieves, what's your opinion on it?
[sighs and gasps]
shirt. You like Nicole Sherzinger?
Yeah. She's got fake boobies though.
Fake boobies don't count.
Yeah, but she's got fake boobies, so Yeah.
Um, who do I like?
I like Yoda and Ja.
You're a sad bastard you are, Jamie Thompson.
Sad sad bastard.
Yeah, Nicole Shig. I know who that is.
She's got fake boobies. Greasy.
She might have a good mouth though.
Obviously, Grezy, I go for the mouth,
don't I? Greasy. It's all about the mouth.
Oh, these baby reels are so cute, Grezy.
These baby reels are so cute.
Have you seen them? The little baby reels. Oh,
this Indian woman was sending me these
uh baby reels cuz she wants a baby in it.
Oh, they're so cute.
Oh, Grey, that's so cute. Greavvesy.
So cute. The little bubbles. Oh,
what do you think about little babies?
Why not we? Why? No.
Of course I can have I can have a child.
Why would it get whised straight into
the care system?
Why? Why would it be taken?
Why though? Grievy,
I think I'd be a good dad.
Grievy, do you actually think that I'm a
troll? I'm not a troll, am I? This UK
signing says that I'm a troll. Why am I a troll?
Why would I be a troll, bro?
UK signing. Why do you think I'm a troll? Roulette. No.
Oh, these babies are so cute, man.
Babies are cute.
Greasy's a funny troll, you know.
No, what I do, Grezy, I'd steal all the baby's milk.
No, but and also Grezy, I I'd want all
the milk as well, would it?
Is that right?
Isn't that right, Grezy?
Yeah, I'd also want all the milk and
there'd be no milk for the baby grievy. Could
you imagine if if you were say Izzy was
was pregnant Greavesy, how big her
boobies would be.
Lots of nutrients and stuff.
I like nutrients.
I don't care about vaginas. I just like
mouths. mouths. As long as they've got a
mouth and they've got boobs, that's
enough for me.
Don't care about vaginas.
Just a mouth and boobs in it. That's
enough. You You always have to weigh up
the mouth cuz Greavves have got quite a
large penis, you see. So, obviously, if
their mouth is quite small, I can't You
know what I mean? Yep. Oh gosh.
I still watch it sometimes.
I agree with you. You would have laughed
your ass off the way Ant-Man said this
to me. Ant-Man was like money. And
Antman was like, "You watch porn from the 70s?
That is [ __ ] weird." He said
grievously. He said he knows a lot of
people that watch porn, but you watch
porn from the 70s. I said, "Yeah."
He said, "That is so weird." Yeah.
I was watching some vintage porn today.
Actually, they were getting [ __ ] in the car.
I need to start this collection soon.
Should I add Autumn in my collection of
women? Nah, she's not good enough.
Autumn's not good enough.
Let me look at the mouth. One second. Nah,
Autumn's no good. He's not going to be
part of my collection. Nope.
Not good enough for me. Nope.
She's not good enough. Greasy.
Nope. Not good enough. >> [snorts]
>> Mate, you're not the only one that
couldn't do it with his misses. He
hasn't done it either with her. Uh, get
it? He also couldn't do it with her, but
that's cuz he's got erectile
dysfunction. H, is that right, Gley?
I'm such a funny [ __ ] Oh, no, mate.
He also can't. His feet don't go in a funny. Yeah.
Do you remember when he was messaging
USA? Is he indigo?
Have you noticed something about
nonslegs as well? He's a proper proper
s. He's a proper white knight. Even that
PC was like, "Oh, why are you sing?"
He was also like, "Why are you sing?"
Yeah, he's a proper white knight. Have
you noticed that?
Yeah, he's a proper proper He's a white
knight as well. A little s.
Another one that just doesn't learn.
Indigo. Just doesn't learn. Doesn't
learn. doesn't learn. You know, 31,
still a virgin,
and you're still defending women.
They grievy. Honestly, lad, you you will
never get through to these people.
Greavvesy. Greavvesy. You It's a mental condition.
It's a mental condition, Greavvesy. You
You won't You can't get through to him,
lad. No matter if they're virgins, women
don't like them. Women despise them.
They will never have a bad word to say about women.
No matter how what their position is in
life, I can't understand them.
I think it's cuz we don't we don't have
a we we didn't have a dady.
Obviously, their dad brings them up that
way, but that that way is not the right
way. I think it's the way their dad
brings them up.
Cuz why is there so many simps in the
world? white knights when their way is
the wrong way.
And it is wrong, but it seems that a lot
of people are like this.
They defend women, but women don't like
them. They've had less women than you,
and some of them are probably virgins,
but they still defend women.
Do you think it's maybe maybe it's from
lack of life experience? Maybe.
I don't know.
Do you remember Grezy? Stop going on
about some girl that don't want you. I'm
not. I miss Bart Quest. You know Fiona
Macdonald. I miss that little account.
Fiona Macdonald. Grezy. I'm not.
Do you remember
Grezy? Do you remember the little
Isabelle days when I used to meet up with Isabelle
and we was on the roulette together?
Cute little times, weren't they?
But no, seriously, I do need to quit um
all kinds of gambling now. Maybe in a
long time I'll go back to the football, but
I can't, bro. I really
I can't do it, bro. It's bad.
Love is bad, bro.
I really can't wait to start this W women collection.
They're so fun to collect and compare. Grievy,
I'll just think about some I've been
with and I'll compare the [ __ ] the
boobs and stuff.
They're very fun to compare. They're like toys.
These women are like toys, you know,
bro. like you could just compare them
and that [snorts] it's funny, bro. You know,
forever and ever.
Why? Why can't I get attached anymore, Grezy?
Why can't I get attached anymore?
Yeah, but what what why could I get attached before?
cuz I already found my mama. Yeah.
So, Indigo, will these people ever leave
me alone on YouTube?
No, Greavves. I like you typing.
Do you think they'll ever leave me alone? Indigo,
I should have took Ronald Pump's advice in it.
I should have took Ronald Pump's advice. Greasy lad.
I need to brush my teeth, bro,
cuz I'm going to go to bed soon. I
brushed them this morning.
Indigo, why do these people stalk me every day?
They don't leave me alone.
Why don't these people on YouTube leave me alone?
Why won't they leave me alone?
What? Should I brush my teeth? Yeah.
I need to brush my teeth, bro.
Yeah, but what about the [ __ ] virgin?
Oh gosh. Might do a little video to
Joseph before I go to bed.
One second. I've lost my teeth here.
I've got a special sensitive um
toothpaste, Grezy, cuz I've got s I I
have sensitive gums. Always
come out first.
Yeah, it is. Yeah.
>> So, I just brushing my teeth.
Peter B owns the Irish, Mr. B.
I own the Irish, lad.
I norally bust my two three times a day,
but it's going to only be twice today.
Yeah. Healed, bro. You know the tooth
that got um that got took out.
I was going to get a [ __ ] hammer to
it. [laughter] It was hurt me that bad.
I'm going to get a [ __ ] hammer to it
in a minute. Remember that one, Breezy? Yeah.
Oh, I always use mouthwash before I brush.
I'm going to get a [ __ ] do in a
minute. Oh, bro, it hurts. You know when
you get your tooth took out 3 days
after. It hurts, isn't it?
Yeah, it does hurt, bro.
Oh, it's it was painful, bro. Like 2 days after.
It's only just healed properly after
like 3 weeks. I'm all good now.
I don't need to go limited to anything.
I'll get a [ __ ] hammer to it, Dusty.
I was going to get a [ __ ] hammer to
it. Oh gosh. Oh, under my little blanket.
Oh [ __ ] hell.
Oh gosh. This blanket is so nice.
[ __ ] hell, man. [snorts] Yeah.
Do you reckon Jamie will ever leave me alone, Indigo?
You reckon if I ignore them, they'll go away? Oh,
do you reckon they'll leave me alone if
I ignore them? Indigo,
what do you think, Dusty?
Yeah, their LTS are spas, bro. He used
to say to me, "Yeah, they do it for reaction."
I said, "Well, I said, "Yeah, but if you
ignore them, they still do it." So, does
it really matter?
Doesn't matter if you react to them or
you don't react to them, bro.
It doesn't really matter. I don't think
they'll ever I don't think they would
ever stop. Well, I think even if you
left for 3 years, I think they would
still do it.
We'd have to test it, bro. We'll have to
test it in it.
No, I think nonslegs would still do it.
I think so, bro. Even after 10 years, I
don't think they would stop, bro. I
don't think they would ever stop. Cuz
where they're so obsessed, the thing is,
bro, where they're so obsessed, I think
that they're always going to think that you're watching.
Hey, hey, Dokock. I was just saying,
yeah, do you think these people will
ever leave me alone on YouTube?
Cuz I feel like I feel like if I ignore
them for like 5 years, I still think
they would do it, lad.
They'd probably think that you're
watching every day. I don't think they
would ever stop, bro. No.
No. I don't think so, bro.
No, it wouldn't be It wouldn't be London
Taylor. It would be Virgin Boy,
they will never stop. No.
Yeah, but LT is a [ __ ] Cuz he says
that they do it for reaction. But I
said, "Yeah, but even if you ignore
them, then they never stop.
Well, I haven't I haven't slept with a
woman for ages, but yeah, I've pulled [ __ ] Yeah.
Well, I haven't been out drinking for
ages, but yeah,
I need to do a video to that, Jo.
So what you're So what you're basically
saying that sock is that even if I come
off YouTube for two years. So saying no
no no uploads for two years and I went
on all the channels, they'd still be doing it.
Is that what you're actually [ __ ]
trying to say?
I'd have to test it, bro. I'd have to test it.
M I'd have to test it.
Yeah, I'd have to, bro. Yeah.
They wish they were me. Don't never be
me, bro. Even at Jo. Yeah. Even if he's
not fat, and that's really him. I bet
you he's an ugly bastard.
I bet you he's an ugly bastard. Even if
he's not fat,
Yeah. Don't never be me, bro. Never be me.
Yeah, that JF. Yeah. O, I was on Lord
Jay's earlier at that. And this guy was
talking about me non-stop.
He was talking about me [ __ ] not,
bro. Every comment he wrote was about me, bro.
Smokey B was obsessed, but he wasn't as
obsessed. He was. Bro, every comment was
about me, bro. I'm thinking, bro, it's
time to just come out the closet now for
everyone's sake. I'm not going to sleep
with you. I don't swing that way. But if
you come out the closet,
it's time to come out the closet, lad.
That is [ __ ] weird, bro. That is so weird.
That is so weird, bro.
Every comment was me, bro.
Every single comment was me.
You wouldn't You won't show your face either.
He won't show his face. Even if he's not
fat, bro, he's stinking just like Nod's legs.
No, Joe's coming out the closet, lad. He
needs to come out of the closet, bro.
I'm going to put him in his place on
this video as well, bro. Saying you're
talking about me. Yeah. Wearing [ __ ]
kids clothes when they're actually made
for adults. Look at your channel, bro.
Your channel is obsessed with me. I'd
rather collect Lego and wear [ __ ]
t-shirts with Spider-Man than [ __ ]
have a channel obsessed with another man
like you, little batty man. And I'm
going to see And I'm going to see what
he's I'm going to see what his response
is going to be.
I'm going to [ __ ] him so badly in this
video, bro. He's not even going to say
nothing back to me. It's going to be
that bad, bro. Seriously. Yeah.
It's just, you know what it is, bro?
This is so addicting, bro. Where these
people are so stupid, bro. It's so addicting.
Like it Oh, it's just so addicting, bro.
That's what it is.
Let me see if that is that.
That Jo does look a lot fatter though.
He does look really fat.
He does look fat in them videos like the
hands and stuff. Weird, isn't it?
He's showing his hands as well.
He's a weird bastard, bro.
I'm going to put this [ __ ] in his place,
bro. And I'm probably going to go to bed. Yeah,
I can't go to I can't go to um leads
cuz it's embarrassing if I go to leads
UK asylum cuz Laney is I'm going to be
bringing people down by doing that
because it's 2026 and and it's like you
haven't learned your lesson.
If I go to leads, then it's like I've
not learned my lesson in all of them
years by with these ugly jealous people.
You're kind of going backwards.
That's why I said to Smokeoky B, I will
happily meet you anywhere in London. You
know, that's being fair. And obviously
with Joe, I'll go to Nottingham.
Yeah, that's fair enough, bro. Cuz that
way it's a reason. It makes sense.
Look at all the times I went to
Manchester full of excuses. All the
times I went to Middlesbrough full of excuses.
It's like there's literally no point in
in in going there, bro. You go halfway.
You want to go there,
they show up, they say [ __ ] They show
up, they don't show up. If they don't
show up, they're [ __ ] Simple. Dumb, bro.
Don't ask them to come to London,
they're never going to come to London.
Oh, 100%. I'm going Sunday. 100%, bro.
100%. then it's not going to be a fight either.
It's not going to be a fight.
And I'll be dealing with this [ __ ] in
Nottingham shortly after as well. So,
I'm not scared of these people, bro.
Yeah, he was talking [ __ ] about me on um
on L's, bro. Even though Joe F was
worse. I'll be dealing with this [ __ ] as
well after. Don't you worry, bro. Yeah.
And he says, "I'm jealous." Jealous of
you? You're the one that's obsessed over
me every day. I got jealous of you.
Why would I be jealous of you, bro? I'm
better looking than you. I've got more
money than you. I've not got a channel
dedicated to you, you clown. Why the
[ __ ] would someone be obsessed with you? You know,
I mean, look, nons is [ __ ] not fat
and I'm better than him and he's jealous
of me. Same with Terry. The summary of
what you people are, you are fat, most
of you people. Okay, so you're not fat.
I need to talk about them gam the
gambling [ __ ] as well, bro. The gambling videos.
I need to I need to talk about the
gambling videos as well. Yeah,
this guy is not going to win against me, bro. Yeah.
Don't know how he's talking about kids
clothes when they're literally made for
adults. I didn't know Marvel only apply to kids. Mad
PJ PJ PJ PJ PJ PJ PJ PJ PJ
Time to come out the closet, lad.
Seriously. seriously is. Yeah.
Who do you reckon's going to win on
Sunday? Indie go. Me or Smokey B?
Me, mate. And by the looks of it, I'll
definitely beat that Joe as well. Definitely, bro.
A lot of these people need to come out
the closet, lad.
the closet. That's why. Um
because I'm I'm I'm Why am I worried? because um well,
basically because I'm trying to help
someone. I'm trying to be a good citizen.
It's time to come out the closet, lad.
It's PJ. It's PJ.
Yeah, man. You need to look at your own
life before judging someone playing with
Lego. In my opinion, you sad bastard. Mia
baby cakes. You just don't know. No.
Yeah, that's what I used to say with
Seaside Mark. If Seaside Mark is so bad,
why do you watch him?
[sighs and gasps] Yeah.
He said he hasn't been to a gym for 20
years. So this [ __ ] has not been
to the gym since he was 18.
What the [ __ ] That is a waste of life.
You've not been to the gym for 20 years
since you was 18.
That is mad, bro. You know, that's
actually a waste of life. That's why I'm
going to the gym soon. It's actually a
waste of life, you know, whilst you're
young. Yeah. You should try to build a nice body.
You should try to um build a nice body,
you know, when you whilst you're still
young. Why have you not gone to the gym
for 20 years?
That is a what a waste of life, bro.
That is a waste of life.
When did I last go gym? Last year, I
think I went gym last year. Yeah, during
the Yeah, I went gym last year. Me?
You haven't been to your gym for 20 years.
That is mad.
Gym's good, man. Yeah.
Yeah. You have nothing in life.
Absolutely zero ambition.
Can't be build meaningful relationships.
They're actually just talking about
themselves. I've got no ambition coming
from the [ __ ] dude that's obsessed
with me every day. Well, I've got no
ambition. Keep blaming women and
everyone else in the country. Oh, I will
do. I will do. And I'll keep blaming
them when I'm in Nottingham as well. Yeah.
I mean, I don't exactly blame people. I
say women are [ __ ] because they are
Yeah, they are [ __ ] I say how I
see it. So what, bro? Yeah. Yeah,
I crave apparently I crave attention.
If I crave attention, why are you giving me attention?
I don't know, bro.
I've got zero ambition, bro. Yet this
guy is sat on YouTube talking about me every day.
Yeah. Okay, man.
I bet you know what? I bet this Jo looks like rice.
I actually I actually uh bet you this
guy looks like rice, bro.
He's another bad looking dude, bro.
Sorry, bro. Sorry.
I know, man. This Jo was talking about
me. Like, I'm going to do a video
straight, bro. I don't want your ass.
You're not getting my ass. So, kindly [ __ ] off.
I'm going to do a video saying that,
bro. like you need to you need to kindly
[ __ ] off cuz you're not getting my ass,
lad. [sighs and snorts] Yeah.
And it's mad because they say that
they're in relationships, but they spend
more time talking about me.
Oh, [ __ ] hell, man.
every single uh people that most people
here that's been exposed have actually
been fat and ugly. So um that's why we
just assumed by your hands
um that you are that you are that you are fat.
But either way that doesn't really mean anything
cuz I mean look at Terry. He's a [ __ ]
He's clapped. Look at Nle. He's He's
[ __ ] lanky and he's clapped.
So yeah, you got some fat hands for
someone that's not [ __ ] uh that's not fat, bro.
I do find [snorts] it weird. I mean, I
could understand if they were going on
about women, Indigo. Yeah, if these
people, they'd rather go on about men
than go on about women.
Think about it, bro.
It's not even like we don't even They go
on more about me than I go on about
women. Think about it, bro. So odd.
Do you not find that mad, um, Dasok,
that they're going about me more than
they're going about women?
talking about people living under
poverty when you're the one living under and Yeah.
Yeah. I know. I know.
Could you [snorts] imagine I actually
got with that autumn rose?
The virgin would get so mad.
So [ __ ] mad, lad.
The skint one. You know the virgin one
in the bedsit.
You spend a lot of time on uh people
that you better than. I give you that,
man. I give you that.
I'd never get without him, bro. Yeah. [gasps]
Yeah, [snorts] bro. Just never get with
anyone on YouTube.
Yeah, I am the king of the tubes, bro.
These people tried shutting me down for years.
They go on more about me than they do women. That's
this guy said I'm fast and got a strong punch, [snorts] bro. Really? >> [snorts]
>> They spend more time on me than their
makebelieve misses. That's
you spend a lot of you invest a lot of
time onto on onto men on the internet.
I never even spent this much time on USA
is he that's
I didn't even spend 1% as much as these
people spend on me than I spent on USA is
you would like I said bro you would
think that they get bored. You would
have thought that they would have got bored.
They never seem to get bored. [ __ ] hell.
They never seem to actually get bored,
which is quite surprising.
No, no, no. We're talking about USA, bro.
I'm just trying to I'm just trying to
compare the two because I went Look at
the thing with USA. Yeah. I actually met
the [ __ ] and I actually [ __ ] the [ __ ] bro.
And well, the thing is, bro, is that
that never went on nowhere near as long
as this has gone on.
Now, this is a woman that I met. So,
this is strange, lad.
I could go and [ __ ] with them every day
if I wanted to, bro. But, you know, and
I never done it every day. Even then, I
Very strange, is it? Look,
I [snorts] don't know why it's just so
comparable. I like to compare that
because obviously you've met them in it
and obviously they're the opposite sex.
So why the [ __ ] are these people on here
obsessed with someone they've not met every day?
Yeah, they're full of hate, bro. They're
full of hate and jealousy. I think it's
because their own life, like I've said
to you, bro. No, I think that's Yeah, I
think it's because their lives suck.
They're jealous and they're also homosexuals.
And also they're homosexuals as well.
They are homosexuals as well, bro. Don't
get it twisted. They are homosexuals.
Trust me, they are homos. Like they're
jealous. They are jealous, but they're
also homos as well. Cuz bro, what the
[ __ ] This Red Star, his gallery must be
full full of pictures and videos of me.
Oh, he's he needs to come out the
closet, lad. That's the only way he's
going to get help.
That is mad.
That is mad, bro. They've got um
Yeah, the sados.
That's mad, bro.
All I've got on my phone is women,
pictures of women and [ __ ]
I've only got the virgin on my [ __ ]
evidence, my little evidence pack ready for court. Yeah,
I've only got my women collection. That sock.
Yeah, I'm going to start collecting
women again soon.
Add to my little collection. That sock.
Okay with you, boss.
Yeah, I need to do a video to this jo
and I'm done. We got this [ __ ] on uh Sunday.
Yeah, my little collection. That sock.
Yeah. My little collection.
They say that they do this stuff. Yeah.
Cuz you've said stuff about kids, but nah, bro.
Not in 2026, bro. No way, man. Not in
2026. If they thought you was a wronging, bro,
they would literally
if they if they thought you was a wronging, bro,
they [snorts] would actually uh
they would actually um
uh they would actually distance themsel
away from you if they actually thought
you was a wrong, they would actually
distance themselves away from you, lad. Yeah, man. [snorts]
Yeah, they were. Yeah, they were my vitamins.
USA Izzy's boobs was my vitamins. Do you
remember that? that sock. Yeah, bro.
They were my vitamins.
I weren't going to leave till I got my vitamins.
Then they got took away from me. Yep.
Yep. Taking a baby away from its mama.
That suck. Someone said that Peter Betty
can't get attached anymore because he's
already found his mama.
That's sock. I was laughing at that,
bro. I was laughing at that. Like some I
used to go like when I was on the train
and that I'd remember what like the
troll comment said and it made me laugh.
Peter Belly can't get attached anymore
because he's already found his mama.
[laughter] Oh, I was dead, bro. Imagine
someone just writing that in it. Yeah.
Yeah, that's funny, bro.
I don't see that account anymore. It's
just picking its moment in it.
Why did you see LJ doing the unboxing
um videos? He's He's being a copycat.
He's being a little copycat. [snorts]
Yeah, he's being a little copycat.
Yeah, cuz I done the Lego in it. [ __ ]
[snorts] copycat. [ __ ] off. [groaning]
[gasps and sighs]
[ __ ] dirty copycat.
[ __ ] you can't do anything on this
community that's suck without some [ __ ] copying you
can you a copycat community [laughter] said that
he was like Grey said this is a copycat community. [laughter]
I don't know why that makes me laugh.
It's a copycat community.
Oh, I was with this American before that
sock. She said, "I really want you, but
I don't think you want me."
I said, "I do."
Then she gave me a [ __ ] in the alleyway.
Then her friends come over and coped us. Dirty bastards.
Yeah, I've still got the video, Dusty.
I really want you, but I don't think you want me.
That's not even [snorts] made up, bro.
Yeah, I got a [ __ ] in the alleyway.
I almost passed out, Dusty.
It was a very good [ __ ]
Yeah, that wasn't her that said that.
That was another one.
Oh, I got caught wanking outside.
No, I can't even remember what happened
to be honest. I know I didn't [ __ ] her.
I don't even know if I came. I can't even remember. Um, so
I was in a nightclub in uh, Brixton a
few years ago and I was really getting
like blue balls and obviously I was
quite far away from home. So I thought,
[ __ ] it, let me go and let me go
somewhere and have a little wank.
right and have a [snorts] little wank.
So I I was under this I was next to this
bike and I was playing with myself and
then this this guy come over and he's
like you're trying to steal my bike. I
said no. He thought he was thought I he
thought I was trying to steal his bike
and I was like I'm not trying to steal
your bike cuz obviously I was like I was
I was like under it like next to it kind
of thing and I said no I'm not trying.
And then and then he started like
grabbing me and stuff and then his
friend pulled him away from me.
Yeah, that was a true story, bro.
No, they didn't catch me banking, but he
thought I was I was trying to steal his bike. That suck
was next to the bike. Under the bike, I
can't remember. But yeah,
he thought I was trying to steal his bike.
Yeah. No, I was just having a little play.
I said to this I said to USA DO, "I like
your boobs." She said, "Thanks. My ex
likes them, too."
I said, "Yeah, but I like them more."
They're mine now. Yeah.
You think I'm a weirdo?
Don't you think nonslegs is weirder
weirder than me?
I would think you would think he's
weirder than me to be honest. Yeah. [laughter]
I think he's weirder than me,
but who knows, eh?
He's sick of this community. That's what
the point of this community. [laughter]
What's the point of this community if
you can't do anything without someone
else copying you?
What's the point? I can't even do anything anymore
cuz every time I do something, someone copies.
[ __ ] annoying as [ __ ]
So annoying. So [ __ ] annoying, bro.
It's the copycat community.
That's a copycat community in it.
It's a proper copycat. [laughter]
I'm going to message that to calm me down. [laughter] One second.
I'm dead, bro. I'm dead.
O, that suck. It's a This is a copycat
community, isn't it?
Proper proper copycat community, ain't it? Yeah.
Oh, for [ __ ] sake, man. It's a proper copycat community
filled with a couple of uh homo closeted homosexuals.
Yeah, it is.
Do you remember um that sock? Sher Co's fit. [laughter]
Oh, Timmy's going live. No one cares.
Go away, Timmy. No one cares, man. [laughter]
Hey, bro. No one cares, isn't it?
It's a copycat community. [laughter]
Do you know women? Yeah. Do you know
when they work, they should get half the
amount that you should be getting
for just being women.
So say someone gets like £13 an hour,
they should get maybe£6 something an hour. [sighs]
What do you think?
They just get half of what they're
supposed to be getting.
I always used to say if you want to rent
a room, you have to pay double.
I always I always said to the women that
they've got to pay double.
Yeah. I used to rent these rooms that s
and when women would message me I would
say um yeah uh it's double for women. So
if the room was 400 they'd have to give me 800.
Obviously they didn't.
Yeah it's double. It's just to make up
for the double standards.
You know I said it's more for women.
Nope. LJ is not coming on Sunday, bro.
He's never coming back here.
He's never coming back here. He couldn't
even afford to come here, bro. Come on
now. That's not even one. And this guy
is not showing up tomorrow either. So,
your only hope really is Smokey B.
Yeah, it's double for women.
I think they should do that. you know,
pay women a lot less money
because obviously the double standards,
isn't it? What do you think, Wister?
Women should get paid a lot less
than men because obviously um double standards.
Yeah, man. I'll see you there.
I'm going to knock your [ __ ] block off.
I can't do what?
Yep. They should
They exist for our pleasure. No, no other reason.
They should be getting no more than6 an hour,
you know, because obviously the the
double standards and the dating for men is bad.
So obviously we need to make it fair in
other ways, you know.
I'm just trying to make it fair. I just
want to make the world fairer, you know.
You know, we're not allowed to complain.
They're allowed to complain.
Oh, just a double standards.
just like what men have got to go
through to get dates and stuff and and
what men need to do like they have to
approach and [ __ ] and the double
standards like people dismissing your struggles.
It's just it's just harder for men. It
always has been. And men don't get to complain
like you have to approach and [ __ ] like
they so if it so then they should get
paid less money then
I mean a lot less money I feel like that
there should be different things bro I I
just want to make the world fair you know
I want to make the world fair
you talk to them as people they're not
[ __ ] people. Them [ __ ] are not
people at all. They're objects.
[snorts] Yeah, they're not people.
They're definitely definitely not. I
used to think they were people a couple
of years ago until they started trolling
me and leading me on. No, they're
definitely not. They're not people.
That's why I don't get laid
really. What about them being stuck up
and leading people on and being [ __ ]
You seem to dismiss that.
What about them being [ __ ]
How about that?
They're not They're not people, bro.
They're They're literally not people.
I don't even know what they are, but
they're not [ __ ] people.
You actually think them bastards are people?
No. No, no, no. They literally are, bro.
There's no point getting into this debate, man.
debate, bro. This debate, bro. Just
leave it in it.
You have your opinion. I have mine.
That's it. No one's right. No one's wrong. Done.
I could care less, bro. To be honest with you.
They're not people, though. Definitely
not people. Their attitude stinks. And I
don't even approach anymore. And I see
enough of it on Ed Matthews channel. I
don't watch HS, but I see enough of it,
mate. And I don't even approach them.
I don't approach, but I see what happens
to other people now. I don't approach
anymore, but I see what happens.
Yeah, I've given up for now, bro.
Yeah. Yeah. I watch uh I watch and I've
seen it as well what what they're like.
So, and I don't and I don't even try anymore.
After you. [ __ ] you, man.
[snorts] [ __ ] you.
Well, good for you, bro. Congratulations.
See, I'm I'm unbiased here. I've got no
reason to lie about these women being
[ __ ] I've been with women. I've had
sex with women.
I don't have no reason. Even if I had a
woman right now, I'd still be saying they're [ __ ]
Does I would still be saying exactly the
same thing, bro. I'd still be So, I'm not biased.
That's what I'm saying. I'm actually
telling you like what I think.
I'm not even I'm not even biased. I'm
not a virgin. So that's what I mean by
biased. So I'm I actually do believe it, bro.
I believe that they are um that they're no good.
Um so yeah.
Well, yeah. You know what? Everyone is a
[ __ ] [snorts] But I'm not biased. So
like what I mean by that is I'm not I'm
not a virgin. I could easily be a s and
say, "Oh yeah, I've had one night
stands. I've been with women." But I'm
not going to say that because I don't
believe they are innocent.
I hate everything about it. The double
standards, the them dismissing struggles
when men struggle.
Um I don't agree with any of it.
And obviously I can't be biased because
I've had women
So that's what I mean
cuz obviously if I was a virgin then
people could be like, "Oh, you're just
saying that cuz you're a virgin."
So what I mean by that? Okay. So okay,
okay. So what I mean by that is say if I
was a virgin and I was saying all of
this stuff, oh they're [ __ ] what's
people going to say?
They're going to be like, oh yeah, but
that's cuz you're a virgin. You've never
been with a woman. That's why you That's
why you hate them. Yeah. So, obviously,
if I've been with women and I've had sex
and I've pulled,
what can someone say? They can't say anything.
No, I didn't have to pay for it. Oh my
god, why is this phone frozen? No, I
haven't paid for it.
So, that's what I mean. So, I'm not
biased because if I was a virgin, they
can say that I'm being bias biased.
They could say that I'm being biased, you see.
Okay, put it this way.
Pe the people that defend Okay, majority
of the people that women um
the people that defend women,
more majority of them have had less
women than me
or they've never been with a woman.
That's why we always say that white
knights don't make any sense. Ss don't
They defend women, but women don't like them.
So, as soon as someone speaks the truth,
oh, they're [ __ ] Oh, they lead people
on. You will get all of these white
knights who don't get women defend them.
I say it how I see it, bro. I really say
it how I see it.
Yeah. Well, they don't defend
themselves, do they?
White Knights do it.
I do feel sorry for men though in this
day and age, particularly around 21, 22, 23. You know,
it must be worse for them having a high sex drive.
Probably can't get women. It must be
horrible. Me, I don't really care. I've
been with women. I'm older. I don't
really give a [ __ ] But like, you know,
if you're that age and stuff.
Um cuz I know they're all the same. And
obviously, I don't really have a high
sex drive anymore. So, I'm not asked.
Well, I've been with women that I've not paid for.
Well, I've been with plenty of women who
have not paid. Why are we talking about that?
Well, it counts as it counts as losing
your virginity. Yeah.
And Yeah, you do pay for it either way.
You pay for it either way. Yeah, of
course you do. Of course you pay for it either way. >> [snorts]
>> If I had a W. Well, I wouldn't Well, I
don't pay for it now because I don't
really crave sex now, but if I if back
two years ago, if I could pay 100 150
for a woman, I would I'd rather pay than
put effort in. If I still had a sex
drive and I wanted women, I would
literally pay the same. Why do you think
I used to use that Only Fans, Dusty? It
was cheaper in the long run.
It was cheaper in the long run.
Yeah, it was cheaper in the long run,
lad. Just pay 150. She'd drive all the
way to me. I get to [ __ ] her without a
condom and she'd go. It was It was
cheaper. No stress, no [ __ ]
Uh, this was obviously a few years ago and that.
So, yeah, man. And to me, that was the
same cuz I get to I got to [ __ ] her
without a condom.
So, I I I it was just better that way.
>> [clears throat] [gasps]
>> I've had women that I've not paid at all
where they've just bought me a drink.
I've had it.
I've had it. Yeah.
Yeah. I've had it. I've even had a woman
buy me chicken and I've not paid her and
I've not I've not bought her anything.
But that's rare though, Dusty. Most of
the time you will pay. If it's like a
one night stand in a bar in a club,
yeah, you might not pay, but if you're
talking about like on a dating app, you
will be paying. You'll be paying most of
the time. Sometimes you'll get lucky and
you don't pay, but most of the time you do pay,
but obviously there has been times I've
not paid. [snorts]
Manchester it pay. Sig had it paid. The
one night stand on my birthday. I didn't pay.
I guess you can say USA. I paid.
If she just said that she just wanted
sex, Dusty, I wouldn't have met her.
If she said that she just wanted sex.
Rare to get lucky now. Yeah. You'll be
lucky to get a date now.
Yeah. Yeah, if she just wanted sex, I
wouldn't have met her, bro. I would have
just got an escort
cuz I could have paid money, get an
escort, not get led on, and not not have
any of them problems. I would have
literally just um I wouldn't have met up
with her if she just wanted sex. [ __ ] that.
Absolutely [ __ ] that, bro. No way.
I thought she wanted a relationship
and stuff. Uh, Dusty,
I thought she wanted a relationship.
That's how she was acting. Yeah.
Yeah. I would have just used an escort.
I would have just used an escort, bro.
If I knew that that was the case. Yeah.
I thought they wanted a relationship,
Dusty. That's what that's one of that's
one of the reasons why I met them, you know.
I'm not meeting someone just to have sex.
I'm speaking with days. [ __ ] that. So, no. Yeah. Basically, yeah,
it don't make sense. It's different if
you you're drunk and you just met someone.
So yeah, [ __ ] that.
If it was someone you've met for a
couple of hours, it's different. But if
you're speaking to someone, why are you
going to meet? Nah, bro. [ __ ] that.
No, no, no, no, no. [ __ ] that, bro. So, yeah.
Nah, [snorts] bro.
I won't be approaching for a very long time,
if ever again.
I don't see the point. I don't really
have a high sex drive anymore.
And women kind of put me off. They made
me asexual. So,
I'll just like I'll just be collecting them.
So, it's pointless.
Just be collecting them to look at them basically, you know.
They really kill a boner. You They're very masculine.
I don't have the I just don't have um
There's literally nothing they can give me, bro.
Cuz I don't have a sex drive any really
anymore. Well, obviously I do, but I can
live without sex. Does that make sense?
I don't really care, lad.
When I was 22, 23, bro, I was out every
[ __ ] I was out three times a week. If
I didn't touch boobs for like a week,
bro, I'd be depressed
cuz I used to kiss and was able to touch
people dusty. I'd be very depressed
when I was 22, 23, 24, 25.
Now, like, nah, bro.
It's gone now. Yeah,
[sighs and gasps]
I think it goes as you go older. Get basically. Yeah. [snorts]
Nah, it will never be like the O'Neal
days. I used to love going to the
O'Neals and Water Street, bro. Three
times a week, O'Neal's casino. But now I
just don't have the drive for it, bro.
It's not the same, man, as you do when
you get older. I need to travel. I need
to do a few things, bro. I need to
That's why I stopped the gambling.
That's why I've stopped doing the
football bets and the roulette. I'm not
going back to that [ __ ] I closed the account down.
I remember I fingered this woman in
O'Neill's bro. Oh my [ __ ] god.
Her eyes was rolling out of her head.
I've got so many experiences. Sometimes
I just masturbate to the experiences I've had.
Yeah, I fingered some people before, bro.
And then meanwhile, whilst I was doing
it, that suck, she was crying over her
ex, which was quite concerning.
That was quite concerning. [sighs] [snorts] Yeah,
it was very weird. Yeah. Fingering. fingering.
I used to like fingering. Yeah.
And I got a [ __ ] in the alleyway.
Yeah. I love that O'Neal's W Street,
man. I used to go on the Thursdays to
get all the American [ __ ]
They used to be full of Americans on a Thursday.
I had so many dates there. And
do you remember when I went to that
[ __ ] You remember when I went to um
Elen Dusty and I met that one from Maiden Head?
Oh, she was a proper [ __ ] bro.
She was chat I didn't even like her yet.
And then she was chatting to this other
guy trying to deny and I didn't even like her.
And I was like, "Stop lying to me.
They're trying they're trying to point
blank lie to my face when I just saw
what you done." I had to put her in her
place. I'm sure you remember that in it
that Oh my god, bro. I had to literally
put her in her place.
I said, "Listen, yeah, she was she lived
in Maiden Head in it." And I went to Elen.
I said, "Listen, listen, listen, listen,
listen." Yeah. You're moving weird, in
it. I know what you just done.
Like, you're weird, man. Proper weird.
Do you remember that, Dusty?
Yeah, that was a that was a weird date, bro.
That was a very weird date.
I've had some really weird dates, you
know, that suck.
But, you know, some of these women,
yeah, they go on dates just to use you
and not even kiss you.
or you will go on a date with someone
and you'll make out with them and then
they just ghost you. They're so weird.
So even if you manage to even get a date nowadays,
there was this Albanian. Yeah. We was
kissing. Yeah. And I was touching her
boobs in the in the Simmons and stuff
and then she said, "Oh, we can't meet
anymore cuz I don't understand English
and [ __ ] We can just be friends.
I'll get a bit of luck. Really?
So, what has women has women changed in 2026?
What has women s as women as women
changed in 2026? Highly doubted, lad.
The most weird date. Uh,
I don't know, bro. There's been so many weird ones. Maybe
it was with that American bro.
I was in a casino, Daki. I said, "Oh,
meet me downstairs." She's like, "Oh, a
casino is not really my vibe."
I said, "It's not really my vibe. It's
not really your vibe. I was starting
getting I was starting getting bad vibes
from her uh from the start and then she
turned out just to be a [ __ ]
That was the most weird one cuz she had
attitude from the start.
Yeah, I think so.
And I've had all I've had I've had dates
with people that have just ghosted. That's sock.
There was one I went on a date with.
Yeah. Uh just before New Year's.
Date went well. Said our um
said our um interest and stuff and then
she just goes uh then she just no she
says oh what she didn't feel connection.
I'm thinking that's how I knew then they
started have that's how I knew they had unrealistic expectations
because a date could go perfect right
you can look your best and then they
still make some [ __ ] ass excuse why
they won't meet you again so it just
then it just became the norm to expect
came that it become the norm to know
what they're going to do
that's how I started realizing they had
unrealistic expectations because um because of
You can go on a date, you can look your
best, you can actually act normal, and
then they make excuses. I went on a date
with someone and they said in 20 minutes
they don't feel the vibe. That's and
they approached me. They gave me their number
and then they said I said, "What? What
the [ __ ] did they expect? I don't know
what they want people to to do, Drock.
I don't know what uh what they um what
they what they expecting from a date.
Before they go on a date with someone, I
want to I want to know what they're
actually expecting from someone.
You get me, bro?
It's so weird.
People on Reddit that suck says that you
they say that you'll meet someone
They say you meet someone.
Yeah. I got nicked
in Newcastle. I got arrested. Yeah. [snorts]
Nah, it's not going to bother me, bro. [gasps]
Why would it bother me? I know what
women are like. That's
so you know when I show like my bad
experiences with women leading me on and
people make excuses for them.
If I show if I showed men if I was
bisexual and I showed men leading me on
and playing games, would they also make
excuses for men as well or just the women? H.
So what? Why do they So why are they
defending women? I've got this woman on
WhatsApp. Yeah, her name is Jessica.
She's French. She's blonde and sexy, bro.
I wish she could suck my dick with them
[ __ ] lovely pink lips.
She's got lipstick on. She's French.
Her little French accent. I met her in
the Weather Spoons.
Make a little French baby.
Oh my god, bro.
She's from Flesh. She's from Flesh.
That's how they talk. Look at the all of
these women I've got on WhatsApp. Look
at this collection, man. I've got a big collection.
If I could get with any woman, it would
be French, you know.
Cuz they're the hardest to get. So, if
you was to ever get with a French woman,
oh, you're lucky, bro. I've never been
with a French woman, bro. Not even
kissed. I don't think Nah,
you you're going to get a French woman.
you got no chance. What what French
women do is if you approach them,
um they are nice to you and then they
lead you on. So, they're not going to
say they've got a boyfriend. They're
just going to be nice and then they're
just going to troll you, bro. They will
troll the [ __ ] out of you, bro. And that's it.
They're just so hard to get. You can't
get them and Italian women. Nah,
I think they seem to be the hardest
Italian and um
Polish is quite hard as well, but I
think that's mainly because they go for
people with blue eyes, but French and
Italian, you got no chance, bro. I'd be
very surprised if you even if you got a a kiss
for from from a French woman. Even a
kiss. Count yourself lucky, mate.
I would be very, very, very, very, very surprised.
Trust me, bro. They are very hard to get.
There was this tenant I had that suck.
Yeah. And I said, "Oh, if you give me a
if you give me a [ __ ] I I I'll I
I'll not let you pay the rent for a
month." This is how [ __ ] up this
country is. Yeah. So I said if you give
me the rent was 350 a month she used to
give me 350. I said I asked her. Yeah. I
actually had the balls to ask her. Yeah.
I was like oh well you know you don't
have to pay if you give me a [ __ ] and
that. I'm like I actually asked her.
Yeah. Over WhatsApp. Yeah. It took some
balls as well. And I'm thinking like
they're going to say yeah. Is it because
they don't want to piss the piss the
piss the landlord off or whatever. No.
But what what made me laugh with this
woman, Dasok, is she she'd she'd give it
to the blacks for free. She'd she'd give
it to the black guys for free. I
actually heard her. I used to hear her
given like in in in the room having sex
with with black guys.
Yeah. I'm thinking, "Fucking hell, mate.
I need to get some paint." [laughter] Ah, mate.
It never annoyed me though because she
wasn't really my type. But obviously
when I was a bit younger and obviously I
was struggling, I thought I could take
advantage of the um not take advantage
but use it to my advantage rather. Um,
and I just thought they were going to
say, "Yeah, she wasn't my type." But
obviously, I'm not going to say no to a
bojo. But trust me, if she was my type,
I would have just made her I would have
told her to um leave if she was my type
cuz there's no way someone I'm liking is
giving someone something for free and
then turning me down and living in my
house, batting out the mate. But
obviously because she wasn't my child, I
just kept the money and that in it. It
was a pissake obviously, but I didn't
like them anyways. It's just something
to ask. I didn't need a £350 a month if
you get me. So, it was my asking. But if
they were my type, no, I'd get them gone, bro.
Doesn't matter who what color person
they were. It doesn't matter what color
person they were. If they were giving
people stuff for free in my face
whilst turning turning out money,
they're gone, bro.
They are gone, bro. They are gone.
Yeah, but obviously I she didn't have no
boobs. That's why I didn't really like
her that much cuz she didn't really have
boobs and stuff. So, how am I going to
get my vitamins? That's
See, I was getting sex from this
19year-old um for a while. That's we
used to meet each other and bang,
but I was always looking at other women
with bigger boobies.
probably she sucking some Willie D sock
and I was always looking for like other
women with bigger boobies and stuff cuz
obviously my vitamins.
Yeah, I need vitamins.
So, I wasn't really getting the
vitamins. So, yeah.
Yeah, USA is here. Big boobies
and stuff so I can get the vitamins.
Do you want to see my Do you want to
see? I've got like a collection of women.
You want to see? I can show you some of
them on my WhatsApp.
If you can see, they're all women. Yep. Nope. Vitamins.
Look, I got some.
These are these I've got about 300 numbers.
Oh, you [ __ ] [ __ ]
One second, bro.
Yeah, I got 300 numbers. Women's
numbers, I think.
Why was I collecting them? Well, I was
messaging them and they didn't meet me
up. Some of them didn't meet me. So,
[ __ ] sake. I got to do this again now.
These are some of the women.
Oh, there's one called Grace. I
approached her outside the train station.
Yeah, Georgia M's from Manchester.
I approached her in L pub.
I've done a lot of women collecting.
Yep. Yeah. I've got a lot of numbers.
And they were all from approaches as well.
And I've only got like most of these on
most of these are women.
There was one I there. Yeah,
they're all women. I approached most of
them. There's not really any men.
This is the one that sucked my willie.
Yeah, I got a lot of numbers
cuz obviously I was trying to find a new
mama duck that could feed me and stuff.
No, I don't really have many men's
numbers. only a couple of my friends.
Well, I do have a few. Yeah,
I was just trying to find a new mama. That suck.
I wish I if I was to get with a woman,
it would have I would I would choose a French woman,
but I wouldn't go out my way to get a
woman, bro. [ __ ] that.
Yeah, they're very hard. Very, very hard to get.
Their standards must be very, very high in it.
300 approaching. I've done more than 300
approaches, mate. More like 300,000 approaches.
They [ __ ] are, mate. Americans easier.
I don't have pictures of the Virgin.
I didn't give a [ __ ] when I was 22, 23, 24. Dusty,
you've never struggled with pulling any
women. I don't believe you. Based on
what I've seen, Dusty, on Ed Matthews
and the guys that are with him,
I think I think you you have struggled, lad.
I don't believe there's a man in the west
that don't struggle, mate. Nah, one second.