Yeah, sorry about that, mate. [snorts]
just didn't want that kind of any more
evidence, but I don't care if he does
either way to be honest. Got enough [ __ ] on him. Yeah,
but yeah, I had to make a new [ __ ] email anyways.
Yeah, but it was an accident.
doesn't matter. Anyways, bro,
I thought I was putting numbers up, bro.
[ __ ] hell. My bad. Anyways, uh let me
put these numbers back up. So, you wait.
You didn't see the numbers at all.
It doesn't matter, mate. I've got lots
of [ __ ] that he's done. I don't give a
[ __ ] because, bro, at the end of the
day. Yeah. Even if he called the police, bro.
Yeah, of course he will jump on it. He's
a loser, bro. You know, bro, you already
know the Scott. Yeah, man. Of course he
will. He's a loser. His whole life is
obsessed with me. Of course he will,
bro. He's a loser. He'll be straight
crying to the police like the loser that
he is. But the police are not going to
do anything anyways, bro. He's tried it
multiple times. But yeah, facts, bro.
He's a proper proper loser.
You know it, bro. You, bro, you know him
better than me now, bro. He's a proper
proper loser. Even with the whole Even
with the whole poster thing, he's a
loser, bro. How are you going to act the
big man on YouTube and then go running
to the police like a loser? Imagine
that, bro. He's a Yeah, he's a proper
proper loser. Wait, so you didn't see the numbers?
You didn't see the numbers, bro?
You didn't see the numbers.
But no, like he actually is a proper
proper loser. Think of it UK asylum.
Yeah. He is so obsessed. Yeah.
Uh he is so obsessed, bro.
He is so obsessed. Yeah. That he's gone
to the police and he's starting like a
whole court case. What a loser. And it
takes a lot, bro, for me to call someone
a loser, bro. And he really, really,
really, really Yeah, they can send it to
him, bro. It doesn't matter. The police
are not going to do anything anyways.
Yeah, they can send it to him. I don't
give a [ __ ] I really don't care.
Yeah, you can. Yeah, no one cares.
Anyways, um, did you see the numbers or
it doesn't matter, bro? The police have
already seen all of the [ __ ] that he's
done on his channel. I've already put a
picture up of him [ __ ] like months
ago anyways. He reported it. Yeah.
Yeah. It doesn't matter, bro.
So, yeah. It's not one rule for one, one
rule for another mate.
One rule for one one for a [ __ ] other
mate. Know what I mean? Yeah. [snorts]
No, bro. Because the police have
probably seen all of what he's done on
YouTube every day.
He's a loser, bro. He is a proper life's
loser, lad. No, it isn't when I'm on
bail, mate. Because if I've got someone
harassing me every day, right, [ __ ]
[ __ ] Yeah, he has not shown the
police what he has done on his channel.
You [ __ ] little [ __ ] I don't give
a [ __ ] about bail conditions. Call the
police, bro. Simple.
Yeah, I'll show him what I I'll show
them what he's been doing and he's going
to get in [ __ ] So, simple as that. You
will not win in the end. Do you know the
maddest thing about this? Yeah. He is
literally never going to win.
He's He's a loser and he's never ever
going to win. He will never ever win. If
it does, if if this even goes to court
in three years, you know, he's not going
to win, right?
You know, he is not going to win. Like,
I swear to God in my mom's life, he's
not going to win.
He is such a loser that he started
something. He's not going to win it in
the end. Two, three years. Oh, it does
work like that, mate. I've been nicked
more times than you've had hot dinners.
And it does work like that. If someone
is harassing you every day and you've
got evidence, it absolutely works like
that. I've spoke to a solici I spoke to
a solicitor the other day and it
absolutely works like that if someone
has been harassing you every day which
you've got evidence. It does work like
that in the washing machine. Yes. Cuz I
had to go to the police station what was
it a few weeks ago and the solicitor
said he's [ __ ] If you've got stuff of
him harassing you I said I do. This [ __ ]
will not leave me alone every day. It
does work like that. Yes. Yes. And when
you have been contact and when you have
been harassing me, it's void. The bail
becomes void. I've spoke to a solicitor
about this. Yeah. Simple. Yeah. It
doesn't matter if I've been charged,
bro. Listen, when someone has been
harassing you, it becomes void. It's
like a restraining order.
Yeah. It's like a restraining order. Why
do you think I've not been arrested? I
put my I put pictures up of him. Why do
you think they've not come for me?
Because it's become void. It's like a
restraining order. Yeah. If someone's
got a restraining order on someone and
someone contacts them. Yeah.
It's void. That's why they don't come
because it's void. Yeah. He can jump on
what he wants.
He can jump on that. He's a And also
said this, you're a [ __ ] skinned
virgin with a fat ugly disabled
girlfriend that you don't [ __ ] Jump on
that as well. Simple lad. Yeah.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Listen, [ __ ] I'll explain it to you
again, Bastic. Yeah. If you are
messaging and harassing someone every
day and then someone messages you, you
can't get a police involved. That's why
the police don't come for me. Yeah. It
doesn't matter about your evidence, Pat, bro.
Simple, man. He's a [ __ ] stinky
little virgin loser. Yeah.
And also, you know, when I kept
reporting him to the police, you know,
when I kept reporting him to the police
as well, that's why they didn't come,
lad. That's why they didn't come.
That's why they didn't come. Oh, another
thing, Jake. Have you asked your
boyfriend um why he's got videos of me
saved? You're very touchy about your
boyfriend. This is the third one now
that's done this
sucking his dick again. Doesn't he put
me all over his channel? Oh, he's
touching about his boyfriend. He's like,
Jo, stop sucking dick, bro. [laughter]
Sucking dick. I don't give a [ __ ] if
he's on B or I don't give a [ __ ] I know
how this works, bro. I literally know
how this works.
Oh, you don't watch him?
No. No. Just Bro, bro, I just just to
just to be on the safe side, bro. I done
it just to be on the safe side.
Just to be on the safe side. You think
the police don't know everything,
brother. I reported him to the police
about five times,
brother. It was just to be on the safe
side. Just in case. Yeah. And I don't
give a [ __ ] I literally do not give a
He's nothing but a stinky dirty little
virgin who's never going to get laid.
And he's never ever ever going to get laid.
He's going to die one. He's going to die
a virgin. HE'S GOING TO DIE ONE. [ __ ] hell. Yeah, man.
Yeah, he can be all over it all he
wants. I don't care, bro. I'm not
talking about it anymore.
He just needs to get laid and [ __ ]
die as a virgin. You know what I mean,
bro? But yeah,
it's not going to happen, lad. The
police are aware of his channel. It's
not going to work like that, bro. The
police are aware of his channel.
So no, it's not going to work like that, bro.
It's not going to work like that. The
police are well aware of his little virgin channel.
They're aware of his virgin channel,
bro. Trust me.
Yeah, no one gives a [ __ ] Oh [ __ ] man.
I think he's live,
bro. He will do me a favor by getting
them involved. He will do me a favor.
Yeah, that's that's doing me a favor,
bro. I could care less.
I literally could care less.
That's doing me a favor, lad. Oh yeah.
Yeah. I'm not pleading guilty, bro.
Listen, listen, bro. I've spoke to my
solicitor about this already. This is
the first time I'm mentioning this,
brother. I've I've spoke to the
solicitor about this. Yeah, I've already
spoke to a solicitor about this cuz they
come up with the other thing and he
basically said that if you've got
evidence of him harassed, I've got I've
got his face. I've got everything. They
can't do you for it. He's going to get
and that's a solicitor, not some idiot
on YouTube, but he said like basically
they can't do one and not the other. He
said if you've got all of this evidence,
I said I've got the [ __ ] lot. Um, and
he said, "There's no way then."
And this is a solicitor. A a solicitor
that's been a solicitor since the 80s,
mate. Yeah. Simple.
Simple as that, bro. Yeah.
No, I don't know. I don't know. And I
don't care, bro. To be honest with you,
I don't know and I don't care.
Anyways, I'm not talking about this virgin anymore.
Um, thanks for looking out for me anyways, brother.
No, they can't do that, bro. Obviously,
they can pull you in and [ __ ] when
people um report you, but no, they can't
let someone harass you every single day
and then try and do you for retaliating.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no. They can't
do that. That's why when I've been
reported, they they haven't done
anything. He's literally reported me
like three times. They've told him to
[ __ ] off. And I only assume they know
about his channel. They literally know
about his channel. So the way they see
it is, "No, hold on. You can't be
harass. It doesn't matter if you're on
bet or not. Someone can't be harassing
you every single day, which they weren't
aware of, and then as soon as you do
something bad, oh, he's bullying me." It
doesn't work like that, bro. That's
literally why the police didn't even come.
Bro, I don't give a [ __ ] Call the
police. I don't care. I'm literally
telling you to call the police. I don't
give a [ __ ]
brother. I don't care. I don't know why
you keep telling me. I don't care. I
don't care. Call them, bro, and make me right again.
I don't care. I don't care. I've told
you this multiple times. Call them, bro.
I don't give a [ __ ] I don't know why
we're still talking about this. I know
how this [ __ ] works.
Why hasn't he been nicked, brother? I've
already explained this multiple times.
Call them and they're going to say the
same thing as what I've said. They're
going to say the same thing as what I have said. Yeah,
bro. I'm I know you're trying to help
me, but I don't care.
Yeah. And I've already explained to you
why he's not been nicked multiple times,
and I don't care. Yeah. Simple as that. You know
the reason he didn't get nicked, right?
I'll tell you why. The reason he didn't
get nicked, if you really, really,
really, really, really want to know, is
because he kept running to the police
crying. Oh, he's bullying me. Oh, he's
bullying me. Cuz he's a loser. Yeah.
Because he's a big loser in life. Yeah.
And I never went to the police once. And
then he kept reporting me and reporting
me, reporting me because he's a big virgin. Right.
And uh and uh yeah,
he he he's nothing but big virgin and he kept saying
and that's why the police took it
serious, bro. Of course. Why wouldn't
they, bro? I didn't call anyone. I
didn't call the police. I don't care
about the bell. I don't care. I don't
care. I'm going to have to type you out
in a minute. I don't care. Go and call
the police for him. I don't care.
I literally do not care about bell
conditions. I don't care. Simple.
I literally don't care. If you keep
bringing it up, bro, I'm just going to
time you out. I don't give a flying
[ __ ] I can't tell you how many times,
bro. I don't care. And no, I'm not on
bail and I don't care.
Simple. This is all because he ran to
the police crying. That's not a win.
That's being a loser. Anyone that has to
get the police involved, bro, over
police be over YouTube is a loser. It's
not winning. It's a loser because when
this actually does go to court, right,
you're going to lose in the end like a
loser. So, there's there's literally no point
because you're not ever ever ever going
to win. You are literally never ever
ever ever ever going to win. Simple. So
you're you're not ever going to win. So
what what is even the whole point of it?
You start a you wait hold on. You you
you you report someone to the police.
You start a court case. You then void
you void the bell conditions.
What a loser. And you're telling me his
life is not dedicated to [ __ ] me, son?
You're telling me his life is not
dedicated to me? He's a loser.
[ __ ] hell. He's a [ __ ] loser.
[ __ ] loser in life with it all.
Women, no money, no nothing.
Simple as that. Yeah, man. Yeah, bro.
Yes. And then when that other person
harasses you, the conditions become void.
Oh, I can leave the country when I want
I want, Dusty. I've got I've got my um
I've got my passport.
I've got my passport and everything. And
I'm pretty sure that if you if you have
got conditions not to contact someone
and they're contacting you, it's void.
It's literally void.
I'm telling you, there they just said
don't contact the [ __ ] Basically,
that's literally the only thing they said.
So, I mean, and then once they're
contacting you and harassing you, then
they're voiding it. They are literally
How long you going to last? What do you mean, bro?
Anyways, I don't give a
Anyways, I don't care about this anyways, bro. Yeah.
Uh, what was we what was that going on, bro?
Yeah, man. He can report what he wants.
The loser can report all he wants.
Yeah. So, then what is it then, Dusty?
So, someone's allowed to contact you and
harass and post about you, but you can't
do it to them. I'm sure that's not going
to that go down well with the police.
I'm sure that's not how it works, Dusty.
It's the same as a restraining order. If
I had a restraining order on you, say I
had a restraining order on you, right?
Yeah. So, I can't contact you and then
you contact me is void. It's over.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no,
no. If you No, no, no, no, no, no, no,
no, no, no, no. You can't have a
condition not to contact someone and
they're allowed to harass you every day.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
That's not how it works. He has he has
already tried. Someone that you've got a
court case against is not allowed to
harass you every day and you can't say
anything back. No. No. No. No. No. No.
No way. No way in hell, bro. No way in
hell. So, hold on. So, you can have a
condition against So, wait. Someone
you've got a condition against is
allowed to harass you every day. Not a
[ __ ] chance, bro. Call the police.
Call the police right now. It doesn't
matter if he's not on bail or not. He
doesn't need to be on bail. If you can't
contact someone, if you can't contact
someone, bro, Jake, shut up. You're not
giving me anxiety, bro. Shut up. Shut
up. Most things go to crown court nowadays. Yeah,
bro. Shut up. You waste man. You've
tried this before. You're not making me
[ __ ] myself. [ __ ] off. Shut up, you
little fanny. He went crying to the
police and most things go to [ __ ]
crown court now. You little fatty. You
little fanny boy. You're not giving me
anxiety. You little fanny. Shut up.
You know, simple.
Uh, no. He's not the victim. Well, we'll
see. Well, well, we'll see if he's the
victim then, won't he? No, no, no, no,
no. Most things go to Crown Court
nowadays, Dusty. Most things they just
pull it in Crown Court or they give you the opportunity.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no. Bro, a
lot of things go to crown court now.
Sometimes they just put things in crown
court. So, and my sister even said,
"You're not there. You're not going to
go to prison."
I do know best. 100% I know best. I know
for a fact that if if you Okay, if I
Okay, so if I had a restraining order on
you, you're allowed to harass me every
day. Or would that void the restraining
order? One second. One second. So, if
I've if I've if you if I've got a
restrain if you've got a restraining
order on me, you're allowed to harass me
every day and I'm not allowed to contact
you. That's not how it works. That is
100% not how it works. Cuz I know how
these things work. No. No. No. No. No.
No. No. No. No way, bro. No [ __ ] way.
Not a [ __ ] It doesn't matter if he's
not a bell. He doesn't need to be. He's
voided the conditions. It doesn't
matter. He's not allowed to harass me
every day. He's not allowed to contact
me. He's not allowed to post about me.
But he does. He doesn't need to be on
bail. He doesn't need to be on bail.
He's literally not allowed to contact me
or harass me because it voids and
contradicts the whole thing. He doesn't
need to be on bail. Call the police,
bro, and and ask them. Call the police
and ask them then. If you don't believe
me, call the He doesn't need to be on
bail. He literally doesn't need to. He
doesn't need to be on bail.
You don't need to be You're not allowed
to contact me. Simple as that. You don't
need to be on bail. Call the police. If
you don't believe me, call the police
right now and and ask them then. If you
if you think I know best, bro. Simple as that. Yeah.
Yeah. He is literally harassing me and
go to me. I know what I'm saying, bro. I
know what I'm saying. Yeah. If if you've
got to court a case against someone,
Dusty, they're not allowed to harass you
every day. There's no way, bro. You can
call the police and ask them. You can
literally call the police and ask them. Yeah,
simple. That's not how that works. It
doesn't take Einstein to know that. It literally doesn't.
It literally does not. Call the police,
bro. Lit. I'm telling you, call them and
you and and they'll say the same thing
because what happened was when I
reported this about five, six times,
they know all about the channel. Yeah.
Ask them, bro. Yeah. Yeah. Go and ask
them. Ask them. Ask them. No, he
wouldn't be arrested for a separate
crime. I've already I've already lit
literally, bro. Right. I'm going to stop
talking about this now anyways cuz we're
just going back and forth. Back and
forth. Right. We're going to stop
talking about this now anyways cuz we're
just having the same thing over and over
again. If you think you're so right
about it, then I'll be getting arrested
then, won't I? Simple.
We're having the same argument over and
over again, bro. And you're talking to
me like I've not been through the system
about a million times. But yeah. Okay.
You know best, whatever. And I'll be
getting arrested soon. Yeah. Simple as
that. I don't know anything. I've not
been arrested about 30 million [ __ ]
times. I don't know how these things
work. No, I'm I'm a stupid idiot that's
got to be getting arrested soon. Okay,
bro. Do you know what? It's so
embarrassing that I don't even like to
tell people how many times I've actually been arrested.
It's actually that embarrassing how many
times I've been put through the system.
It's actually quite embarrassing to be fair, lad.
I know I'm right because he's already
tried to call the police on me, lad.
He's already tried to call the police on
me about two times and they told him to
[ __ ] off because they know about his
channel, bro. Because they know about his channel.
because obviously where I was reporting
him and I got a crime reference number,
they know about his channel, so they're
like, "Fuck you." Basically, of course
I'm right cuz he's already tried a
couple of months ago.
So, um, yeah,
and they basically know that it's tip
for tat and the solicitors has informed
them as well. So, yeah, bro, you can do
what you want, bro. Okay, then. Good for
you then. Well, I'll be getting arrested
soon then, won't I?
Well, if I'm on Okay, then. So, why
haven't the police come for me then? Ask
ask you this. Okay, then. Okay. Okay.
Okay. He has reported me two time three
times now and they've not come for me.
They've told him to [ __ ] off. So, does
not does that not make me right what I'm saying then?
Yeah. Does that not make me right about
what I'm saying? Because he's actually
reported me three times for putting
pictures up and they and they told him
to [ __ ] off. So, so doesn't that prove
that I'm kind of right with what I'm saying?
And they've not even tried to contact him again
because he's probably not seen her yet.
Okay, mate. Okay. Okay.
Yeah, bro. Okay. Well, then I'll be
getting arrested soon then, won't I? Yeah. Yeah, [snorts] [sighs]
I don't care, bro. I really really
couldn't give a [ __ ] I don't even know
why we're talking about this, bro. I
really can't give a [ __ ] I really don't
give a [ __ ] lad, to be honest. You know,
A, I won't be getting found guilty, and
B, I wouldn't go to jail even if I did
get found guilty.
So yeah. And why are we talking about a
court case that's not even happening as
well? Why are we even talking about
this, lad? Yeah. Okay, bro. Whatever.
Yeah. Okay. Well, then I'll be getting
arrested soon then, won't I? If I broke it.
Yeah. Okay, bro.
Yeah. No one cares anyways. I'm not
talking about this anymore. Yeah.
Yeah. Yeah. Okay. We're not talking
about this anymore anyways. Well, I'm
not talking about it.
Um, so yeah.
Yeah. Anyways, moving on now.
Yeah, that's the same thing I was
clicking on. Yeah, bro. [snorts] Yeah, man. Ah yeah.
[snorts and clears throat] Yeah, man. Yeah.
Proper, bro. Proper
proper loser. Is it?
Yeah, man. He's a proper proper loser.
And Dusty, do you know why I done that?
Because they tried stopping my money. Yeah.
He tried stopping my money as well.
Yeah. Do you know Do you know why I done
that? Because um they were trying to
stop my um money, bro. Is it?
Yeah. He's a proper proper loser. Proper
life's loser. So yeah, Dusty, you know,
like you can never ever feel sorry, bro,
for like people cuz it's not like it was
YouTube and it got out of hand. They
wanted to make it real life, so I'll
make it real life. You want to make it
real life, I'll make it real life. It's
as simple as that. I told them multiple
times, "Leave me the [ __ ] alone or I'm
going to do I'm going to go to your
area." I told them multiple times,
"Leave me alone, Dustin." They wouldn't
do it. So I thought, "Fuck it." Yeah. I
said, "Leave me the [ __ ] alone or I'm
going to come to that [ __ ] virgin
area of yours and put posters all over,
you [ __ ] virgin." I was like, "I'm
just going to leave it. Just going to
leave it." Got out the bath, bro. The
[ __ ] these benefit people are calling
me dusty. And I thought, "Nah, [ __ ]
this." I thought, "Fuck this, mate." And
I went, "Yeah, your fault." I told them,
"Leave me alone multiple times, bro." I
told them multiple times, "Leave me
alone." And they wouldn't do it. And
they wanted to try to make it real life,
so I'll make it real life. Simple. Yeah.
You want to make it real life, I'll [ __ ]
with your life. It's as simple as that.
You [ __ ] virgin [ __ ] You understand
what I'm saying, bro? And then what did
the loser do? Went running to the
police. What a loser. Everything he says
in these community posts is literally
him. Ugly loser just looking in the
mirror every time, bro. Do you know what
I'm saying? You went to the police over
YouTube, you [ __ ] loser. That's the
lowest of the low. What a loser.
What a [ __ ] loser. And then he was
just waiting, right, just for any excuse
to get them involved. Imagine being that
much of a loser. I could never imagine
being that low in life. And I've had
I've had loads, lad, you know.
No, they never stopped my money. They
tried to stop my money and they were
getting me to send stuff as well. And
no, it we know who it was, bro. It was
that red star and him. It was no one
else, bro. It was literally no one else.
Any It was either him or it had
something to do with him. Either way, I
don't give a [ __ ] So, and he was the
closest thing. It wouldn't have been
anyone else. Trust me, it wouldn't have
been anyone else but two or three
people. Trust me, it would not have been anyone else
but them kind of them people had.
You know what I'm saying? I know, bro. I
really I I do need to actually come off
of it, bro. I do, bro. To be fair. Yeah.
It doesn't It doesn't really make sense,
does it? Like, you got a bunch of
middleweights people jealous of you
every day. They're never going to stop.
And even if you leave, they're never
going to stop. So yeah, why am I really
on it, bro? Why really? Yeah.
I think I'd just do it to talk to Greasy
and stuff, man. To be honest,
yeah, it doesn't really make sense. But
no, it was either him or Red Star or
someone else. Trust me. But it wouldn't
have been anyone else. Trust me.
Yeah, it would literally not have been
anyone else. It would literally
be no one else, lad. And it doesn't
matter UK asylum, whether it was him,
whether it was Red Star, anyone
associated to that channel, they're
still trying to [ __ ] with your life. So simple.
But yeah, it does, bro. Is it? Yeah, it
does. It does. It should be fair. I do
need to leave, to be honest, bro. To be
honest, I do need to leave. Yeah.
Do you know what I might do, bro?
Honestly, bro, I think we need to just
make a new channel and get all the good
people on that channel
where none of these people can find us.
But it's who's not going to dox the
channel. Really, bro?
That's really, bro, that is literally
really um the the best way forward. If
you actually do want to come on YouTube,
you're just going to have to start a
whole new channel. I've got another
channel, but that's like where my
approaching videos are. I don't give
that channel. You need to start a whole
new channel where none of these people
um can find you.
You understand? Like where like
Greavvesy, Steven Howard, maybe you.
That's the only way, bro. And then you
can just Yeah. fill your boots
basically. And they can't find you.
They're never going to stop anyways.
Even if they if they will never ever
leave you alone, ever. Even if you left.
But you know, obviously they can't find
you. So [ __ ] it. They're just being
annoying themselves. I think that is
literally the only way, bro.
What else, bro? You know, if you want to
go on YouTube. Yeah. [snorts]
Yeah. [clears throat] For real, lad. For real.
It's weird though. UK asylum, bro. But
cuz when we talk about this, bro, it's
just how they can be so obsessed and
jealous of someone that they don't know.
My mom couldn't answer it.
Bad, bad, bad mental health
every day for years. [ __ ] hell, bro. Yeah.
Don't even try and figure out. You'll
lose brain cells, lad. Yeah.
They're not even trolling, bro. They're
just self projectors.
No, they're not troll. They're not
trolling. They're just self-reflectors.
Trolls are actually funny, lad.
So, yeah. Who do you reckon it was that
tried stopping the money, bro? Who do
you reckon it was that was trying to
stop the money?
Yeah, it was either him or Red Star or
someone else. It doesn't matter, bro.
So, I wasn't doing a bad thing. They
they wanted to start [ __ ] with
people's life, so I thought, "Yeah, I'll
[ __ ] with you." [snorts]
Um, simple. I'll [ __ ] with you. You [ __ ]
with me, I'll [ __ ] with you, you [ __ ]
little [ __ ] So, as you see, it's been
going on for years and years and years
and years and years. [snorts] But what
he done, UK signing, what this loser
done is he kept running to the police
multiple multiple multiple multiple
times when I never cried. do is bully
me. Uh cuz he's a loser and he can't
beat me in a fight or can't do anything.
So he runs the police cuz he's a coward.
Um and so then obviously what happened
was I never ever went to the police.
Yeah. I mean now if you report me, bro,
they're not going to do anything but it
doesn't matter. So what it is, bro, is
And then he done it again and again. So
now when I report him, they're not going
to um it's just going to go like it's
just they're not going to arrest him
because obviously he's called the police
on me. But when it does go to court,
bro, he's [ __ ] And if he tries to
report me, he's [ __ ] They're not
going to do anything because of what
he's been doing. But obviously where I
where he's tried where he's played the
victim so much cuz he's a loser.
Anything that I will try to report now,
um it's going to look dodgy because what
they're going to be like is, "Well, hold
on a minute." They're going to be like,
"Well, why are you reporting him now
when he's when he got a court case
against you?" But anything he tries to
report me now, the police will tell him
to [ __ ] off.
But it doesn't matter if I even if I
reported him every day. Um, and it
doesn't get to me either. He doesn't get
to me, bro. Going being at the police,
the posters and everything, it was worth
it. It was worth that two day in the
police cell. I don't give a [ __ ] It was worth it.
It was absolutely worth it, lad. And the
posters, nothing really happened for the
posters. The police gave me a lift and
they gave me a lift back. Worth it. It
was actually worth it. So yeah, I don't
give a [ __ ] if he's on bail. I don't
give a [ __ ] So yeah, anyways, UK
asylum. Yeah. So say if I reported him
every day, if I reported him every
single day, the police are not going to
do anything because where he's hyped up
that he's a victim, they're going to
think, "Oh, it's weird. Why are you Why
are you reporting him now?" Do you
understand what I'm saying? And so
that's why it doesn't matter what you
report. Uh, no, they didn't, Dust.
Dusty. Um, um, I don't give a [ __ ] I
would rather go I would rather go to
jail. Simple as that. I, Bro,
you think I'm going to plead guilty when
this little [ __ ] virgin has been
harassing me every single day. I'll go
to jail. Which I'm not going to go to
jail. I'd risk going to jail. [ __ ] it.
I'd rather go to jail, bro. Think about
it, bro. Think about like this. Yeah.
You have got pages and pages and pages
of this loser harassing you every day
and what you're going to plead guilty
and what do community service or pay
money or are you going to risk it and go
not guilty? Show that this [ __ ] has not
left you alone for years. The non-stop
harassment and the chances are the good
chances are that you know you're not
going to get found guilty. And even if
you go to jail, oh bro, I'll take jail
any day. Simple. Simple as that. That's
how bad it is. And that's how any normal
person would see it. And that's and
that's what I basically told the
solicitor. I said, "The reason I didn't
go guilty is because he has not left me
alone. He keeps harassing me. I've got
pages. He will not leave me alone. This
little virgin since 2014, this virgin
will not leave me alone." Um, and he
understood it completely. I said like,
"So, yeah. Um, there's no way, bro." I
told him I'd rather go to prison. Um,
even though I won't, but yeah, there's
no way I'm pleading guilty. Not a
[ __ ] chance. So yeah, man. Yeah.
Yeah. Are you [ __ ] mad? And that
means I'm going to have to do community
service or pay a fine. Hell no. If I had
done something wrong, then I would have
plead guilty. If I had done something
and not and someone else was innocent,
then I would have just plead guilty. But
no chance. Not a [ __ ] chance in hell.
You know, I've got a big ass evidence
packed and there's no denying it, bro.
I've got his face saying stuff. I've got
him ringing me. I will take it all to
court. Simple, bro. I will literally
take it all to court with me, bro. And
say this little virgin needs to be
incarcerated. He has not left me alone
[ __ ] years. Something needs to be
done about this virgin. Simple. But
yeah, Dusty, that's why he will never
get that's why he won't get arrested, lad.
You know. Yeah. No one gives a [ __ ] I
don't care. I literally don't give a
[ __ ] But yeah, Dusty, that's why he
won't he he can't get arrested.
He can't get arrested. And what
basically also what the solicitor said,
Dusty, is that uh where the where the
court advised me Yeah. uh to to report.
Yeah. And obviously I got a crime
reference number, right? And the police
have not done anything, they're going to
be held responsible for that now. Um
because obviously there's a crime
reference number. They've not done
anything. So it's all going to go
against him. You know what I'm trying to
say? And obviously the police ain't done
nothing. I don't I don't give a [ __ ]
bro. The only reason he is not on bell
with bell conditions is because he kept
crying to the police. Yeah, because he
kept crying the victim. But all of the
bell conditions I've got a void. I'm
pretty sure they void. I'm 100% sure
that they are void.
Yeah. Yeah. It doesn't matter, bro. The
court even said um that like obviously
if you can show what he's doing then
it's tit for tat. Tit for tat. Tit for
tat. He's not going to win, bro. He's
not going to win. It doesn't matter,
mate. And I'm not on bail either
anymore. And I'm not on bail either.
Yeah, it is whatever. And I'm not on
bail. That's [clears throat] why when
he's reported me, they've not done
nothing. It is whatever. Yeah. And I'm
not on bail either. Otherwise, the
police would have come for me. Yeah. So, yeah,
I know it is whatever. And I'm not on bail either.
So yeah, clearly clearly I've got no
bail conditions for them to have not
come. So yeah,
but yeah, Dusty, it's not going to work,
lad. It really in the end, it's not
going to work. It doesn't matter how
long it takes, it's not going to work. Yeah, man.
Nah, bro. I had to make a new email. But
yeah, they're not going to win in the
end, Dusty. It's like you if I reported
you, Dusty. Yeah. And I was a dirty,
stinky grass and then you tried
reporting me, they're not going to
arrest me. Do you understand, lad? Um
I don't know. Not next December. The the
next December after that. Yeah.
Oh, nothing, bro. Just this little nods legs virgin. Yeah.
Yeah. Whatever, bro. Yeah. Long time, bro. Years.
Years. Uh, Dusty. Years, lad.
And obviously I've got a Crime reference
number, so um Yeah.
Yeah, bro. See, Dusty, if I started
playing the victim by that loser, he
would have got nicked. But obviously,
I'm not so much of a loser in life where
I have to get the police involved over YouTube.
Simple [snorts] as that, bro. Yeah.
Yeah. Years, bro. Years. [snorts]
Yeah. Yeah, it' be a couple of months, isn't it?
Yeah. Okay, bro.
But yeah, Dusty, if it was something I
had done, then I would have plead
guilty. Obviously, bro,
shoplifting, I would have been like,
"Okay, I've done it. I'll pay the fine."
But no way is this [ __ ] going to be
getting away with [ __ ] harassing me
for years. No [ __ ] way. Not a chance
in [ __ ] hell. So, yeah.
No chance, lad.
Not a chance in [ __ ] hell, Dusty.
Yeah, bro. Like, not a [ __ ] chance.
Yeah, if it was shoplifting then um
then obviously Yeah. I' I'd plead guilty
and pay the fine. Of course, bro. If
you're guilty, you're guilty. But no
way, bro. No [ __ ] way.
No way, lad.
Not [clears throat] a chance. [snorts] Yeah.
Yeah. To be honest, they started trying
to [ __ ] with me in real life, Dusty. So,
yeah, they tried [ __ ] with my money
and [ __ ] That's what I'm saying, bro.
Look at how I look at what I done, bro.
Over a little bit of money. They tried
stopping. And you really think that this
red star stopped my sublet money and I
didn't do anything? Bro, come on now. He
didn't stop anyone's money?
Yeah, we all know that. Why do you think
I don't I don't get mad, bro, when he
says that? Because you never stopped
anyone's money. When they tried to stop
my money, you already saw how I reacted.
This whole conversation is about, buddy, bro.
This whole This is literally all about money, bro.
like this whole thing that we're talking
about and it and it's the truth, bro.
They're like, you want to call people
names on YouTube, then it is what it is, bro.
No, he did try to stop my money, him,
Red Star. It doesn't matter, bro. It
would be someone in that gang of people.
Isn't that right, Dusty? It would be
someone in that gang of people. Trust
me, bro. Trust me, 100%. You know that
Red Star is a dirty, stinky little grass,
bro. You know he's a dirty, stinky
little grass. So, at the end of the day,
by the way, you know that commu, that
part of the community are grasses.
So, even if it was Red Star that it not
him, it's just as bad. Simple as that.
So, and you know that they're dirty,
stinky grasses. They talk about
grassing. They're police grasses.
They're grasses. Simple as that. So yeah,
but I think when I'm done with these
clowns, bro, um this week I am actually
going to make a new channel
and just try to get the decent people on
that channel. To be honest, bro, the
more you actually But the more we
actually talk about it and the more we
think about it, bro.
Shouldn't even be on here, bro. To be honest,
I just want the same people, just a different channel.
Oh, I don't because I don't want these
people following me. Like Red Star,
nonslegs, all these self projectors. Oh,
I don't want them following me
because I don't want them watching me. I
don't want them following me. I don't
want to give them content. It would be
the same people obviously on here like,
but them. They will never find me. They
How would they find me, bro? I've got a
channel. They've never found me. I've
got a cold approaching channel. They're
not going to find me. They will never
find me, bro.
Yeah, they can record every Oh, I'm not
worried about that. Oh, I don't give a
[ __ ] about that. Putting a picture. Oh,
I don't give a [ __ ] about that. You can
record it and send it to the police. Oh,
I don't give a [ __ ] about that. I'm just
speaking for the future.
They will never find me. Lol11. I've got
a cold approaching channel, lad. They
will never find me. They will never ever
find me, bro. I've got a cold. The only
reason they found the other one is
because I linked it on Reddit. They will
never find me just by name. Never. They
will never ever ever find me just by
name. It will never happen. And it's never happened
unless one of you [ __ ] leak it. What
are they, bro? [ __ ] What are they?
[ __ ] Einstein or something. Let me
see, bro. One sec.
Uh, they can't find people, bro.
Unless you link it to them, they'll
never find you. I've got a channel right
now, a cold approaching channel. You'll
never find it.
You'll never find it, lad. What have
they got? No. The only reason they got
it before is cuz I linked to it on
Reddit. They're not They're not going to
manually find you, bro.
So, yeah, that's what it will achieve to
be honest, bro. Leave them bored all day.
no content talking to themselves. Oh,
you could just get off YouTube and live
your life, you know.
Yeah, I got a cold approaching channel.
I haven't uploaded any more on there cuz
I've just left a few on there, but Yeah. Yeah, bro.
Yeah. [snorts] Yeah. I got a cold approaching channel.
But yeah, that's what happens. Dusty, you see
that's what happens, lad. Yeah. [snorts]
Please do the Yeah, bro. Yeah, man.
So, you're saying that that's not even
if I left. So, what if I left and come
back in 5 years and I and I just went on the channels?
They would have long left, didn't it?
These people like say I left for 5 years
and I come back, what would have their
uploads been within 5 years? Do you
reckon they would have just left YouTube? Maybe. [snorts]
Nah. No way, bro. I think that Joe, that
nons legs and that Nah, bro. No, I don't
think so. I think they would they would
post every day
in hopes that you're watching because
they're so obsessed with you. They will
think that you're you're watching every
day cuz that's how obsessed they are. It
would never it would never ever happen.
So LT don't know what he's talking about
because he says that they do it for
reaction, bro. No, no, no, no, no, no,
no, no, no, no, no, no, no. They do it
cuz they're mentally obsessed. People
used to People used to troll Timmy for a reaction.
No, no. They're mentally mentally obsessed.
No, no, no. They are literally literally mentally obsessed. Yeah. [snorts]
Has the police ever took your phone, Dusty?
They were never They were never able to
get any of my fold phones.
Yeah, they tried to get it a couple of
times, bro. I was too fast for them.
[snorts] Yeah, you never give the police
your phone, bro, because chances are you
might not get it back.
That's where the whole system is [ __ ]
Uh the system's [ __ ] you know, that
it's really really
the way the systems [ __ ] the systems
really [ __ ] dusty, you know, cuz cuz
think about it, bro. Yeah. Think about
it like this. Yeah. Because obviously
imagine they got this phone, bro. The
police got this phone right now. They
never got it, but their intentions was
to get it. So it's like trying to kill
someone, but you didn't kill someone.
The intent was still there. That's the
way I see it. And I wouldn't get this
phone back, bro, unless I plead guilty
when someone's been harassing me. I
wouldn't I wouldn't have got the phone
back for many, many years. Do you not
see how that's all wrong, bro? So,
someone's been harassing you. You've
retaliated. The police would have come,
they would have took your phone, and
they wouldn't give you give your phone
back unless you unless you plead guilty. Um which um
or you you waited 3 years.
That is madness in it, bro. When they
come on my door, I put the phone in the
garden. I said, "You're not getting my
phone. No way." Because they want it for
evidence, but then when they take the
phone, they And sometimes they don't
give it back, Dusty. Sometimes they
don't give the phone back.
Um they don't give your phone back.
Sometimes they don't give it back. I've
got things that they've never gave back. So,
and if they try to take my phone,
they're not having my phone. So, that's
as simple as that. They will not They're
not sl They're not getting it. Simple as
that. So, cuz I will fight them, bro. If
they try to take my phone, trust me, I
will. Yeah. And they won't be getting it
without a fight
over my dead body. Would they be getting
this phone? Bro, are you mad? Do you
think people like collect numbers and do
all of this [ __ ] for you to then think
you can come and start taking people's
phone? No. That is when I would do something, bro.
That is when No. No. No. No. No. No. No.
No. Trust me. Yeah. It would be a fight,
bro. And I don't care. Simple.
Oh, because I cuz I because of the whole
Sher Cole thing and him just copying
people and being weird. Yeah. Yeah, bro.
Yeah. I think they take your phones for
a few things nowadays. I think even
domestic they take your phones, don't
they, Dusty? I know I know a friend. He
He's been arrested for some domestic and
they took his phone.
Yeah, I'm sure they took his phone.
Never give the police your phone, bro.
Trying to get is trying to get the phone back. So yeah.
Yeah, bro. Because he played victim.
Because he ran to the police and played
victim. Don't worry, lad. It will it
will come. It will all come out, lad.
Yeah, but he done domestic and his phone
did get took. Dusty, his phone has been
took and it was domestic. He's actually
They actually did take his phone. I
think they can take your phone
when it's like
they can for something else because they
took his phone. But no, they're not
taking my phone, mate.
Cuz they might as well just put me in prison
until they give my phone back.
But they're not taking my phone, mate.
They're not [ __ ] taking my [ __ ] phone.
cuz if you get charged, you're not going
to get the phone back unless you plead guilty.
So, it's kind of like um
they're trying to [ __ ] you over
basically if you think about it. And
then obviously you've got your evidence
on that phone. So,
no, he doesn't play it clever, bro.
Because he's going to get [ __ ] in the
end, bro. Being a dirty grass is not
playing it clever.
He's He's actually [ __ ] himself up.
No, he's actually [ __ ] himself up.
He's actually f He's actually bailed all
the He's actually voided all the conditions.
He don't have the upper hand at all
because he's voided all the conditions
[snorts] and he's going to lose in
court. It doesn't matter if he's not on
bail. It doesn't matter. He's voided all
the conditions that came with the bail
by harassing me.
It doesn't matter if he's not on bail.
He's voided all of the conditions.
Dusty, I'm telling you 100% they're
void. It's got to be void. It's the same
with the restraining order. If you have
a restraining order on me and I contact
you, what happens? What happens to that
restraining order, bro? If I have a if I
if the courts tell me Yeah. not to not
to contact you, not to contact you,
right? And then I contact you. What
happens to that restraining order? Tell
everyone. Tell this indigo here right
now because he doesn't understand it
because he's a bit slow. So I've got a
restraining order on you and you've
contacted me. What happens? What
happened to that restraining order, mate? You know, simple.
I have I have let them know. I have let
them know. That's why they don't do
anything anymore, bro. He's reported me.
I put a picture up. Yeah. A couple of
months ago and he reported me. The
police told him to [ __ ] off. They do
know, bro. They do know. They do know.
The solicitor knows as well. The
solicitors told the police. That's why
they haven't been. Yeah, bro.
The police know what he's about, bro.
The police literally know all of what
he's about. So, yeah.
Bro, like the thing is, like I said,
you're not ever going to win in the end.
You're never ever ever ever going to win
in the end. Trust me. 100% you're not
going to win in the end. And it's kind
of stressful as well, Dusty, cuz think
about it, bro. That is actually putting
a lot of stress on them as well.
Like that's how you know he's a loser
because that means you've got to do all
of this and report this and that. He is
a proper proper loser. Like it's a big
thing going to the police. takes I I
done it about four or five times and
then I and I couldn't be bothered. I had
the crime reference number. I've got
everything I need. I've got all the
proof I need that the police didn't do
anything. So, it's as simple as that.
But no, bro, like he must have done it
multiple times as well, Dusty. More than
two times. He's a proper life loser.
He's a proper proper life loser. It's
not that you call the police, bro, once
and no. Like, you've got to, you know.
So, yeah. He's a proper proper life loser.
And this is what I'm saying, Dusty. I
couldn't even be obsessed with a woman
like this, bro.
I couldn't even be obsessed with a woman like this.
And you're not And you're telling me
these people aren't [ __ ] homosexual.
Yeah. He's not been arrested, bro,
because he's played the victim multiple
multiple multiple times. But what he has
done is he's voided the conditions. Yes.
He's not been arrested because he kept
crying to the police playing the victim.
Yeah. But what he has done is voided the conditions.
I'm not repeating myself anymore. Simple
as that, bro. I've explained this to you
multiple multiple multiple [ __ ] times.
Well, I'm telling you that is exactly
how it works. Well, I think that is how
it works cuz I know how it works cuz
I've spoke to a solicitor. So trust me,
it's exactly how it works. So, and if it
isn't, then I'll be getting nicked then,
won't I? So, that's it.
Oh, it is exactly how it works.
No, no, no. It is exactly exactly how it
works because I've known before people
that's got restraining orders and then
the person's contacted them and it's
voided restraining order. Yeah.
Oh, I know exactly how it works. Trust
me. And the solicitors tell me how it's
worked as well. So, yeah. [snorts]
So, then what you're saying, Dusty, then
is basically then, so they're allowed to
post about you. They're allowed to
harass you, but then you're not allowed
to say anything back.
I don't think so, bro. Like, I know the
police have got a vanetta against me and
[ __ ] and they are biased, but nah, bro.
No way. No way. Can someone a rash and
post about you every day and then as
soon as you do it back? Nah.
Not a first or second time. There's
there's there's no way, bro. There's
literally no way because at the end of
the day, uh, Dusty, he is literally not,
uh, he literally is not allowed to talk
about me. He's not even allowed to. He
cuz it jeopardizes the case.
It literally jeopardizes the case.
You know, do you know Do you know what
I'm saying? So, do they care about this
stuff? Surely division. No, it's not all
what they care about because when some
the court has already told me, you know,
is if he's been harassing you and the
mate, the court has already told me.
The lit literally the court has
literally already told me.
So, it's it's as simple as that. And
also, I've tried reporting them and
they've done nothing. So, what? They're
just going to let them get away with it.
It's not going to happen.
It's literally and you can't talk your
way out of it as well because it's got
your face on it and everything. So, I
don't think they're going to let one
person get away with all of that and
then do the other for it. I I can't see
that happening. But we'll see in it.
Time will tell.
Time will literally tell
cuz really they shouldn't even be
talking about you.
They literally shouldn't even be talking
about you, bro. dusty. They shouldn't be
talking about you because obviously the
case and that is it. So I'm sure they
would have been told to not talk about
you. So yeah,
I'm not sure how that I'm not sure that
works, bro. I'm not sure that's how it works.
No, no, no. I'm sure that's not how it
It's like It's like Okay. It's like
someone Yeah. It's like someone Yeah.
getting beaten up. Dusty, put let's use
this analogy. Yeah. It's like someone
being beaten up, right? And then you're
proving in court that it's self-defense.
You bet someone you and and then proving
that it's self-defense. This is pretty
much what this is. Is this is in another
way. Why am I going to become Muslim, bro?
You know, so trust me, mate. It's not
It's not going to work. It's really,
really, really, really not going to work.
Trust me, it ain't going to work, bro.
What you think is going to work, how
it's going to work, you know,
in a normal case, maybe if it was one or
two things, maybe. If it was the USA
thing, nah, maybe. You know.
Yeah. Okay, bro. You keep telling
yourself that. Yeah, man. You keep
telling yourself that.
But if you have got [ __ ] almost 200
things of what this [ __ ] has done, I'm
sure the court would have a lot to say about that.
They have got a lot to say about that.
Trust me, they would have a lot. So what
are they just going to do? Completely
ignore it and make it one rule for one,
one for another? Nah, mate. They're not
the police. Do you understand? So yeah, simple. [gasps]
Yeah, man. Why am I going to become Muslim?
[snorts] Do not go and Lord a channel dock. Huh? Yeah.
[snorts and clears throat] Yeah. Never.
So, you've got 174 things of what this
[ __ ] has been doing and the court's just
going to ignore it. Yeah. So, you have
got this [ __ ] harassing you and what
they're just going to ignore it and do you nah
nah nah nah nah nah nah nah nah nah nah.
Simple as that. It's not going to work, bro.
What do you think, Dasok?
It's not going to work, bro.
It's not going to work. They will 100%
let you off
100%. And they've also still been doing
it as well. See, if they wasn't still
doing it, then they'll be like, [snorts]
well, but the fact that they have still
been doing it, it doesn't matter if he's
on bail. I don't give a [ __ ] I'm not on
bail either. It doesn't matter if he's
not on bail. It doesn't matter. I'm not
on bail. He's voided the He's He's
voided the conditions
by contacting me and talking about me.
It doesn't matter if he's not on bail.
He's voided all mine. See what I'm saying? Yeah. Simple.
So what? Like Okay. Okay. So So what
you're saying is then I'm going to go to
court, right? and
and this guy's continuously done it and
they're just going to be like, "Nah,
we're going we're only going to do you."
No way. No. No. No. No. No. No. No. No.
No way, bro. Absolutely no way.
Absolutely no way. So, what? They're
just going to let someone keep harassing
you every day until the court gate and
they're not going to do anything?
Absolutely no way. Absolutely
no way. And I swear my life on it,
you know. Well, he's harass Well, no,
he's not. Well, no, he's not allowed to
because he's harassing me every day. So,
no, he's not because he's actually
harassing me. Um, and and it's not it
could harm the court case. It will it
will harm he's already voided the
conditions. So, but no, I mean, he's
he's literally harassing me every day.
It's definitely definitely going to harm
the call case. There's a difference
between talking and harassing someone
every day. Let's let's get that. It's
not a crime to talk about someone.
It's not a crime to talk about someone
every day. You are literally harassing.
So, good luck. Yeah. Good luck, ma'am. Yeah,
bro. You've said he's not on B about a
million times. We don't care.
We literally literally don't care, bro.
Yeah, we don't care about this bell. I
don't know why you keep repeating
yourself. He's voided my I'm not on bail
either because he's voided my
conditions. I'm not on bail either. So,
we're both not on bail. Simple. Yeah.
You know what I'm saying? Well, no, it
will count because I will show where
I've reported him and the police have
done nothing. No, no, no, no, no, no,
no. because I will show the crime
reference number which I've reported and
they've done nothing about it. So yeah,
and he's not he's not clever. He's just
a little virgin. He's just a little grassing virgin.
That virgin ain't smart. He lives in a
castle bed sitting his 30s. [ __ ]
smart. This stupid little [ __ ] If he
was smart, bro, why am I still live on YouTube talking?
That little [ __ ] Anyone can cry to the
police being a victim and be a loser. It
doesn't make them smart. It makes them a
loser. Especially when they're going to
lose in the end cuz they're loser from
the start and they're going to be a
loser in the end. He hasn't got me done.
I'm still here. I'm still living my
life. I'm still talking about him and
there's been no consequences.
I've been talking about him for the past
year and I'm still not been nicked. What
do you mean he's smart?
Running to the police, being a grass is
being a loser. That's not being smart.
That means you're so much of a loser.
You can't handle someone in real life. Yeah.
Okay, bro. You keep telling yourself
that. Yeah. You keep telling yourself
Trust me, he has definitely voided it.
Trust me. Yep.
Yep. Trust me, bro. You're not going to
win. I promise you, you're not going to
win. Stop this. You're not going to win
with the police. I promise you on my on
my dead dad, on my mom's life, you are
not going to win with the police. And
that is my promise to you. Like, I will
invite every single person right to this
court case. You're not going to win. I
promise you, you're not going to win. It
was a It was just a waste of time you
doing this because you're not going to
win. Loser boy, virgin boy. You're not
going to win and you're still going to
be skinned. So, what the [ __ ] is the
point? You know what I mean? Yeah.
People are not allowed to harass you
every day, [sighs and gasps]
mate. I don't care how serious it is.
[ __ ] hell. I don't care. Shut up.
We've been over this. We've been talking
about this for the past an hour and a half now.
I literally don't care. And I don't care
to understand. I don't care. Simple,
brother. I've been to the police
multiple times. We're not talking about
this loser anymore. Why are we still
talking about this skint virgin,
brother? It doesn't matter if you're not
a bro. You're b you're literally
breaking the [ __ ] law every [ __ ]
day. Do what you got to do, bro. Simple.
Yeah. I don't give a [ __ ] what he's all
over. I don't care. I do not give a
[ __ ] I couldn't give any less of a [ __ ]
if I tried. I don't care. I'm not scared
of the police. I don't care. I'm not
going to be getting arrested. I don't
care. I don't care. Do what you've got
to do. I don't care.
I literally don't care.
I literally do not care. Go and call the
police. I don't care. That's the last
time I'm saying this. [ __ ] hell. [ __ ]
in [ __ ] hell.
Call the police. Call them. Call them.
Call them. I don't give a [ __ ] Loser.
Loser boy. Do it. Loser boy. I don't
care. [ __ ] hell. I don't know how
many times I've had to say that.
Yeah, I'm proper pooing myself. See you later. Anyways, um yeah.
Uh yeah, we know that's you, Timmy,
buying that account.
Uh we know that's you buying that account, lad. [clears throat]
Yeah, bro. Call the police on him. I've
called the police on him many times.
I've got a crime reference number and everything. Yeah, man.
Yeah, man. Call a piece all you want, bro. Yeah,
he's a proper loser, bro. Proper life loser.
See, the thing is, yeah, Dusty, I could
probably report him like every day, bro.
But I've actually got a life.
I'm not a loser. I So, I couldn't I
couldn't do it, bro.
Well, I hope you've took something out
of this, Dusty.
I hope you've learned something from this.
I the moral of the story is basically,
bro, never meet someone with autism.
I think you uh I think I think you
should you should learn by by by by mistakes, lad.
You know what I'm saying, bro? You need to um Yeah,
you need to um uh
never never meet someone with autism
or don't let them know anything about
you. Never let them know your name or anything. Yeah, lad.
Oh, it's so weird, lad. I know. It's
proper proper disabled. It is, bro. Bro,
it's not just this, though. It's just
It's this community that makes you lose brain cells.
Yeah, maybe it's pointless making a new
channel. I've got my cold approaching
channel and maybe I'll just go live once
in a while probably in it just to check
if it's the same losers.
Yeah, to be fair, bro. Yeah, you just go
live like once a week or something, is
it, bro? For like an hour or so,
it's pointless making a new channel,
bro. You just go um just come on
occasionally to see if it's the same
losers, isn't it, Dusty? I guess that
makes more sense, bro. Yeah.
It is proper disabled to be fair. Bro,
how do you think I feel dusty? I've got
so many people obsessed with me every
day. They want my ass.
I've never had so many men fancy me, lad. Jesus Christ.
[ __ ] hell, bro.
Imagine you just contacted someone, bro. Virgin boy.
I don't know how other people's life can
revolve around other people
that they don't know. Dusty madness.
Oh, loads of things, mate. And I've got
loads of things on my evidence pack already.
Oh, loads and loads and loads of things.
I've got loads of things that he's done.
That's definitely harassment.
Harassment at the very minimum.
Oh, I've got everything. And you know,
I've got stuff as well because a lot of
the stuff on that channel, Dusty, he deleted.
Um, he's deleted stuff that I've got.
All of the things that he's deleted,
I've got Yeah, he's not smart, mate.
Trust me, it will all come out in the
courtroom, lad. Everything he's deleted,
I've got, you know, them videos I've
literally got. He's not smart. He thinks
he's smart, but he's not smart. Cuz all
the things that he's tried deleting,
Dusty, I've got it all. Everything.
Do you not understand what he was trying
to do, Dusty? What he was trying to do
is this little virgin was try to delete
all of the stuff talking about me um
when he went to the police, but I've got
everything. And I said to the police as
well, why is all of them things gone off
of his channel, bro? He's not smart.
He's actually really thick.
Okay, bro. Well, they will. They will.
They will, though. The judge will care
when someone's been harassing me. Same
as self-defense. Same if you was
upright. for beating someone up and you
proved it was self-defense, they will care.
They literally will care.
How do you think people get off with
self-defense, you idiot? What do you
think? What do you think their first
charge was? They They literally will
care. They literally literally will
care. I've spoke to two solicitors about
this. Trust me, they will care.
They they they they definitely
definitely will care. Oh no, he's really
really really thick. All of the things
that he's deleted I've got. He's really
really really really thick.
He's really really really thick. He's
thick as pigshit.
No. No. He's really really really thick.
All of the things that he's deleted,
I've got I've got them saved
with his face and everything. Talking
about me with his face. So, I've got
everything, bro. Believe you me. Don't
you worry about what I've got, but I've
got enough. All of my little evidence back. Yeah.
Yeah. Okay. Well, bro, we will see in
court, won't we?
We will see in court, won't we?
Yeah, you don't need to worry about
that. I'm not worrying. Well, we will
see in court, won't we?
You know, we will see in court, won't
we? Don't worry about it, man. We will
see in court. Deep down, you know,
you're going to lose, you know. Yeah.
Yeah. It doesn't matter. It literally
doesn't matter, bro.
I'm going to come off YouTube for 5 years, Indigo,
then I'm going to come back.
What do you think to that?
What do you think? What do you think? Huh?
Okay, bro. It doesn't matter then. I'm
going to jail, bro. You happy now?
Yeah, man. I'm going to go to prison.
Are you happy? I'm on bail. I'm going to
go to prison. Did that make you happy, bro?
Yeah, I know, bro. I'm going to get
nicked. I'm going to go prison. Oh,
sucks to be me, bro. You happy now? [snorts]
Yeah. Okay, bro.
Yeah. Yeah, bro. I've been arrested. I'm
going to go prison. Didn't you know
that? Yeah. Oh, Dusty, do you know I'm
going to go prison?
Yeah, I'm going to go prison, bro. I
hope you meet me tomorrow, Jake.
Which is definitely definitely Terry. [clears throat]
Yeah. Yeah. No, I'll go prison me, bro.
Yeah, I'm going to go prison, bro. I'm
going to go prison. Yeah. Sucks to be
me, bro. I'm going to go prison, man.
Yeah, I'm going to go prison, man.
I'm going to go prison.
But no, I'm coming off YouTube soon anyways, lads.
The obsession with Peter B is getting weird again.
All eyes on me, Dusty. Whenever I come
on, I'm sick of it, Dusty.
I'm sick of these middleweights
obsessed, jealous people. Leave me
alone. I think the closest you're going
to get to them leaving you alone is leaving.
But then they're still not going to
leave you alone. I don't know, man. I
think they'd maybe come to your Maybe
they'd come on the door. Maybe if you
left YouTube, they'd come on the door.
I think they were trying to [ __ ] with
you was some other way.
Maybe, bro. Maybe.
Yeah. Well, if he's done nothing, bro,
you've got nothing to worry about, don't
you? My evidence pack says otherwise.
It shows him doing a lot of indirect
stuff with his face as well. Just leave
it to the courts and leave it to the
police. Let them deal with it, lad. Yeah.
Harassing someone every day is breaking
the law. I've got harassment and
everything. Bro, you seem to be
panicking a bit. Like, I've got what
I've got on you. Don't worry about it.
You seem to really really be panicking
cuz you know you're [ __ ] everything
I've got. You know I'm [ __ ]
Okay, then go and do a video right now
mentioning my name. If you're if you're
so sure, one second. Right. If you're so
sure that you can do this and you can do
that, why don't you go live right now
talking about me?
Do it then. Do it. Do it.
Literally do it right now. If you've got
if you literally can do what you want,
go live right now and do a video
mentioning my name.
Go and do it then. If you're not on
bell, yeah, okay, you're not on bell,
whatever. Go and do it then. Go and do
it. Go and do it. Go and do it. Show
your face right now and talk about me.
Go and do it.
Exactly. So, shut the [ __ ] up cuz you
know you can't do it and you avoided it.
That's why. Do it. do it. Yeah. Yeah, bro. Exactly.
I don't care, Indie. Go.
No, you haven't. Just do it right now
then. Go live right now and and show
your face and talk about me
and see how big you are. You don't even
need to show your face to be honest. You
can't do that because you know you can't do that.
You know you can't do that. No, you're
not allowed to mention my name. That's
why you don't mention my name. That's
why you mention me indirectly so I can
say exactly the same thing to you
because the police have told you to
button it. I'm going to say the same
thing to you now. You don't mention my
name and you don't do it indirectly
because the police have told you to button it.
The police have told you to button it. A
big button. Exactly, mate. That's why
you don't go live anymore.
You don't mention my name.
Yeah, exactly. Cuz cuz he's been told to
button it, Dusty. He's the virgin's been
told to button it. So, he's [ __ ]
telling me that I can't say his name,
but he can't say my name. He literally
He literally can't say mine. [ __ ] virgin.
So, they reckon if I come off YouTube,
Dusty, they'd like they'd come in the
door or something?
I think these people are way too obsessed to um
to ever stop, bro. What do you think?
What What would the best solution be, Dusty? Um,
I don't know, lad.
Yeah, man. Go live right now and say my name.
What do you think, Dusty?
What do you reckon these people do as
soon as they wake up? Dusty,
what's his full name? Virgin boy. Skim boy.
You know his name. Virgin boy. Is he a virgin?
Yeah. So what do you what do you think
these people do indigo as soon as they wake up?
I have mentioned him. Virgin boy. Yeah.
Yeah. Okay. You can't mention my name.
You can't mention my [ __ ] name.
You can't mention my name. Yeah.
Dusty, do you think Red Star takes one
day off of YouTube?
Do you think he takes one day off of YouTube? Nah.
You reckon he takes one day off of YouTube, lad?
You don't follow him. Why, bro?
Oh, man. Bro,
when are these people going to come out
the closet, Dusty?
When are these people going to come out the closet?
Don't they get bored of being jealous
and obsessed with someone in 2026?
How can they be so gay? And how can they
be so jealous of another man? Not even
going to try and figure it out, lad.
You literally don't stop, do you? Every day.
Every [ __ ] day, bro. What the [ __ ] >> [snorts]
>> No, if you left, um, I think a couple
people would stop.
Indigo, if I leave YouTube, does that
mean they'll leave me alone?
Like, I don't react to them ever again.
So like never again. You reckon they'll
leave me alone? Do you reckon?
Cuz LT said they done it they do it for
a reaction in it. So
maybe not reacting to them.
H who knows? So they'd leave me alone? Yeah.
No, bro. I think they would try and No,
they wouldn't leave you alone, bro.
No, no, no. I'm talking like in the future.
I'm talking about the obsessed channels.
Do you reckon they'll ever leave me
alone if I didn't react to them? [clears throat] No.
They hate you. Their jealousy is that bad, bro.
No. Their jealousy is that bad towards
you, bro. They'll never ever ever ever stop.
Never, bro. Cuz they are it's an actual
obsession. You see,
there's a difference between like people. No, there's Yeah, [snorts]
I don't know why. I don't have picture
saves of him. It's just on this um Streamyard thing.
I don't need to put it up again.
Maybe if I left YouTube for 5 years.
Nah, bro. But do you know what's so
weird? Where these people are so obsessed.
You actually think about it sometimes,
bro. Like Timmy's been on here longer
than me. He doesn't get that many people
obsessed with him, bro. I've got I've
got really bad people obsessed with me,
bro. They actually want my ass.
I've actually got people that actually
want my ass.
Like actually want my ass, bro.
No, they actually want my ass, lad.
I think people like I don't I think with
Timmy people just try to wind him up and
[ __ ] but with me it's different, bro.
No, with me it's a lot different, lad.
They actually want my [ __ ] ass, lad.
It's [ __ ] weird as [ __ ]
Yeah, but what if I ignore them though, Dusty?
Yeah, but what if I ignore them, Dusty? >> [snorts] >> Um, nah, bro.
It'll be the same in [ __ ] 2050. You
[ __ ] You'll never Yeah.
Yeah. Ed Matthews gets trolls, but I
don't think he gets people that's
obsessed with him.
See, that's another thing. He gets
trolled. He gets [ __ ] and he's not
he's not said anything about kids or
anything. And he gets loads of trolls.
He gets swatted and everything, bro. And
he ain't done anything bad. Obviously,
he's a bit of a [ __ ] sometimes, but
he ain't done anything really bad. And
he gets loads of trolls, bro.
Think about it, bro.
Dusty, think about it.
They get trolled badly, bro. They They
get swatted, man, as well.
>> So, that's the same thing with here. If
you didn't say any mad things, they
would still um they would still do it,
bro. They would still do it. These
people are actually obsessed. Well, I
don't think people are actually obsessed
with with Ed Matthews, man. I think they
just [ __ ] with him.
I don't know. Maybe people are jealous
of him as well. I don't know. But I
don't think people are obsessed with
him. [ __ ] knows.
But bro, you don't you shouldn't use
kids as an excuse, man. Just say that
you're just say that you're um just say
that you're homosexual.
I don't care about homosexuals, bro. If
you just come out as gay, bro, then
that's it. But unfortunately, I don't
swing that way. So, I won't be giving
you my backside, Jo,
etc. I don't want I don't want I don't Yeah,
I don't think this guy's straight, bro.
I can't lie. Jesus Christ.
Jesus [ __ ] Christ.
Yeah. I don't know how much [ __ ] I'm in.
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Bro, you're not
scaring me, lad. [snorts] Get a life,
bro. Get a [ __ ] life. [clears throat]
I need to do this video to Jo, man, cuz
we need to do this Nottingham thing soon. Yeah. [sighs]
No, no, no, no, no. Yeah,
bro. I literally don't care, bro.
I really, really don't care.
>> [clears throat]
>> I remember them poster videos. They were
funny as [ __ ] in it. Come on, don't
lie. That made you laugh your ass off in
it. [snorts] Yeah, man.
I always said I was going to do it, but
I weren't actually going to do it, bro.
It was only because of the um the money
thing and that.
Yeah, man. It was only because of the
money thing. Otherwise, I wouldn't have
done it. I don't care what anyone said.
I told the police as well. They said,
"Oh, why did you do it?" I told them everything. Yeah, man.
Yeah, man. I told them everything.
Weird, bro. really weird.
And would you believe that some of these
people are in relationships as well that
are doing this?
Oh, one second. I want to I like these
American things, bro.
No, that was a different one. No, that
was a different one. That was the posters.
No, on this one I just I just said no comment.
Nope, it was a different one.
Yeah, these people are still obsessed
with me, John. Man,
every single day it's getting creepy
again, lad. I might have to take a break
off YouTube. For some reason, they want
my ass, bro.
They want my young ass.
There was one guy earlier, John, and all
he kept talking about was me. Every
single comment was me. And I'm thinking
at this point, bro, just come out as gay. Like simple.
Yeah, bro. They've been doing it. Is it
still going on, lad? They've been doing
it for years, bro. They've been doing it
for [ __ ] 5 years.
I'm sorry, bro, but I don't swing that way,
bro. Do you know the maddest thing is,
bro? You wouldn't even You wouldn't even
stalk a woman the way that these people
stalk me. Do you not think Do you not
know how mad that is? Obviously, you
wouldn't know that what I'm talking
about, bro, because you you've only been
on you've only you've only discovered my
channel yesterday. I just can't stop
thinking about this is and if this does
not prove that they're homosexuals, I
don't know what will.
They're definitely homos, bro. Or maybe
bisexual. Oh, they're bisexual at the
very least. They've got to be bisexual,
bro. At the very least.
Maybe they're bisexual. They definitely
like men. They love talking about men as well.
Ooh, my skin, bro. They make my skin crawl, John.
I don't know, bro. They do it every day.
Do you want to see a channel that's been
doing it uh for years, John?
I seem like I've got autism. Thanks,
man. Hey, bro. Do you want to see a
channel? One of the channels that's
doing it. This phone is [ __ ] up, bro.
I'm sure you've seen it.
I don't know why they do it, bro.
How they can sit on the internet for years.
They don't get to me, bro. They don't
get to me at all. They
They're just weird.
They don't get to me. They weird me out.
Cuz I'm sure these people say that
they're straight, but there there's no
way these people are straight, bro.
I couldn't even stalk or harass a woman
the way the way these people do this.
That's how you know they got problems,
bro. That's how you know they got problems.
And And the And the weirdest thing is
they've never even met you either.
They've never even met me, bro.
There you go, bro. That's one of the channels.
That's probably the worst one on there,
bro. So, this is basically this, but
loads of different channels.
One year. It's so mad when you actually
see the years that they've been doing
this. Wow. And they haven't got bored once. Jesus Christ. Jesus.
They they they swear by their life that
they're not jealous. So, if they're
really saying that they're not jealous,
then they've got to be uh
um the only thing that they can be is
gay. It's as simple as that.
But I yeah, like I said, I do believe
they're jealous, but they're also gay as well. So,
yo, [ __ ] hell, man. Yeah.
No, I quit gambling, bro.
Oh, I don't gamble anymore, bro.
I've kind of quit.
So, yeah. Oh, my hair and beard's
getting annoying now. I need to
literally get a cut, man. [ __ ] [ __ ] hell.
No, no, no, no. Hey, John,
where did you go?
Did you come back? Yeah.
Two years. He's been Oh my god.
They've been doing this for years, bro.
Hey, if you go on the channel. Yeah.
Let me see the community posts.
So, they've been doing this every day
for 2 years minimum.
I don't know, bro. I think they're gay,
John. To be honest with you, bro. I
actually think they're gay
cuz they say that they're not jealous.
Yet every single person that has been
doxed usually is fat and ugly.
They usually um
fat, ugly, and uh really ugly people or
they're just ugly. Um so they swear
they're not jealous. That's debatable.
So then the only thing it could be is
that they're homosexuals.
That's the only thing it can be. Bro,
I don't know what your guess is, but if
they're swearing that they're not
jealous, [clears throat] then they're gay.
They literally are gay. There's nothing
else that can explain why people would
sit on online, bro, for years every day
recording and stalking another man.
Unless you've got any tips or any
anything that I'm not uh
it's very very
strange, isn't it, lad?
What would your guess be?
I don't want to put words in your mouth.
I think that they hate themselves.
I think they're jealous. And I also
think that they're gay as well.
I think it's three things, but I don't
know about you.
Definitely don't know about you.
And by the way, John, it's it's every
day. It's not like streamers where like
they're trying to get a reaction. They
are actually obsessed. So even if you
left YouTube today, they would never
stop even after 5 years.
And I'm just thinking of my bad I'm just
thinking of my experiences with women.
And I've never been this obsessive,
bro. Like like [snorts] for years and
years every day. I haven't, bro. So yeah,
I [snorts] don't know, lad. It's weird.
And they're not bullying no one. They're
not bothering anyone. They're just
proving themselves to be weird. Like
they never ever get to me. And you know,
they don't understand, John. Like,
they've never ever made me question the
way that I look. Not one of them have
ever got to me. Not any of them these
self projectors have ever got to me.
They're actually just so weird.
Yeah, bro. He's not the only one.
There's another one. I'll show you
another one, bro.
Uh, [groaning] I'll show you another one
if you want, lad.
Yeah, these it gets weirder, bro. It gets weirder.
Yeah, it gets weirder. I'll send you this. Um,
no, he's definitely definitely a homosexual.
Definitely a homosexual.
The same as that JF as well.
No, definitely a homosexual.
Yeah, there's loads of people that do
this, bro. There you go. That's the channel.
That's one. That's two.
Then I'll send you another one as well.
That may be a breach of bell. I don't
give a [ __ ] Tell someone who gives a
[ __ ] And I'll send you another one as well.
I don't give a [ __ ] Go tell someone that cares
and I'll do what I want when I want.
And that's another channel. So yeah, you
can take a look at them two channels and that's basically
and there's obviously people in the
comments that do it as well, but you you
get the you get to uh Yeah, I'll do what I want.
I'll do what I want when I want. Thank
you very much.
I will do what I want when I want. Thank
you very much. So, yeah, that's two channels, lad. Yeah, bro. [sighs]
I think so, bro. Yeah.
That made me laugh. I'm He said He said
I'm fast and got a strong punch.
[clears throat] That's funny, bro. I'm
strong and I've got a and I've got a and
I've got a punch. That's funny, bro. Yeah.
See you later, lad.
Did you see it, John?
Mad. Madness. Madness.
>> [clears throat]
>> [ __ ] hell, bro.
No way, man. [cough]
>> [clears throat]
>> Oh, there's another one as well, bro.
But they're not jealous. Don't forget,
John. They're not jealous of me and
they've got a better life than me.
So, they say they they swear to their
blue in the face that they're not
jealous and they've got nothing to be
jealous of. Yet, they will sit online
every single day, bro.
And they they do this. They've got
channels dedicated to men.
I'll give you a story, John. Yeah. Cuz
you're new here. Yeah.
I met someone, bro, about it's almost 3
years ago. Say 3 years ago now, bro. And
they [ __ ] with me. They led me on.
They gave me this mad false hope, right?
And this was some woman, bro, basically
that I actually met and and and and and
got with, not going to get into ins and
outs. And I was like mad for like a
year, bro. And that was someone I met,
someone I got with, and I was mad for
like a year, then I just couldn't be
bothered anymore. So that tells me, bro,
that if this is someone that you've met
that's a woman and, bro, you just have
left them alone for the past year and a
half, they have got to be gay. These
people on here have literally got to be
gay. There's there there's there's
nothing else that they that they can be
but gay, bro.
Because think about it, you've met
someone and that was someone something
that actually happened in real life with
someone that you've met, bro. I can't
remember the last time I went on their
[ __ ] on their [ __ ] You know,
it's strange how long people can keep
doing this for, bro. But they swear
they're not jealous and they swear
they're not disabled. So strange, bro.
And it's not even women. They're
actually stalking men. They're batty
men, bro. They're absolutely They're
actually batty, bro.
I wouldn't mind if they were stalking
[ __ ] women, bro. [ __ ] hell.
Yeah, they're mad. What? Did you see all
the channels, John?
I don't know why they're doing it, bro.
They're saying it's because I've said
mad stuff um about someone's kids years
ago, but nah, bro. Come on now. This is 2026.
That's not the reason why people are
obsessed with me, bro.
Nah, bro. There's There's no way. I
think they're homosexuals. Um
I think they're generally homosexuals, bro. Simple.
I think they're closeted homosexuals.
That's what I think.
Um, I generally think that's what they are.
I don't know, bro. What? I don't know, lad.
Oh, what are you? What do you think?
weird. Weird, lad. [snorts]
Oh my god, it's 2:00 in the [ __ ]
morning, bro. Jesus Christ, man.
But yeah, John. Um, yeah, I don't plan
to go back to gambling, lad anyways.
I don't plan to come back from gambling, lad.
Go back to gambling. Sorry.
[ __ ] that, bro.
I think there's a timer. You just say
enough is enough in it.
I stopped for a year, bro. I've only
recently got back into it, lad. But I'm
done anyways with gambling. So [snorts] yeah, mad. All
>> [clears throat]
>> right, lad. I'm gone. Yeah, I'm probably
going to do a video on this [ __ ] um
advising him that he needs to actually
come out the closet and um yeah bro got
to go sleep and I'll see you when I see
you man. So that's that bro in a bit.
Yeah man. Peace.