getting on it, mates. On the on the
collection, a good old collection.
>> You pick
Yes, sir. Put it in there.
>> Thank you, Captain.
>> Yo, I'm out and about, man. I'm on approaching
trying to find a little candidate.
No, a collectible. I've approached like
[ __ ] seven people over. My first
drink. I'm on my first drink. [ __ ]
I'm about to do some serious sending.
She looks a bit s.
Yeah, I about seven
getting on the [ __ ] thing, mate.
Oh, I'm telling you, it's getting worse.
It's getting worse. It's getting [ __ ]
Won't be live anymore, but I'm near that
location where that guy said, so no
[ __ ] about now. Come on.
Your little pest.
[ __ ] the whole [ __ ] days as well,
man. Got myself trimmed.
[ __ ] I'm out drinking, bro. 6 6:00.
I'm right around the corner, man. I've
just been sending these approaches over
trying to [ __ ] fill up my collection.
>> Yeah, I'm [ __ ] [ __ ] bro.
That's reserve, isn't it?
I don't like this place to be fair.
Oh, [ __ ] draining. It is.
It is [ __ ] draining, lad. [ __ ] draining.
About eight approaches sober, Mr. Be
mate. It's [ __ ] draining, especially
in this weather, lad.
I sure do, Captain.
Of course it'd be rude not to, mate. Oh,
I hope we actually get some numbers
today. We will do, but getting worse in
2026, mate. Getting worse.
But anyway, we're not complaining, bro.
We'll leave that until later. Oh.
Yeah, it seems to have gotten worse, man.
So, where is this guy? See, it's a slow
the [ __ ] again.
Slow the [ __ ]
[ __ ] I don't know train station. I'm a crazy
I'm going to cut this uh soon we don't
hear from the sky cuz I've got some
approaching to be doing lad. Wow. This is
I'm just out on the piss, bro. I've done
eight approaches. I've done them
completely sober. My first drink. I'm on
my first drink, bro. Trying to collect
some new iszies. You know how it is.
I had two sausage rolls before drinking
cuz the place I wanted to go was shot.
Should be all right. Yeah, bro.
Nah, nothing, bro.
Nothing yet, lad. But they were sober,
to be fair.
They were sober, so they're on the
street. I haven't done him in the pub yet. Yeah, bro.
So, where is this guy anyways?
Where the [ __ ] is this guy at?
>> Yeah, mom.
One second, bro. I am out collecting UK
asylum, but I've only done him sober yet
in the in on the street. Nothing on the
street in it. So, sometimes you don't
get lucky in the street, but I
definitely will be getting some here in this place.
Yeah, man. 100%.
>> Yeah, I'm out collecting UK signing. I
went to the barbers madness.
>> Well, what do you think I'm trying to
[ __ ] do, you [ __ ] What do you think
I've been trying to do for the past
[ __ ] hour? Yeah.
All right, Stephen Alvin. It's getting
worse, man. It's getting harder.
It's definitely definitely getting harder, mate.
It is actually getting harder, bro.
Compared to like a year ago, year after,
year and a half ago. It's getting harder, bro.
It's getting way harder, bro. It's hard
to even get a combo out of someone nowadays.
Yeah, I'll do it on the way back.
It doesn't matter though, bro. It's
[ __ ] There's [ __ ] everywhere, bro. It
doesn't matter about the month. Could be
[ __ ] July. Still still the same.
I have tried bro but I done a lot sober
someone offered me their Instagram but I
said no they're leaving in two days but
so where is this guy anyways
I was speaking to one from Boston but I
was talking to an American she was like
Stephen she was like Um,
she said to me, "Yeah,
um, I was talking to her." Yeah.
I was talking to her. Why is it so busy
today? It's quite busy today. Um, she
was basically saying that she's from America. I
like Boston said she lives near me. Told her from
she near the city. I said, "Oh, let me
let me get your number." And she said,
"Oh, I've got a boyfriend." I was like, 30.
>> I just don't care about anything else. I
just want the bloody numbers. I just
want to be their friend.
UK asylum. I just want to be their
friend. But no, it's getting worse, bro.
Trust me, it is. It is getting 100
worse, bro. It's getting It's getting
It's so bad, bro. I swear it's never
been like this, bro. Ever.
Even though it's always been [ __ ] it's
never been like this. It's It's bad,
bro. It's really bad, lad. But at the
same time, the weird thing about it,
Stephen Howard, is it's not normal, but
it is normal. Does that make sense?
It's not normal, but it is normal. Does
that make sense? Because it's 2026. It's
only getting worse. So, best accept it now, it
actually feel sick, bro. I had two
sausage rolls. That's enough, though. I'm sure.
Maybe it's just a beer.
Anyways, is this guy coming? But I'm
going to cut this. I'm going to end the live stream.
>> Yeah, it's definitely definitely got
worse. No, I'm not putting my camera on, lad. I'm busy.
I'm the lights are off now. So, I'm
busy, lad. Sorry.
We should get some numbers. We will get London.
You know what? This is actually a vibe
for Thursday. It's actually a vibe. February Thursday.
My stomach is hurting me, bro. I did
have two sausage rolls.
But it is get it is definitely getting
worse then because if you when you used
to go out on the street Yeah.
When you used to go out on the street,
right? You would get
you would get like one in seven, one in
eight. Now you can approach 50 and get
one number, bro. It's bad.
I'm looking clean as [ __ ]
Yeah. Like you can you can it's got
worse. It's got worse and the attitude
of some of them as well. Anyways, [ __ ]
all that. We'll talk about it later when
I come back.
But you know, it's 2026 though. You
know, it's never going to be different. So,
get used to it.
Hopefully people here will be more
inclined to talk.
>> You know what? I feel really confident
today. You know, Steven Howard, even
though I ain't done for months, I
haven't drunk for [ __ ] ages. I feel
confident as [ __ ]
Like, I just don't give a [ __ ] You know
what I mean? again.
One down and two to go then, is it
Stephen Howard with a Spider-Man
t-shirt? That's one That's one down and
two to go. >> Yeah.
None of these little [ __ ] idiots are
going to show up anywhere, bro.
>> None of them will ever show up anywhere.
>> All I wanted to be your friend. All I
wanted to do was be friend.
But yeah, bro. I need to go in a minute.
Anyways, I'm enjoying I've not been on YouTube.
>> Nah, not really, bro. I haven't done it
for ages and I'm confident as [ __ ]
Well, yeah, I guess so. I guess. Yeah, I
done it at a train station. I'm not
scared. Me. I'm not scared, bro.
I was a bit apprehensive the first one,
but I've only just started drinking.
We're waiting for this idiot. Where's he at?
>> I got my shoe bombs on and I've got my
jeans in a bag.
Even if we can get a couple of numbers,
I'll be happy with it to add to the
collection. We will get numbers. Well,
we will be getting numbers. Not if we What's up,
Oh, see if this guy
Yeah, I'm out. I'm out. I've done eight
approaches over [ __ ] nothing so far,
but they were on the street. So
hopefully we get more here.
Well, we will be getting more. We
getting bites today, bro. One sec.
>> Yeah, bro.
Yeah, I've done seven, eight sober, but
they're getting worse, Bob. It's getting
worse, man. Definitely is getting worse.
It was nothing like this
bit ago, bro. It's getting worse, man.
It's getting [ __ ] worse.
I don't e nothing really bro.
Right. So this guy's not coming. Huh?
But I'm not far away from where he's
saying me. Where is this guy?
Now we just got Smokey Be now to do and
Joseph Bar and they're definitely not
showing up. But I'm telling you right
now, they're definitely not showing up on there.
>> Let me have a little peek. See what's
going on down there.
There a couple women there, but
I'll do it in a minute. Can't be
bothered. [ __ ] drain, bro. Hey double
what you done.
Cool. Right, I'm leaving. I'm put this
off in five minutes.
I need another beer, mate.
I also mate
it looks all right. forget
what I'm doing.
>> Yeah, stay definitely
draining. Stephen Hard is very draining.
You're doing it sober. [ __ ] draining.
Very boring. Very draining.
Yeah, I will do it in a bit though.
Yeah, a couple spread out.
>> Question five.
I need to meet you
and the other part's been blocked off.
So about to go to this place with this
bridge been blocked on [ __ ] annoying me.
I'm going to get this bit up.
coming in, mate. Today
busy today, bro.
I'm not videoing it, lad. I'm not
videoing it. And I wouldn't on this channel anyways.
Is there a dentist? I don't think there is.
get this drink. I'm going to send it.
>> Yeah, it is getting worse. It's
definitely getting worse.
This place is also a no virgin policy asylum. No policy.
You don't bro you don't do
no [ __ ] [ __ ]
It's quite busy for a Thursday.
>> Yeah, but normally if you come here on a Thursday,
I still prefer Thursdays. Wouldn't you
guys see? It's busy, but it's not busy.
It's just perfect. I'm in.
Saturday is just around. I'm in.
>> I I didn't go out. I didn't go out I
didn't go out boxing day. I didn't go
out. It's too too busy. It's too busy.
>> Too um too busy. It's overpriced.
>> I prefer March April. We not
[ __ ] in a
right. I need to go now.
>> Yeah, I will come. Oh, I'll be back later. 6:08. Yeah, 6:08.
Yeah, from the [ __ ]
>> Right, I'm going in. Yeah, I'm going in
the deep end, lads. So, wish me luck, >> Captain.
>> Right. Hopefully this time we'll [ __ ]
get a number for the [ __ ] collection.
Done. Nervous, Pete. Never nervous,
mate. That's yourself, lad. Never been
nervous in my life. Stop talking about yourself.
>> Nervous? [ __ ] nervous? What? You
[ __ ] idiot. You clown. You don't even
leave your house.
Your self projector.
Nervous of what, bro? No. Nervous of
what, bro? Never.
Nah, you're nervous. You're fat. You're
ugly. You're housebound. Everything that
you call other people, you are yourself.
No, I'm at your mom house.
Anyways, I'm ending this now and I'm
approaching. So, see you in a bit.