There we go, man. Look at you straight
on here, you [ __ ] idiot, man. We got
about five numbers. Oh, [ __ ] [ __ ] fat, bro.
You know, you can always rely on good
old England, is it? Never going to change, lad.
>> I'm on my way back now, bro. I didn't
even eat. Well, except from Sausage World.
Good old England.
Never changes. Love England, man. [ __ ]
weather, [ __ ] people.
What isn't there to love? You know,
>> nothing, bro. Just chilling. I went to
this brass house and an argument in this brass house.
Hey, bro. But do you listen, bro? Do you
understand now? Listen, bro. I'll
explain more when I get home, bro.
Do you understand now, bro? Why I don't
go out? This is literally the reason why
I do not go out, bro. The drinking, the
[ __ ] the [ __ ] And it's got worse
now, bro. This is exactly
right. This is exactly, bro. Why do you
not go out, bro? Literally, [laughter]
it's a mad You got to laugh at it, bro.
You have to laugh, bro. Come on. Let's
laugh at it, bro. Cuz it's cuz it's so
pathetic and depressing that you just
got to laugh at it.
Yeah. But do you know the thing is
though, UK asylum is Asia Asia's getting
bad now. Even Asia is getting bad. In 10
years, that country is going to be that
continent is going to be finished. No,
bro. Long story. Long story, bro. I'll
explain it when I get home.
Yeah, I'll explain it.
>> No, no, no. Basically, what happened,
bro, was I went in there and you know
how I like my you know what. And she's
like, "Oh, you can't do that in my mouth
and stuff." I was like, "What? No, no,
no, hold on, hold on." Then she asked
someone else and she's like, "No, you
can have sex, but you can't have that."
I said, "No." And then the security
guard starts. I said, "Don't open the
door for me. I'll leave when I'm ready."
Yeah. Get that right. Yeah. You're not
going to open the [ __ ] door for me.
shut that door now and I will leave and
I'm ready. Yeah. And I had to tell her
about herself and he didn't say nothing
cuz he knows, bro. What can he say? He
would have got knocked the [ __ ] out. And
that's exactly why I don't go out, bro.
Like I literally do not go out because
of this reason. Like drinking obviously.
Um it's bad now. And at the end of the
day, bro, in 10 years, Asia is going to
be finished. So I'm not surprised why
it's a lot worse here now. To be fair, I
did get five numbers, but
no, it's not a waste of money, bro. I
only spent about 50 quid to be fair. Um,
but it is virtually impossible now. Like
if you have not met, if you did not meet
anyone, bro, about
it's impossible now. Like
it's it's never happening in this
country. And if you don't get to Asia
before before that's finished, then
you're [ __ ] there, too.
>> And the thing is UK asylum escort was
about 38 40. She's an escort and she's
middle age. And she's telling me she
doesn't suck dick. Bro, are you and
you're you're telling me that, bro? No,
it's bad, bro. You need to leave, bro.
There's even got to be like better
country than this as well, to be fair. Um and uh
yeah, she's like, and there was another
one as well. She was trying to say bye.
I said, "No, no, no. I'll go when I'm
ready." And you ask the cutie guards
aren't going to do nothing. Yeah. Watch
who you're talking to, [ __ ] Yeah.
Because you might just want to No, she
just didn't want to do it without it.
She didn't even see it either. I said,
"Nah, you I will leave and I'm [ __ ]
good. I'm ready, you stupid little
cunt." And I was slagging her off in
front of the security guard. What's he
going to do to me, bro? Nothing. You're
not even going to put his hands on me,
bro. He was quiet as a mouth. Like, I
should have I should have recorded it.
So, yeah. But anyways, this is one of
this is why I don't go out drinking,
bro. Like, this is what I'm saying. This
is one of the reasons why I don't deal
with this [ __ ]
But yeah, anyways, it's just negative,
bro. So, we're going to go home, order
some food, and he's saying about Benon as well.
But it's getting worse. It is definitely
definitely getting worse.
Uh, you literally got no chance there now.
And you know, the maddest thing is about
this as well, UK asylum, is it's not
normal, but it is normal, if that makes
sense. Like, it isn't normal, but in
2026 [ __ ] is normal. That's the most
mad thing about it is it's not normal,
but it is normal, if that makes sense.
Yeah, it's never going to change it. You
know, even Asia's bad now. Like, even
Asia's bad. So,
>> this message told him about it.
Yeah, I might get that, bro. I might get
something else. I don't know. Got the
last train back anyways.
It's boring, bro. boss the [ __ ] out of me.
Thing he didn't go live, did he?
But do you see what I mean? Now, UK sign
him. Like, all jokes aside,
um, it's really bad, bro. Really, really
bad. And none of it surprised me either
because what Ant-Man told me about, you
know, Thailand now, it it didn't even
surprise me either.
We never change, lad. Never change. And
in 10 years, Asia is going to be bad as well. So,
I got some women's numbers.
Yeah, I got some numbers.
>> We are now.
>> It's not even funny, bro. I wish I could
laugh at it, bro. But it's really funny.
It's actually quite disturbing to be
honest cuz like obviously if it's like
it now it's going to get weird. It's
going to get worse. It's really bad,
bro. But to be honest, I expected it,
bro. Like you I expected it. I did
expect it to be fair.
Which is bad to say, but
It's good though. But I felt confident
in that obviously. But
>> thing is UK. Sorry. This is way
different lad than it was two years ago.
It's way different like two years ago,
bro. You would actually It was never
like this. It was never like this. >> Yeah. service.
>> You know, lad, you know,
don't want to eat, bro. At least I'm not
like sticking out. It will never change,
lad. It will never change. It will never
change. That's why I don't go out, lad.
No, I'm good, bro. I'm all good, lad.
No, I'm just going to go home and get some food.
Just sad what the world's come to, isn't
it? But I mean, I expect it in it.
>> We are now at the gap.
>> It is bad to be fair, lad.
>> And you know the thing is UK Asylum,
it's only getting worse.
The thing is, bro, it is actually only getting worse.
It was way worse than it was two years
ago. Tell me, bro. [ __ ] knows what's
happen. Oh [ __ ] we only like Okay, [ __ ] almost. Yeah,
it's bad, bro.
I blame Tik Tok. I blame Instagram, bro.
I don't disclose.
>> Yeah, bro. I told I told her as well
like I I told I told the security bro I
said close the door. I will open it when
I'm ready. Close the door now. You're
not going to open the door. I will I
will leave when I'm ready to leave. You
understand that, [ __ ] Yeah.
I said that to him, bro. I shut the door
now. That's what I said to him. I'm not
finished. I I'll tell you when I'm
finished. And it's just negativity and
toxic that [ __ ] that people don't need
in their life, bro. You know what I'm
saying, bro? And that's why I don't I
don't blow out
um on nights out and stuff. So, um
>> the next station is
>> not good.
It's not good, bro.
I don't know.
I'll be back live when I'm back.
Anyways, we're not sleeping this [ __ ]
Anyways, I'm going to end it live when
I'm home, bro.
Yeah. A bit roy.