Oh, [ __ ] hell,
man. No one come on yesterday. I think
they were all in the good oldicles.
The good old
nesticles. Give it a [ __ ] world.
I [ __ ] win, mate.
Another ball in there. Nothing to
do. Nothing to do
today. I think that man pulled
yesterday, didn't he? [ __ ]
time be called on a [ __ ] Sunday.
Well, got four days to wait until this
thing comes out in the cinema. [ __ ]
hell. Long wait a minute. four [ __ ] [Music]
days. Needs to hurry up, man.
Then come out basically.
Who's job hunting? I don't need a job,
mate. I've got enough money. I get
enough money. I'm good,
bro. Speak for yourself, though, man.
Yeah, you can get yourself a
job. Speak for
yourself. I have enough money. I'm all good. that to yourself. Not me. [ __ ]
hell. I never need to work. I've got
brains. I don't need to work. I've got a brain,
lad. [ __ ] working is dead.
To be fair though, to be fair, if I was
self-employed, I'd probably work days
that I don't drink cuz I'm on a detox
and there's like nothing to do and I
don't obviously I don't gamble anymore.
Well, I don't gamble. I just gamble 20
pound a week on a football.
So, if I was doing like a self-employed
job, I probably would work every other
day just cuz there's nothing else to
do. I'd probably get into like a routine
cuz I'm not drinking for a while, not
protein for a while.
So, cuz it's [ __ ] boring.
So, yeah, it's just nothing to do, mate.
Just binge watching
[ __ ] It's boring, isn't it? It is
man. It is boring. My
house. I was actually thinking of doing
that yesterday, but it take too long.
We would take too long,
mate. Yeah, honestly would take
ages. Yeah. I don't know when I'm going out drinking
again. [ __ ] wild, bro. [ __ ]
wild. Um, yeah, maybe two weeks cuz I
don't gamble anymore on the machines, do I?
I was actually thinking maybe do £100 on
fishing frenzy but nah good man I'd
rather save now man [ __ ]
that woman I pulled what what women I pulled many
women I just can't be bothered with them
anymore mate that's why I don't bother
Yeah. Yeah. Don't know what to do today. Nothing,
man. Uh, self projectors get banned.
Don't even get a reaction.
Yep. Um, yeah, bro. There's been a few of them.
Nah, mate. I've got standards. I'm
good. Yeah, exactly, bro.
Exactly. Yeah, I don't I don't play the
machines anymore. Cult, the the gambling
machines. I'm probably just going to
chill, man. Probably binge watch some
series. I'm [ __ ] bored,
man. So, I don't approach it anymore really.
So, I'm I'm on a approach and alcohol
detox. I can't go to cinema cuz there's
nothing I want to watch. It's [ __ ] in
it. Waiting for that film to come
out. It's not coming out till the 28th.
So, I would have done a football bet if
there was football on. Stock 20 quid on
it maybe. But nah. And I'm not playing
them rig machines. So, [ __ ]
knows. Job center meeting for
what? What? You on um you on job seekers allowance? Yeah.
You're a job seeking
all the systems are
down. So, how much do you get a month, cult? W
madness. No, I'm not playing them fies,
bro. I'm done. I'm not playing
them. [ __ ] that. I am not playing them,
bro. You having a [ __ ] rank if you
think I'm ever going back on them [ __ ]
machines. No way. No [ __ ]
way. £900. I could live off £900 a month,
n I couldn't live off 900 a month. I
couldn't even live off a grand a
month. [ __ ] I couldn't even live off
it. I could not live off that me.
Well, I I suppose I
could. The main channel's still there.
It just doesn't let me go live on it
because it says it's connected to too many
Streamyards. Too many
Streamyards. Nah, can't live off that,
bro. 1,500 is probably the bare
minimum you could live
off. Yeah, I get [ __ ] three grand a
month. And even sometimes that
goes if you're not
careful. I remember I [ __ ] last month
I had about I had 600 pound in one
account. By the time I got my passport
done, the time I went out drinking, got
food, got a haircut, I had about 150
left just out of that £600 on a different payment.
So yeah, I get three grand and it still
[ __ ] it still goes. So
So yeah, I need to really start saving
now cuz I need to leave this country.
So, I'm not And it's like even when I go out drinking
again, even when I go out drinking
again, I'm going to [ __ ] um when I go
out drinking again, I'm going
to I'm going to um pre-drink. Like, each
time I go out drinking, I don't want to
be spending more than £50. Not cuz I
can't afford it, because I'd rather save
my money and do other things. It makes sense.
Yeah, you're [ __ ] in
it. Yeah, you're
[ __ ] You're [ __ ] up. Time to start planning ahead. Yeah.
So, yeah, like I'll pre-drink before I
go out. I like I'm I'm going to do one
day. I'm going to do Thursday and
Saturday. And that Thursday and
Saturday, I don't want to be spending
more than £100 on two of them days. I'm
going to make it worth I'm going to make
work. Yeah, it doesn't matter about four
double captain Morgans because by the
time you get to central London, you'll
sober up. So, I'm just going to get I
don't want to be spending more than £100.
Yeah. Gambled it all the way. Yeah, [ __ ]
that. [ __ ] that. That will never be me
again. That will never be me again,
buddy. That's why I stopped gambling
because I realized like well I do the
football and that but like I realized
that how much
time you waste on it and how much money
you waste on it and then you look back
and you can never get it back. The money
is nothing. It's the time you you lose
and and you know and the money as well.
Like you you're never going to get it
back. So why why not just stop? Just do
the football. I just do the
football or if you're into scratch cards
but roulette all of that. [ __ ] all that.
You can do so much more without money.
understand? Just unnecessary stress that
people don't need. It's not even fun anymore.
Yeah, that's that's okay. Like maybe
even me, I might do 150 this month, but
it will only be 150. Who knows, bro? Who
knows? I might get really really bored,
but I will know my limits, you
know. I was thinking of doing 100 today, but
nah. Nah, bro. Easy, bro.
Easy. But it's pointless. This is
pointless. Yeah, I've hit it many times
though and I've had loads of money. I've
lived life, bro. So, I'm I'm good. But
yeah, you know what I'm saying, Co? The
thing is is that
like we can lose like it's just
pointless gambling. It's just pointless
gambling. Pointless gambling.
That that's it. It might as well just save your
money. It's what I do
now. Yeah. I haven't I haven't had sex
for ages. I just get [ __ ] Me. I
don't even care about the
sex. But I will do a day. But the thing
is is like when I go out Thursday,
Saturday, I need to get my haircut
again. And it's like £35 get your hair
done. So, I'm not in I'm not in no hurry
to to go out and try
again cuz it's just the same [ __ ] in
this country. So, wanted to leave
soon. But yeah, you shouldn't be
gambling £200 a month if you only get
£900 a month. You shouldn't be
gambling 2000 a month. Even I don't
gamble 200 a month
now. Yeah, it's not going to happen,
bro. I'm not gambling. Done. I'll do my
football bets every week and that's
it. 20 pound a week on the football and that's me done.
Simple. That's me. You're not going to
take me into gambling, bro. My My mind is made
up. Yeah, you should be gambling 2000 a
month if you get 900 pound a month.
Definitely should be
gambling. So yeah, I just do 20 pound a
week trying to win 500 and just build it
up. But I don't I don't do no bother that.
Yeah. Yeah. That's how much it cost me.
About 35 quid.
And then you go out approach just to
hear I've got a boyfriend. It's a
madness, isn't it? I do it like every
three weeks now. I don't really waste
money doing it. But yeah, just to hear
I've got a boyfriend. Hey, it's a
madness, in it,
cult roll on Friday. I can go to the
cinema. So I'm going to go cinema
Friday, do a football bet Saturday. I'm
still not drinking. So yeah, it's going
to be ace. Going to be [ __ ] ace.
And then I'll probably do it again in maybe two weeks. Yeah. Yeah,
bro. Yeah. This woman said, "Come to
America. I'll get with But she's [ __ ]
51 years of [ __ ]
age. [ __ ] hell,
bro. 51 years of [ __ ] age. You
know, how many numbers do you reckon
I'll get approaching Thursday and Saturday? Probably probably
[ __ ] two days. probably about seven,
eight. I've played 50p spins and no, not
really. Yeah, I've done 50p. You don't
know. You don't get the same buzz. I'm
not I don't want to talk about gambling,
bro. [ __ ] [ __ ] [ __ ] The
industry is dead anyways, so [ __ ] it. But
yeah, it's a sad life in England, is it
cult? It's a depressing sad life in
England. But my friend Antman
pulled. Yeah. You're not going to take
me to gamble, buddy. I'm done with it.
I'm done with anything other than the football. That's it.
Anything other than the football I am
[ __ ] done with. I'm probably I might
do a 30 pound football on
Saturday. Yeah. I mean I know it's not
just it's the weather, the women, the
government, the gambling everywhere.
It's like everywhere you go, cult, you
see the same women, you see the same
women, you see the same men, you see the
same MPCs, you you meet the same people
everywhere you go. It's [ __ ] dead
boring, isn't it? If you're 21, would
you smash a 50 year old?
No. Yeah, he
pulled. See, when I used to go to
escorts, I wouldn't even [ __ ] them. I
would just get a [ __ ] And a lot of
them would be like, "Oh, what? You don't
want to have sex?" cuz I was like,
"Nope." They used to think it was weird.
Yeah. Let's see if I go out Thursday,
Saturday if I get a date.
Nah. Oh, I still got the other woman
that lives near Birmingham. I can go and see her. Be
arranged. I don't know who he pulled. He
has to show me her. He's still sleeping,
but he told me like 4:00 in the morning
I pulled. But good on you, man. I'm
[ __ ] happy for you, buddy. I mean,
you went out [ __ ] two days. You
[ __ ] deserve it. No, I need to pour. Am
I? So, what other things do you do to
get by, cult? To make
money. It's hard to make money
nowadays. No, we're not repeating about
women. We're actually talking about
gambling and other things. Yeah.
these people really bore me, bro. These
people really, really bore me. But
yeah, but um yeah, it's hard to make
money nowadays. It is hard to make money
nowadays. Like if you're just on
benefits, the only thing you could do is
save just save your benefits. There's nothing
else. There's literally nothing else.
There's a few different ways, but that's
why you plan ahead. That's the whole
point of you planning ahead. You
understand? But I used to I used to get
like [ __ ] 900 pound a month and I
still used to go Manchester and
everything, you know.
Bye-bye. I do anything, mate. Usually go
out and do laboring on
site. What? Like cash in
hand? Do you know what I was thinking of
doing? Yeah. I was actually thinking of
going to America, going to Australia.
Yeah. For about 3 months. They have a
lot of cash in hand jobs over there. And
you would make a lot of
money. I'm not telling my business on
here how I get money, but just know that
I do. I've got my ways. But
anyways, what I was saying is [Music]
um you go Australia, right? Or you go to
America, there's a lot of money out
there, like cash in hand. So, what you
could do is you go there for 3 months. I
don't know how Australia works, but I
know America, you can go there for three
months with a visa. You go to America,
man, you can
make hundreds a
day, you know? Trust me, you can, bro.
There's a lot of money out there. And
Australia as well, cuz Australia, you
don't they don't tax as much as they do
here. Yeah. I mean, at least you at
least you do it, bro. That's good, man.
100 a day. That's good.
I'd probably be doing something that's
Yeah, there's a few ways to get make
money, but I'm not going to say what the
ways are, but I plan well ahead. But
there you go. You got one, bro. Go
Australia, go to America. There's lots
of cash in hand jobs out
there. That's why loads of people try to
immigrate to Australia, but it's too
hard. For example, a cleaning job,
right? You go to
Australia, cleaning job, they'll pay you
good money, bro. Good. And even security
over there, they get paid more than they do
here. Yeah. And it's mandatory to tip as
well, but I'm saying there's cash and
hand jobs, but I Well, maybe. But I know
America, I know Australia, you can make
money in that country. I know you can.
My friend, he's planning to go there in
two months, save a bit of money, and
he's going to go Australia, work there,
go Thailand, work there. That's what you
should do. Do it for 3 months. 3 months
a year. Just send it, brother, and then just come
back. Yeah, you have to tip over there
as well. That's [ __ ] wrong. E Yeah. Bye-bye.
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
Yeah, it's mad,
bro. It's mad,
eh? And you have to tip as well. You tip.
Yeah. What about you, V? Could you live
off a grand a month? I mean, you could.
If you had everything paid for, you
could live off 500 pound and save 500 a
month, I guess.
I mean, technically it is doable. It
would just be
long. It would just be long, man.
Yeah. You just be skint like
Sean. You just be skint like that
virgin a little bit. Yeah.
Yeah. So, you don't have much left over.
Well, you do, but a lot of it goes on
rent. I don't know what you keep saying
about these side hustles. There is no
nowadays. There's literally there is no side
hustles. What side hustles is
there? Because there is none. You can't
get a cash in hand
job. So, there is no side hustles unless
you [ __ ] go out shoplifting. I'd love
to know what these side hustles
are. My phone bill, well, I only have a
SIM bill. I pay my SIM bill. That's like
17 in the next
50. So, all in all, I probably spend
about £100 a month.
Uh 50. Yeah, probably about 100 pound a
month is my outgoings.
That's phone bill, gas, electric, gas,
electric, phone bill, internet
bill. Yeah, I got about £100 outgoance a
month. And I've already paid all my
bills, so I'm all good,
man. Yeah. Oops. Sorry about
that. We get these self-p projecting
fat, ugly 40y olds coming my chat now and then.
Yeah, they ain't got nothing better to
do, buddy. We just don't pay him no
attention. Sad losers. I buy fake
clothes from China and sell them in UK
as they young people to best can't afford real. Yeah.
Yeah. You should be able to make money on eBay.
I guess you still could if you went to
charity shops, but charity shops have
gone gone higher now, so that's harder. Yeah. Yeah. [Music]
It's cold today, ain't it?
Oh, it's cold today.
Yep. But I still think the cinema is
good to go to because it's still very
cheap. Like you can go to the cinema for
like £25 including drink, hot dog,
popcorn. It's still quite a
uh it's still quite a
cheap sort of
um a cheap [Music]
um one second, bro.
Uh I wonder why gambling's not taxed.
I wonder how you can just go into a
casino and win thousands and then not
get taxed. That's crazy. That is
it taxfree. Is it [Music]
I'm going to do I'm going to do a 30 pound football
bet on Saturday. I think I'm going to do
a double both teams to score. No draw.
Yeah. One second, bro.
Well, I don't even tell her much to be fair. When
will Well, tell her that it's impossible
in this country because all these women
apparently have boyfriends. That's what
you should That's what you should tell
her, lad. You know, I was in the Chinese uh
yesterday. I heard this guy, "Oh, are
you from Newcastle?" He said, "I sure
am." And we was talking and funny
enough, me and Antman was talking about
going to Newcastle
um at some point. And we was talking
about it. And I was talking to this guy
for like 15 minutes. I said, "Yeah, I
used to love going up there, man. Like
the people are friendly, easy to get
women there. A lot a lot easier than
London." And yeah, man. I was kind of
missing it a little
bit, mate. I can get a nice meal and do a football bet. Remember?
Yeah. But yeah, football bets are not
worth it because you go into the shop,
you spend [ __ ]
£20. I don't They're all right, man.
Just the accent's so [ __ ] weird, isn't
it? I'll tell you that for nothing,
mate. I've been Newcastle three
times and I had women approach me.
That's how you know it's like London as
well because when you go to like
Nottingham or when you go to like
Newcastle, you don't have the same
struggles. That's how you know it is
London. That's a lot lot worse. you know.
Yeah. I remember this one from
Carlilele. I got her number. We was
kissing like mad, bro. She was from
Carlilele. She said she likes drug dealers and
that. Obviously, she probably knew I was
from London. Probably thought I was a drug dealer.
We'll settle with Burger King. No. Why
don't you get yourself a nice Indian, man? Why
not? I don't know what I'm going to
have. Yeah, cuz I need to save a bit of
money as well. Even though I have money,
I just I just need to save. I want to
get myself in front. So, I
think Chinese again, maybe.
Lucky you, mate. I get
nothing. All I get when I go out is I've
got a boyfriend. That's all I
get. That's all I get. D
lad is I've got a
boyfriend. But if I can make it work
with this Indian
woman. No, Manchester. Manchester,
they're stuck up
too. Scotland's quite Scotland's cheap,
but it's very touristy.
Edinburgh. Yeah, that's the thing. It's very touristy.
Um, Edinburgh. I actually thought
Scotland was going to be better than
Newcastle in terms of a night out, but
nah. But no, Manchester, it's not even
about there's too many gays. They're
stuck up there as well. I've been
Manchester like 10 times. And they're
all stuck up there as well. It's not
even It's not just, bro, there's a gay
village. It's [ __ ] because they're all
stuck up there as well.
I know these things, bro. I've been all over the
country, so I know all of these things.
But the thing
is, yeah, and Birmingham is too big.
Birmingham is [ __ ] because it's too big. Like
London, it's absolutely pointless going out in
Birmingham. And the only reason people
still go out in London is because
they're tourists. You know, most of the
people that go out in central London are
tourists because people from this country are
skinn. Yeah, it's you go out,
you approach a woman, they pretend they
have boyfriends, of course. What else is
it going to be like, bro? Or they're not
interested. Or are my skin? Why Why
would you ask such a stupid question? Am
I skinn? I'm never skinned. I literally
told you I've not been skinned for the past 3
years. You owe your mom
£3,000. Yeah. Good luck, man. Good
luck. Yeah. They don't like 90% of
men. They don't like 90% of
men. You know, me and Antman was talking
about this yesterday. He pulled in the
end. Oh, stop repeating yourself, man,
before I block
you. Yeah, I had £25, which means I weren't
skimmed. And you're blocked. Bye-bye.
God, can we just get normal people on this
channel instead of these repeating
little downies? Like, can we just have
like a normal conversation without these
little mongos coming in? [ __ ] boring, man. You
know, same atmosphere every time you go
live. It's it's the same atmosphere delayed. But yeah, [ __ ]
idiots. I can't believe these people.
I'm on YouTube every day doing this. It's so
sad. Mate, you would have you will have
a problem in
London. You will have a [ __ ] problem
in London getting [ __ ] women. I say that for
nothing. You will have problems in
[ __ ] London. 90% of people [ __ ]
do. You [ __ ] will here, mate. Trust
me. You [ __ ] well will
here. They all [ __ ] stuck up. Yeah. Yeah,
man. See my face. Me,
lad. Not insecure. Me. I'm
tired. I'm [ __ ] tired,
bro. Oh, does he now? right there,
bro. Get along with that.
No, no, no,
no, mate. You would struggle with
lad. Oh no.
Yeah, it's a
madness. Why do these people call me ugly?
cult like they're never going to make me
insecure. They always talk about my
looks on this community, but they don't
make me insecure
ever. They never stop me showing my
face. They never make me look in the
mirror and be like, "Am I ugly?" Like,
are they trying to like make me
insecure? It's crazy, bro. Is it? Like,
they call me ugly, but
[ __ ] I don't know. It's weird, isn't it?
Are they Are they trying to make you
like insecure like them or something? Strange, isn't
it? Don't ever make me insecure, buddy,
about my looks or anything. I don't know
why they do this on YouTube every day,
bro. It's sad why they do
this. The back the beard makes you look
like a terrorist. No, it doesn't. Every
time I go out, I always get my beard
trimmed. You know what a terrorist beard
looks like. A lot different to what my beard looks
like. So having a having a trimmed neat
beard does not make you look like a
terrorist. The [ __ ]
bro? But I think what the problem is is
I know I think I know what the problem
is. Whereas there's there's few
problems. Obviously, they're stuck up
and the fact that I don't look fully
white. So, they either go for like white
people or they go for black people.
Obviously, I don't look [ __ ] fully
white and obviously I'm not black. So,
they that's one of the reasons as
well. Yeah, I did say that.
Yeah, people say
things, but you know what I'm saying?
Like, and that's that's probably what it
is as well, bro, cuz I don't look, you
know. Yeah. So, that's what it is. No, I
I don't bother with them
anymore. I don't bother with them
No, I don't bother with
them. I'm not going any for a few weeks.
Can't be asked. They're [ __ ] boring. So,
yeah. And that's what it is as well.
They're incredibly racist cuz there's this black
guy they go around approaching
But they don't get
anything like they say. And that's how
you know it's not you. Because when you
see people go around in London
approaching, they get the same thing as you
get. Even like the black people as well.
There's this black guy. There's loads of
people on Instagram, right? And they go
around approaching women like I used to
do and they get exactly the same
[ __ ] They get exactly the same [ __ ] So
that's how you know that it's them. And
obviously that's what it is. And and
it's to do with your race as
well. It is to do with your race as
Defer, bro. They're very racist in London.
So that's it.
Yeah, I know. That's what I'm saying. They're
racist. That's why that time when I hate
mentioning the cunt's name, you know, she
uh that [ __ ] stupid
[ __ ] in Boston hooked up with me cuz
obviously we were like similar heritage,
you know what I'm saying? So um similar
heritage, you know,
like you know what I mean? So that's
what probably why they got with me. So
yeah, but and like Yeah, bro. But yeah, they
don't go for
foreign looking people.
I look like one of the car wash
lads. Car washing lads.
Yeah. [ __ ] hilarious,
man. That made me
laugh. I've tried with Turkish people
before. They still say they got
boyfriends, but not many. Not Not many of them.
Yeah, I need to I you know that's one
thing I've never done because that
Morgan was Syrian, right? She was Syrian
and what do I have in me? Turkish and
Syria is next to
Turkey. Yeah. Even though she went for
black people, you're the same race kind
of almost. But obviously that's
why I don't look Romanian. No one's ever
told me I look Romanian. People told me
look People told me I look
um People have told me I look
uh Albanian but not Romanian. Someone
told me I look Scottish. How can you look Scottish?
[ __ ] Syria's next to
Turkey. You got Turkey then you got Syria. see?
Yeah. With Turkey, then you got Syria.
So where she was from, like her heritage
was next to obviously where where my heritage is. So
yeah, that's why it's my
mama. No, but all Yeah. All jokes aside, that's
why. No, they're not the same thing. But
this that I got a [ __ ] by an American
in the alleyway and she was blue-eyed with
freckles. You're like, I really want
you. I swear to God, bro. I'll I'll
never forget it. She said, "I really
want you, but I don't think you want
me." I swear to God, it's not even made
up, bro. This bartender I'm [ __ ]
friends with, he was looking as well. It was a
madness. It was a madness, bro. I swear
now I was fingering her,
bro. And anyway, she gave me a [ __ ]
blow job in
madness. I really want you, but I don't
think you want me. I swear to God, bro.
I couldn't believe what I was hearing.
Funny. It was funny.
But yeah, it is my um race.
Definitely. Definitely, bro. Cuz if you
put somebody that's got the same looks
as me who looks completely white with
blue eyes on dating apps, they'll get someone. Find
someone. But they're either racist.
They're even racist toward black people
as well. The people assume that, oh
yeah, they go for black people, but
actually they mostly go for white
people. That's the thing. They actually
mostly go for white people. And yeah,
some of them go for black people, but
mostly they go for white people.
Yeah, I got foreign mates as well. So if
you're like Indian or Chinese, you're
[ __ ] No woman will ever go for you.
You are actually
[ __ ] That's mad to say, but it
is. If you're Indian, you're [ __ ]
Indian. Yeah, if you're Indian, you're [ __ ] bro.
Chinese. Why not even the worst to be fair?
is what it is.
E yeah, there's this Indian woman that
I'm speaking to. I'm going to meet her.
She lives near Birmingham. She's agreed
to meet, but she sounds very posh. She
doesn't have an Indian
accent, but yeah, she's I'll just get
with her in it.
She was all right to me as well. She
even though she's she was born here and
stuff. Where go see her? [ __ ] it.
Traveled 100 miles. Eh. Yeah.
This one's all right as well.
But I just still think women are just
evil [ __ ] To be honest with you, I
still think they're evil. They've all
got the same
minds. They've all got exactly Have you
noticed that they've all got exactly the
same minds as well?
Don't know if you've noticed that, but yeah. Uh,
boyfriend. They've all got boyfriends.
Cult. They've all got
boyfriends. I just think women are evil. Me
cult. Yeah. I mean, I'm still waiting
for one to prove me wrong. I'm still
waiting to this day for some for one
woman to prove me wrong that they're not
all the same. And
uh yeah, I don't think I'd ever be shown different.
Yeah, I've had sex
about six times that weren't escorts,
which is pretty bad to be honest,
considering how many approaches I've done.
But yeah, it is what it is,
eh? Do you think I'd have more success
if I lived in Leeds
cult? If I actually lived in
Leeds, you think I'd have more success
then if I lived in
Leeds. Yeah, that's excluding
escorts. But that's ex Well, no, not six
times. Like six different
people. No, six different people.
But it's not really low. It's impossible in this
country. There are some people that
ain't even kissed anyone. It might seem
low to you, but I mean, it's impossible
to get anyone in this
country. So, I mean, six would would
actually be all right. But then that's excluding escorts
and Yeah. And I mean, six different
people. So, maybe
like seven times.
Yeah. Well, it's not it's harder
nowadays. It's harder
nowadays. Yeah. If you're counting
escorts, huh? Easily 200. Easily
200. I've probably been with more
escorts than anyone my
age. Just mad.
So, how have you how have you had 40
people? I don't understand
that. Yeah, I can't get [ __ ]
all. It's very like it's very like
obviously you've got your experience and
people have got their experience, but
people will say things, but when you
actually go out, it's completely
different because when you try to speak
to someone, they say they've got a boyfriend.
when they give you their number, they
[ __ ] you around. So, I don't know how
all of these people and I see people get
rejected as well. Like, I see people get constantly.
So, now I I don't know how people do
it because you are actually seeing
people getting rejected. You actually
see people get rejected as
well constantly even in like real life. Yeah.
So, if I go out on on Saturday doing
approaches cult, what do you think I'm going to
get? Like, what response do you think
I'm going to get? It's so mad though cuz
I got two one night stands. Yeah. Two
years ago, I had two one night stands in
the same week. It was a
madness. Well, no, one week. I think I
did. Yeah. One was Friday and one was the next
Saturday at 19. But it's just dead.
I'm not I'm not thinking way into
anything. I'm telling you my
experiences. I'm not thinking too much
into anything. I'm literally telling you what I'm
experiencing. So, your mates are not
pulling out every weekend. No [ __ ]
way. No way. Or your mates going out
every weekend and bringing birds back.
No way, bro. Trust me. I've I've I've
been all over the country. I've seen
people get rejected. I've seen people try. It's
[ __ ] How are you telling me I'm
thinking way too much into it when I'm
literally telling you what I
experience? That doesn't make sense. So,
no. And I and I'm telling you 110%
they're not. And I'm telling you 100 and
million 10% they are not because we are
in England right and women are in what's
England it's a westernized country I
know these things I've lived life I've
gone out I used to go out three four
times a week I know exactly what I'm
talking about I've pulled myself I'm
telling you 110 million% they're not
because you never even see it like it it
even happened to other
people I told you about all of them
videos I see on Instagram, all the [ __ ]
I see in real life, I'm telling you that
they're not they're lying to
you. I mean, if if if you're talking
about like they're going out, they're
going out, right, and kissing somebody
and dancing with them? Yeah, they could
do that every week. That's believable.
But you're telling me your friends are
going out every single week, right?
Yeah. And they're pulling women back and
shagging them? Nah. doesn't even sound
believable. And I've I've done it as
well. I've actually I've pulled people
I've took people back and checked them.
I don't believe you, bro. I'm sorry. I
don't believe you because I don't even see it
happen, you know. No. If you go out with
five to 10 people, you just look
desperate. If you go out with more than
two people, it's a cockfest and you're competing. Yeah. So that's
100%. I pulled last time I was in
Nottingham. I won't listen to anyone.
I'm I'm literally telling you what I'm
experiencing. Right. All right.