Yo,
just wanted to say something here quickly.
Won't be on long.
But have to say something.
This guy needs to keep my [ __ ] name
out of his [ __ ] mouth. Honestly, bro,
I was watching back some of his [ __ ]
Yeah. And it's like, bro, if you want to
argue with these little
[ __ ] idiots. That's on you, man. But
keep my name out your [ __ ] mouth.
Simple as that. Chatting bare [ __ ] bro.
Chatting so much [ __ ] [ __ ] You're
trying to use my name for clout, you
[ __ ] idiot. No, there's no welcome
back. I'm not back. This is just a
[ __ ] Monty man. I'm not [ __ ] back.
Not at all. I'm not [ __ ] back at all,
mate. I'm just saying I don't understand
why this body man Yeah. keeps [ __ ]
mentioning me like talking talking my
[ __ ] name like what the [ __ ] It's
not like I'm on the [ __ ] comments.
You know what I'm saying? Keep my name
out of your [ __ ] mouth, you stinking
dirty copycat. It's as simple as that.
Yeah. Do you know what he doesn't
actually realize? He sounds he sounds
like a 10year-old. You know, isn't this
guy supposed to be 36? And when he's
talking about people not getting laid.
Yeah. Um he's when he's talking about
people not getting laid, right? He
sounds about 10 years old, bro. I swear
is it only me or this this guy sound
like a 10-year-old? Yeah. And then he
copies then he's copying things that I
say as well. He says, "Oh, well, the
reason people do this on here is uh
because they're gay and jealous." Yeah,
that's what I said. Copycat. Yeah,
that's what I said. That the people that
do this, like the channels dedicated to
people are just gay and je gay or
jealous. Yeah, I said that. Don't let it
come from you. I said that cuz it's [ __ ] obvious.
And then he starts copying [ __ ]
things I'm saying. Keep my name out your
[ __ ] mouth, bro. It's as simple as
that. This guy doesn't realize Yeah.
that everyone and everyone Yeah. I don't
even mention this guy. I don't even
[ __ ] go like comment on his [ __ ]
Yeah. No one, bro. Everyone and everyone
and everyone has had Natalie G.
Literally everyone has. Like he bro,
this guy I I have been I've been with
more [ __ ] than this guy ever has and
ever will do, bro. Yeah. 100% ever have
and ever will do. Trust me. He's been
with two people that you wouldn't even
pay people to get with. That's how sad
it is. You couldn't even pay normal
people to get with [ __ ] Kaye or, you
know, get to get um or get with um
Natalie G. Do you understand? Like he's
keep my name out your [ __ ] stupid
[ __ ] mouth when you arguing with
people. That's it. It's simple as that,
bro. [ __ ] off, man. Bringing my [ __ ]
name into it.
You know what I'm saying? Like some
baldy guy, some baldy skinny guy is
talking about me. Talking about [ __ ] me. Yeah,
trust me. I was going to [ __ ] come on
these [ __ ] bro. And I was going to go
on these hangouts and start madness. But
the thing is, bro, if you start The
thing is, bro, if you start with this
guy, yeah, this is why I don't go back
and forth with these people anymore
because all it's going to be is, "Oh,
you come here or you come here." It just
goes around in circles, but we would
have got owned on the Streamyards, bro.
Trust me, he would have got owned on the
Streamyards. [ __ ] off, bro. Keep my name
out your [ __ ] mouth. Yeah, I don't
want anything to do with anyone in this community.
Just Monty, man, bro. Just Monty,
[ __ ] stupid idiot, bro.
Yeah, I don't give a [ __ ] if he's
slagging me off, bro. These people are
irrelevant. But I just don't understand
why this mod is is um
is um talking madness, bro. And no one's
even saying anything.
No, just tell him. I He just needs to
keep my name out of his [ __ ] mouth.
I've been laid more times and he's had
hot dinners, mate. And he's 36. He's not 10. Yeah.
Yeah. He's a [ __ ] idiot, bro. Keep my
name out your [ __ ] mouth, you stupid prick.
That's it, bro. I haven't been been on
here, bro. Since I started talking to
this person, I've been talking to them
every day. Going to be meeting them
soon. I don't need to be on here. I
don't need to talk to anyone on here,
bro. They're all idiots. And at the end
of the day, he's he's he just copies
everything I say as well. He copies
everything I say. Oh. Um Oh. Um Oh, what
was it? Uh he copies everything I say.
Oh, these people that do this are gay
and jealous. Why are you copying me, bro?
Why you being a copycat? I said I said
all of that stuff.
Yeah. Now he's copying me trying to act
like he's the one that [ __ ] come out
with that [ __ ] No, bro. No. No. No.
No. You're copying
>> me what I say cuz it's [ __ ] obvious.
Cuz if people wasn't gay and jealous,
they wouldn't do what they do on YouTube
every day. It's obvious. Then he's
trying to act like he's the one that
come out with it. [ __ ] idiot. Yeah,
[ __ ] he's a clown, mate. A proper
proper proper clown.
Yeah, he's copying. But he was
mentioning my name. Yeah, I was I went
knocking these live stream. He's
mentioning my name. I don't know why
this cunt's mentioning my [ __ ] name.
No one wants your ugly Nat G [ __ ] um
woman. I could have had her when she was
more in her [ __ ] prime and I rejected
her. And also, I've been with my all the
only two women he's ever been with is
women that you couldn't even pay anyone
to get with. And he and he's flexing my
name and he's talking about me. [ __ ]
off, man. Yeah, he is copying. He said
that, "Oh, the people on this
community." Yeah, like the ones that
have got channels dedicated to people
and comment, they're jealous
or gay. Where did that come from,
Greavvesy? That come from me?
Yeah, that come from me. I said that
about like the virgin and [ __ ] Red
Star and them people because it is
jealousy and gayness
because if they had even one person to
speak to outside of this community, they
wouldn't be doing it. It's obvious. I'm
so [ __ ] what, bro? You know,
you need to keep my name out of his
[ __ ] mouth, bro. [ __ ] me. [ __ ] idiot.
He's a clown, bro. [ __ ] clown.
Yeah. Yeah. The only virgin is you,
Timmy. Stop self projecting.
The only virgin is you, lad. Yeah, he
does. He done it with the he done it
with the um they're gay and jealous.
Didn't you hear him, Greavves? He said
the people that do this are gay and
jealous. I knew this. I already knew. I
already knew this. I had already said
because as soon as I started talking to
um you know Christian Izzy um Greavves
was the last time I went out. Have you
noticed I don't come on here much anymore.
I don't really come on here much anymore.
No, cuz I don't need to, bro. I
literally don't need to. And it would be
the same with these people. If they had
a life or whatever, they wouldn't they
wouldn't be doing this. And then he
because I said that he's he's he's
copying what I'm saying.
And what's he going to say to me? Is he
is he going to say that I'm jealous of
somebody that I could have I could have
been with Natalie G [ __ ] six, seven
years ago. Bro, imagine what she looked
like six, seven years ago right up until
now. So what what you going to say that
I'm jealous? Are you going to accuse me
of being jealous when you're the one
talking about me? [ __ ] idiot. I
should have just knocked this [ __ ] out
when I went to Birmingham, bro. I should
have just knocked the [ __ ] out of him.
That's what I should have done to be
fair, bro. And yeah, he might be strong
by the hands, greet, and stuff, but he
wouldn't beat me in a fight, bro. I can
tell you that for nothing. [ __ ] idiot.
[ __ ] mad. It's madness, man. It's absolutely madness.
Well, it's nice to see you message me on
um Instagram, Grezy, when you've been
deprive deprived of content. Poor [ __ ]
And I was listening to some other things
today. I just caught up on some things
and to be honest with you, none of it
makes any sense.
None of it makes no sense whatsoever, bro.
No, it was Mont No. No. To be honest, it
was Monty, bro. It was Monty. It was
Monty. He kept mentioning my name. He
kept me I was I was going to go on the
Streamyard, bro. He was mentioning my
[ __ ] name, bro. And I was going to
start madness. No, it was It was him. It
wasn't. It was him. It was him, bro. He
was [ __ ] annoying me.
All right, Greg. I sent you a Oh, griev.
I'll tell you. Yeah. What happened?
Yeah. So, remember that O'Neal I I used
to go to? The news I used to go to that
they banned me from? The one I used to
go to three times a week. Basically, my
friend went there the other day. uh the
other day and the bouncer was asking for
me, right? Cuz obviously he's he's
where's he gone? Why doesn't he come
here anymore? I said, I'll give the
bouncer my number. The bouncer messaged
me. We was talking in it and I was like,
"Oh, where's them army cunts?" He's
like, "Them army [ __ ] ain't been coming
for a while. They've been on an
operation. They've been on a mission. I was dead.
Them army [ __ ] ain't been coming for a while."
Cuz they all used to go there, didn't
they? Them army [ __ ]
Oh, that made me laugh. But yeah,
and it's not even just Monty, bro. I
don't even want to talk about these
people, bro. Bro, this this Lord, bro,
even this Lord Jay is proper disabled.
Like, he's saying
he's saying that, oh, he's saying, bro,
he's saying about, "Oh, I wouldn't go
out by myself. I wouldn't go out
drinking by myself. I wouldn't do this.
I wouldn't do that." But you'd sit on
YouTube all day by yourself talking to a
bunch of losers that will never meet
you. But you wouldn't go to a pub by
yourself. The guy has got the guy has
got no life experience, bro. Like he
literally has got no life experience.
Think about it, bro. If you went out by
yourself as much time as you spend on
here on these Saturdays, you would have
actually like made friends, bro. Yeah.
That weren't just online. Like nothing
this guy says makes any sense.
I'm sure he's actually disabled, bro.
I'm actually sure he's disabled. So
you'd rather sit on here on a Friday,
Saturday talking to people for hours
rather than just go out by yourself
drinking. He's got no life experience,
bro. Really, really ain't got no life
experience. You know, if you actually go
out drinking in packed places, you
people don't even realize you're by
yourself. They literally don't even
realize you're by yourself because the
places are so packed.
He's a [ __ ] clown, bro. He doesn't
know anything, does he?
He really really does not have any life
experience. Bless him.
Just a 44 year old with no life
experience. Sad really, isn't it, Grezy?
A 44 year old with no life experience.
Bless his little heart. And he's too old
to change it. There's no turning back
now, lad. No turning back now.
No turning back now, lad.
But yeah, Christian is he's been fine.
Uh, Greavesy, she's been absolutely fine. Yep. [ __ ] me.
He says he says this guy says on his
channel, right, that oh, I've I've
wasted my my 20s on here. And I'm
thinking, bro, I've done more in four
years than you've done in two decades.
The [ __ ] bro? But I guarantee you, bro,
I've been to more restaurants than this
guy. I've tried more food than this guy.
Been to more I've done more things. I've
been to more venues than this guy has.
And I'm younger than him. And And he's
telling me that I've wasted my 20s on
it, bro. The guy is just simply self
projecting. You know, I was I was on
here and I was living life when I was on
here. Living [ __ ] life when I was on
here, mate. And I've I've still got I've
still I've still got all my [ __ ]
videos as well. So much self-p
projection on this community, bro. It's
really, really, really sad.
And by the way, uh I saw your thing,
Grezy. I saw the the video that you sent
me. I actually commented on it. I said,
"I don't like white knights and simps."
And that's what what that guy was doing
when he was trying to say, "Oh, you're
harassing women." And no, I would have
told him to [ __ ] off, you stupid s.
Stupid white knight. I don't like, you
know, grievy, you shouldn't send me
stuff like that. You know, I don't like
anything like that, Grezy.
You know, I don't like anything to do
with Simpsons and white lighting and
offending women. You know, I hate all of
that [ __ ] unless there is a Unless
there's a valid reason for it. Someone
being attacked, someone being, you know.
Yeah, of course they're not going to say
a word. They're not going to Do you not
understand these people? Do you not
understand that these people that defend
women, they're opportunists, you know?
Yeah, bro. They'll like, do you really
think, bro, if they were opportunists?
That's what I'm saying. Yeah.
And that's it, bro. They're they're
opportunists, that's why. But, you know,
I don't like anything like that, Gregy,
like white nighting and singing. You
know, I hate the double standards and
all of that stuff. I hate all of it, bro.
I hate I hate all of that stuff. Unless
someone's being physically attacked or
something, then yeah, [ __ ] them, bro.
You know, you know, the thing is and oh,
it grieves you. I was thinking about
this. Yeah. You know, the other day I
was actually thinking about this cuz I
thought this um Christian Izzy was was
was going to um was listen to me. I
thought she was going to ghost me, but
she never ghosted me and we're talking.
But listen, bro, I want to know. Do you
not think it's weird? Yeah. That there's
one rule for one in the dating game and
one rule for another when trying to
meet. Think about it, bro. Yeah. You get
all of these people on the internet that
say, "Oh, you need to speak to a woman
for weeks. You need to speak to a woman
for months." And what came to mind, bro,
was Joe F and that Ricky Millington.
Okay. So, you approach someone grievy
and you speak to someone for 3 weeks,
four weeks, two months, 3 months. Okay.
And then they [ __ ] you over. Then what
happens? So then wouldn't it make more
sense in trying to meet them as soon as
possible if you've approached someone?
But you can't do that, can you grievy?
Because if you try to meet them, oh,
you're coming on too strong. Oh, you
need to speak to them for 2 months. Do
you generally think in this day and age
just because you've spoken to someone
for two months that they're going to
feel any kind of way [ __ ] you over
just because you've spoke to them for
two months. But yet, when a woman wants
to meet you straight away, there's
absolutely no problem. That's the
biggest That's one of the the the
biggest double standards there is.
Grezy, listen. You obviously this this
one's this one's different. Obviously,
she's I've spoke to her. I know her life
and stuff, bro. She's different. But I'm
saying normally like normal people that
work. You go out on Thursday, Grezy,
listen to me. You go out on Thursday,
you get someone's number, right? So,
you're texting someone. No, so you want
to meet them by the Sunday or by the
latest next week. That's fine. You don't
need to you don't need to speak you
don't need to speak to someone for weeks
and weeks and months and months grey
someone that you've approached. Why are
there all of these emphasis and rules
when it comes to men? I would love to
know that you know and this is the only
thing I I would love to know
you know why is there always little
rules for us? Am I lying? Tell me I'm
lying. You can't even tell you know I'm
right. It's it's the truth though isn't
it? Oh you need to speak to people for
weeks and weeks and bumps and bumps and bumps.
when when that just makes it worse
because then when you get [ __ ] over if
you if you do get [ __ ] over then what?
You know what I'm saying bro?
So no you approach someone you should be
meeting them within 4 days but obviously
there are some um exceptions but you
know you should be meeting somebody
within a couple of days. Yeah. Damn right.
Damn [ __ ] right. You should be
meeting someone within a couple of days.
No, it's not even. It's just a No, it's
just a double standard, bro. That's all it is.
Like, okay, Greasy. Okay, let me Okay,
let me explain it. Ch. Okay. Right. You
meet So, say you meet someone on a
Thursday and you're texting them and you
want to meet them by the Monday. People
will have all of these things. Oh,
you're trying to meet them too fast. Oh,
you need to speak to them for longer. R.
Yeah. Even if you speak to someone
longer, they will still [ __ ] you over.
There's still a high chance that
someone's going to [ __ ] you over.
There's no need for all of this extra
stuff and speaking to people for months.
It's all excuses. That's what I'm trying
to say, bro. Like, it's But yet, when
somebody wants to meet you within a
first message, no problems. There's no
problems. There's absolutely no
Obviously, with this person that I'm
speaking to, the situation's different.
You know, I've sent voice notes and I'm
not going to tell you exactly what
they're doing, but trust me, bro, they
are they have got [ __ ] going on. It's
not for me to tell people's business,
but I'm saying generally on a rule,
you don't even need to speak for a week.
If you've approached someone, you don't
even need to speak to them for a week
before meeting them.
I don't think you don't I don't even
think you need to speak to them for the
week. I I think within 10 messages, you
need to be trying to schedule a meet.
And even if it's for even if it's for
like the next Thursday,
I would say the next Thursday the latest
or whenever you go out Saturday, the
next Saturday. You don't need to be
speaking to people longer than a week.
That's what I That's my experiences.
That's what I would advise people
cuz at one point I generally thought I
was going to get [ __ ] over,
but I didn't. But usually um you do. No,
I can't be bothered with him. He's just
a self-projected virgin. No, I don't
argue with stupid people, bro.
Stupid stupid stupid people that can't
have a conversation that just project
their virginity. If I wanted to go on a
self-proing channel, bro, I'd go on LJ.
We're done with these little clowns.
They can't come and have a conversation.
They literally can't even have a They
can't even come and have a normal
conversation or a debate. If somebody
can come in and have a normal
conversation and a debate, then fair
play, bro. I'll let them up. But you
can't argue with an idiot that's just
calls people a virgin when he's a virgin himself.
[ __ ] weird, bro. [ __ ] There's no one
can can actually have a debate.
Why don't Joe come on and have a nice debate, Grezy? Yeah.
But yeah, yeah, you you can speak to
them for like a week or two if you
haven't approached them. But if you've
approached them, Yeah. You want to be
meeting them within a week maximum
unless there unless there there's a
there's a good reason for it.
Like this person that I'm speaking to,
they are I'm not going to get into what
they've told me and stuff, but yeah,
it's it's and they me I watch she
messaged me 23 times at 2:00 in the
morning. Grievy, I was watching Two and
a Half Men and bam, 23 messages. I'm
thinking, "Fucking hell, man. What the
fuck?" 23 [ __ ] messages. Jesus Christ.
So, yeah. It was like 2:00 in the morning. Yeah.
Yeah. See you later, you little self-reflector.
But yeah, that's how you know, bro. But
Monty needs to stop copying my words.
He needs to stop copying my words. Oh,
someone lied saying that they were going
to come come on my door yesterday.
Grievy, they never
childish, pathetic people. And you would
have thought you'd think like these
people are older than you
saying that he's going to come on
people's doors and it's all for
attention. This is what I was trying to
say to Cory. I didn't come on talking
about this. It was Monty that I've come
on talking about. This is all for
attention. It's cuz they're gay. Like,
why do you think Monty man copies me so
much? All of these people that do all of
this [ __ ] it's because they need
attention from men. Because they're gay.
They don't get no attention in the real world.
That's why they're sat on YouTube from
the time they wake up to the time they
go to bed. Cuz they ain't got no one.
They ain't got nothing. They're just
life losers. Tell me I'm lying, Grezy.
Tell me I'm [ __ ] lying.
I'm not lying. It's It's the truth. It's
the [ __ ] truth.
Why the [ __ ] are you people sat on here
from the time you wake up to the time
you go to bed? Come on, bro. I'm I I
just want to know. Like, I'm just I'm
sure a lot of people want to know. You know,
Monday today, this [ __ ] [ __ ] won't
stop mentioning my [ __ ] name. So, I
put a link up for Monty. I'm not letting
Timmy in. He's a [ __ ] [ __ ] bro.
Let that [ __ ] in.
Little self projector.
Oh, now it's not even letting me put the
link up. One second. I'll put a link up
in a minute. We need to show you something.
Look at these.
Look at these. Greavesy.
Whoa. One needs his hair back on. Okay.
No, I'm not letting you on either.
You're also disabled, lad.
So, I'm not letting you I'm going to be
on for about an hour and then I'm done.
So, that's that. Oh, what?
So, what was chat GBT saying then? Um, Grezy,
what was it saying? Do you remember?
I forgot, bro. Sorry. It's been a while.
Do you remember what what it was saying?
>> Do you remember what it was saying?
What? What? Like blend in with the crowd.
Yeah, blending in with the crowd.
I put the link up. Did you get it? I
don't think you did.
Did you know?
I put the link up, but I don't think
you've got it. It hasn't come up. Why
did the link come up?
No, it said to blend in with the crowd.
Blend in with the crowd.
It wasn't a few days, bro. And it's a
week and you can't even take a day off
of YouTube. So, stop self projecting.
And now I don't need to talk about that.
What's there left to say?
People said it to fit in. That's it.
We've been over it a million times. Now,
I was talking about Monty Man not um
um being able to keep my name out of his
mouth and how he copies what I've said
about you people about you people on
here that do this. You're gay and you're
um you're gay and jealous. He literally
copied me. I don't need to talk about
that. What's there to said? People said
it to fit in. Okay. Oh well. Copycats.
Been over it a million times.
But no, we'll talk about you people and
Monty to be honest. Yeah.
And it wasn't a few days, bro. It was
over a week. You should try taking a day
off of YouTube at some point, bro. It'll
do you the world of good. It will do you
the world of good, you know, taking one
day off of YouTube. Do you know what I
noticed as well? Um, you know, Grezy,
you know, when you you stay on here and
you interact with these people, they're
kind of like um where you're where
you're actually like engaging with
retardants, your personality changes and
you don't even know it. It's it's
subconsciously I I swear to God, bro,
I'm not even joking. because you're
interacting with retards like Timmy LJ.
Obviously, there's some dec there's some
good people there, but for the most
part, you actually start subconsciously subconsciously um
becoming different. I can't explain it.
But I'm not even chatting [ __ ] I swear to God,
you don't even know it because you're
engaging with retards, rain dead
retards. So, naturally, you'd go insane
after a while.
That's why I was like, "Oh, I'm sure
when I went out last time I was different.
I feel like my personality was different
because you're not on here engaging with
retards." You understand?
Why do you think people got off here and
live their life, bro? Certain people
because they know what it is.
I don't know. Ask Greezy why why people
thought that. I've got no saying about her.
I I don't know.
Why do they say that?
It is a copycat community.
[ __ ] copying my sayings. Monty man's
copying my sayings. You've got [ __ ] L
trying to be me. You'll never be me.
You'll never be able to go to clubs and
approach women. Never.
Ever. Ever. ever would you be able to be
like me, bro? You got him trying to be
like You got LJ trying to be like me, Grezy.
Can't you see? Look, look at these
clubs. It's just copying.
That's all it is. What's the point of
being a part of a copycat community?
Boring, isn't it?
Even someone else called LJ a copycat.
It is a copycat community.
No. Do did you mean it greasy when you
said it's a copycat community?
They copy my food. They copy me going to
a club. They copy my sayings when I say
these people are gay and jealous. Bro,
he can't even cold approach. He's
anxiety would never let him cold
approach. He can't code approach.
When I went out last time, I got five
numbers. He didn't even get one. He
can't approach. He's got uh he's got anxiety, lad.
He's got anxiety, mate.
So that ain't never happening, bro.
That ain't never happening.
Yeah, I am. I just don't know why this
Monty keeps talking about keeps talking about me.
Just go and [ __ ] knock him out in it. Greasy.
Timmy, you're not you're just something
to laugh at, Timmy. I want somebody to
come on here and have a nice debate. Yeah.
But yeah, what I was saying, Greaves, is
they make up all these little rules for
men. Oh, you need to speak to someone
for this amount. Like you don't like
they what they'll say to you Grezy is
that oh you need to speak to someone you
need to speak to someone for longer
right you need to speak to someone for longer
but then if you speak to someone for
longer they say you need to meet them
straight away so they've got all of
these what I was saying is they've got
all these little rules for men when it
comes to dating that isn't for women. Do
you get what I'm saying?
They've got all of these little rules
and even if you don't if you completed
every single rule then they would say
the opposite. Does that make sense?
No one said anything when USA is he
wanted to [ __ ] meet me within the
first message. Grezy, no one had a
problem with that. It's not letting me
put the link up. I don't know why.
But yeah, no one had a problem with that. Grezy,
they had no problem with um someone
trying to meet me. If I if I tried to
meet someone within the first message,
mate, I'd get they'd be after me. I'd
have people being after me. But if a
woman wants to meet you straight away,
that's completely fine.
That's why I feel like it's stupid,
Grezy, if anyone even asks people.
Let me try and put this link. Um, they
try to ask people for dating advice.
What's your What do you think?
I'm trying to put the link up, but it's
not working. Why
is anyone going to actually join or
what? I might need to restart the
stream, bro, because it's not letting me
put a link up. Yeah,
it's a weird, very weird world we live
in, bro. Very weird world we live in.
Yeah, Christian is lush. Greasy. Absolutely lush.
I was thinking that I I could put her
number on um YouTube and people might
not like message her. I was thinking
maybe if I put her number out there,
people's not going to message her, are they? Nah.
No, she's actually cool, bro. But I
didn't Oh, bro. You're gonna laugh at
this crazy. Yeah, I shouldn't even be
saying this, bro. You know that certain
people watching. So, I was in bed with
Crash um the night like LT said that he
was going to come on the door. Like, you
remember that that time he said he was
going to come. I know. He said he's
cousin or something. So, I was lying in
bed with Crash, right? And I'm I'm sat
here with I'm sat here with my
Spider-Man t-shirt with anxiety. Why do
you think I've got anxiety? Do you think
it's because someone's going to come on
the door? No. The reason that I had
anxiety is because I was worrying
whether this person was going to message
me back or not. Because now I'm attached
again, Greavvesy. So I was I was
actually having anxiety thinking if
somebody was going to message me back or
not cuz I was getting attached again.
Not because of what you thought I would
have. That's the most funniest thing
about it. You would have thought it
would have been the other you would have
thought it would have been the other um
the other way around, but it wasn't.
Because me and Crash was ready. We was
ready for war, bro. Me and Crash was
ready. Me and Crash was ready for war.
We were ready for war. But no, you would
have actually thought Yeah. that. No,
bro. I was [ __ ] myself, bro.
I was [ __ ] myself. And that's why
this is why I say to you, you need to
try to meet people ASAP, unless there's
an um exception. You get it, bro? Cuz
this is what happens. And Grey, I was
too deep in it. Creepsy.
Right. Let me restart this stream, bro.
One sec. Cuz I want to put the link out.
It's not letting me. One sec. Maybe I
can go back to it. Two sex. Yeah. 1 second bro.