Yo yo
you know what? Yeah. I want Autumn to
join this. Yeah. I was going to do a
video, but I can't be bothered. I said I
was going to go live at 4, but yeah,
I saw your photo. Saw your photo, man. I
mean, you're not my type, to put it
politely. I mean I I deem you as below average
but then again autumn like you got to
understand him like I've got a life you
see I'm not a ma like people like LJ J
and B and all of them people I'm not a
low life ma so I can go out and actually
meet women normally you see you see you
get these people that are begging you
right but you don't understand right you
don't understand um all that I'm not a
lowife ma like these people that beg
you, you know, or like the virgin that's
singing on your channel. Bro, I'd rather
be internally single than internally a
virgin that can't get a normal woman
that's still a virgin like you.
Internally a bedsit virgin. You're
calling, bro. You're saying that people
live with their mom when you're in a
council beds owned by the council, you
loser. Like, if someone actually owned
their own property, right, and then have
to target disabled women. I could I
could understand it. I could actually
take offense to it. How is some little
virgin in a shitty council bed sit with
no teeth and an ugly face with disabled
clothes talk about me? What the [ __ ]
Some little virgin like that is trying
to talk about me. I just went on this
autumn roses channel and the internally
ugly that can only get disabled is
talking about me. An ugly [ __ ] with a
fatty disabled is talking about me.
Really, mate? Look, you know the thing
is bro. Yeah. is that um we don't think
every single woman is fat. We think your
girlfriend is fat. Yeah, that's what we
think. We don't think every single
girlfriend is fat. We think Sarah is big
and fat. Well, yeah. We don't think
every who who said every woman's fat.
No, just your girlfriend's a fat [ __ ]
Just like Kayle's a fat [ __ ] We we
never said every woman is is [ __ ]
um and you know the thing is bro like
you know the thing is with this person
Mr. Beam, bro, you could be 50 pints in,
right? You know the woman that internally
ugly face is with with internally no
teeth. You could be 50 pints down, bro.
And I swear you wouldn't even get a
[ __ ] off this [ __ ] I swear, bro,
that is a that is a court case right
there. You went you went near that girl
sexually, bro. You're you're getting
locked up, bro. And I swear to God, bro,
even with Natalie G. Yeah. I generally
think you could say, "Yeah, if I was 40
pints in and she come on to me, then
yeah, she could suck my dick, bro." Yeah.
Yeah, I did actually. Yeah. Yeah. More self-projecting
and Yeah. But I mean, you could actually
say that. Yeah, bro. Like, you say 40
pints, but bro, but Sarah, nah, you
would never go near that disabled [ __ ]
You can never
You can never ever go You could never
ever ever um
You could never ever ever
It's none of your business what I have,
bro. I don't discuss my life on here
with you people.
I don't discuss my life to self projectors.
You know what's so mad, Mr. B? Yeah. You
know, I went on LJ's channel. Yeah. Uh
was it two days ago?
No, it was yesterday, bro. And he was in
this club. Yeah. And the ratio looked
[ __ ] good. The ratio looked good. It
didn't look like there was any man
there. It only It only seemed to be
women there. It only seemed to be women
there. So, I'm thinking, "Fuck, we don't
get this in London. Normally, it's a
cockfest." So then you go on the
comments, right? So there's a comment
that So then Autumn comments, right? And
then he's like, "Oh, oh, you should come to Belfast."
What? You're telling someone to come to
Belfast when you're in a club full of
women? I'm really starting to think, bro,
these people are [ __ ] I'm starting to
think, do you know what? I never thought
LJ had anxiety before. You had You're
not called, bro. You people are single,
lad. You're not going to get at me. You
people are single fat ugly virgins. I
don't care what you say, bro. You're not
going to trigger me. Yeah, she might be
beyond stinking Smokeoky B, but she's
not worse than Sarah. That's why I said
you'd accept a [ __ ] If you was 40,
50 pints deep, you would accept a
[ __ ] from her, bro. Come on. That's
what I'm saying. There's certain levels.
I would I [ __ ] I would, bro. Listen,
you people are internally ugly virgins.
Go self-reflect on another channel. Anyways,
um yeah, but I mean, if you was 40, if
you was in that many pints down deep,
lad, what you would accept a [ __ ] if
the [ __ ] was coming on to you, that
Sarah, you could never go anywhere near
her, bro. You get locked up.
Internally and ugly that can only get
disabled. That's his that's his that's
his name. Internally the ugly [ __ ] in
the bedsit that only can get disabled.
He's jealous, bro. Do you know what he
thinks in his head? He thinks this
autumn fancies me, bro. Have you Have
you seen how many community posts he's
made about me? The virgin's getting
jealous again because this woman is
coming across, bro. Oh, bro. I don't
even think I could tell Smokey B about
this. I don't even think he was around
back then, bro. Was he Was you around in
the Izzy days?
Maybe not. No, I don't think he was.
Maybe he was. You need to know someone that's
Was you? I don't think he was, bro. So,
you might not understand.
I think Autumn loves Peter Belly. What
do you think, Reezy? You keep posting
about me. [ __ ] off.
She has a lot of white knights. She has
a lot of simps, don't she?
Don't know what I'm going to eat today,
bro. Maybe a curry. I don't know. I
But what I'm saying Yeah. But you know
this virgin? Yeah. Nons. He's very
obsessed with women giving me attention.
This he's he's a very very insecure
virgin. I'm not going to keep going on
about it, but bro, he is so obsessed
with women and me. Put me and women
together. He's very, very, very, very
obsessed. His autism is bad, bro. Look
at autism posting about me. Every single
community post he's wrote, he's posting
about me. He's he's virgin jealous, bro.
It's so It's so weird, bro. It's so
weird. Mr. Internally [ __ ] ugly that
could only get disabled.
[ __ ] hell. He's the internally ugly
one that can only get disabled. I've
never ever been with anyone like that in
my life, bro. And I've been down bad.
Trust me, bro. I've been down bad, bro.
And I've kissed some Montters. O, do you
know that? Do you know that person that
looked transgender? She wasn't even as
worse as Sarah. She wasn't even as worse
as Sarah. No way, bro. [ __ ] no. She
wasn't as bad as Sarah, bro.
It's so weird, bro. So weird.
He's very obsessed with me and women.
I've noticed that even [ __ ] eight
years later, seven, six years later,
where [ __ ] whatever it is, he's very
obsessed with women, bro.
I think it's cuz he knows. Do you know
what it is with him? He knows because
he's ugly and he knows that no normal
woman could ever fancy him. This is
where the jealousy and the insecurity
comes from. Because think about it, bro.
I'm talking mad stuff about Sarah. Yeah.
But that doesn't mean other people
couldn't like her. That doesn't mean
that ever that doesn't mean that some
people might like the way that she
looks, but then if somebody really did
like the way that she looked, yeah, they
would literally get off a YouTube and go
on with their life. This is why I don't
come on here anymore, bro. This is why I
don't come on here anymore, bro. If if
if that like I'm not even with someone
at the moment. I'm speaking to someone
every day. I haven't been on here for
days. If you if I'm wrong and you're
seeing something different, then bro,
you would be living your life off of
YouTube without your misses, bro.
without without posting about me every
day. You [ __ ] weird, lad. That he's a
[ __ ] It's because Yeah, because he
knows that no woman could ever fancy him
for his looks. That's what he hates me
for. But I'm telling you, bro. I'm
telling you 100%.
Cuz this autumn has posted about me. I
just went on the channel. I was like,
every single comment the virgin's there.
The skimp boy. Every single comment. I
can't see one comment where he's not
there. He hates the fact that you're
better looking at him. He doesn't even
know how to like digest it into. And
this is not me reacting, bro. This is me
telling you the truth. Yeah. He's done
it with every single woman, bro. I'm not
even reacting. I'm telling you. Like,
this is an opinion, bro. I don't comment
him much. He does this with every single
woman because he's ugly and no woman
fancies him. He doesn't like it. I'm
telling you, bro. I swear. Do you know
what I don't understand? Smokey B. I
know we don't like you to Can I Can I
Let me just say something to you about L
J. Yeah. What I found was weird the
other day is he's in a club. Yeah. Yeah.
I don't know how many clubs you've been
to. You This guy is in a club, right?
Just listen to me. Yeah. He's in a club
where there's women. There's more women
than men, which is rare. London, there's
more men than women. In most cities,
there's more men than women, right? So,
there's women everywhere. I'm thinking,
"Oh, [ __ ] me." You know? That's like a
That's like [ __ ] being a [ __ ]
child. That's like being a That's Yeah,
he's in a relationship with a disabled
girl. Yeah, he had to resort to disabled
cuz no normal woman would have him.
Yeah, he's in a relationship with a
disabled, which is what I wouldn't want.
Anyways, onto my story. So, so he's in
this club, right? Why is he asking bro
to come to London? Bro, I met someone
two weeks ago. I speak to them every day,
bro. I speak to them every day. If if
I'm in a Why to me, Smokey? just doesn't
make sense, bro. Look at all of the
stuff. Yeah. That happened to um Monty
and Natalie and all of the relationships
that's formed and developed. Look what's
happened. It's all ended in in disaster.
So, why would anyone, and I'm sure you
can agree with me on this, bother with a
woman on YouTube when nothing good is
ever going to come out of it? It's going
to end bad, bro. Let's just say like the
singing worked or whatever the one, bro.
It's going to end badly. You know, we
know it, bro. Why would you? Why would I
don't even bother with women online
offer this community. I don't bother I
don't bother with no women online, bro.
I I if I approach someone and I'm
speaking to them, I speak to them, bro.
I don't I don't bother with no woman online, bro.
Especially not this community. So why
how can you be in a club full of all of
them women and then you're still cuz
he's got anxiety. He can't talk to no
one, can he? It's obvious, bro. It's
obvious, bro. Like I never thought I'd
say it. It's obvious, isn't it? It's got to be.
Like I said, it but if a woman if a
woman on this community travels to you
and she's begging for it, then yeah,
that's a different story. But
they give themselves away too easy, bro.
People in this community, bro. And he's
not the only one. V does it. Mike does
it. Why do you think they do it, bro?
Why do you think Mike and V does it? Cuz
they're ugly as [ __ ] If they went to a
pub, bro, they could never pull a woman.
They could never pull a woman. They
could never get anything from a woman
with a woman, bro. That's why they
That's why they big women online, bro.
They're [ __ ] weirdos. Like, you know,
you you got a fat you got a disabled woman, bro.
You got a disa you got a disabled woman.
And I don't want to be in a relationship
with a disabled woman, bro.
All the women I've been with is better
than what he's with. Simple as that. I
don't need to be in a relationship right
now, whether I could or I couldn't. I've
been in I've been with many many women
and none of them have ever been [ __ ]
disabled. None of them have ever looked
like that. So I think what you mean is
you're Mr. Internally extinct from going
near any normal woman because you ain't
got the looks for it. I think that's
what you mean. I think it's it's a bit
of self projecting. Yeah, it's a bit bit
of self projecting on on your side, lad.
I mean, I've actually been in a
relationship, but you still Why does it
matter? Does it really matter what
anyone does, bro? Really? you know.
Yeah. You know, it doesn't really
matter, does it? I mean, this whole
thing is just silly anyway, isn't it?
What What is the whole point of this? I
don't understand the whole point of
this. You show better women, you show
better looks, you show better money,
they still talk [ __ ]
yeah, they're just Yeah. What the [ __ ]
What are we even talking about, bro?
This doesn't even It doesn't even make
sense, does it?
You can show them a 10 out of 10 model.
You could show them a million pounds and
they still talk [ __ ] Insecure people
are insecure people, bro. It's what it is.
Yeah, bro. He quite he he he says that
I'm ugly, bro. But I'm literally better
looking than him. And no one on the
community will ever deny it. Even people
that don't like me, I'm better looking.
I've had women fancy me. I've been with
women. And he still It's insec. Do you
not understand? It's insecurity, bro.
What what his channel when I just gone
on autumns it's it's jealousy and then
you're trying to talk about people
living with their mom. You live in a
[ __ ] council bedset. Look closer to
home. Like these people I don't think
their brains work properly. Lad
generally don't think it does. He's an
ugly [ __ ] with a disabled girl he's not
happy with and he hates it and he hates
the fact that I can go out meet women.
I'm better looking than him. That's
where the jealousy comes from. Bro, what
the [ __ ] I'm on Autumn Rose's channel.
every single community, any every single
thing that he's wrote, he's there.
What the [ __ ]
Because he's he's scared, Mr. Bean.
Don't he's scared that Autumn fancies
me. He's scared that she's obsessed with
me. He doesn't want a woman liking me
cuz he would never have it because he's
too ugly. Cuz he where he's so ugly, he
could never have a woman do that. That's
where the jealousy comes from, lad.
No, no, no. You laugh at it, but I'm
tell I'm I'm trying to break down the
psychology of it, lad. You can laugh.
Yeah. It's funny, isn't it? Yeah. Funny,
but it's the truth though. We can laugh
at it, bro. But it's the truth. Think
about it, bro. She's made about five
community post on me. I get it. You're
obsessed with me, bro, but I don't like
you. So, yeah. Thank you. Yeah, bro.
Very, very, very um That's why I don't
come on him anymore, bro. Really?
Four years together and he still ain't
[ __ ] her. It's a madness, isn't it, lads?
Uh, she is disabled.
He needs to get [ __ ] laid. He's going
to die a virgin. What's the date, bro?
It's It's his birthday in 5 days and
he's still a virgin. [ __ ] hell.
And there's no point in talking about
the girlfriend, bro, cuz I'm just going
to ignore it. If you say, "How can
someone with a girlfriend be a virgin?"
I'm just going to ignore it cuz we've
been over it multiple times. If a
[ __ ] ain't sex, a girlfriend ain't
sex. And I put my And I put my [ __ ]
arms crossed when I say that. Yeah,
mate. [ __ ] Yeah.
Yeah. I don't care what people on here
say, bro. They're irrelevant.
Just like you.
You I've seen your comments as well
calling me an incel. Why? Because I
because I can go out and speak to women.
something that you can't do.
We've all seen you people [ __ ] a lot
of you people on LJ's [ __ ] s over
[ __ ] all bro calling me an incel.
Why? Cuz I can speak to women unlike
you. It's jealousy. It's [ __ ]
jealousy. Don't [ __ ] listen, bro. Do
not do not um
do not ever listen to what Monty man
says cuz he he he copies he copies what I say.
He copies what I say, bro. He literally
copies what I say, bro. [ __ ] me, man.
2026 and you people are still doing
this. You know, like I've said to you
multiple times, the more you do this,
the more it shows I'm right about you.
You know that. The more it shows
everything I say is right about you. Get
off of YouTube and live your life.
Simple. Why can't any of you do that?
Why can't any of you? Let's talk about
this now. Yeah, this is 2026. Why can't
any of you people come off of YouTube
and live your life and stop talking
about people? Come on, bro. Can I Can I
ask that? Can I ask that question?
I haven't been on here for 9 days. I
won't be on here for another god knows
when. 2026. Why can't you people do
that? I can do it. A lot of normal
people can do. Why can't you go? Why
can't you do it, lad?
Bro, the guy is a [ __ ] [ __ ] bro. I
went on Autumn Rose's thing here. Every
community post he's commenting, he's
scared she fancies me, bro. That's his biggest fear.
His biggest fear is that Alton Rose fancies me.
It does make sense. It makes lots of
sense. Maybe not to a [ __ ] like you,
but it does, bro. He's very He's scared,
you know, bro. Very scared.
Who are they trying to bully now? Who's this guy? Huh?
Yeah, we've been over this already, lad.
Yeah, disabled misses that don't give
him sex. Yeah, good for him, bro. No one cares.
No one. You don't need my email, lad.
I think I'm going to get
curry today. I think
I keep getting addicted to these
curries, lad. They're addicting, bro.
But I'm just going to get a curry, you
know, cuz I don't want to end up like
[ __ ] virgin boys, misses [ __ ] fat.
Why do you Why can't you stop talking about people?
Yeah, I don't care what people think. I
know you don't [ __ ] I know you've got erectile dysfunction.
I I don't care what people think, bro. I
I mean, I know you're a virgin, so I Why
do I care what anyone thinks?
I don't care what London Taylor thinks.
He's irrelevant. I don't care what
anyone thinks. I know that you're a
virgin and I don't care what anyone
thinks. Just like I don't care what
anyone thinks about me. I don't give a
[ __ ] about people on social media. I
know you are the biggest virgin going.
Obsessed, jealous skin. I know what you
are. I don't care what any anyone else
says. Your skin, you're a virgin. You're
[ __ ] ugly. You got no teeth. Just a
virgin on YouTube. Really?
I mean that's that's what you can say in it. Yeah.
O Dusty, do you know? Yeah. What's so
funny, bro? Yeah. Just like what Kieran says
the guy called me a virgin even though I
got his channel banned for pornography.
Like I literally put a porno up.
I literally put a p uh No, I'm not
overweight, but try again. I literally
put a porno up, lad. You don't need to
contact me, bro. You can contact me on
um You don't need to contact me. Yeah,
he's obsessed with me. He's got a whole
channel dedicated to me. And also, Lord,
and also your boyfriend's obsessed with
me, doctor, cuz you can't stop talking
about me. I can take a day off of YouTube, lad.
Yeah. You people are the ones that are
obsessed with me. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
Yeah. I mean, how many people have we
got channels dedicated to me? You You
jealous people obsessed with me and it
is real. How many channels is is
dedicated to me? Answer answer that
question, brother. Answer your answer that question.
How many times do you little weirdos
talk about me? Let's talk about
obsession. Come on. I'm here, bro. No
need to ban anyone. No need to How many
times does you, your boyfriend, and the
virgin go on about me? Do you want to Do
you want to go? Like, all I've said is
you're obsessed and you got fat, ugly misses,
bro. You are the ones that are obsessed
with me and it's very real. Yeah, it's very real,
bro. Bro, bro, I was off of here for
nine days. And what was you doing in
that nine? What was you lot doing in
nine days, bro? Talking about me. So,
good for you.
You know, bro, what was I doing then?
You don't know what I was doing. I
wasn't entertaining [ __ ] retards, was
I? So, I mean, that's good, isn't it? At
least I wasn't on here entertaining
retards like you. You know what I'm saying?
So that's that, bro.
And I can lecture you people. Oh. Oh,
sorry. I can lecture lecture. Yeah,
that's what you said. I mean, I can
because you people come on here every
day talking about people that you don't
know. It's not normal. So, I can lecture
you little weirdos when you're coming on
here talking about people every day that
you don't know.
When you are the ones that are on
YouTube 24/7. You're supposed to have
this life. Yeah. You're supposed to have
this money. [ __ ]
four grand. [ __ ] that. I don't think
I've ever even lost four grand.
The most I've ever lost was two grand.
[ __ ] that, bro.
I don't I haven't gambled since.
I'm done. Done, bro. I told you when I'm
done, I'm done. Simple.
Yeah. Okay, bro. Well, better late than
never then, isn't it, doctor?
Well, I don't need to prove anything to
you little self-reflectors. See you
later. Anyways, um I mean Yeah. I mean,
everyone's got their I mean, everyone's
got their [ __ ] everyone's got their
um moment, you know? So, yeah.
But you people on YouTube every day. Am I lying,
bro? Do you know why I don't comment it?
I've been speaking to this woman every
single day who I met the other day and
I'm thinking why do I need to be on
here? And then it makes me think of a
lot of you people. It makes me think a
lot of about you people, you know, like
V and this. If you weren't ugly and you
had money, why are you on here? And you
can't answer it cuz you know I'm right.
If you I put myself in this position
here. Okay. So, I'm speaking to someone
every single day and I've got other
people I can talk to. I can go and do
things. Okay. So, what I'm asking then
is if you people Yeah. aren't lonely or
whatever. Why are you sat on here 24/7?
What's the verdict? Can't answer because
you know I'm right. Simple. See, Monty
is an idiot. He copies things that I
say. When I say that people are gay and
jealous, he can say it, but he can't
explain it cuz he's an idiot.
You know what I mean?
I hate to break it to you, but a lot of
you people are wasters on here. You
actually No, no, no. You actually are,
bro. You actually are.
You can do things with your life, bro.
Why I don't come on here, but and I
won't be on here tomorrow. I don't care.
I don't need to, you know?
Yeah. Was I? Good. Okay. Well, I'm not
now, am I? Well, I'm not now, am I?
Because when am I going to be on YouTube after today?
You are weird. Like, you know what? It's
also what you do on here as well. You
come on here talking about other people.
You ain't got a life. You ain't got a
Mrs. No way. No way, bro.
There's There's no way. I was too busy
talking to [ __ ] Christian. Izzy
Grezy. Yeah, I don't have time to talk
to these [ __ ] weasels anymore. These
stupid people. [ __ ] that. And I was
going out and I was doing stuff as well.
Yeah, I'll be on there tomorrow. I don't
think so, bro. I don't think so.
I don't understand how L wouldn't want
to go drinking by himself, but he'd sit
on YouTube on a Saturday talking to
people that will never meet him. But he
won't go out drinking by himself. He's a
[ __ ] He's a clowny, isn't he?
He really He doesn't make any sense.
Anything he said, whatever he says makes
no sense. It He just doesn't make any
sense, does he?
Yeah, but Smokey B, you're missing the
point. You can be alone with a life. How
about be alone with a life?
He's an idiot, bro. that Lord J. He
wouldn't go out drinking. But bro, I I I
sometimes go out drinking alone.
Sometimes I go out drinking with people.
I didn't know it was such a big thing.
I don't know. I don't know.
See you later.
There's nothing wrong with going out
drinking alone. I prefer it alone.
You meet people anyways regardless. If
he had went out alone drinking
1% of how much he spends on here, lad. Yeah.
He would have actually made made friends
or acquaintances. Why wouldn't you go
out drinking by yourself, bro? I went
cinema by myself the other day. I didn't
know it was a thing, bro. What the [ __ ]
It's It's weird. He's weird.
Yeah. I mean, that's what I'm saying.
You You die alone anyway, Smokey B. You
don't need to wait on anyone. You don't
need to you know what I'm saying? You
don't need to you don't need to you you
like you don't need to rely on anyone.
You know what I mean? Why wouldn't you
go out when you go out?
Yeah. See you later. Self projectile.
If you go out, bro, you'll meet people
anyways. So you that's better than I've
always had a good night out by myself
cuz you get talking to people and and
stuff and I don't understand how smoke
how uh large a pool the other day with a
ratio like [ __ ] that there was like
[ __ ] 10 women to one men and then
he's begging all him. Come on, bro. You
know how it makes you look silly. You
know that. Yeah.
Yeah. Exactly. Bro, you're born alone.
Yeah, you you don't understand Smokeoky
B. You only have yourself. Do you not
realize that? That's yourself is always
guaranteed. You know, people can ditch
you at any time. People can [ __ ] you
over at any time. You know, I was
telling Greavves a story about a tenant
and some other guy. Bro, you don't I bro
you can only rely on you only should
rely on yourself. You should never rely
on anyone else. Always rely on yourself.
People will [ __ ] Bro, even I'd say even
family could [ __ ] you over. Anyone's
family. I'm not saying I'm saying
anyone. You know what I'm saying? I try
to not deal with people if I don't have
to. I speak to about four people and that's it.
Yeah. But what I'm saying is No, no, no.
But what I'm what Okay, smoking me,
right? This is this is my this is my
logic on this. Yeah. Okay. So, if he
doesn't need to pull, why is he begging
all on YouTube? Think about it, bro.
Yeah. I don't need to beg women on
YouTube because I could just go out and
approach someone if I wanted to. I could
just get their number and keep keep it
off of YouTube. Just like the person
that I met two weeks ago, I speak to
them all the time. You think I'm ever
going to bring them on YouTube? [ __ ] no,
bro. Why would like you wouldn't if
you're missing what you're missing the
point I'm trying to make. Like, if you
generally generally don't care, that's
fine. But then why are you begging
autumn? It's stupid, bro. I'd never beg
no women on this community and never
never have, never will, you know? It's
all It's different if the woman's coming
on to you and traveling to you, then
yeah, bang the [ __ ] and leave her.
[ __ ] But I wouldn't beg some woman on
YouTube. I don't need to, bro. I can
just go out and [ __ ] meet someone.
Wherever it goes is wherever it goes.
But you Yeah, I don't think you get the
point in what I'm making.
Why do you think Alton Rose is obsessed
with me, bro? Cuz I don't give the [ __ ]
attention. Take a leaf out of my book.
Yeah, but I maybe but I don't flirt with
women on YouTube, bro. [ __ ] that.
Maybe, bro, but
that ain't me, bro.
That definitely ain't me, lad. Each their own. Yeah,
she's way out of my league, bro. That's
just self-p projecting, brother. That is
self-p projecting. And do you know how
we know that's self- projecting, bro? Is
because I've been with better than
Autumn. When When people say that a
woman is out of your league, what they
mean is it's out of their league. It
that's that's always been a thing. Yeah.
Like when people say, "Oh, you're
punching." They're talking about their
fat, ugly selves. Cuz if Autumn wasn't
out of their league, they wouldn't care
about Autumn. They'd be meeting women
that are better than her. But they can't
do that because they're fat and ugly.
Fat, ugly, and gay. That's why, bro, why
do you think Monty man copies everything
I say? There's no way you could pay me
to stalk men on on YouTube 24/7. They
know they're gay. That's why they're
writing capitals cuz they're gay and
jealous. Bro, why do you think Monty was
saying all of this [ __ ] yesterday? Red
Star, he's gay. He's jealous. He's got
no life, no woman. It's obvious. It's
too It's obvious. No, it's not rattled,
bro. It's the truth. No person with a
life stalks men on YouTube 24/7 like a
loser. And I can say that they've got
nothing. They've got nothing in their
life and they know it. Nothing. Nothing
going for themselves. No money, no life,
no future. They got [ __ ] all. That's why
they're on here from the time they wake
up to the time they go to bed. wreaking
a jealousy every day to people that they
don't know. I mean, the thing is, yeah,
the whole the whole thing in itself is
disabled because it's not even like
these people know you. They don't like
they don't even [ __ ] know you to be
even doing it. That's what makes the
whole thing so weird. That's why I don't
come on here cuz you're arguing with a
bunch of jealous fat loss that you don't
know. What the [ __ ] bro?
Weird, bro. Weird. Weird. Weird.
Yeah. See you, man.
See you later.
Yeah, but he would meet her though.
Yeah, but but but okay. Smoking me. But
you don't know the half of it. Did you
know that he had phone sex with um Did
you know that he had phone sex with Oxo?
I bet you didn't know that, did you?
He had, you know, he had phone sex with
Oxo in it,
bro. You don't even know the half of it,
bro. You don't know the half of it.
Didn't you know about him and that Sarah
thing when he was like, "Oh, suck my
[ __ ] Suck my [ __ ] bro. Come on.
Come on, bro. He You don't know the half
of it, lad.
You don't know the half of it, bro."
Yeah, but she's in America, bro. Yeah,
bro. The only way I would ever get with
a woman online is if they come on my
front door, bro, begging for it.
Yeah. You want to link up? Yeah.
So weird, bro.
Why would you have phone sex with a
woman in America? That is [ __ ] weird.
Who you've never met, bro? That's so weird.
I don't think he can approach women. I
think he's scared smoking me. I don't
think he could. I think he's got
anxiety, bro. I think I think he does,
bro. Maybe I'm wrong, but I think he does.
Think I'm gonna get a Vindaloo today. Um, Greavvesy.
Oh, I'm so greedy, bro. I'm so greedy.
>> Hello, Peter. Did you see my girlfriend
in the communal post? >> Huh? >> Hello.
>> No, I haven't seen it. Oh, yeah, I did see it.
>> Have a look, man. She's fit, man. N J
jealous is going on about her life now
as I've been doing her all afternoon in
the bedroom. One second. One second.
>> Hello, big virgin boy.
>> Oh, I saw your I saw I saw your thing
about um Cheryl Carl. One second. I
didn't even respond to it. No, you
literally was saying that to fit in
because you was being teased. You said
that if I didn't find her attractive. Uh
I was gay. Never in my life have I had
to resort to a disabled girl like I'm
not cuz I'm not cuz I'm not ugly like
you. I like normal women. I like normal
women. And funny enough, you should
bring my mom up. My mom never starved
me. And I don't live in a bed sit owned
by the council like you. We should cough
every single time we do it. And you know
what? Every time I've shown money, it
was my it was my money and not my
daddy's money. It was money that I had
more money than you.
>> Did you?
>> I mean, you need to you need to like
make this whole thing make sense. You
can't come on here and say that people
are skint when you're living in a bedsit
owned by the council. Your mom starved
you. You have no
>> Shut the [ __ ] up.
>> You have no moral high ground. You got
starved by your [ __ ] mom. Your dad's
a nons. You're too ugly to get anything
normal. Mr. Internally only being able
to get disabled.
>> It's Do you not find it funny how every
girl you've been with is disabled and no
one's I've been with never been
disabled? Do not do not know. Do you not
find it funny though?
>> Do you not find it funny how you've had
to show daddy's body and I've showed my
own? You know I'm right. That's why you
can't answer it. You know I'm right though.
>> I've never been with a disabled person.
>> Your girlfriend.
Listen, brother. I have seen that
picture and that is no normal woman,
bro. That is no normal woman, bro. I
swear to God, bro. I have been down bad.
I have been down bad and never have I
resorted to something as ugly and
disabled as that.
>> That's where the jealousy comes from
because you are too ugly to get a normal
woman. Wasn't you? That's why you were
stalking USA. Is he is he? Just because
they got with me, it doesn't mean you
get with them. They don't do you big.
>> They don't they don't [ __ ] with ugly
like you. Just cuz they got with me,
bro, they don't [ __ ] with ugly like you.
Ugly boy with no teeth. And stop [ __ ]
Listen. Yeah, as as [ __ ] as England is,
as [ __ ] as England is, you do realize
that dentist is on the NHS? Ugly boy.
>> Why won't you let me speak?
>> Ugly boy. You can literally go to the dentist
know that you scared.
>> Fix fix your ugly toothless mouth and
fix your ugly girlfriend trying to talk
about other people.
>> When did you last speak to your mummy?
Since you were When did you last speak
to your mummy?
>> I've not spoke to that [ __ ] in 12
years. Why won't you let me speak? Big
nose. She sto
I Listen, you're the one that resembles
a rat. You ugly looking [ __ ] Your face
is melting. You ugly. My nose isn't big.
You're the one that Bro, your skin your
face is melting. You're ugly. Everyone
on this community knows I'm better
looking than you. Listen, I won't let
you talk. I won't let you talk.
>> I bet you won't say my full name. No big man.
>> Everyone knows I'm better looking than
you. You ugly [ __ ] I've never The women
I've been with proves it. I've never
been with ugly ugly Sarah. Ugly disabled
Sarah. Never. Never been with that ugly [ __ ]
>> You can cuz you're ugly. I mean, you
can't even function in a normal [ __ ] environment.
>> I ever for
>> Okay. Can you Okay. Can you just Can you
just Can you just Can you just answer
this question? So, you're you're trying
to tell me that you didn't say if people
didn't find Sher Walker attractive,
they're gay. Is that what you're saying?
I don't [ __ ]
hairline. You don't.
>> You don't have a full hairline. You're
bald. No, you No, you [ __ ] don't,
mate. You can't even grow face wear, you
ugly rat. You look like Coronation
Street, you ugly [ __ ] No, you [ __ ]
have a full head of hair.
>> You're You can't even grow a beard, you
ugly [ __ ] And you got balded. What the
[ __ ] You look all right looking [ __ ]
>> Shut up, bro.
>> Yeah, I have a full hairline. You don't
>> You do not have a full hairline. You're
[ __ ] balding worse than me. You ugly
[ __ ] You're balding.
>> You ugly [ __ ] Shut up. You ugly boy.
You just said,
>> "Brother, you can't even grow facial
hair." Where's your facial hair?
>> You just said worse than you. So you
>> Where's your Where's your facial hair?
>> You just said worse than you.
>> Where's your facial hair?
>> You just said worse than you. So you
can't even grow it, bro. You're bored.
>> Autistic as [ __ ] Aren't you diagnosed
with autism? One second. Aren't you diagnosed?
>> I am.
>> Yeah. Shut the [ __ ] up, you ugly [ __ ]
Just shut the [ __ ] up. You're diagnosed
and I'm not. Shut up. You have become.
>> You're diagnosed and I'm not. So shut
up. You have become.
>> You said
>> so. Doesn't that mean that you're projecting that?
>> So a diagnosed autistic virgin is
calling me an autistic.
>> On one second. So a diagnosed autistic
virgin is calling me autistic. Yeah,
that makes sense. Go on.
>> You won't let me speak. You're [ __ ]
>> Yeah. Yeah, that makes sense. Yeah.
>> So you going to answer the question or not?
I don't know what anyone's push.
>> Did Didn't you say that people that
don't like Sherlock was gay because you were copying? >> Yeah.
>> Words. It made it sound like I said that.
>> You literally I swear to God if my dead
dad you said that. You little copycat.
>> I swear to God that this little virgin
was showing off cuz you knew that if you
didn't say it, Biles and Jackie would
give you a [ __ ] bolican. They used to
bully you at school when you got
>> Who are Miles and Zachary? Who are Miles
and Who are Miles and Zachary?
>> The Scottish that used to bully you.
That's why you start talking about
>> never heard of them. Listen, remember can't
deny she's ugly. You little virgin [ __ ]
>> How much How much do you weigh? I bet
you're about deny it. You're not ugly. I
can't deny it. You [ __ ]
>> Can you just let me Can you just let me say something?
>> You [ __ ] virgin.
>> Can you just let me say something?
>> Yes, virgin boy.
>> How much do you weigh? I assume about 16 stone.
>> No, I'm not fat and ugly like your
girlfriend. Your girlfriend's ugly. Stop selfing.
>> I never I never said every woman's fat.
>> I never said every woman's fat. I said
your girlfriend's fat cuz she's a fat [ __ ]
>> But she's fat.
>> She's a fat [ __ ] Listen. Listen. Who
who? She is literally fat. She is
>> You're wearing
>> She was literally fat.
>> You're You're wearing Spider-Man shirts
because you can no longer fit into Stone Island.
>> Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Really?
Really? Really? I mean, when was the
last time I wore Stone Island? >> Exactly.
>> I mean, at least I can I mean, at least
I can afford it. Unlike you, your skin,
your championship clothes. Maybe maybe
if you sucked your dad's dick a bit
more, he might give you some more money
to show up for YouTube and you cancel
Medsit. Cancel Medit. Why don't you own
your own home?
>> You need the cow that cancel [ __ ] before
talking about people. I'd rather live
with my mom than live where you live in
that [ __ ] hole. I would even take a
woman back to that [ __ ] hole. You virgin.
>> You live in your mom's spare.
>> I would rather live with my mom in a
house than live in a council bed. Yes. A
virgin cancel bed. [ __ ] I would rather
Yes. I would rather Yes.
>> I would rather live closer to London in
a house unlike a bedit. Yes.
>> You're not letting me speak. You're so [ __ ] annoying.
>> You [ __ ] ugly virgin [ __ ] Mate, when
you own your own house, then start
talking about people. When you've got
your own house, then
>> not many people do own their own house,
>> but they don't live in a [ __ ] cancel
shitty virgin bedsit that you live in. You
>> I don't live in a bedit.
Show Okay. Show us your Show us your
house. Show us your room. You know what?
Show us your room. Show us your living
conditions. Everyone see your living.
Show us my mom's house. Everyone see my
mom. Show us that little virgin bed.
>> Don't let me speak. You don't let me
>> I told you literally everyone's seen
where my mom lives. And it's not a
virgin bedsit where you live.
>> That shitty virgin area. That shitty
virgin area that you live in Little India.
>> Yeah. I don't there's I live in a
predominantly white area and I don't
>> You live in Little India. It's Little
India. It's an all virgin [ __ ] hole.
>> If if I did If I did, I'd be proud of
that. But I don't. It's actually pretty
white. It's pretty white where I live.
Pretty posh as well. But um yeah, where
I live, I don't live in a bed seat. I
live in a flat,
>> one bedroom.
>> Let's see your Let's see your living conditions.
>> Uh no, your house.
Let's see. Let's see the virgin that
talks about people living with his mom.
Let's see your living conditions. Let's
see it. You won't show your You won't
even show Everyone's seen my mom's house.
>> [ __ ] You don't let me speak where I
live with my girlfriend. We share the same bed.
>> No, no, no, no, no. Show us the the
whole You don't So the whole bedsit. So
So was the whole
>> I don't live in a bedit. I live in a flat.
>> YOU LIVE IN A LITTLE BEDIT. YEAH.
Someone just said a [ __ ] I would say if
I lived in a bedit, do you know?
>> Someone just said someone just said a
shito hole. I agree. It was a [ __ ] hole.
>> It's very nice where I live.
>> [ __ ] it's full of virgins like
yourself. Like a big virgin.
>> It's full of virgins. I like it.
>> The struggle is real being a virgin and sleeping.
>> I know. But maybe you'll get hopefully
>> maybe this year you'll get laid. One day
you'll get laid. I've got faith. Once
you once you sort out that erectile
dysfunction, you might just get laid
>> asleep in the same bed with a woman every night.
>> Uh, do you? Good for you. Anyways, maybe
you might get laid. Maybe, maybe, maybe,
maybe, maybe you might get laid.
>> I reckon you'll die of virgin. I think
you're too ugly.
>> Don't you have a single bed? You don't
even sleep in a double bed.
>> No, I've got a double bed and it costs
more than your [ __ ] You DON'T EVEN
HAVE A BED. YOU GOT A super bed. You got
a sofa bed? You You got a sofa bed?
>> I have a bed that I sleep in with my
>> You got a sofa bed, you little virgin.
And yes, I've got a double I've got a
double bed worth more than your anything
in your shitty virgin bed set.
>> I swear you had your camera on earlier.
I saw that blow. Yeah, I've got a double bed.
>> I I saw that electric blow heater on the
side of your bed. That can't be good for you.
>> I've got I've got I've got a double bed.
Something that you can't afford, mate,
cuz you [ __ ] scoot. And another thing,
>> no more copying my holidays. No more copying,
>> you know, is that
>> if that was true, I went there for a
singer, but if that was true that I
copied you by going to Amsterdam, wouldn't
>> I [ __ ] went to Amsterdam, but next
thing I know, some [ __ ] rat looking
[ __ ] with his fat girlfriend is there.
What's the coincidence?
>> I don't remember you doing any of the
things that I
>> cuz I all next thing I see is some
[ __ ] virgin lunatic with his fat
girlfriend. So, I can't even go anywhere
now. You call me, doesn't you?
>> So, you call me a virgin, but then you
say I've got a girlfriend. That makes
>> Yeah, you're a Sorry, sorry, sorry.
You're a virgin with a Are you going
You're a virgin with a fat girlfriend
with disabilities that if you went
anywhere near her sexually, you would be locked up.
>> Yeah, but that's not a thing. That doesn't exist.
>> Well, it does with you, mate. It does
virgin by you. It does.
>> She'd need to have something really
proper wrong for me.
>> She does. She's disabled. She does. She
does. She's vulnerable disabled. She's
got something wrong with her. And you do
as well. You've got erectile
>> dysfunction. Yeah. But wait, I'm pretty
sure you you can be in relationships
with Down syndrome people, can't you?
>> I'm sure.
>> I I I I don't know. But I know that
you've got erectile dysfunction and
you've never had sex.
>> I know that there's no law that states
that you're too disabled to consent to
sex. You'd need to be like,
>> there [ __ ] is. If someone's got a
violent [ __ ] child,
>> dementia or something, I don't know.
There need to be some brain brain issue
where you can't, you know,
>> you know what? I might do I might do a
video, you know, talking about stories
you told me about your dad.
>> But I've never told you anything about
my dad. You know very little about him.
>> His birthday is the 1st of September.
>> So you remember my dad's birthday?
>> But you said you haven't told me
anything about your dad.
>> Yeah, I've told you very little about him.
>> Oh, so you have told me stuff then. No, you know,
>> and you told me when And you told me
when he went to Australia to try to
escape his crimes.
>> This is where the autism goes in.
>> That never worked, did it?
>> The weird thing is, you know, mine and
my dad's birthday cuz you wanted to meet
me on both of them days and I said, "No,
I can't do that. It's my birthday. No, I
can't do that. It's my dad's birthday."
>> No. No.
>> Why are you making kitty noises?
>> Oh, and another thing is I remember your friend Christian.
>> That's why
That's why you mist
bro. The only m is you. I'm better
looking than you'll ever be. You ugly looking.
That's why I'm
>> You know what you should do, right? Put
a poll up. Yeah. On and and and ask
who's better looking. No one could ever
deny I'm better looking than you. You're
ugly. You're [ __ ] ugly. And you're
talking about me.
>> I've When have I ever had to resort to a
disabled girl in my life?
>> Never. No. No. No. Tell me. Tell me. Uh
>> well the 19year-old you said that
>> she wasn't disabled.
>> We heard her talk. We heard her talk.
>> You talk.
>> You said you needed a walker to her. Cara.
>> Isn't it funny how I'm so ugly but I've
been with more women than you? That's
mad that isn't it? That's [ __ ] mad that.
>> Well, I don't base my love life off of
body count. But
>> ugly person has been with more women
than you. That's mad, isn't it? I don't
base my I don't base my love life on
body count, but I've seen with plenty of
women on here and
>> Yeah, disabled women. Yeah, but not
normal women like me because you ain't
got the looks.
>> You can't prove that.
>> You can't prove that any of them are disabled.
>> I mean I mean Natalie G was going to get
with you, but you weren't her cuppper.
You weren't You weren't for her.
>> Good. Thank [ __ ] for that.
>> She rejected you. She rejected you.
your your two your your um
>> you know your tone started changing when
when you weren't far out.
>> You didn't do it far, did you?
>> Why don't your clothes fit you if you're not
>> fit me, mate? They do fit me.
>> Go and put a Stone Island jumper on.
>> Why do you wear ugly clothes from the
charity shop? Cuz you ain't got the
money. Cuz you're skinny.
>> My Never mind that. Your your clothes
don't fit you. Uh, well, they do because
I'm wearing them right now. So, yeah.
>> You're not gonna You're not gonna
project your ugliness and your fat
girlfriend onto me. You're wasting your
time, lad. You're wasting your time.
You're wasting your [ __ ] time.
>> Why are you going to call?
>> Okay. You You want me You want me to to
to put a Stone Island jumper on right now? >> Yeah.
>> Put your camera on and open your mouth
and show us your teeth. >> No,
>> I'll do it. Exactly.
You toothless ugly. Go to the dentist.
You virgin. Open your mouth. Show us
your gummy teeth. Show us your missing
teeth. You [ __ ] virgin. And then and
I'll put the stone island on. You got
missing teeth. How do you have missing
teeth at 31?
>> Why do you speak so fast and not let me
speak most of the time on here? Is it good?
>> Why have you got missing teeth at 31?
>> Cuz I hadn't had two of them removed in 2019.
>> No, there's there's more than that.
>> There was there was no big teeth to grow through.
You got Mrs. Faith, you [ __ ] burden.
>> Yeah, many people do.
>> That is not front teeth, mate. Not
[ __ ] front teeth.
>> You got front teeth. You're not front
>> So, back teeth would would be a different case.
>> You know, I was trying I was I was
trying to go to the pub with you the
other month, but it was a no virgin
policy. No virgins allowed. And
obviously, you being the biggest going,
they can't hear you. Waxy's little
sister in Chinatown. I've contacted.
>> No virgins. No virgins. No skin virgins.
He said, "I wanted to go with you, but
they don't allow virgins." Sorry. Sorry,
mate. I tried.
>> Why are you going to court in a couple of years?
>> No. No virgins allowed. No virgins
>> Why did that guy say your belly button
was sticking out when the when the um
security guard was owning you outside?
The same reason I told them to shut the
[ __ ] up and they stood sat down. A bit
like you when I went to your area and
you were scared to meet me.
>> He laughed. He laughed at you saying
your belly button was sticking out.
>> Why did you let me go to your area and
you didn't come out?
>> So you're fat.
>> Why did you let me come to your You know
you know that London Taylor, you know
what would have happened if he come the
other day. I would It wouldn't have been
like what you done. You little scared
[ __ ] I would have been like you. Oh,
I'm not a fighter. You don't even know.
I had something planned for him. Not
like you. You little virgin [ __ ] I
[ __ ] traveled I traveled over an
hour. You didn't even come out of that
shitty virgin bedsit. Was it you?
>> Why? Why did he say your belly button
was sticking out?
>> I I don't know. Cuz I told him that his
girlfriend's ugly and to shut the [ __ ] up.
>> Why did that
>> Why did you let me come to your area and
you hid? Why did you stop going to
events because of me?
>> Why did Why did you stop going to um
blow and harrow? Because of me. For my
>> I've never I've never stopped.
>> Yes, you did. Yes, you did. I stopped
you going to end.
>> I stopped it. I put a stop to it. >> [ __ ]
>> Why do you speak and then you only let
me say one little bit of a [ __ ] word?
It's so annoying.
>> I'm the artistic [ __ ]
>> I'm the bug that stopped you going and
doing what you enjoy.
>> You're very fat, Peter.
>> No, your
girlfriend's fat and you're ugly. So
that's two. She's very fat and you're
very ugly. Do you know what's so mad?
You know, you know if she break You know
if she breaks up with you, what you
going to do? because you're too ugly to
go and meet another woman. Like they'll
see that ugly rat face and be like
they'll see your missing teeth and be
like, "Fuck looking.
>> You're [ __ ] autistic as fuck." You don't.
>> Again, you're diagnosed with autistic, so please.
>> Yeah, but I let you speak.
>> You But you can't call someone autistic
when you're diagnosed yourself. It don't
make sense. It's like your girlfriend
It's like your girlfriend call It's like
your girlfriend calling someone fat. It doesn't work.
>> Yeah, but you're fat.
>> No, your girlfriend is fat and you're
ugly. She's fat and you're ugly and and
you're a skinny little lanky [ __ ]
Lanky and fat.
>> She's fat and you're a lanky little [ __ ]
>> Get a picture of her and put one up
where you can prove that she's fat. No,
>> I mean uh the one that you've put up
recently. She's She's fat.
>> Put that up all for all for everyone to
see so they can judge for
>> everyone everyone's seen it. Everyone's
seen it. I mean, what do you what do you
people think? Let's Let's ask the chat.
Put put it up for people to see so they can judge.
>> They've already seen it. They've they've
>> There's plenty of pictures of us
together. She's not fat. You're fat now.
You're fat. That's why you don't wear the same.
>> No. No. I'm not fat. I'm in better shape
than you and your fat ugly girlfriend.
You're not I'm in better shape, brother.
Yeah. Someone said that she's disabled.
>> Why are you making autistic noises?
>> I don't know. Why was you diagnosed with autism?
>> Cuz I'm autistic.
>> No, I'm in I'm in better shape than you
and your fat ugly girlfriend. You little
self-protected ugly [ __ ]
>> Prove it. Turn your camera on right now
and pull your Spider-Man teeth. Shut up.
>> I will do when you show us your mouth
and your missing ugly [ __ ] mouth
teeth, you virgin [ __ ] Yeah.
>> Yeah, but I'm not doing that.
>> You know what? I You know what? I wish
you would meet me. You know when you
used to meet me, man, and used I would
have Oh, man. See, I feel like you pick
on people that younger than you. Cuz I
would tell you about your virgin self to
your virgin face, you big virgin. You
remember when you used to project your
virginity onto me.
It's all cuz you was the virgin. But I
didn't know it back then. No, no, but I
didn't know it when I was 17, 18.
>> Makes sense.
>> No, no, it does make sense because
remember when I was telling you
>> the prostitute stories and I and I and
you was choosing not to believe it
because you were the virgin.
>> Because they wasn't true.
>> Well, they was true. They was true. Wait, >> wasn't
>> they was true. My mom literally told you
they was truth. I'm not a virgin. I hate
to break it to you, but we're not all
virgins like you. I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
Okay. Shut the [ __ ] up. Ugly rat face with teeth.
>> Ugly [ __ ] with missing teeth. Balding
ugly rat with no teeth. No teeth. Shut
up. No teeth. Ugly. Shut up. I'm talking.
>> I'm a gummy bear. Cool.
>> You're a gummy bear. Ugly cut with a
ugly girlfriend. Yeah. And your mom
starved you. Should shut the [ __ ] up.
Yeah. And your mom starved you. Shut the
[ __ ] up now. Anyways, just because
you've never had sex cuz you're a
virgin, it doesn't go for me. Virgin
whose mom starved him, it doesn't go for
me. Just because you've never had sex.
>> Just because your mom starved you, just
cuz your dad's a nons and your stepdad
beat you up, it doesn't go for me. Thank you. [ __ ]
>> You're backwards as [ __ ] You don't let me talk.
>> You know why didn't the virgin Why
didn't the escort thing happen? Cuz
you're a virgin. cuz you've never had
sex. There's no doubt I want you.
>> You're back. You're backwards. You don't
even let me [ __ ] speak. >> [ __ ]
the all the So, the prostitute story,
right? How can you lose your virginity twice, PJ?
Is his mic off? Is his mom owning him
right now? I think his mom's like
bullying him right now, saying, "You
bastard. You get off YouTube. You're
bringing a [ __ ] embarrassment to this family.
Yeah, his mom's shouting at him right
now going, "Get the [ __ ] off YouTube, PJ."
Think someone put nude up on my [ __ ] bro.
Anyways, I'm kicking this [ __ ] now. Weirdo [ __ ]
What a way to void the [ __ ] whole
thing, eh? We [ __ ] funny.
Oh, sorry, Greasy. Not every day, bro.
Oh [ __ ] I think he just went back, bro.
But he never
No. Sorry, Dusty. Not every day, bro.
Not every day. I'm going to order a
curry in a bit.
What a way to [ __ ] the whole thing up, eh?
Oh, Laney's going mad.
Oh my god. Laney heard me shouting.
Probably disturbing the neighbors and [ __ ]
Yeah. So, I was just talking to someone, bro.
Don't know whether to get a vend today
or not, to be fair, bro. Oh, bro.
What did I eat earlier? The steak in it.
I might not eat again. I don't know.
Maybe I won't.
That's so weird, bro.
Well, that goes in the little evidence pack. Who's that? H
I don't know what I don't know if I
will, bro. I don't know.
He's put five gambling. One, two, three.
He all them [ __ ] He put one, two,
three. He put five gambling videos up today, bro.
Yep, exactly, bro. I've got it there,
bro. I've got it there. It's fine.
Yeah, bro. But I'll be [ __ ] off
anyways after today again. Grievy, lad.
Go talk to Christian. Christian Izzy
probably for about two weeks, I think.
And yeah, try and meet them and then Yeah, bro.
That'll be me done, I reckon.
Um, I messaged you on Instagram. You
didn't get it, bro.
Should I get a vindaloo? Should I not?
I cannot eat today, G. I don't have to eat today.
I don't know.
What should I do?
Are you going to eat again or no?
Maybe I'll just get like a chow mane or something. Don't know.
Maybe I just get I don't know. Let me see.
You I don't need to take it serious. Me,
bro. Well, I've been eating better, so I mean,
you must be What? Are you really
overweight, bro? You must be really
overweight to be saying that.
Are you like really overweight or
I'm all right, bro? But I don't know.
Well, I've just been eating better.
You're 5 foot seven. Nah.
Yeah. The shorter you are, the worse it
looks. You're 5 foot seven. Really?
You're 5' 7?
I think I'm like 5'9 and a half.
Probably if I put my back straight. It's
hard to do. Maybe 510.
That's not normal, bro. 5' seven is
short. I'd even consider myself quite
I'm like 5'9 and a half, 10,
but I'm a big bastard, bro. You're 5'7.
It's not. Are you sure that's the average, bro?
Quite short, I think. 5'8. 5'9 is the
average. I think I'm just average
height. I think I'm I think I'm average.
Do you wish you was taller? I don't
think I do.
No, maybe like
an inch. But it is what it is, isn't it?
That's the only thing you can't change
is your height as well, Grezy. That's
the only thing you can't change.
That's the only thing you can't change.
Well, you can get surgery, but I mean,
you can't actually do anything to
actually change your um
No, I didn't realize that, bro.
How tall are you, Harry?
Oh, you got a savoy. Oh, bro, I want a
savoy, man. Is it chicken or is it pork?
Cuz a lot of the places here are halal,
bro. So, they don't even have like
normal pork savoys. They have savoys,
but they're not pork.
Yeah, I like Savoy, bro. But it has to
be pork, obviously.
Yeah, I know it does. I know it does. I know.
So, what are you doing this year,
Greavves? You going anywhere new?
You might as [ __ ] Well, bro, whilst
we're still young. That's why I don't
come on here anymore, bro.
That's why I don't really come on here
anymore, bro. I've got a life to be
living. I've got [ __ ] to be doing, bro.
To be fair,
I'm trying to see where I could get some food.
Yeah, Laney was Laney was just mad at me
and stuff, which is understandable
about YouTube and stuff
cuz LT was making threats last week, isn't it?
So, um, she was bit obviously people
would be scared. I wasn't scared, but yeah,
cuz obviously it's happened before. You
know, someone smashes your [ __ ]
windows. It's not not good, is it?
That's why I'm coming off this [ __ ]
bro. That's why I haven't been on it for
like 9 days. And even if I'm not going
out and I'm saving money, I'll just find
something else to do whilst I save up,
bro. I'm done, bro. I swear I'm done
100%. I might come occasionally and say
hi and that to Greasy, but I mean like
proper like on it, bro. Nah,
you might as well just live your life,
bro. [ __ ] that. [ __ ] that.
You know, and and do you know what this
nons legs and that I was like, bro, they
they can do this every day. I can't do
this, bro. Every day. They're Sadax,
bro. They're [ __ ] Sadax.
Yeah, I wasn't scared. I was getting
anxiety the other day, Greezy. That was
because of Christian Izzy. That wasn't
because of that.
No, I wasn't scared. I wasn't scared, bro.
But obviously old people would get
scared. Obviously, if it's happened
before, what the [ __ ] bro?
I wasn't scared. I was only scared I was
going to get ghosted.
Don't want to get ghosted, bro. Scary,
Yeah, I'll talk to Timmy, bro. Cuz
No shouting, Timmy. I've got a headache. Right.
I'm trying to
What should I get to eat? Squeezy man.
A nice bindaloo.
So what? When are you going to get a
takeaway? What? Did you already do a
week shopping grievy? How much did it cost you?
No, I can't get a savoy.
I can't because most of the places are halal.
No, most of the places are halal and I
don't want a chicken savoy. Thanks. That's disgusting.
There's only one place that I know.
There's only two place I know that that do pork
in like around this area, bro. Cuz where
that's where they're halo, they're not
going to do pork, are they? So, and
that's supposed to be pork. But yeah.
>> All right, PJ. What is it with these
lowife YouTubers getting really jealous
of lives? Hey Timmy, bro, I went on your
channel and do you know what I think?
>> What's that?
>> But that girlfriend of mine, Peter.
Yeah, that beautiful woman is so jealous
that he's gone looking.
Why does he want my girlfriend? Can't
you all get your own women? It's not my
fault. I'm a sex god. Call me a liar. I
don't I'm getting sex. >> Yeah,
>> you can't get sex. Can you, Peter?
Timmy, you was being a bit of a copycat today.
>> Can't get any sex, can you, Peter?
>> No, I'm a virgin.
>> Good, lad. At least you admit it. We can get
>> Why would you cop Why would you copy
Lord J's videos today, bro?
>> Why do you copy Lord J's videos? I
haven't copied Lord Jay's videos.
They're my videos.
>> No, but you put the gambling you put the
gambling videos up as soon as he was
gambling. Timmy, it doesn't look good, man.
>> What What are you on about, Peter? How
can I copy someone's videos when they've
got my voice in? You absolute that you
need to go back to school if I Timmy
Greavvesy. What is Timmy voice him?
Wouldn't that you absolute donuts?
>> What What's the verdict of what Timmy
is? Greavvesy. What's What's Timmy been today?
>> Timmy likes me. He knows I'll go to
Derby and knock two sheets out of him if
he's cheeky to me. Unlike you, Peter
runs away from every fight because you're scared.
>> Yeah, but Timmy Lord.
>> No, no, no, no, no, no. But Peter, come
on. You have run away from every fight.
But no, but Timmy LJ went live today
gambling and all of a sudden you started
putting in gambling videos up.
>> Well, fair play J's done gambling if he's one.
>> And hey, Timmy, do you remember Do you
remember that time? Do you remember that
>> Do you remember that time? Do you
remember that? Do you remember that time
I had a haircut and then you got one
straight away to me?
>> Oh my god. So, we're all copying you,
Peter. Is that it? Yeah.
>> I think you're a big fat dirty stinking
copycat today. Yes.
>> I think you're a big stinky big I think
you're a big skint loser virgin. So,
what's the difference? Well, how can I
be a virgin when I prove I've had sex on
video? We [ __ ]
>> Oh, here's the autism again.
>> Come on, Peter. You talk about
>> This is autism. This is how you lose
brain cells. This is how you lose brain
>> More [ __ ] sex than you, lad.
>> This is how you lose brain cells
>> for a living.
>> This is how you lose brain cells. Uh, Grey
>> Grimsy thinks you're a [ __ ] mate. He's
He winds you up.
>> Okay. Okay. So, do you think do you
think Nons is a virgin?
>> Yes, I do. And I think he's a [ __ ] and
I think he's going to go to jail for
benefit for his AIS out now and no one's
getting away with nothing.
>> He's an idiot, man. This to me is a
bummed by a big fat Polish man.
>> What the [ __ ] are you talking about?
>> Any of these internet people to save
him? I like Red Star. I'm not slacking
him off, but Red Star ain't going to
save him. the
>> n but you know you know but Timmy you
have to agree Timmy you have to agree yeah
>> listen listen listen Timmy Timmy one
second you have to agree though that Red
Star's got no life bro like listen
>> I'm not going to say too much I'm the
only one who knows who Red Star is and
we're friends so I'm not
>> if you got his address give me it and
I'll give you some money
>> I've told you it's money Mike how many
more times do you want to tell you
>> I can't say he's I'm sorry I'm not allowed to
>> I'll give you £500 pound for the for the
for the address.
>> Three and a half grand and I'll tell you
>> you're not I want the address.
>> Bro, honestly, honestly.
>> No, honestly.
>> One thing right now. All I'm going to
give you a clue is they're from island
>> Pat mustard.
>> No, someone else. But it ain't >> Pat
and it's not V.
>> When are you going to get a life to me though? Seriously,
>> I got one. You've been on YouTube all
day with mash money. I wasn't on. This
is my first time on YouTube in 10 days.
>> Been out having fresh air.
>> Okay. So, the so the curry and the ricey,
>> you're the one who's been complaining
all day levels to
>> I have to kick Timmy, bro. He's giving
me a headache. So, yeah, this uh curry
and rice is 20 pound. Greasy.
Curry and rice.
okay with you, boss?
Is that okay with you, boss?
I was going to get the ticker, but I
kind of I want to try and cut down on certain things, you know.
What do you think?
Just get a curry in it, I think. Yeah.
Don't want to have a bear belly, you know.
What do you think? Oh no.
I'd get a burger from Burger King, but
it's just going to come cold, so it's pointless.
Right. This is my last takeaway.
All right, Grezy.
All right, this is my last one
cuz I'm going to [ __ ]
be very unhealthy if I keep
No, no, no, no, no.
How much money have you got, Grezy? How
much money did you save this month?
I need to start saving money for
Christian Izzy and stuff. It's another
reason I can't be gambling anymore, bro.
Cuz I'm going to need money for that as
well. Well, it's not because of that. I
stopped gambling before that, but you
know, I don't want to get into that [ __ ]
Well, is that how much money you've got? Bless you.
Is that how much money you've got? Bless you.
And you get when you get paid again.
You don't have 10 grand. Greavves.
How did you get 10 grand?
How did you have 10 grand?
Did you just save it?
Well, it's easy how you got it because
you don't even [ __ ] leave the house, do you?
Or did you just save it?
How did you get it? Did you save it? Clear decky.
How did you get that, Grezy? Did you
just save it?
I need to get a new whatever. What do
you think, Grezy? The mommy [ __ ] say
been going to the pub for a while.
They're on a mission. I think they're on
some kind of mission, is it?
No, seriously. How did you get 10 grand?
Did you just save it?
How long you What did you do? Did you
How did But I don't know how you done
that though. You stayed in for that
amount of time. That must be boring, isn't it?
You stayed in for that time though, didn't you?
Which is quite boring.
That's boring though, isn't it? Staying
in that that amount of time. How did you do it?
So, how long did it take you? What? A year?
Do you know what I would do if I was
you? Yeah. You don't You live your life
how you want to live your life, bro. But
I'm not you. But what I would do, bro,
is I'd save I'd still say I would save I
would get in shape. Yeah. until around
May. Yeah. And I'd stack your money
until May and then just have some fun
for like three months, bro. Go Scotland, go London,
go um, you know, even like a different
country. I generally would do that if I
was you, bro. Why not? Why not stack
your money till summer and then just
have some fun?
I would do that if I was honestly you,
bro. That's what I am doing.
I don't gamble anymore, bro. I haven't
gambled for a couple of weeks. I'm done
with it. When I said I was done, I'm done.
And Greavvesy does get takeaways.
Don't you, Greavvesy? You do get takeaways.
He doesn't though previously I I haven't
gamble I don't bro the only thing I
gamble now is football
did do me last month though cuz I could
have had a lot of money going over but
bro I don't I gambled last I I gamble I
gambled 20 on the football on Saturday
but that's cuz the machine didn't
have£10 notes bro I do£10 on the
football every week
maybe but bro I don't gamble more and
20 maximum on the football. Now, I'm
done with that [ __ ] bro. I'm done with
it. And I don't play roulette either. I
closed the account down, everything. I
didn't go back to it, bro. I'm done.
When I say I'm done, I'm done.
And say I meet this person soon, I'm
going to have to have money. Oh, well, I
would like I I would like to have money.
I'd like to have a certain amount of
money before I go out. So, obviously
obviously I can't gamble and risk risk
it, you know. So,
I don't g I don't I mean would you would
you even count £10 on football as
gambling? I don't.
But yeah, honestly it wasn't allowing£10
notes out the machine. It was 20. So I
just put 20 pound on the football.
That's probably why I look well now. You
know I don't look stressed in the eyes
and that cuz I'm stressful, bro.
Yeah, [ __ ] gambling, bro. But seriously,
no greasy, bro. Listen. Yeah, just save
your money until May and then just go
Scotland and that. Why don't you just go
Scot Why don't you go Scotland? Yeah.
Why don't you go Edinburgh and then
Glasgow, Grezy? Honestly, why don't you
go like Edinburgh on a Friday and
Glasgow on a Saturday? You said you
always wanted to go Scotland. You might
as well. [ __ ] it, isn't it? You're
getting in shape now.
I'm saving as well, bro. Even if it's
slowly but surely, I am saving.
Yeah, [ __ ] it. Why not?
You don't want to look back in 10 years
and wish you done this and wish you done
that. You know what I'm saying? I'm
being serious. I'm not even like
trolling. I'm being deadly serious, bro.
You should live your life, bro. Honestly,
really, I'm being deadly serious. I'm
really being deadly serious.
Deadly serious, bro. I'm not even saying
[ __ ] I'm being real, you know.
Find yourself a lovely Christian. Bless you. Um
yeah was [ __ ]
see when when that law when that law J
was saying I've wasted my life on there
bro that is self projecting
I don't know if you go on LJ's indigo
bro I've done more in four years than
he's done in his whole life there's
foods I've tried he hasn't there's
places I've been he hasn't and I'm not
even just talking about traveling And
then I'm talking about venues and stuff.
That is that is hardcore self projecting, bro.
That is hardcore like self projecting on his part.
Nah, she won't ghost me, bro. I've been
speaking to her for ages. She won't ghost me.
We speak every day. We what she won't.
So, and it won't be a meltdown, bro. For [ __ ] that.
That's mad, bro.
Yeah, LJ self projects a lot, bro.
The only reason I didn't go to more
places, Greavves, is cuz I would, if you
live in London, yeah, you go, you can do
so much in London. There's no need to
really go anywhere else.
And I did travel as well. That's the only reason,
Grezy. That's the only reason
cuz you live in London. You get to do
what you want. Why? No one's going to
think to go abroad, are they? No one's
going to think of traveling out the
country. Do you get it?
So, I've done more than egg, bro. I
would honestly say, would you honestly
say, Greavvesy? I would say that I've
gambled more than Joe and I've gambled
more than LJ 100%.
I would say I've drunk more than I I
think I've done a lot more stuff than
both of them, bro. I swear to God.
See you later. I would say I've actually
done more than them, bro. I swear to God.
Trust me, they never had the life that I
did at 24, 25, bro. Trust me.
My life is still good now. I still got
money now. But I'm saying they didn't
have my life, bro. 24, 25, 26. No way.
Uh oh, bro. No way.
More designer clothes than them. Drunk
more than them. I've gambled more than
Trust. I have, bro. Really have.
Can't wait for this bindaloo. Greavvesy.
What do you think about the whole tenant thing? Grievy,
that's why I don't like people. That's
why I don't deal with people, bro.
It's true though, ain't it?
Don't know why L wouldn't go out
drinking by himself. There's nothing
wrong with it.
I don't think there's anything wrong
with that at all.
I don't see the
He's weird, isn't he? Bro, he's very weird.
Very strange. Why you even do that?
He's an idiot, bro. Oh, I like
you little copycat.
Person didn't reply.
Nope. Not letting you in. Nope.
You didn't come back on Instagram, Greavvesy.
Was I depriving you of content, poor Becker?
Was I depriving you of content? You poor Becker.
The Reddit mods can't get through my VPN. We
>> Can they Yeah.
So, when did you last have a takeaway?
Be you didn't answer. When did you last
have a takeaway? Bless you.
Come on. Food. Oh, bless.
So, do you just get one every Saturday
then? Bless you. Oh, bless.
You must just get one every Saturday, is it?
Would you be a Would you be a landlord, Weezy? No. Never again.
That means dealing with people. No.
[ __ ] that, bro.
Oh, I also went cinema though, didn't I? Yeah.
No, Greasy. No.
Uh-uh. You don't want anything where
you're dealing with people if you don't
have to. Does that make sense, Grievy?
You saw what I wrote to that [ __ ] It
was on my phone.
Don't try and play games with me, you
stupid little [ __ ]
You know what I'm saying?
I hate people that try to play games.
Greasy, are you the same?
I hate people like in in in that kind of
way. Do you get it?
When it comes to that kind of stuff, I
hate people. You know what I mean?
I can't explain it, bro. Like
Don't know where he is. He's another
bullshitter, isn't he?
Bless Greavesy then. If he's got 10k,
bless him. But answer me this. How do
you stay in and not get bored?
I happen to stay in, bro, cuz I'm trying
to save a bit, but it's [ __ ] boring,
bro. Well, I still go out now. I just
don't go out pissing on a drink of that. But
that's cuz I'm obsessed with saving.
Once I get obsessed with saving, I don't
want to spend. How do you not get bored? Greavves.
Guess you're used to it. Is it?
You just stay in and you just stay in
and watch Tik Tocky.
You just stay here and watch Tik Tock. Lad
You must what do you actually do?
What do you actually do, lad? Huh?
Notice Monty's not been on here today
after talking my [ __ ] name, the
prick. So, he's got all of this mad [ __ ]
to say and then when someone calls him
for it, he's not here, is he?
Why has he got me on his [ __ ] thing?
That L. What a weirdo, bro.
Let me see. I'm on it right now.
Yeah. Look at that lost beard. It's
lovely, isn't it? Yeah.
How much is that Lord J on the bound? Ooh,
I know. Don't stop putting the fake wins
up in it.
So, why did Okay. Okay. One second. One
second. Hold on a minute. Didn't Didn't
um Joe say that if you go live in the
bookies, you get banned. Yeah, right. Yeah. Wait,
you want my WhatsApp?
Why do you want my WhatsApp? What the [ __ ] my WhatsApp.
200 win is nice, bro. You know why I'm
saying it's nice? Because it's so hard
to win money nowadays.
Yeah, that'd be nice winning 200, bro.
That's a lot of money nowadays to win,
bro. So hard to win nowadays.
I'd be happy with that.
Yeah, that's good. Is it
any window that [ __ ] bro? up V's on YouTube again.
I swear this virgin V's got no life in it.
He's on YouTube again.
Straight on YouTube, Grezy.
I watched Monty Man's live, Grezy, where
he said, "Let's talk about this community.
Let's talk about this community."
I was dead.
Why do you want to add me, bro?
Even though we're really you, which it probably isn't.
It is you. Why do you want to add me,
bro? What the [ __ ]
This community is weird, bro. Very weird.
Let's talk about this community. Greasy.
Look at that [ __ ] beard, mate.
So, did you go to the shop to get eggs
and milk, Ramsay? Oh, that's so cute. Bless you.
Bless you. If you nip to the shop then,
Grey, you went shopping in you. lens.
Hurry up, man. Why is this taking so long?
It says they're working on my order,
Grezy. I want my bloody vindaloo, and I
want it right now. Thank you very much. [ __ ] starving. Wow.
I don't know if I trust you with my WhatsApp, bro.
Um, is there anything else you have?
You got uh Instagram, bro? If you got
Instagram, you can message me on Instagram.
I got Instagram, I got Snapchat,
I got email. You can email me if you want. [ __ ]
I've got an email.
Yes, it pjx@yahoo.com.
Pretty sure everyone knows my email.
Yeah, it pjx@yahoo.com.
Simple. There you go.
I'm not sure what sense you will be
talking into me, bro, because I'm not
going to be on here after today for a
long time. So,
[ __ ] email [ __ ] Greasy messaged me
on WhatsApp because he was being
deprived of content. The poor [ __ ]
So, I had to come back, you know.
The poor [ __ ] Poor [ __ ]
Poor [ __ ] now.
So, do you reckon that account's still
around then, Greavesy?
Or what? What did you say? It's picking
its moment now.
What? Do you reckon it still comes on YouTube?
Do you think it still comes on YouTube? Yeah.
What do you think, Captain? Huh?
Yeah. I remember when I was approaching
the women around Liverpool Street. He
said, "Oh, there's nothing Peter Belly
can do to change his [ __ ] situ."
And he says, "But people on Reddit say
you can get sex whenever you want." Grieves
sat there. What? So, what is it doing?
Is he sat there waiting like a little watchdog?
M. Was he being like a watchdog?
Was he being a little watchdog? For sure.
Nothing, bro. Just order some food.
Yeah, just chilling, bro.
What about you?
So, what was Timmy being today then? Grezy,
what was what was Timmy being?
Come on. What was he actually being?
Bro, there's no coincidence.
Bro, the reason why I don't really come
on, I was going to come on yesterday,
but it's pointless. It's just the same
[ __ ] isn't it? Yep. Smokey B.
Yeah, Smokey B emailed me, bro.
Wonder what he wants. No.
Come on. I want this bloody food.
But do you understand what I meant about
dealing with people? Grezy.
Yeah, I checked it. I saw it, bro. Yeah, it's you.
>> Yeah, bro. I see it.
Yeah, I got you, bro.
I got you, man.
Was me and Crash waiting last week,
Grezy. We was waiting for the windows to go in.
Me and Crash in it.
Me and me and Little Crash and the
little characters. We was waiting in it.
Nah, it's not funny, bro.
No, it isn't funny. If I live by myself
and that I find it funny, in it cuz I
don't care about like Yeah. Not when
it's not your house and that and it
isn't funny, bro.
You remember that big house Ed was in?
Greavvesy. That big house, bro.
Imagine the windows.
They got spotted though. Ain't it? They got spotted.
Yeah, they got swatted though, bro.
They did get swatted a few times in it.
They did get swatted a few times, lad.
Yeah, I got your number, bro. I'm not
going to leak you. I don't leak people,
bro. But I mean, what do you need, bro?
I mean, yeah, Smokey B, bro. Like, the
thing is I I'd give you my number and
that, bro, but
maybe you'll hack into me and then
you'll find Christian Izzy.
I don't want anyone to find Christian Izzy, Grezy.
Maybe you might hack my WhatsApp.
What if he hacks my WhatsApp? What if
Smoky hacks my WhatsApp? Weezy,
then I have to find a new plumber. You
know what I mean? No, seriously though,
bro. You might hack me. I don't leak
people's stuff, bro.
I wouldn't leak you. I don't leak people's stuff.
Smoke. I don't leak people's stuff, bro.
Just email me. Veraroomi,
bro. You know what I mean?
I don't have a I don't have a another phone.
I can't get over that though. Grezy know
that count. Yeah, that account used to
mock me. Grievy them army [ __ ] were
laughing at you. Greasy laugh.
Do you remember? I don't know why that
made me laugh the other day cuz a
bouncer said, "I ain't seen them army
[ __ ] for a while." Exezy
them army [ __ ] were laughing at us. No,
he said at you and then he changed it to
us in it. Oh mate,
that I don't know why that made me laugh, bro. All right.
What do you reckon they're going to do
with that house, Greavvesy?
I don't think they're going to give it
to someone, are they? You know the house
that's that they're doing up. Do you
remember you remember the story? I don't
think they can. I don't think they can
auction it, can they, Greasy? Cuz of the YouTube thing.
They can't, Grezy, can they?
No, I don't leak anyone either, bro.
Just just email me in it. Just email me, bro.
No, they can't. Do you know why they
can't sell the house to someone? Grezy,
do you want to know why?
Grievy, do you want to know why the old
house they can't auction it?
I can tell you. I can tell you if you want.
the old house. Uh, the other house I was
at, they can't let anyone live there. I don't
I don't think so.
Do you want to know? Do you want to know why, Creepsy?
I can tell you why if you want.
Only if you want.
Won't take long.
Dusty, you know, the old house, they
can't um they can't auction it. I don't
think they can let other people live there
cuz say there's there's like a new
family that move into that house and
then someone from YouTube
sees when someone someone from YouTube
sees someone coming out of that address
and they're going to they're going to
attack them in it cuz the whole
cuz the whole YouTube it
because of the whole YouTube thing.
Anyone that's associated to coming out
of that address will be under attack.
They'll be under attack.
That's why they can't do it, bro. It's not safe.
They can't do it, bro. It's not safe.
The windows went in that old house.
Screams. I've I've got the picture where
the windows went in.
That's really scary, bro.
That's really scary. Like, imagine. No, seriously.
No, that's actually really scary, bro.
Cuz say you've just moved in a house yet
thinking it's all safe and then you got
people talking in the house, you know. Yeah. Yeah,
I think he told me when I come back I'll
never forget that day, bro. I was in
Notting I come back from Nottingham in
it and they said they were going to do
the house and I made sure not to go back in it.
I made I made sure not to go back in it.
No, [ __ ] that. Yeah, when the house when
the house was on alert in it. No,
no, that scared me, bro.
That's actually pretty scary if you
think about it.
Yeah. [ __ ] windows went in and everything.
But do you know what I think it was,
Dusty? Yeah. Do you know? Do you know?
Do you want me to tell you the truth? I
I think if you weren't making money from
that house, I don't think they would
have done that, you know. But
I don't think they would have done that.
Well, no, they didn't know though, did they?
No. I know they didn't know, did they?
No, I can't even say that cuz they
didn't know, did they?
I would have been like, "Oh, maybe they
done it cuz they were jealous." But they
didn't know about the house, did they? So,
that's scary, bro.
So, people will be giving you guides.
What do you mean?
Yeah, but if that tenant was in that
room that night, he could have died.
Grievy, you think that's funny?
You actually think that's funny? It's
not funny, bro. H
You think it's funny, is it?
You think everything's funny. You It's
not funny. Someone could have died.
Someone could have actually died. Grieves.
You think everything's a laugh?
Smokey B wants to talk,
bro. You can email me, lad.
Yo yeah, I've got loads of stories about
that house, bro. I'll never forget.
Yeah. When that woman come in the door
and she was fat and the tenant wanted to
get rid of her and we was like, "No, no,
you can stay. You can stay."
But it also shows what people are like,
bro, in it. So I learned what people was
also like, which is a good thing.
Trust me, bro. I would never.
No. Don't like dealing with people if I
don't need to deal with people. Simple as that.
That's why a lot of people just work and
just don't deal with people. People are
headaches. Do you get it, bro? People
are actual headaches.
Headaches. They play too many games.
This is why people just don't deal with people.
You know what I mean, Grezy?
Can't believe the cheek of that tenant
the other day trying to be racist.
Bang that door. What door?
What with the weight bar?
Over gambling. That was years ago, bro.
No, I can't even say London Taylor done
it because of the money because they
didn't know I was making money in the
house. No, I don't think so, bro.
That is weird though, is it, bro?
Smashing people's windows over YouTube. That is
That is That's some psychotic behavior,
is it, bro? Yeah.
I don't think there's anything someone
could actually say to make me do that.
To make me do that.
I don't think so, bro.
There's nothing anyone could say that
would make me do that, bro. I don't
think so. There's something that someone
could do. Like, for example, grievy.
Like, say, say I was in a relationship
with someone and someone [ __ ] it up
over YouTube or something mad. But
saying that at this age maybe not then
maybe I would but not there's nothing
anyone could say they would have
actually had to have done something
cuz I don't think a words could wind me
up that bad bro
think about virgin boy I done [ __ ] I
done I done that poster [ __ ] cuz he
tried stopping my money so otherwise it
would have never went to that
no I don't think so bro people can say
your mom's this. Your mom's that.
That's weird. Why someone would do that,
bro? Over words. That is weird. People
can say, "Oh, racism and that, but nah,
bro. That is wild."
So, what? You was prepared to kill
someone because of [ __ ] words online.
Maybe some people are like that, bro.
But not me.
No, that is psychotic behavior, bro.
What do you think?
What about you, Smokey? Do you reckon
you could smash people's windows and
[ __ ] over YouTube? I don't think I
could, bro. Unless they actually had done something.
That is weird, bro. Obviously, I'm not
black, so I don't know what it's like
when people are racist, but I don't
think it would wow me up that much, bro.
No, I'm not I'm not joining these panel,
lad. You got my email, so you can email
me what you want to email me, bro.
No, [ __ ] him, bro. I don't like the guy.
No, I can't go on that channel, bro. I
lose brain cells. Sorry, man.
Where is this [ __ ] curry, man?
Oh, bless you.
I wouldn't smash people's houses over YouTube.
That's a bit weird, is it, lad?
Yeah, I got your number, bro. But can
you just email me? Just email me what
you want to email me, bro.
Just email me what you want to email me, lad.
I'm not going to give your number to
anyone anyways. Just email me. Have you
been sp Have you been speaking to LT?
I don't speak to LT, bro.
I don't speak to LT, lad.
Nothing to do with me, matey.
Yeah, I can't I can't. Bro, just email
me if you want to talk. Just email me,
lad. I don't have two phones anymore. So, yeah,
you have to email me, lad, if you want to talk.
Nah, he's not a good lad, bro. He's not
a good lad. I don't like LT, bro.
My mom was scared the other day. I wasn't scared.
Oh, I was scared, but not cuz of that. I
thought I was going to be ghosted, bro.
I wasn't scared, bro.
He isn't normal, bro. I don't I don't
like him. Simple as that. That's all I
need to say. I don't I don't like the dude.
Think about the [ __ ] you done to the
house as well when my mom was living
there, bro. You don't do that [ __ ] when
an old woman's living there, bro.
Think about it, bro. You don't even do
it usually. Like, you don't see me
smashing up people's houses. You know, I
spoke to my friend in Amsterdam. I told
him the exact story. And he said, "Yeah,
if that was him, you know what he would
do? He'd come on a house." Yeah. He'd
come he'd come on he would come on the
door and he'd say, "Oh, why are you
doing this? Why are you doing that?" He
said, "Yeah, under no circumstances
would he ever smash someone's house
unless they touched unless they touched
his kid. That's the only way he would do that."
So, I spoke to people about like and
they said that's No, that's weird, bro.
I think that's the only way you could do
it if someone like done something bad to
you, bro. I feel like that's the only
way you could smack someone's house up. Yeah,
that's that's [ __ ] up, bro.
I don't speak to him, lad.
Like, I just I was just saying stuff
about my mom cuz my mom lives here. It's
her house and that, but I'm not scared.
I'm not scared, bro. This is four or
five years later. I'm not scared. But
obviously, I'm not going to stir [ __ ] in it.
Yeah. Because when my mom lives here in
it, so if I was by myself, bro, like,
bro, I'm not I wasn't scared anyways.
That's that, ain't it?
No, I'm just saying I don't like you.
It's as simple as that. I'm allowed to
say I don't like you. I'm not talking
smack about you. I just don't like you.
Simple as that.
Nah. Nah, I'm not talking smack. I just
say I don't agree with the [ __ ] that you
do. People allow their opinion on you,
lad. It's as simple as that.
Yeah, people's allowed an opinion, bro.
Why are people not allowed an opinion?
People can have an opinion without
saying it to your face if they're not
being malicious. Come on, bro. It's the internet now.
But you got my email anyways, mate. So, yeah.
And that's that. People
cannot agree with things that you say
and critique you on them. You know that
without having to say stuff to your
face. You do realize that.
That's not causing trouble. That's
having an opinion.
I told you I think that you're biased.
Yeah, you are. So what? I don't care.
You are biased, bro. So what?
So, if someone thinks you're biased,
they have to call you biased to your
face, bro. Come on. Uh, yeah.
Why is this taking so [ __ ] bastard long?
So, just email me what you got. Email me, man.
Come on. You said you got something to
say, so you can just email me, bro.
First time on here in 9 days. I'll be
off my longer tomorrow, bro.
This is just dedicated to Greavvesy.
This little live stream.
Well, you No, I just said that like you
said that you're going to come and adore
and that is it. Oh, no. I didn't tell
her. She read it. She was actually
reading it on YouTube.
She was reading it on YouTube. She read
what you wrote. I didn't actually tell
her. I actually remember it. Yeah, bro.
She watches this channel, mate. She
knows what she knows who you are. So,
anything that you write Yeah.
She watches his channel. Yeah.
But no, I just don't understand like why
you do things that you complain what
other people do. I just find it weird to be honest
when you're also a victim of their [ __ ]
just like I am.
like you're a victim of these people's
[ __ ] just like I'm a victim of their of
these people's [ __ ] but then you go and
do the same thing as they do. So, it
doesn't make sense. I'm not going to get
into it again, bro. I'm not going to
lose brain cells again, but it just it
really does not make any sense.
So, how are you going to be a victim of
their [ __ ] like I am and then do the
same thing as what they do? It don't make sense.
You know what I'm saying? I just don't I
just don't understand you. I really don't.
Monty was talking smack about me yesterday, bro.
Like madness. He was saying some [ __ ]
madness yesterday. Come back on here
today and he's he's nowhere to be seen.
I said, "Stop [ __ ] keep my name out
of your [ __ ] If you want to argue with
LJ, that's on you, bro. Don't don't
involve me in your little gay [ __ ] bro.
I'm not involved. I'm not involved with
your little [ __ ]
Don't [ __ ] involve me in your [ __ ]
pathetic, stupid arguments.
[ __ ] annoying, bro. Yeah,
no one's talking [ __ ] about anyone's
cousin. You're saying that you're going
to get someone on the door to slap an
old woman in their face?
What the [ __ ] bro? And I'm talking
[ __ ] How am I talking [ __ ]
Well, I don't really care anyways to be
honest. I don't even know why we're
still talking about this.
So, you haven't been going on anyone
else's channel then? No, just this channel.
I find it hard to believe you don't see
people that talk [ __ ] about me, to be honest.
I find it hard to believe. There's a lot
of channels doing it.
I was speaking about your kids, bro. You
were speaking about people's family,
yourself. Yeah. You were speaking about
people's family yourself.
Yeah. Did you Did you Did you say that,
bro? You literally, bro, I find it hard
to believe that you've never seen
someone call me a virgin. But if it's
true, it's true. I I just find that hard
to believe, bro. I find that very very
very hard to believe.
Why would you even like say anything
about people that's tried to get you in
trouble, bro? You're [ __ ] mad. Yo,
you're just I don't understand you, bro.
I really don't.
Well, when I Well, when I Well, what's
it? So, so it's okay for people to call
me stuff, but then when I call them
stuff, it's got a lot to do with you
then. So, it's only got something to do
when I say something back to them then.
But that's what you're not but this is
what I'm trying to say. You're not
making no sense
because if not if they're insulting me
got then me insulting them's got nothing
to do with you then. It's as simple as
that. Why do you care? They're biased.
You said they're racist. You says that
you say they're biased. You say that
they're racist. So, leave them. [ __ ] it.
It doesn't matter how stupid it sounds.
Just let me just let me slack them off
in it. Why do you care?
See, you're contradicting yourself. And
what makes it and the worst thing about
it is is that, bro, they've you're
you're literally a victim of their
biasness as well. So, I don't know why
you even care, bro. You're you're you're
a victim of their of their [ __ ] as well
as I am. So, why would you care about me
calling them whatever the [ __ ] I call them?
So you must be trolling then, isn't it?
But then how but then at the same time,
how can you moan at these people that
are being or saying that, "Oh, you
didn't go to Nottingham because you're white." Yeah.
You You said that these people are
biased. So why do you care if I go them then?
I call someone a virgin because they
call me a virgin when I've proved I've
had sex. Simple as that. So it's
it's the one I met a couple of weeks ago.
She's actually nice to be honest.
I don't argue about bro. I haven't been
on it in nine days. I'm not I'm not
arguing with them. H
you I don't think we'll ever know the answer.
Well, I don't know, man. It just seems
weird what I mean because his channel
got banned for pornography. Like, he put
he put a [ __ ] He put a he put me
getting a [ __ ] on his channel and he
got banned. His channel got banned.
No, she's not. and he got and his
channel got banned and he still calls me a virgin,
but I'm not allowed to call him a virgin.
We'll never know, Grezy. Let's just
change the topic because I don't think
we'll ever know.
I don't think we'll ever know. So,
someone's channel gets banned for
pornography, yet they still call me a
virgin, but I can't call them a virgin
cuz they've got girlfriends. Doesn't
make any sense. But anyways, we'll move
on from that
cuz I don't think it would be any more
different if I got a girlfriend
tomorrow, would it? So, no, they aren't
flaking anyways. They're not flaking. No.
Also, you've never called him a grass as
well, LT. I've noticed that you've never
called him a grass.
You've never called him a grass
and you've never called him out on being
um beaten at the money game. So don't,
like I said, you just can't moan about
these people if they ever want to
antagonize you again. You can't moan
about them. You can't moan about these people.
I don't think I've seen you call any of
these people grasses.
No, I don't think you you have. And I
don't think No, I don't think you have.
I've never seen you call him a grass, mate.
He's a [ __ ] idiot. You know, he went
on my hangouts today arguing with me
with his real voice.
He's just [ __ ] the whole thing up. You
do realize that?
They don't even take him serious anymore, bro.
He [ __ ] the whole thing up, bro. I
can't track this food. I'm starving, bro.
Oh, I'm starving. [ __ ] hungry, lad.
But no, they haven't flaked off,
Stephen. I've been speaking to them for
ages, bro. They seem all right. But yeah,
I can't put a tracker. There's no
tracker on this one. Why?
I don't [ __ ] know why. Yeah.
Yeah. Maybe, bro. No, they don't flake.
They don't, bro. They sent me like They
sent me like 23 messages at 2 in the
morning, bro. I don't think so, bro.
And you didn't say anything about that V
being racist. That V was actually being
You don't say anything about him. But yeah.
Yeah. That B. He's that bro. He's a typical.
He's a typical keyboard warrior.
Yeah, he's a typical keyboard warrior,
bro. He is.
He's a typical keyboard warrior.
Why don't we all go for a curry? Us
three. Hey, Greavvesy.
Me, Smokey B, Elie, we can all have a
nice spot of lunch.
Isn't that right, Alie? You be a good little fellow.
Or could you be a good little fellow in public?
You could all go for a nice toy.
What do you think about that, Grezy? Us
three going for a curry. Go on, be a good fellow.
Yeah, he he does it to me and Monty as
well. I don't give a [ __ ] about Bonnie
anyways. He was talking [ __ ] bro. But
I'm He was talking [ __ ] all day yesterday.
Does this guy not understand that? I
could have had Natalie G when she was
more in her prime. I could have had
Natalie G when she was more in her
prime, but I don't want that [ __ ]
I don't want that [ __ ] bro.
I literally don't want that [ __ ] How
he thinks that I'm I can't say I can't
say anyone's jealous because to be
honest some of the people on here might
be jealous cuz they can't get anything
but like bro I don't need to care about
the handy bro. Especially when you've
already bro I've already rejected the [ __ ] [ __ ]
Like that's someone you'd only like I'm
not going to lie. Like I was saying
earlier, if I was 50 Guinnesses in 50
and it kept coming on to me, then yeah,
maybe they give me a lo, bro. See you.
But you know, you know this the wolf
Sarah, bro, you could never get with
that, bro. Ever. Doesn't matter how damn
bad you are. Doesn't matter how damn bad
you are, bro. There are certain things,
bro, where you could just like accept a
[ __ ] if you was out your head drunk.
But not even that, bro.
You [ __ ] stinking, bro.
And you know the thing is with this
Monty as well, you do realize he's only
been with like two people.
Haley and Natalie, bro. They're both
like he's only been with two people and
they were both stinking like and he do
you know what he's talking about getting
laid and I swear this guy's 36.
This guy is 36, bro. And he's talking
about let getting laid. He sounds like a
[ __ ] He sounds like a teenager, bro.
Just like someone else we know. Hey, Dusty.
And then he was calling me ugly. I was
like, "Bro, you're you're calling me
ugly. This guy is calling me ugly. He
started bringing me up for no reason."
I said to my mother, "This guy this guy
doesn't keep my name out of his [ __ ] mouth." Yeah,
I'm going to end up having to say
something, bro. I'm sure Greg would like
that in it. I was going to join, bro.
Like, but I didn't want to go on it
yesterday cuz I was speaking to someone
and that I don't want to be put in a bad mood.
You know what this modding man needs to
understand, bro? I helped him and he was
literally [ __ ] and he's slagging me
off. I don't even talk about the guy. I
went all the way to Birmingham. Yeah, I
bailed the [ __ ] out with food and drink
and he's coming and talking [ __ ]
You know that. You know how mad that is
if you think about it. Like the guy was skin [ __ ]
Yeah. And then it's not even like I'm I
don't even talk about him and then he's
slagging me off. I don't even talk about the [ __ ]
He's an idiot, bro. He's an idiot.
People don't think, you know, people
just don't think
when before they say stuff. Do you know
what I'm saying? They just don't think
before they say stuff. I just ordered one.
Think about it, bro. Without me, he
would have been [ __ ]
When I thought this person was ghosting
me the other day, I was getting scared,
bro. I was getting scared, man. I didn't
have anyone to like, well, there's no
one I would talk to about it, bro,
because it's embarrassing, isn't it?
Can't even really say anything. The guy
slags me off, bro. He's a [ __ ] big
snake, bro. He's a big snake. Big
[ __ ] big snake, bro.
He's a snake, bro.
Where is it? [ __ ] food.
Yeah, I know, bro. I need to go. I need
to try that Carolina Reaper. Carolina
Reaper burger again.
Yeah, I need to try that Reaper burger again, bro.
I think LT is going to fancy that Autumn
Rose, you know.
What do you think? You seeing her?
bloody like her.
Is she Is she a bit of you, man? Is she
a bit of you?
No, she's obsessed with me, bro. [ __ ]
posting about me and all sorts, bro.
[ __ ] off, man.
That LJ was trying to be me the other
day. Going to these clubs, but he could
never be me, bro. He could never be me.
Could never ever be me, bro.
Oh, that should be me, [ __ ]
There we go.
I [ __ ] hate this cold, man. [ __ ]
>> What's up, bro? Are you good, man? Yeah.
>> Yeah. Thanks.
>> What's your obsession over her and why
do you badly want? I don't have an obsession.
>> I don't have an obsession with that
[ __ ] [ __ ] bro. That's That's Lord.
They have an obsession.
He went to this over 30s club the other
day. Yeah. He went to this over 30s club
the other day. Yeah.
Didn't get anyone's number and then he
comes back to begging women on YouTube.
That is a madness, bro. That's a
madness. That guy is so He's such a He's
such a stupid idiot, bro. No.
No. He is a No, but Log is a s.
Scream the word s. No, but he actually
is a s. No, no, no, no, no. But he
actually is a s, bro.
You're going to a club, bro, where the
weight where and then you're and then
you're begging the women on the Doesn't
make sense, bro.
That doesn't make sense.
They don't make sense. [ __ ] idiot, bro.
There we go.
Oh, got two. Lovely. >> Yeah,
it doesn't look too bad to be fair.
They never look as good when you order them, but Yeah.
Yeah. One second.
Oh, I love window, man.
I could eat this every day in the winter, bro.
That's what you need.
That's what you need. LG, mate. B.
I got some Coke.
Yeah, I need to go on a plate to be fair.
So, what are you are you two going to
meet up then?
Smokey B and LG are you going to meet up? Yeah.
Yeah, I wash up anyway. But
I think we all know a certain person
that wouldn't there.
that wouldn't there, lad.
We won't get into that though, will we?
Not not mention any names, but
Yep. Sure there is.
Bro, this Do you remember when when [ __ ]
Lord J was having that power when it
defeated him. Bro, this can't defeat me.
The only thing that defeated me is that
Carolina Reaper burger, bro.
That Carolina Reaper burger was was
something else, bro.
What do you think, Greg? Do you think
there's a certain person that can have this?
I definitely think so.
Where's Triple H gone?
Nah, it can't be worse than that.
No, I don't see him anywhere though. I
don't see him anywhere.
I don't see him anywhere that like anywhere.
Well, that's how Reaper Burger was.
She said she was good looking to fit in. Groovy.
That's what chat GBT said.
That's what chat GBT said, isn't it? Not really. Boom.
Oh, this car is really nice. Wish I
could share it. Have you noticed haven't
had a drop of drink since the last one? music. Oh,
not even breaking.
Nah, bro. It's easy.
Yeah, bro. It's easy, man.
I've been eating curry since I come out
theical. Since I got removed from theical greasy, you know,
since I got removed, since I got chopped
off lately forward to me, I've been
having this. How cute is that?
Ly would never eat a vigil.
Lady would never eat a vigil. Too hot for lady.
She has what the virgin has. A ka.
Yeah. does what the virgin does.
Christian Izzy likes Kobe as well.
Yeah, he likes as well. Yeah.
How cute is that?
See you later.
Never had call, mate. I'm a man. I'm a
big strong Turkish man
that can pull American [ __ ] and have
hot curries. Isn't that right, Rosie? Where's L2?
Where's Where's L2? Nope.
Up afterwards. I've had a I had a foul
two months ago, right?
Still didn't defeat me. No,
I had one. Um, yeah, two months ago at the restaurant. Yeah.
Yeah. It was on YouTube. Yeah. Well, no.
Look, look where you see.
I'm a man's man.
The right always win as well.
No, I'm not going to make this a [ __ ]
food channel. I don't want to provide
these [ __ ] content. I don't like
most of the people in this community, land.
Most of people. So why I do that? We look
I'm not struggling.
I'm not basing at all. Yep.
Well, maybe if you had your own lives,
you'd have your own content. Is that right? Yeah.
You have your own little content.
Think I'm finished this now. I'm going
to wash the plate now that after my popoms.
Did I make you hungry, Grezy?
That make you hungry, Captain?
Do you actually think I'm gay? Be honest. Huh? All right.
You think I'm gay?
You think I'm gay? Cuz
leg was gay. Why would he say that movie?
Why does he lie so much? It makes him
look like such a dick.
He always lies.
Backing me off, is he? One second, captains. Oh, yeah.
Yeah. One second. I'll join in a minute.
One second. One sec, man. One sec. I
just have a Yeah.
Yeah. He keeps offering people out to
come to Birmingham, bro. Come to He
keeps offering people to come to B. Tell
him to come to London then. Yeah.
One second now.
What's this up with me? Two seconds. Captain,
you want to do? Yeah, cuz it's good,
bro. Keep my name out your [ __ ]
stupid mouth. It's as simple as that.
Are you going to Are you looking forward
to this, Squeezy? You've been looking
forward to this, haven't you?
You haven't seen it now. What's it?
Uh, it's Monty Man and Natalie.
That's his channel. Monty man and
Natalie. Yeah. One second, bro. Telegram coming now.
You're mentioning my name, bro. So, you
know, if you got something to say, you
can come and [ __ ] You know what I mean?
No, I agree with you, man. You're a good guy.
Right. Let me join now. One second.
Yeah, bro. He kicked me.
He kicked me, bro.
Yeah, he kicked me, bro.
Yeah, he kicked me. [ __ ] idiot.
That was me.
Moo. Mama. That's me.
Well, that was me. What the [ __ ] Why
did you kick me?
You couldn't hear me. One sec.
ended it. He ended it. He ended it.
He ended it. He ended it. He ended it.
Cuz he knows what I'm saying, bro. It's
It's true, bro. Don't talk my [ __ ] name, bro.
Don't talk my name, bro. If you want to
argue with LJ, you argue with LJ, I
don't care. Keep my name out your [ __ ]
So he didn't answer me. We
Why would Why would Why would thingy Why
did he Why was he saying I was gay then, Dusty?
Why was Nons saying I was gay?
I'm not gay, Dusty. Why was he saying I was gay?
I'm not there.
Why would you say that, bro?
No. Why was Nex calling me gay?
Why was Why was Why was Nes calling me Gabby?
And I'll ask you a Let me ask you a
question after this then since that's
what what what you want to say. Yeah. So
do you not think we do that? Like
there's more chance of people like Red
Star and that being gay.
coming online every day stalking a man
from the time they wake up to the time
they go to bed. Do you not think that
maybe they've got more of a chance of
being gay than me?
No, I didn't offer Monty anything.
That's made up. That's [ __ ] and
that's made up.
No, no, no, no, no. That's literally
made up, bro. That's literally made up.
Right. Do you want to know the actual
story? Yeah, Grezy. Right. We went back
to where we were staying. I had to climb
over cuz the the cameras
cuz there was no one allowed in. So, I
had to climb over
the fence. We went back. Yeah. And he
was like, "Oh, yeah. Um, we should get
an escort. We should get an escort." And
obviously, I didn't have the money cuz I
I um remember what happened when I
picked the wrong bank card. My sister
literally had to give me £150, bro. And
had to pay it back when I got back cuz I
took the I took the wrong bank card. You
remember? And he's like, "Oh." But I
said, "I can't do it. I can't do it."
So, no one offered him a [ __ ]
[ __ ] He's a lying bastard.
Tell him to swear on everyone he knows
life. He can't do it. He's a liar. He's a bullshitter.
He's an absolute bullshitter, bro. The [ __ ]
He's a bullshitter, bro. Proper bullshitter. Cuz
when I went to Birmingham, I I brought
the wrong card by accident and I had to
my sister had to give me 150 cuz my
other card was at home and well I
couldn't access it. So
So I had 150.
So no, bro. He's he's a [ __ ] idiot, man.
Well, there's no signs that suggest I'm
gay. I mean, I don't stalk men on
YouTube every day. When I go out, I
speak to women. All the people I speak
to on my WhatsApp are women. So, I mean,
there's no signs that I'm gay, but
there's signs that these people are
severely gay. Like Jamie Thompson, Red
Star, they are definitely gay.
I mean, I don't know, bro. There's no
signs that I'm gay, but there's signs
that they're gay. Definitely.
Definitely gay. When I start stalking
men on YouTube 247 every day, Greavvesy,
I'll start questioning my sexuality.
That's when I really start thinking,
"Yeah, I might be gay, bro."
That's why um Monty Man started saying
what I was saying cuz he's copying.
When I start acting like one of these on
here, then I'll start thinking, "Yeah,
yeah, I might be gay, bro."
But until then, nah.
Like I said, the way I see this, uh,
Dusty, is that you would not st You
would not Okay, put it this way, Dusty.
Yeah, this is what I've always said, and
I'll say this to the day I die. You
wouldn't stalk women the way these
people stalk men. Like, you know what
Red Star does in this Jamie Thompson?
You wouldn't do that to a woman every
day for 4 years, let alone another man.
Do you understand? So, when you actually
see it like that, oh yeah, they're gay.
They they've got to be gay. And when and
when I said that, Monty man started
copying me because he knows I'm right.
Because if you are speaking to a woman,
right? Say you've actually got someone
in your life and you're speaking to
someone and you're generally not gay.
You wouldn't come on here recording stuff 24/7.
That's gay, bro. That is homosexual
[ __ ] Literally that red star. He's a
closeted gay, Joe. He's a closeted gay.
They hate that they're gay.
That's why they write in capitals when I
say it because what I'm saying is
correct. It's the truth.
They've got channels dedicated to
another man. That's [ __ ] [ __ ] It's gay. It's gayness.
And the curry was very [ __ ] nice.
Yeah. What's up? Why don't Steven jump
on my panel and have it out? Why am I am
I lying Steven about this Jamie Thompson
and this Joe F? I'm not lying, bro. They
are gay and jealous.
I've never wanted someone's ass as much
as they want my ass, bro. In almost 29
years of me on this planet, I've never known people
want another man's ass so much.
I've never known it in my life, bro.
Never in my life.
They're gay, bro. They're homos.
No, they are gay, bro.
Maybe you don't fully understand what
I'm saying, but yeah. Yeah.
If he was bisexual, I would be with a
man right now, wouldn't I? If I was
bisexual or gay, wouldn't I be with a
man right now? cuz people
people will um eventually
will get with someone if they're gay or
they're by now. Like Timmy, he's
bisexual. He's kissed a man.
We've seen him kiss a man.
Nope. That's not true at all.
Not at all. At all.
Yeah, they are definitely gay, bro.
They're definitely gay on here.
I think they're jealous and they're gay.
I think it's three things. I think it's
I think they're jealous. I think they
want your ass.
And they hate their lives.
You could not pay me. Okay, put it this way.
See, Red Star, you know what I'm saying
about you is the truth. That's why
you're going all mad. Okay. Okay. Put
put it this way, Stephen Howard. Say,
say somebody says to me right now. Yeah.
Okay. Let's use this analogy. Yeah.
Someone says to me, "Okay, we're going
to give you £20,000."
Just listen to me, bro. Yeah. We're
going to give you £20,000, but you have
to come on YouTube every day and stalk
men. I tell them to [ __ ] off. Now, these
people are doing it every day for free.
They're gay. They're gay jealous homosexuals.
Do you understand the point I'm trying
to make? Even if someone offered me 20
grand to come on here all day, every day
recording stuff and being a loser, I
wouldn't do it. I literally wouldn't do
it cuz I've got a life to live. I've got
things to be doing, things to be people
to be talking to, and people to be seeing.
Do you understand? That's what separates
me and the people that ain't got a life.
You get it?
Tell me I'm lying, bro. I feel like a
lot of people in this community don't
have the mental capacity to understand
what I'm saying.
It's And the And the maddest thing is G
uh Steven Howard is that they
they um they don't even know you.
That's what makes it so so so weird is
that they don't even know you. Do you
understand? They like they've never met
you. They don't know you. Do you understand?
Very very weird community, bro. Tell me
what am I am I lying though, Steven? Am I lying?
If they can do this every day for for
years, stalking men all day every day,
there's got to be something wrong with them, though.
There've got to be something seriously
wrong with them. It's like Reddit mods.
They they they mod Reddit for free.
What? For free, bro. You going to pay for it?
Uh definitely homosexuals.
Definitely homos. Yeah,
they are, bro. Definitely. You would you
would you couldn't even pay me to have a
channel dedicated to another man.
You couldn't pay me, bro.
You um you couldn't pay me, bro. Yeah,
but it's not just him, though, is it,
bro? It's nons legs. It's Red Star.
There's there's a few of them, bro.
People would just live their life if
they were better than you, bro. I'm sick
of repeating this, bro, but I haven't
said this in ages, but they would
generally just live their life. Why do
you think I don't come on? I'm too busy
stalking I'm stalking I'm too busy
talking to this um
to this Christian Izzy, bro. I don't
have time for these weirdos and I
definitely don't have time to stalk another man.
Maybe I'm the only one that thinks this
way, bro. Maybe. But I just to me if
someone's got a better life than you,
they wouldn't be doing they wouldn't
live to [ __ ] with people every day. What?
No, talking. I meant talking. See,
they're making me lose my mind now. So,
then I was thinking, Dusty. Yeah. So,
you've got this woman you speak to every
day. Yeah. So, you don't need to be on
here. So, if they had someone to talk to
every day and they weren't gay, they
would literally leave you alone. They
would literally not bother with you.
Literally, they wouldn't bother with you, bro.
They really wouldn't bother with you.
Yeah, they literally wouldn't bother with you.
>> Yeah, I haven't been I haven't been on
YouTube for nine days, Mike. I've got
I've got stuff to do, people to be
talking to, bro.
I can't I can't be on here, bro, with
these. We're just talking about how like
these people are proper gay and that on this community.
Got no life and that, bro.
stalking men every day. Bro,
I just don't I would You know what, bro?
I actually would love to understand if
it's not like, bro, like, let's just
have it out cuz I won't be on YouTube
for a while after today. Anyways, I want
to know like if you're not gay and
you're not jealous, why do you do it every day?
No. No. I want to know, bro. Like,
you're better than people. You've got
more money than them. You're not gay.
So, why would you waste your life on
YouTube stalking other men? I just want
to understand. I'm trying to I'm trying
to um empathize, you know? I I don't get it,
I mean, are they are they are they being
paid a million pounds? I don't think so.
And I'd love to know why they do it.
It's really weird.
It is very, very, very weird.
If they're not gay and they're not jealous.
Yeah. Don't believe it because it's [ __ ]
I can tell you the story, bro. I went to
Birmingham. Yeah. I lost my card. So my
sister had to give me £150. I brought
the wrong card. So my sister had to give
me £150. Lucky as [ __ ] she was awake
otherwise I would have been [ __ ] So I
said, "Oh, give me 150." We went on a
drink. I done some approaching. Went
back to his. He wanted an escort. told
him I didn't have money for the escort
and yeah, nothing no [ __ ] was
mentioned, bro. What's he all about?
He's a [ __ ]
He is an absolute [ __ ] And why didn't
he say that? If that was the truth, bro,
he would have said that as soon as I
went back to London. Think about it. He
would have been saying that
before I went back to He would have been
saying that before we had beef. He's a
liar, bro. He's a stinking liar. He went
live today. Yeah. He didn't even let me
in. Told him to keep my name out of his [ __ ] mouth.
Yeah, I told him, bro. [ __ ] what? I
was seeing some of his [ __ ] yesterday.
Keep my name out your [ __ ] mouth. Simple.
Stupid idiot, bro. He would never come
for me like he did Rice, bro. Never.
You get uppercuted straight in his chin.
It would never happen, bro. Never.
He might be stupid, bro, but he's not that stupid,
you know? Yeah, he might be strong by
the hands, bro. Like squeezing, but not
in a fight.
Trust me, bro. Trust me.
That's why he didn't let me in. Cuz he
knows I'm right. Cuz I tell him
everything about Natalie G and I said,
"You want to start calling people ugly?"
Really, bro? Come on. Why do a panel if
you're not going to let people in? I'm
not slagging you off talking about me. Yeah. So, yeah.
Don't understand how these people can
have jobs when they're sat on YouTube 24/7 stalking men.
Let's get the truth today, Grezy. Why
not, bro? It's a lovely Monday. It's
just past4 to 8.
Let's Let's try to understand why these
people do this.
If they're not jealous and they're not gay,
like I said, are you being paid a
million pounds to do it or what?
Cuz no one could make me stalk men every
day on YouTube.
No one could make me I don't care what
they've done and I don't care what
they've said. I don't give a [ __ ] I
couldn't sit there recording men on
YouTube every day, bro. It's gay. It's [ __ ] weird.
Does anyone agree? Does anyone disagree?
What's people's thoughts on it? Come on.
Let's have it out, bro.
Come on. I think you're jealous and I
think you're gay. Simple as that.
Because you know it deep down. What else
What else will it be?
Yeah. No, bro. I just want I just want
answers to be fair.
They literally, you tell me one person
living their best life that could sit on
YouTube waiting for men every day to stalk.
I just want I just want the answers,
bro. I just want the answers, bro. Like,
I really I would love to know the answers.
Cuz you say I'm always think I'm right,
but I'd be happy to be wrong, bro.
It's just so gay.
It honestly is so gay. And you also you
you know what it is as well when you
when you when you put yourself in their
shoes. When you put yourself in their shoes,
you just know that they've got no
they've got no life because they
wouldn't do it. Bro, it's very Do you
not understand how abnormal it is?
Because a lot of the people in this
community are not normal. They might not
say, but do you not understand how
abnormal it is?
I don't know, bro. Maybe it's just me.
No one's going to get blocked for
disagreeing, but just give your opinion.
I I don't I don't want people I just
want people's opinions, you know? You know,
cuz to me, my life is precious. My time
is precious. That Yeah. Okay. I had that
thing with nons legs today, but that's
it, bro. For a very, very long time, if
ever again. Because my life and my time
is precious because what I say about
them is the truth. What they say about
me can't be the truth if they're willing
to sit on here every day doing what
they're doing. Tell me I'm wrong. Come
on, bro. There's 28 people watching. Come on.
They're better than you. They've got
more money than you. They've got a
better life than you. Fine. So wouldn't
they be out living their life as opposed
to giving someone like me their time
every day? Think about it, bro. You need
to put You need to play devil advocate,
devil's advocate here. Do you understand, Grezy?
Me, if I'm better than someone, I don't
I don't interact with them. I go and I
live my life and talk to other people.
But they do the complete opposite.
Do you understand the problem with that?
>> That is so weird, bro.
Or the other the other thing could be
Steven Alward is they're disabled like a [ __ ]
They could just be like disabled so they
can't do anything but do this. I mean
that would explain a lot as well.
I don't know. They're weird is it?
I think they hate the fact Yeah. Do you
know what I think as well? I think they
hate the fact that you're better looking
than them. You're younger than them.
you've got more about you than them. You
can go out, you can meet new people.
That's what I think as well. Steven Howard,
I also think that's the jealousy part.
And then also they're gay as well. Yeah.
Yeah. But we're not talking about the
arguing. We're talking about the people
that are sat on here stalking people
every day, lad.
We're not talking about the people that are arguing.
We're talking about the people that are
sat on here from the time they wake up
to the time they go to bed stalking people
of other platforms.
>> What do you think of it, Rory? Why do
you think they do it?
No, I'm not listening to Timmy, bro.
He's a [ __ ] [ __ ]
>> That's what I'm saying. I can't even
speak to Timmy. You just lose brain
cells. It's the same [ __ ] with him. Oh,
you're a virgin. Y bro, I can't be
annoyed with listening to it, bro. He's
a [ __ ] He's a [ __ ] [ __ ]
Nah, he's a [ __ ] He's a [ __ ]
bro. I can't listen to him. I want
someone that could actually have like a
good debate, that could actually talk,
you know? Do you remember that time
people was coming in talking about like
the debate? We were having debates and
stuffy about the double standards.
That's the kind of debates that I want.
That's the kind of people I want joining.
People that can actually have a conversation.
No, he's a [ __ ] He's a [ __ ]
[ __ ] bro. There's no point letting a
[ __ ] [ __ ] up.
He's a [ __ ] He's a [ __ ] bro. He
just gives you a [ __ ] headache.
I'm not letting that [ __ ] up, bro.
You know what is so weird about these
these and then I don't know why Timmy,
right? This is how you know you never
win with these people. Greasy, I don't
care. Is that you get Timmy that's still
calling me a virgin and I don't care.
But listen to me, bro. I don't care cuz
I know he's the virgin and I'm not. And
it's like I got someone's I got three
channels banned for pornography that I
put up. So think about it. Think about
it, bro. It just shows you you will
never you're never going to win with
these people no matter what you show
them. And I don't care what they say cuz
it's self- projecting. It doesn't wind
me up. I'm just saying, bro, who wants
to hear the same repeating stuff every
day? It's boring. Not triggering.
Boring. There's a big difference. Don't
get confused. And it's like, bro, you
you show you put your [ __ ] dick up a
[ __ ] woman, Greasy, and they and
they're still calling you virgins in 2026.
Come on, bro.
This is 2026.
I want someone on here that can actually
have a good debate. Someone that could
actually have a chat.
That would be great content. [ __ ] madness.
No, I'm not letting him up, bro.
He's a [ __ ] bro. He's a [ __ ]
So Greavvesy, why did why did Nons legs
call me gay then?
Why didn't he say if I don't like
someone I'm gay? I think you said it
earlier, but I forgot.
Yeah, that was a thing on chat GBT. It
wasn't bullying. They used to tease
people, didn't they? If they fought another way.
H and that Canada goose trend needs to
stop. It's so boring. The next time I
see someone with a Canada goose code
grieves, I'm going to go up to them and
be like meow.
I'm going to go up to them and be like
and I'm going to record it. You little copycat.
That's what I'll do. Yeah.
[ __ ] boring, bro. People that have
got no mind of their own are boring as
[ __ ] No, they're boring, bro. People
like that are boring.
Life's all about being unique, isn't it? E.
Well, what was Timmy being earlier, Greavvesy?
No, he said that if I didn't if I didn't
find Sherco attractive, I was gay.
That's what he said.
I don't find her attractive. I think
she's [ __ ] ugly. And apparently that
made me gay. Interesting.
Gay. I'm gay. That make that makes someone gay. Interesting.
Why did you say that? Steven Howard.
No, it's not funny, bro.
I don't think it's funny, bro. I think
it's just copying.
What do you think, Grezy?
In before you're gay. They already knew
what was coming in it.
They already knew what was coming.
Grievy in before you're gay. They knew
it in it straight away. Everyone knows
that copycat trend. That was going for years, bro.
Someone must have started it. Greasy.
Someone must have [ __ ] started it.
Yeah, someone must have started it, bro.
What do you think,
Vezy? Someone must have started it now.
Yeah. Yeah, I blame the X Factor as
well. Nothing to write home about.
There was literally nothing to write
home about at all. Um but they seem to
love I don't know back in the day they
seem to love um putting pedestals on
these average looking celebrities. I I
don't know why.
Yeah. It's weird.
But did you actually hear arguments
where people didn't agree and then they
get they got called gay? Greavves. Yeah.
Did you actually hear it or you just
chatting [ __ ] I did hear it, bro. They
they mentioned it on the Inbetweeners
and obviously Virgin Boy.
That means someone's gay.
Yeah. Yeah. Well,
yeah. It's just copying, bro.
Same as Justin Bieber. Same as Justin
Bieber, bro. Same as Justin Bieber.
The Justin Bieber one was [ __ ] bad,
bro. In 2011, 2012. All the girls used
to copy each other, didn't they?
Yeah, they used to copy each other
and you know it's copying as well
because if the if the people are not
famous, no one cares.
Nope. I'm done with gambling, bro. When
I say something, I mean it.
Unless you count£10 a week on the
football as gambling, then no, I don't gamble.
Do she seems really nice, you know,
Christian is he?
She seems really nice.
I said to her, I want to buy her some Ugg boots.
Greasy. Some UGG boots like I bought my mom.
How cute is that?
Yeah, that's really cute, isn't it?
I really did think she was going to [ __ ]
me over the other day, though, bro.
But then I thought,
nah, she's invested too much.
I don't think so, bro.
I would have cried the other day if I
got ghosted grieving. I would have I
would have I would have cried.
No, I'm joking. I would have cried. I
would have been pissed off, though.
Wouldn't you be pissed off? Don't like
being ghosted, bro. I don't like
speaking to people for ages and get
ghosted. [ __ ] that. Don't like being ghosted, bro.
I already found my mama grievy
cuz he's already found his mama.
Because he's already found his mama.
So, do you reckon if I put a picture up,
just a picture? Do you reckon they'd be
able to find them with just a picture?
Nah, but I wouldn't do it anyways. I
would never show anyone people I meet,
bro. Never. Never. Ever. Ever. Ever.
What you think they could find her from this picture?
That's why they would never ever ever
know what she looks like. Ever. None of
these people would ever know nothing. Never. Bro,
that LJ is obsessed with Autumn Rose.
You know, bro, she's obsessed with me.
All her community posts are about me.
Sorry, you're not my cuppper.
You're not my cuppper. Cup of tea. Yeah.
Yeah, I saw it.
I can't put her pictures up on that,
bro. Cuz we got a virgin on here that
likes to um who likes to stalk women.
Virgin legs. He's very jealous when
women um give me attention. Was giving
me attention. He was going [ __ ] mad.
He's such a jealous bastard when it
comes to women, bro.
me and women, bro. He's such a jealous bastard.
I've never known someone so jealous of
um getting attention from women.
Have you seen the channel, bro? So weird. Yeah.
Yeah. I saw it, bro. I saw it.
Yeah. It's okay if they find her after a
year, isn't it, Grezy? If you're dating
someone for a year and then these people
found her, then it wouldn't matter. It
wouldn't matter, would it?
Because where they know you so much, I
don't think they would just leave you
for things that you've said. Do you get
me? Nah, I don't think so. If you're
with someone, say you was with someone
for 6 months, a year. Yeah. And these
people found out who she was, then
they would they would have met you so
many times that I don't think they would. No.
You It makes sense, isn't it? You just
don't want them to find out before or if
you've just met them. Do you get me? Yeah, man.
Did you get me, bro?
I miss Trip H's little voice. Gives
Greavves. I can't believe you said that.
That is so gay.
You miss his little voice.
Nope. I don't go out much anymore, bro.
I'm stacking money. Nah,
I'm stacking money, matey.
That's the last takeaway now for a while.
There is no look alike I can find of her.
Is that cute? She was messaging me at
2:00 in the morning. Um, Greavvesy,
so cute, isn't it?
I was trying to laugh about it, bro, but
I was actually [ __ ] myself when I
thought I was getting ghosted. I was
messaging my friends Greavvesy saying,
"You find the dating game funny, isn't
it?" The dating game makes you smile, isn't it?
The dating game makes you smile.
The dating game's funny, ain't it? Nah.
Got to be out again. I don't know.
I don't really go out much anymore.
It's only cuz that guy was pissing me
off. Some guy owed me money and that in
it and he was being so long about giving it back. Uh,
I hate people, you know. I really hate people.
I hate relying on people. I hate I just
hate the way people are, bro.
If I was a billionaire, bro, I'd live in
an island with a dog with no one there.
Be lovely, bro. Just a little Frenchie.
with me. Christian, Izzy, a little
Frenchie. That's it, bro. Lush. What
more could you need, you know? Yeah.
I would literally do what Richard
Branson does, bro. I'm not even joking.
No, I actually would, bro. I hate people.
That [ __ ] tenant pissed me the [ __ ] off, bro.
You you know what I mean though greedy
about people in it?
I don't know soon, bro.
Cuz this guy was he owes me he owed me
money and that in it and he was being a
[ __ ] about it.
It's a long story, bro. But yeah,
that's why I hate people, bro. I don't like people.
You agree with me though, Greavesy? Really?
Yeah. Little puppy.
My friend in Amsterdam, he's got a he's
got a dalmatation.
Breie. He's got a dalmatation.
What was them army [ __ ] doing? Greavvesy. Yeah.
Do you hate people, Stephen Howard?
Yeah. The the the the army the army lads
haven't been going to the pub for a
while. The bouncer told me the other
day, Stephen Hour, that the the army
lads ain't been going for a while. I
think they're on a mission. So, if I'm
not on here for a while, Grezy, you know
I'm on a mission, right?
I'm a man on a mission.
I'm a man on a mission. Yeah, they ain't
been coming for a while. I was dead, bro.
They been coming for a while.
Do you remember Greavvesy the Indonesian fella?
You remember the Indonesian fella?
The Indonesian fella.
That guy used to say all the time. Is it?
One sec. I need to brush my lashes. Lovely. Dust.
Sorry, I was brushing my [ __ ] teeth.
Right with you, C.
I need to cut back on the co. I'm
drinking a lot of it again and it's bad for you.
Don't want any more cavities.
I was angry with you. I don't want any
more cavities, lad.
Oh, [ __ ] hell.
Yeah, they can find people with him at
church, can't they? Yeah, they can. Oh,
lush, lush, lush. Oh.
Oh gosh. Grezy.
I'm in my little nestle. Squeezy.
You still there? Steve
Money was telling you to [ __ ] Yes, matey.
You want to hear a story about this
tenant? Um, Steven Howard,
I told Grezy, but you wasn't on here. Do
you want to hear the story? This is what
people are like.
I hate people. I hate people.
Why couldn't the world just be full of dogs, lad?
You want to hear the story, lad?
So I was in a cinema.
What was it? Day before yesterday. I
watched this film. Tenant messaged me
and he was saying he was asking me to
lend him £50.
I basically turned around and said, "Why
don't you know like the ex tenant?" I
said, "Why don't you know anyone else
that can lend you at r?" I said, "Why
didn't you ask this guy?" He said, "Oh,
we already asked him." And he said,
"That's the reason white guys die
alone." So, obviously, I didn't read it
properly. I didn't read it properly
until I got back cuz I I said, "Listen,
yeah, bro. I don't know what white guys
you're talking about, but I'd rather be
a white guy and die die alone than be a thie Pakistani."
Um because I mean, like, you stole my
after shave and you stole my t-shirt.
So, I'd rather be some white guy that
died alone and be a thieving Pakistani
Muslim. That's what I said to him. said
a voice note and he's like, "Oh, you
know, £50 is nothing." I didn't even
remember any money. I said, "If£50 is"
And it's like, "If£50 is nothing, why
are you asking me for 50?
Don't ask me for money. Stop looking at
me for money." It got p It was getting
annoying that people would look at me for money.
It was It gets annoying, bro, when you
got somebody from a who's part of a big
community asking you for £50. I did take
offense to it. Yeah. Then he was like, I
said, "If£50, bro, £50 is nothing. £50
is a lot of money to you, mate. You used
to have 5080 last you
a month and you're trying to tell me £50
is nothing." And I said, "What if if
white guys are this? Why are you asking
the white guy for money? That must say a
lot about the people from your religion
then." Then he says, "Oh, I earn 3K a
month. I I live in a big room alone and
I pay 620 in rent and you think I'm
playing with you for £50. Grow up." I
said, "If you got all of that money,
which you don't, why are you asking me for £50?"
And what he was doing, he was trying to
get money off of me so he could give to
the other tenant who claimed that I owed
them money. Do you get it? Okay. It was
so obvious. It was so obvious, bro. It
was so so so obvious. Cuz if you're
getting over three grand a month, bro,
you must be doing heroin to to be asking
someone for I've been on the same money
for months and I ain't run out of money.
I haven't borrow had to borrow money
from anyone. It just doesn't happen,
bro. It just doesn't happen. You know,
if you're paying rent, you have two and
a half grand left. Why you asking for £50?
So, what I think he was going to do is
he was going to give it to the other people.
So, yeah, I'm not stupid, bro. I was
born on a day and it weren't yesterday.
Ant-Man's a bit different, bro. Antman's
a bit different. Antman doesn't know
anyone. He He's in a different country.
Do you understand?
When someone from Pakistan is asking you
for money, bro, the first thing you're
thinking is why is no one Why do they
not know anyone that can give them £50?
Isn't that Isn't that the first thing
you'd be wondering? Greavesy, think
about it. They know all of these people.
Trust me, they do. Pakistani people know
a lot of people. Why are they asking you for £50?
Think about it, bro.
It's not like it's your sister or you
know what I'm saying. Why are they
asking you for £50?
That was the first red flag.
And it's not even that grievy that
everyone is is like family to them. [ __ ]
with Pakistani people they become very
close. Yeah. They they're a close
community, bro. Like they put it this
way. Yeah. I know about the religion and
stuff and I've been taught about it.
Yeah. I've been in a mosque. They will
literally help. If somebody had nowhere
to go, they would take them in and look
after them. They look after their
people. a lot like white people. They
don't look after each other. They would
help them, bro. Trust me, they would.
So, don't. I said, "Don't look at" and I
was getting annoyed. I was like, "I've
got Ant-Man looking at me for money and
I've got him looking at me for money. [ __ ] off."
But with Ant-Man, it's a bit different
because he does pay me back and he
doesn't know anyone. It just got
annoying with him. I was like, "People
need to learn to manage their money
better, bro." When was the last time I
had to borrow money off someone?
I never did. I don't think
Even back when I was maybe had no money
last year, maybe the one I still never
asked anyone for money.
Like if you can't manage your money,
that's your problem.
You know what I'm saying, bro? I just
hate people that look at me. It's annoy.
It does get annoying, bro. Don't look at
me for money, bro.
I need to do stuff. I need to save. I
need to move on with my life and that,
bro. You [ __ ] know what I'm saying?
No. What do you think about this 10-in situation, Dusty?
>> Yeah, but bro, he it's his own fault,
bro. Like, at the end of the day, yeah,
he can manage his money better. Like,
bro, like at the end of the day, bro, he
might get 6700 pound a month, but that's
worth a lot more out there than he needs
to manage his money. But I know when he
asked me, no one else has given it to
him. Whereas this Pakistani guy, he was
trying to have me on, bro. It's too obvious.
But Ant-Man, he doesn't know anyone that
will. Trust me, bro. Like I And he
always gives it back as well. But he
need at the same time, he needs to
manage his money better.
But that guy, it's so obvious what he
was trying to do. Trying to tell me you
get three grand a month, brother. I've
lived with you. I know how much money
you get and I know how much money you
had. Stop playing games.
And this is why people don't like
Pakistani people. This is why people are
racist. There's racist people out there.
It's because that's the reason, you know,
that's the reason why people don't like
they they come here and then they start
thinking that we're dumb like them. They
start thinking that we're dumb. They
think can come they think they can come
to someone's land. Yeah. Someone's
territory and scam them. How does that
even make sense, bro? So,
don't get no three and a half grand a month, bro.
Why do people love playing games with people?
And then this guy owes me money as well.
It's mad, bro. That's why I hate people.
At least when At least when they took
the house dusty, I never had to deal
with anyone ever again. Feels so good
not having to play games or chase people
for money. Oh, it's so good. It's so
nice, bro. Yeah, you might get a little
less money, but Oh, [ __ ] well. You
know, that's the fun part about it. So, yeah.
Three and a half grand a month. Yeah,
right, bro. Then he says £50 is nothing.
They used to have £80 to last them a month.
And he's telling me
and he says, "Oh, you need to think and
rethink." I said, "No, you need to
rethink. I don't need to rethink
anything." That's what I said, Greavvesy.
And I and I sent him a voice note on my
mom's phone cuz he blocked me. Never
heard back from him.
Never heard cuz he know he knew what I
was saying was right. Yeah.
And I was going to say to him as well,
bro, if you if you if you wind me up one
more time, I'm going to smash you up
when I see you. If I ever see you again.
Yeah, cuz he he was always scared that I
was going to beat him up. When I said,
"Bro, I'm not going to beat you up." I
tried to get in the house one day, bro.
He was so scared. I said, "Bro, I just
want to get my stuff." He was so scared.
He always worried that I was going to
hit him. I said, "No, but I will hit you
next time. If you message me again and I
see you. If I ever see you, I'm going to
beat you up.
I'll beat him up, bro. Trust me.
What did he eat? Um,
no. I think he used to just eat like frozen food.
50, bro. 50 is something to me. So, to
some What they used to do, what what
they do is they work. No, no. What a lot
of them do, right, is they work and then
they will send money home and have
they'll have like 80 to100 left for a
month. That's how they live.
They would work, get less than they're
supposed to because they're immigrants
until they get a certain thing and then
they will have literally no money. They
would live like that every single month.
And then he's trying to tell me he gets
three grand. Okay, bro. Really?
They live like that every single month.
Every single month.
Work, give money back, have literally
nothing for the rest of the month.
You get me?
Don't [ __ ] try and scam me, bro.
So, what do you reckon would have
happened if you got the £50, Steven? I
think he would have gave it to the other tenant.
That's what I reckon. I reckon that's
exactly what they were doing. I'm
thinking, I'm not being funny, but you
stole my 100 pound after shave.
Uh, and a t-shirt. So, if if unless
until one of you want to own up to who's done it. [ __ ] off.
I reckon that's what they were going to do, bro.
That's what I reckon they were going to do.
I reckon they were going to get that money
and then um yeah, I reckon what what
what do you think we 100%
100%. It was too obvious. It was too
And obviously where I don't know where
they live, I wouldn't be able I wouldn't
have been able to do anything about it. Yeah.
And it never made sense because they
were living in they were living they
live with their overdraft.
Never trust Pakistani people. Never trust them.
Never trust Pakistani people, bro. Never.
And that's not even being racist, bro.
Trust me, I've had my fair dealings with them, bro.
And it's okay for them to be racist,
which he's been, but then no one's
allowed to say anything back.
Pure racism, bro. That's what he is.
Yeah. Peter Belly's not stupid, is he?
Pet is not stupid, bro.
So, is that exactly what you is that do
you actually think that's exactly what
they were going to do?
And you wouldn't be asking for £50 in
the first place either. You'd be asking more like
they just made it so obvious.
They made it so obvious.
That was too obvious. But
Yeah. See, if he said like, "Oh, give me
150 to 100." It would have looked less obvious.
What they would have done is they would
have either gave the 50 to the other guy
or he would have um they would have just
had a party with the 50 and just bought
loads of food.
Maybe he would have gave it back in it,
Steven. I would maybe he would have gave
it back in it. Yeah.
Yeah. They would have gave it back
though. It Stephen Howard. Nah.
And you don't know where they're living
as well. If they lived with you and that
then it would have been different
cuz you know they're going nowhere. Do
you know what I'm saying? But don't try
and mug me off. Don't try and mug me
What's so bad is I didn't even [ __ ] them
over either. To be honest, I could have
literally not even told them that the
thingy were coming. I didn't even [ __ ]
them over and they [ __ ] me over royally, bro.
I didn't even [ __ ] them over. Really
think about it. Never,
never, never, never.
I like girl. I'm not gay.
A little copycat.
You're a little copycat. No.
Wait, when was this?
You doing a football bet on Saturday on
uh well or tomorrow? Tomorrow's Tuesday.
Are you a little copycat, Grezy? Are you
a little cop?
I need a new I just I need this new fold
in July, bro. His phone's almost packed up, Grezy.
I thought it was it was broke the other
day. I was like, "Oh no, how am I going
to speak to Christian Izzy?"
That was That's what I the first thing I
was thinking of. Grievy,
I'm not going to speak to Christian.
I've lost. I don't even
I do like£10 a week on the football and
that's it. I can't be bothered with
gambling anymore, bro.
Can't be bothered with it.
I can't be [ __ ]
Yeah, she's very fit, bro. Very fit.
>> Yeah, she is,
bro. Of course she is. I'm talking to
her, bro. She wouldn't If she wasn't
fit, I wouldn't be talking to her, would I?
I'm not like a virgin boy. Jesus Christ.
I'm not like the virgin [ __ ]
>> So, you get three and a half grand a
month, but you're in a you're using your 500 overdraft.
Yeah, that makes a lot of sense, doesn't it?
Yeah, that makes so much sense, isn't it? Yeah.
>> Yeah, that makes a lot of sense. Yeah,
Yeah, that makes a lot of [ __ ] sense, doesn't it?
Hate people. Steven Howard. I [ __ ] hate people.
[ __ ] hate him.
Hate the way people are.
Hate the way people are, bro.
I'm I'm I'm trying to find a way to [ __ ]
someone over at the minute. Usually
I don't like people taking the piss out of me.
People talk about benefit money. Yeah.
Well, it's different if you got a job.
Oh well. So what? You have b So what
people might say about benefit money and
stuff. Grezy. What? What? What about it,
bro? Don't have to answer to no one. You
don't have to deal with stupid games. Am I lying?
I still need to find a way to get
someone back at someone some someone
done to me.
This guy's been pissing me off. Greasy,
the one that made me go out drinking.
Just waiting for Just waiting for him to
[ __ ] him over, bro.
You need a job and pit, bro. That's what
you need. Yeah. Don't Don't sublet any house.
Trust me. Do not sublet any house.
That's all I'm saying. And don't do it.
Don't do anything where you need to deal
with people. Obviously, job is a job is
different because obviously you get
paid. You're going to get paid, but no.
[ __ ] that, bro. No. No. No. No. No.
Never again, bro.
I'm still dealing with these [ __ ]
idiots even when I don't even do it.
[ __ ] that, bro. It's better, bro. Slow
money. Slow but steady money is better. Trust me.
No, let's go.
This guy's proper took the piss out of me, bro.
Nah, Greasy. Cuz there was no proof.
There was no proof, Grezy.
Nah, there was no proof, bro. I got rid
of them before [ __ ] uh
before they No,
cuz it wasn't in my name.
The house wasn't in my name.
So, if anyone would have got it would
have been Laney.
It's nothing to do with me because I
wasn't on the tendency.
Do you get me? No.
Can't believe I got away with that for
years, bro. Jeez. Yeah, bro.
Yeah, I keep everything private, bro.
We're talking about the house that I
don't have anymore. Yeah. Yeah, but it's
the house. We don't have it anymore,
bro. Of course. You don't think I'm
going to be showing people Christian
Izzy and that, do you? Not gonna say her
name where she I'm not even gonna say
her age. Nothing. All you know is she's
a Christian. That's it. No need to know anything else.
Of course you keep it private, bro.
I'm just saying I don't like dealing with people.
This might this guy made me go go like a
headless chicken for something Grezy.
He had me going around like a headless
chicken. When I have the chance to [ __ ]
this guy over, he is getting [ __ ]
over, bro. Trust me. Watch.
I'm not going to get into it, but yeah.
I don't like people taking the piss out
of me. Simple as that.
Like, this is why I say don't deal with people.
This is exactly why I say don't deal
with people, bro.
If this if it was off this community,
I'd tell you what it is. But obviously,
I'm not giving these all retards any ammo.
But yeah, if we was off this community,
I would say it, bro. Yeah, if it was just us. But yeah.
Yeah, I got his number, but he doesn't reply.
Being a landlord's not good cuz you got
to [ __ ] around getting your money.
That's the thing.
Waiting around, [ __ ] around. I hate
anything to do. I don't want to deal
with people if I don't need to deal with
people. Do you get me?
I don't want to deal with people if I
don't have to. Does that make sense?
No, it's not all you need, bro.
Trust me, bro. It's something that I
can't discuss on here because of these
people. But yeah,
sorry I can't say. Yeah.
I like gold.
I'm not gay.
No, no, no, no, no.
You saw that. Would
you ever sublet Stephen Howard?
Uh-uh. What do you want to do, bro? You
want to win like a 100red grand, bro?
That's it. You want to hit You want to
win like 60 to 100 grand. That's it.
60 to 100 grand, bro. That's it.
Yeah, but it's [ __ ] doing that because
it's you have to always chase people for
money when you're doing that. I don't
like [ __ ] like that, bro.
That's why I hate I used to hate it, bro.
so much responsibility. It's It's
annoying, bro. I'd rather just work to be fair. Yeah.
usually said he likes the uh the the Scottish accent.
Yeah, Grezy likes a Scottish accent.
Do you remember who Tam was? Grezy Steven Howard.
Do you remember who he was to me? Tough.
Do you remember? Do you remember? Yeah.
Tom, your dada.
Tam's Peter Belly's dada. Remember that
Grezy? Tam your d.
That was the same account. Was it Grimsy?
Tam your dada.
I don't see that account. It's probably
on a mission. I don't see that account
anymore. Tell me your data. Your data.
He was my dada, wasn't he?
Yeah, that was my dada.
Tom's my dada from Scotland. Greavvesy.
I don't know why I called him my dad in
it. I met him in the Weather Spoons.
He's a Celtic fan. Yeah.
I would. Yeah, that account was like,
"Tam, your data. We need to find him."
Grezy, I reckon it's the same person
behind that account, in it, that keeps doing this.
Like, Greavvesy the poor [ __ ]
And you already found your mama. It's
the same person, isn't it, Griezy? It's
got to be.
It's the same person, is it, Greavvesy?
It's got to be.
It has to be the same person. It's too
obvious, isn't it?
Do you remember the account name, Greavvesy?
I think it was like fire or something, weren't it? Grey,
I can't believe Greavves got 10k. No,
seriously, Greavvesy, how long did it
take you to save 10K?
How long did it take you to save 10k? Seriously?
You never used to work?
How much money was you making from work a month?
You never worked, Grezy.
Okay. How how much was you making a month working? >> Yeah.
I hate people, Dusty. I hate dealing
with people. They play too many games.
Do you get me?
I hate people, Dusty. I hate dealing
with people when I don't need to. Do you get me?
I hate people, bro.
bless you, Grezy. If you're on £1,200 a
month, Grevy, bless you. Oh, bless.
Do you remember Uber delivery? Dusty
doing an Uber.
Uber on a bike.
Do you remember? Bless you.
You could still make money doing that.
You still could make money. Could
you imagine Grezy doing it in central
London? Nah, I don't reckon you could do it, lad.
I reckon you could do I reckon you could
make decent money, bro. If you done If
you done eight hours a day.
Yeah, you could break your back, but you
could still make money.
Yeah, but Dusty, you could still make
money, isn't it?
You can make about 150 a day some days.
I used to come back [ __ ] mate at
midnight when I used to do it. Greavvesy.
Yeah, but it's an e- pedal.
No, no, dusty. But it's an e- pedal,
so it's an electric pedal, so it doesn't
even It doesn't hurt your legs.
No, it's an e- pedal bike, lad.
So, no matter what you do, it doesn't
hurt your legs cuz it's it's supported
by it's an e- pedal bike.
Yeah. So, your legs are not going to
hurt. It don't affect your legs.
You rent the bike that, bro, what you do
is you go to a garage. What I used to
do, I used to go to the garage, rent the
bike, and then just But when that [ __ ]
runs out of battery, then you're in trouble.
Then you're in big trouble, bro. If
you're away if you're far away from the dock
and um if you're far away from the dock,
bro, and that [ __ ] runs out,
God help you, bro. It happened to me.
So, you need to make sure you
I had it before when I was putting it
back on the dock. Yeah. and it wasn't wasn't working.
It wasn't it wasn't having it.
But I reckon if you done eight hours a
day, you can make money.
I don't have tick squeezy.
I've got Tourette's.
Oh, there was this guy. Yeah. He said,
"My name is Jack and I've got Tourette's." [ __ ]
He said [ __ ] Straight after that, Grezy
[ __ ] I was I was I was laughing, bro. Yeah.
[ __ ] having that, bro. Yeah. Yeah, man.
So, you're never going to work again
then, Grezy. You're just going to lie about
just going to lie about Yeah,
you just going to lie about
Do you remember when you was mocking me,
Grezy? Haha, that's funny.
Greasy. Haha. That's funny.
Yeah, I know. He was mocking me in it.
Oh, bless you.
Oh, your little conditions. Greavesy. God bless.
I think I'm falling in love again.
Grievy, any tips for me? No. Falling in love.
We was talking about babies. Greavesy.
We was talking about babies and um she
do like kids and stuff. I said, "Yeah."
And I said, "If we had kids, who do you
reckon they look like?" She's like, "For
[ __ ] sake, probably you. You've got strong features."
Yeah. She said, "Probably me, Grezy."
How cute is that, Greasy? H.
How cute is that?
A new addition to the world. Greavvesy,
you can't have kids. Do you remember
that, Grezy? You can't have kids.
No, I can't. I couldn't have kids anyways.
It would get whisked straight into the
care system, is it?
Yeah, it would get whisked straight into
the care system.
Yeah, I can't have kids, bro.
That sounds so mad, doesn't it?
Straight into the curse system. Nah,
you shouldn't say stuff like that though, Grezy. you know,
no, I don't think would it actually be
risk straight into the care system.
Yeah. Ant-Man was saying the Sher Cole
thing wasn't copying. He said he
generally believed everyone wanted her
back in 2010, 2011.
Well, I can tell you something. I
[ __ ] didn't want her.
But I can tell you. Yeah, he actually
told me this the other day. I didn't
[ __ ] want her, mate. I don't know
about you, Grezy.
I said I would have triplets and then
leave them with Laney.
She's like, "Oh, God help God help me.
Imagine I had triplets, Greavesy.
Imagine I had triplets.
Whisk straight into the care system.
Straight into the care system. Mad. Yeah.
Do collecting women. Greavvesy.
collecting women. Is that cute,
Greavvesy? Yeah, it is cute.
I'm going to say to Christian Izzy as
well when we meet again. I'm going to be
like, you're mine. No one else's.
She says, do you remember when she was
saying to me how how many women how many
women have you been with? I said, oh, just three.
Did I tow a porcupine agree with you?
Did I tell a porcupine?
Did I tell Porcupine Greasy? Yeah, I
just said free and stuff. Yeah,
Grezy, have you seen that guy that keeps
pouring milk on his head saying 62 62?
You have seen that, isn't it, Grezy?
No, he's mad.
You have seen that ain't it?
He keeps pouring milk on himself. Is it?
You saw it in it.
That's funny when you saw that Indian
guy. Is it?
Why will she be gone? She's my new friend.
She's worried I would cheat in that
grievy. I won't cheat.
In it grieves you. I would never cheat.
You can trust me in it.
I don't know. Maybe I would.
No, I don't think so. I think I would
speak to other people.
I don't think I could help myself. Grezy,
I wouldn't. I don't know. Not sure.
It's all a game to me, Greavvesy.
To me, it's all a game.
Is that funny? That's all a game, Grezy.
It's all a game.
It shouldn't be treated as a game
though, should it? We see Oh gosh,
I've already got a little Lego
collection, don't I Greavvesy?
No, he's 5'7. Bless him. Bless you then
if you're 57 in life.
Bless you then. Reeves is a short ass,
everyone. Reeves is a short ass. He's a
big short He's a big fat stinky short
ass. Oh gosh.
I bet Crash is [ __ ] taller than you. Look, Crash.
I love Crash.
He's a good little teddy. I love Crash.
He he he I I sleep next to Crash.
You know what's nice, Grezy? Sleeping
next to a dog. They're so warm. Oh my
god. Have you ever slept next to like a
dog? Bro, they're lovely.
If you put your hand Yeah. on their
fire, it's so warm.
Yeah. Like a dog. Yeah. No, they're cute dogs.
So, so Steven Howard, why did Nons leg
say that I was gay? Because I don't like Sh again.
Why did he say that again? Steven Howard.
Do you remember that Griezer? Are you
still there? Do you remember? Did you
see the video of me of me and that New
Zealander when we was walking back to
her place? What did you think of it?
No, listen. Greasy. Greasy. Did you see that video?
Tell me what you think of it.
You remember Grievy? Did you watch it?
Grey, did you watch it? Huh?
Greavves you. Did you watch it?
I agree with you. Did you watch it?
Did you watch that video?
I'm going to link it to you.
Tell me what you think.
Even if you have seen it, you probably
ain't seen it for a while. This is one
of the one night stands I had. Greasy.
Watch it. Tell me what you think.
Watch it, Grezy. Tell me what you think.
Steven Howard, tell me what you think.
Watch the little video. Come back.
Watch the [ __ ] video I sent you, you [ __ ] [ __ ]
Can't do with these two [ __ ]
Go and watch the video that I sent you.
I just linked you a video.
Go and watch it, bro. It's me.
Don't watch it.
Can you watch the [ __ ] video I sent
you? You [ __ ]
You ask me. Oh, you even remember her,
Greavvesy. Did you like the little
voices that I done?
I was talking about babies and stuff, is it, Grezy?
Yeah, I was talking about babies, wasn't I, Grezy? Yep.
She like the baby talk.
Uh, this was some someone from New
Zealand who I
I put my penis inside.
Do you believe we had sex, Squeezy?
Oh, yeah. We was talking about We was
talking about babies in it.
We were talking about Bubbers. Reezy,
we was talking about babies.
No, I didn't. Why did you see the video Pip Smoker?
I I I linked it. Go and watch it. Tell
me what you think.
Nope. Nope. Nope. No. I never spoke
about babies with with her
or done any silly voices, funny enough.
No. Done with this one, though.
Funny, ain't it, Greasy? That's funny,
Greasy. That's funny, is it?
What do you think of the little video?
Do you like it?
What bit did you find cringe?
What bit do you find cringe?
Why is it cringe, lad? I think it was lovely.
Yeah, that's cute.
Do you think I'm a troll? Nah, I'm not a
troll, bro. I'm not a I'm not a troll. I
don't know why people think I troll,
why do people think I troll? I never troll, bro.
Why would people say I troll when I
don't troll? I swear it's annoying, bro.
I never troll.
No, I don't troll, bro. I'm being serious.
I like that video. I think it was quite cute.
Obviously, the Virgin was jealous that I
was getting some Punani,
something that he can't do.
I was getting a bit of Punani, mate. Uh,
I'm not a troll, bro. Why am I How am I a troll?
Did you like that with me and Vist? Me and Sig.
Virgin boy was singing that autumn.
He was singing autumn, bro.
Why am I How am I trolling, bro? I
actually met this person. Why would I troll?
What do I get from trolling, bro?
Why? How do I throw
I see that Jeff comment on Nons's
channel a lot. Steven Howard.
I see Jo comment a lot on his channel.
Well, what did you think of Sig Dusty?
Yeah, he said join my panel, Steven.
The alleyway mon pretends he got a
[ __ ] up Chinatown. Delusional big. Oh
my god, bro.
I don't lie about anything.
Oh, I'm actually in good shape, bro. I
actually I'm actually looking more
healthy. I'm not even fat.
Join the panel, Steven.
Why is he another Why is he another Thompson mug?
Why is he another Thompson mug, lad?
Why? Why is he another Thompson mug lad?
I thought Jo was all right.
No, I thought I thought Jo was all right.
Nah. Is he [ __ ] bro?
Jamie talks. Jamie Thompson has spoke,
bro. He sounds like a [ __ ]
He No, no, he has talked.
Fatty Thompson has talked, bro. No, he
actually has spoke.
No, he has. He's a [ __ ]
Yeah, he has. He's coming to Hangouts,
bro. He's a [ __ ]
Bro, he is
Oh my god, bro. He's Yeah. Look, I I'll
show you. I'll show you. God, bro.
Yeah. Here, lad.
Yeah. Oh, he's a [ __ ] bro.
That is what you call fat, mate. That's
what you call fat.
That's literally what you call fat, bro. [ __ ] hell.
That's what you call fat.
That's what you call That's what you
That's what you call fat, bro.
I need to send a number to someone.
J some of these women's numbers.
Yeah, I might give L some of these
women's numbers. Steven Howard.
Did you Did you listen? Oh,
Jack and Miles,
the two Norwegian lads. Yep.
I know everything.
Dark past. Stephen Howard, he's got a
very dark past.
Mick Jonathan Robinson.
I don't have ticks, bro. I don't have ticks.
Yeah, cuz he's got autism. That's why.
He's a [ __ ] bro. Yeah.
Oh, saving money is so boring, Steven
Howard, man. But it has to be done, bro.
It's so boring.
You take like a code all bro just to
pass the time. It's so boring is it?
Wait, what the I just went on Red Star's channel, bro.
Not bold and 1% laugh. Yeah, I went on
one of these comments. Might as well
just go full lo at this point.
Okay, let's see your hairline.
Oh, bro, this account was made 19 years ago. Oh, bro.
And you're telling me that I might as
well go bald like L J. Bro, I'm not even
balding to begin with. And your account
was made 19 years ago.
Your account was made 19 years ago.
Also, Virgin Boy is actually bored himself.
Guess it's another uh form of projection.
You actually want to see my hairline,
Stephen Owen? I can show you if you
want, lad. I'm not bored at all.
Yeah, his account was made 19 years ago.
And he's saying that I need to I need to
be like L J.
L J lost his hair at 15, bro. He's never
had hair. He's lost his hair at 15.
Yeah, I can show my hairline if you want, bro.
Hey, I'm not insecure about my hairline,
bro. Cuz I'm not balding. The only
people that say I'm balding are people
that are already bored themselves. Self projecting.
Bro, they're self projecting, bro. I'm
not going bored. 19 years Yeah.
He's a [ __ ]
I'm not even I'm not even balding, bro.
These people are obsessed with balding,
but the only ones that are bored is them.
They don't say anything. [ __ ] hell.
I'm the best looking on this community, lad.
Steve and I are on the best looking on
this community. Lad
PL is better looking than all these [ __ ] That's
what I'm stay on for a little bit longer
because after today I'm done for a long time, lad.
Yeah, they do, bro.
Christian Christian Izzy said I looked good.
So what I'm I'm going to listen to her
while I not ugly old men. I'll listen to
her and not and not ugly old men. You
know what I'm saying, bro? Yeah.
I'm clearly balding.
Well, I'm really not balling.
And let me ask you this as well. Oh
[ __ ] Oh, he's
But bro, you're But you're already bowled.
Yeah, that's nice, bro. That's cool. But
you're already bowled.
Is there Is there anything that these
people say on here, Steven, that doesn't
apply to themselves?
I generally can't think of one thing
they try to say that doesn't go for
themselves. Right. Balden, they're bold.
Ugly, they're ugly. Skin, they're skin.
Single, they're single. Is there
literally anything they say that doesn't
apply to themselves?
Yeah, but bro, you you are the only one that's bored.
You can convince yourself that I'm
balding, but it doesn't bother me, bro,
because I'm not balding.
You're literally bored. You're already bored yourself
and you're trying to convince yourself
that I'm balding. There's literally not
one% of me that's balding,
but you keep telling yourself that.
I'm better looking than you. I've got
more hair than you, bro. You're You're
talking about yourself. See you later, lad.
You know the people that are doing this
are 40y old bald men already. Stephen Howard,
Bro, if I was Listen, Stephen Howard,
bro. Yeah. If I was bored and all of
this, they wouldn't Do you think they'd
be wasting their time on me, bro? I
don't I don't waste my time on them. I'm
off of YouTube for ages tomorrow, bro.
If I was really all of these things,
then isn't the jokes on them for wasting
their life on me every day?
Yeah, definitely, bro. Definitely. Definitely, bro.
Yeah, they're [ __ ] just jealous ass
people, bro. That's why I don't really
come on here anymore, lad. Like
that's why you [ __ ] bro.
I think I'm the best looking on this
community. Steven Howard, lad.
I'm the best I'm the best looking on
this community, lad.
I don't know one person that goes for me
that's better looking than me.
Timmy ugly. Lj ugly. Nons legs ugly.
Terry ugly. Uh Jamie ugly.
Do not see the pattern. Steven Howard,
do you not see the pattern, lad? me.
Yeah, they say they say that he's not a
virgin cuz he's got a girlfriend. Steven Howard.
Yeah, I know. They say that he's not
he's not a virgin.
I'm a virgin. But I'm a virgin. Even
though I've literally got people's
channel banned because of my porno. But
I know. But apparently I'm a virgin. Is it strange?
They're very strange people, bro.
Yeah. Very weird. Uh,
you were absolutely nowhere near that girl sexually.
Yep. I know he would be. I know, mate. I
know, mate. I know, mate. Yep.
I'll be going out in March, Steven. March, lad.
So you don't you're not interested in
the football anymore now.
No, you're not you're not interested in
the football anymore.
Yeah. Mid-March. Yeah,
maybe St. Patrick's Day.
Nah, maybe not. Do you know what? I
don't really like going out when it's
events. It's too over. No, I'll go out
on a Thursday again
in March. I don't really like I don't
like going out when it's like New Year's
Eve and St. Patrick's Day. It's just too [ __ ] that.
Oh, bless you then, Steven. I You should
play the roulette.
Yeah, you should play the roulette. Meow. No,
you said she was good looking to fit in.
Now I'm looking at her. She's not even
making my dick hard.
Gerald Cole 2010. Nope.
My dick's still soft.
Doesn't do it for me, lad.
Doesn't do it for me. Maybe you
I don't understand what's so special.
No, doesn't do it for me, lad. No.
Did he [ __ ] touch me? The little virgin.
I [ __ ] knocked that virgin [ __ ] out.
Who do you think would win a fight,
Steven? Me or Monty?
Who do you think would win?
I reckon I would win in it. Yeah.
Should I go and Should I go to
Birmingham and fight Monty?
Did you do I should I should go? Nah, bro.
Then I'd have to meet London Taylor and
London Taylor would
London Taylor would would would defeat me.
London Taylor would defeat me, bro.
So I can't, man.
He would defeat me, bro.
Maybe he's the only one in this on this
community that could beat me, bro.
LJ couldn't beat me. Nope.
Oh, yeah. I could Yeah, I could I could
own him as well.
Like Cory was talking about this the
other day. I said, "Yeah, bro. Prime
owned me, but bro, that was [ __ ]
years ago, man.
You're like that was so long ago."
Yeah. I could own that prime definitely, bro.
Ro. Yep. Monty. Yep.
But maybe LT could beat me, bro.
Unless I trained for like 4 months.
But yeah, he wouldn't even be able to,
bro. He would
he wouldn't be able to outpower me, bro. Uh um
what's his name? Uh Prime, bro. No way. Nah, bro.
My is powerful.
He's very powerful.
Him and his little mates.
He would never f Bro, he couldn't even
face me in Birmingham, bro. When I was
in When I was in Birmingham with Monty,
he couldn't he couldn't even he couldn't
even face me, bro.
I was in Birmingham with Monty. He
didn't he he was nowhere to be heard of,
bro, when I was with Monty.
Yeah, he'll never face me, bro. Same
with Lord J.
Same with Lord J. Yeah.
No takeaways now for a little bit. Need
to save some money, Stephen.
>> Yep. We all know the story, lad.
I'm actually [ __ ] in my head as well,
bro. Like, I'm psychotic.
I'm very, very psychotic, bro.
Very psychotic. Trust me.
I'm not going to get into it. Yeah. But yeah.
Laney was scared the other day. I wasn't scared.
Laney was scared. I weren't scared.
Not me, bro.
M YouTube though is it.
It's boring saving is it Stephen?
But it has to be done.
Has to be done bro.
Hate saving. It's boring, bro.
Just get too obsessed with it.
Yeah, bro. I got money, bro. I can go
out. I've got money. But I'd rather
build more. I'd rather build some more
money in case I just want to fly
somewhere or something. I want to build
like a little balance bit more money up, you know?
And this is the perfect month to do it
because no one goes out February. Well,
it's just a [ __ ] month, isn't it? So,
you have to find a month you can do it.
You get me?
Just in case I want to go on a trip
somewhere, you know, whatever. I just
want to build some more money up. So, yeah.
Couple grand I think, bro. Yeah, man.
Just skin again. Why?
I want about 150k, bro.
That last a long time.
150k in it.
That should last a couple of years now.
Oh, bless you.
Hard to get money nowadays, isn't it? Steven Howard.
Yeah, it's hard to get money now, dude.
But can't even [ __ ] win.
Hard to win, isn't it?
I want to study the football, bro.
I want to put £50. Yeah. On both teams
to score and a team to win. Might get
like a good cash out in it. Steven Howard,
there was I put six on it the other day.
The cash out was £36.
If I had like 60 quid on it, the cash
out would have been sick, bro.
Yeah. I don't gamble anymore, bro.
Except £10 a week on the football. Yeah.
Yeah, I was thinking of Christian. I
wake up thinking of Christian. Is he
How cute is that?
Yeah. So, I'm just going to like find
like a good lineup and do a both teams
to score and score to win two or three
teams. Put 50 on it
and see what cash outs I can get.
Yeah, I'm speaking to someone. Yeah.
I haven't messaged them in a couple of
days. I need to message them again. She's nice.
Yeah, but if you get a cash out, bro,
even a cash out, it's good. It's going
to be good money if you could even get
well maybe two teams then just put 80
pound on a on a two both teams to score
and to win. It's a good cash out isn't it?
I don't know. Probably not, bro. I don't
know. I don't want to gamble anymore.
I'd put 500 pound on two teams, but
the odds are so [ __ ] now.
The odds on the football are so [ __ ]
Yeah, the odds are so [ __ ] now on football, bro.
Hey, Porky. Pete, still single?
Oh, V. You just talking about yourself,
lad? Sorry, I just read that.
An obese fat [ __ ] is calling me Porky. Oh, bro.
You're a proper self-reflector, aren't you, lad?
What about if you put £500 on roulette
online, Steven Howard? There's a chance
you could win like four grand, isn't there?
Uh, I have had a misses and it makes
absolute sense. You people have never
had a misses. You've never even had sex,
you little virgins.
It makes absolute sense. You people have
got low on yourselves.
No misses, no girlfriend, no sex life.
It makes absolute sense. You people are
[ __ ] fat, ugly bastards.
Fat, ugly people with no misses. It does
make sense. It makes perfect sense.
Come on camera right now, bro, and I'll
prove it. Bro, I am I am the best
looking on this community,
bro. I am the best looking on this community, lad.
from people that have shown their for
people that shown their faces anyways.
Okay. Well, come on here and show us
what you look like then.
Or even have a chat. Come come up for a chat, lad.
Listen, come come in a hangout and we'll
have a chat.
I'll let you up, lad. You can ask
whatever you want. Come on and let's
have a chat.
Come on, you little self-reflector.
No, I am I know I hit a nerve there. No,
I am the best looking on this community.
Look at Nons's ugly. L J ugly. Jamie Thompson
ugly. Timmy ugly. Terry ugly. Prime
ugly. Yeah, you're all ugly.
You are literally all [ __ ] ugly.
[ __ ] ugly bastards. Pat, ugly, bomb, ugly.
They all seem to be very ugly, don't they?
Can't think of anyone on here that's
normal looking. But me? Nope.
Can't think. Gray cat. Ugly.
Oh, you're not coming in, you ugly
virgin. See you later. Launch legs. Ugly
Steven Howard. You know, like I told you
before, bro, the more they do this, it's
only proving me right.
It's only proven that I'm right about
them. You do realize that?
The more they do all of this, the more
it proves that you're better looking
than them because they're giving they're
giving you their time of day every day.
They are literally No, they are ugly.
Every single person on here that has
shown their faces that are still on here.
Yep. They're ugly.
I know the truth hurts, bro. But yeah,
I know, Dusty, man. They just need to
get a life, these people on here. Like I
said, I'm off here tomorrow again, bro.
I'm not coming back for a long time.
Yeah. No, seriously, they um It is sad.
They need to get a life, bro. They need
to come out the closet, get a life.
I don't know how they can do this every
day for years, bro.
They're [ __ ] gay and jealous, bro.
That's where, like I said, that's where
Monty got it from. They're gay and
jealous. They know, right? Steven
Howard. Yeah. Listen, people like Nons
legs and LJ, they knew they know they
can never get anything with the way that
they look. They can never get any woman
with the way that like B. They know that
they can never get any woman
with the way that they look because
they've got ugly looks. So, obviously,
that's why they're obsessed with me.
They know you're better looking than
them. It kills them, bro. Trust me.
You're better looking than them. You got
more money than them and it kills them.
It's the truth. True facts. That's why I
don't come on here much anymore, bro.
You rarely see me.
Yep. That's true. Better money, better
looks, and it kills them. Yep. Yep. It
true. Yep. Ronald Pump was right.
Definitely that. Definitely.
Why can't I go on her channel, bro?
Just been talking to Christian Izzy,
bro. Just been chilling.
Just been chilling, bro. Went to the cinema.
Some people's got a life, bro. Unlike these people. Hey. Hey.
I'm not liking Laney's attitude lately, Steven Howard.
I'm not liking her attitude lately, laddy. No, no.
See you later.
I know it's 2026, bro. Why Why do you
think I'm not on here anymore, Dusty?
I went on here today cuz uh Grevy was
messaging me on Instagram, bro. I know,
They need to get a life. They need to
come out the closet and get a life in it, lad. Oh,
they ain't got no life, bro.
I think they're jealous of a couple of
things. I think they're jealous that I'm
better looking than them. Uh, they're
jealous that I've got a mom. They're
jealous that I've got more money than
them. Jealous that I got family. Jealous
that I've got a nice bed, better
clothes, I can go out and cold approach women.
I think they're jealous of a few things.
I don't think it's just looks, bro. It's
not just looks they're jealous of.
They're jealous of you're more confident
than them. You're better looking. You
got a mom. I think there's a lot of
things that they're jealous of. And them, well,
they're just sat on YouTube 24/7, no life. So,
yeah, I think they're jealous of a of a
couple of things, bro. To be fair.
Oh, and you're younger than them as well. So,
if you look at these people like via
what? Um, uh, they're on YouTube.
They're on YouTube 24/7.
No, they're on YouTube 24/7.
I don't know how people can be on it
24/7. And this is a one-off for me, bro.
It just shows that they don't have
anything in their life
to be on there 24/7.
Yeah, they ain't got anything in their lives, lad.
The Lego's downstairs, bro.
I haven't even touched the Lego, you
know, Dusty, the the the new set that I
got. I just bought it for Jar Binks. Yeah.
What do you think of that, Dusty?
What do you think, Dusty?
Yeah, I just bought it for the little characters.
No, I don't I don't make content for
mongos, lad. I don't entertain mongos.
This is just a one-off, lad.
I don't need to make content for mongos.
So, Dusty, what you're saying is right.
So what you're saying is if I try to
meet a woman quickly, Dusty, there's a
big problem, ain't it? Like I'm coming
on too strong and stuff. But then when a
woman wants to meet me straight away,
that's fine, right?
That's fine, isn't it, Dusty?
They make different rules for men, don't
they? It's one rule for them and one
rule for another.
People on Reddit are idiots. You should
never ask for You should never ask
anyone for dating advice.
This the most stupidest thing to do, bro.
You would You should never because you
See you later, Virgin.
See you later, virgin boy. Um,
yeah. No, like u.
So, what you're saying, Dusty, is it is
it is it double standards then?
That's [ __ ] funny, bro.
Is that what you're basically saying
then, Dusty? It's double standards. Why
am I going to ask people for advice on
Reddit UK asylum?
You want me to ask people for advice?
I'm not asking people for advice.
I'm never complaining. I'm not asking
people for advice ever again. Do you know why?
Because of double standards.
I'm not doing that, bro.
No. Cuz they make excuses for women in
it. So there's no point.
Yeah. I'm not asking for advice. I don't want advice.
You know, I'm saying UK asylum.
Do you think it's pointless asking for
dating advice, Bob? bills.
I think it's I think it's I think it's pointless
cuz they're always going to defend
women. So why would you ask for advice?
I just find it pointless.
So you ask someone for advice, right?
Okay. Let's see your messages. So you
show them the messages and they're
always going to make excuses for the women.
So that they're not they could never
give you fair advice because they're
just biased from the get- go. So why
would you ask anyone for advice?
What do you think, Steven Howard?
I think the only people that should ask
for advice is gay men.
There's no point asking for advice. Nah,
bro. I still hate women. Even though I
talk to I talked to this Christian.
No, self-improvement isn't key because
no no amount of self-improvement is
going to is is going to change stuck up
[ __ ] This is what I say to people on
Reddit all the time. I could be a millionaire
with a mansion.
I could have the best body in the world.
You don't know me. It's not going to
change women. No matter what I am, I
could be homeless, broke, I could be a
millionaire. That's not going to change
how women are. Women are the way they
are, and they'll never change.
You You self-improve because you self-improve.
You're supposed to self-improve for yourself.
You don't self-improve for women.
Why would you do that? You go gym, you
save money because that's what you're
supposed to do.
If you think if you're thinking that
your your situation is going to change
with women, then you'll be sadly sadly disappointed
cuz sadly that's there's nothing that changes them.
Steven would listen, bro.
I went out that Thursday cuz this guy
was pissing me off and I just happened
to meet someone. Do you think if this
person, let's just say by the low chance
they [ __ ] me over, right? You think I'm
going to go and approach again? Never.
I will never, bro.
I mean, you go I mean, you go for
escorts because they don't give you sex.
So, I mean that just contradicts itself
because you will go for escorts because
they don't give you sex in the first
place. Escorts exist for a reason.
Why are you talking about escorts anyways?
So, I'm only speaking to one person,
Steven, and I'm giving them the benefit
of the doubt. They [ __ ] me over or
whatever, I'm done.
Just like I was done for three months
last time. I don't care. You know,
I hate women.
I generally do, bro. And I'm not biased.
I generally do hate them.
And the more I went on Reddit, bro, the
more I think about it, bro. And the more
it pissed me off. I generally do hate
them. I hate them. I hate dating. I hate
double standards. I hate them, bro. I
do, bro. Honestly, I do.
I don't give a [ __ ] if they get put off
easy. They're [ __ ] Cuz the way I see
it, yeah, Steven Howard, yeah, is
they've done all of these shitty things
for years and years and years and you
still have people defending them.
You still have people defending these [ __ ]
You understand what I mean, bro? So
that's why I hate him, bro.
I generally do hate him. That's why I
gave up. That's why I got away from it.
I went for a drink cuz I went for a
drink. [ __ ] it. Why not? After 3 months.
I generally hate him, bro. I do. I I'm
only speaking to this person because I
think we'll give someone the benefit of
the doubt one last time in 2026 and that's it.
She [ __ ] me over, she's done.
That's it. No, I don't think she will
[ __ ] me over. But yeah,
I hate everything about dating. I hate
everything about women. You don't
understand, bro. I hate everything about it.
Just remember, in dating, you can't do
right for doing wrong, Steven Howard.
You can't do right for doing wrong.
You do this, they tell you to do that.
You do that, they tell you to do this.
Do you understand, bro?
But what I don't understand, Stephen
Howard, is how people defend them
knowing what they're like.
You know, maybe I'll do like a panel one
day and then maybe people could tell me
why they defend these kind of people.
You know what I mean?
Why they defend scum. They're not
innocent like women. They're not
innocent like kids. They're not innocent
like babies. Children are innocent.
They're not innocent. So, I'd love to
know why people defend them the way they
do. I would love it to be explained to
me because they can't say I'm a virgin.
I've had more women than them. So, I I
would want I would want somebody to
explain it to me why they do it.
You know, when majority of women are
bad, I'd love to know why they do it. I
would love to really know why they do it.
I'd want it to be answered, you know, one day.
They're [ __ ] They're stuck up to
[ __ ] I know that by the last time I
went out as well. So,
why do you get all of these virgins
or if they're not virgins, they've been
with very little women?
Um, and why they defend them? I would
love to know. Like, they don't get women
or they're virgins, but they still defend women.
It's weird. I don't know how people can
defend them [ __ ] But uh
I don't know how they defend them is mad
to me. But yeah,
the scum of the earth, bro. Really are.
I got four numbers. I only had one reply
and that's the one I'm talking to now.
And I only went out cuz this guy was
pissing me off as well and it was
something to do, you know.
He was actually winding me up, bro. So, yeah,
I can approach. Don't forget, I'm not
scared to approach anyone. So, I could
do it with anyone I see. But nah,
once you've met one, you've met them all.
And the thing is, bro, let's just say
this person is different, which I think
they are. Yeah. You got to think about
this, bro. What What does that tell you,
Stephen? How would you
Doesn't that tell you that if this
person is different, right? How many
people you have to meet to find someone
different? Think about it, bro. Yeah.
Well, I'm clean and I'm tidy and women
are still [ __ ]
If I had a sex drive like I used to,
bro, I don't really have a sex drive
anymore. I would just join the pool industry
or just use escorts. But I don't have um
I don't really care about that stuff.
I'm not saying what she is, bro.
I would if I was I would generally just
I would if I like had a sex like a big I
would just join the porn industry or
just use escorts
and I'd probably just get on with my
life. I just stick to one person. I
wouldn't get into no relationship with
any of these [ __ ] I wouldn't bother
with them. I wouldn't, bro. Seriously.
They're such [ __ ] When I went out two
weeks ago, the attitude with them gets
worse and worse and worse. Stephen Howard,
it gets worse and worse and worse.
Yeah, bro. You already know, bro. You
already know. Yeah. They don't know
anything. The age. They're not They're
never going to know about her, bro.
Never. And the skint virgin in the
bedsit is never going to know either.
Yeah. Let's just hope that um
she is Yeah.
But yeah, women are cons. They all they all cons.
Why do they defend them?
Why do people defend them?
Yeah, I don't come on here anymore
really, bro. It's just the same repeating [ __ ]
I was getting scared the other day. I
thought she ghosted me, bro. I was
getting that anxiety and [ __ ] and I
don't get anxiety.
It was the same time LT was supposed to
come on the door. Yeah, I wasn't even
getting anxiety over that. I was getting
anxiety about this [ __ ] not replying back.
I thought they were they [ __ ] me over,
bro. I weren't scared of anyone coming
in the door.
Don't know yet, bro.
But we'll see.
But if they do [ __ ] me over, that's the end.
I would just
Yeah, I know. I'll just give up, bro. I
don't care. I didn't go out to try anyways, so
[ __ ] strike, bro.
No, I just got anxiety about that
because it's stressful. The whole dating
thing's stressful, isn't it?
But it's funny how people defend women
when they are complete [ __ ] Well,
uh, well, what happened to it was, um, I
might have found somebody after
approaching about 10 million people in
the in in the space of four years. So, I
mean, Asia is probably the only way to be honest.
I mean, I'd rather go to Asia than try
for another five years.
I know that for a fact.
Asia is the only way, bro.
It is the only way.
Better lie, cheaper, better food. You
don't get Well, you get [ __ ] women
there as well now, but not like you do here.
Yeah, you might as well go Asia. Yeah,
I'm still going to go to Asia, I think.
Yeah, I'm still going to go.
I think I'm that's one of the things I'm
going to I'm going to live there for a
bit. A month or two months, I'll still go. Yeah, why not?
Might as well. Everyone's moving there.
Everyone's going there now. Everyone's
sick of this country. The system, the
women, the whatever. Everyone's sick of it.
There was some [ __ ] I was talking to on
Reddit the other day, Bob, and I showed
her my approaching video. She's like,
"Oh, can you explain it to me?" I said,
"No, if you if you don't if you can't be
bothered to watch the videos, then I'm
not explaining it to you." I've noticed
that more women you come across now are really [ __ ]
Really, really, really [ __ ]
They're just really [ __ ]
Yeah. I don't know why people defend them,
but they do.
Yeah, they do defend him. You got a
virgin in a bedsit defending women when
women don't like him, but that doesn't bother them.
They know they're going to die virgins.
They know women are never going to like
them, but they still defend women.
They'll be like 90 on their deathbed
on their last breath like they
I'm dying. And all of that singing and
white lighting never got them a woman. Imagine
that, bro. They're dying on their deathbed.
Yeah, bro. I'm the same. I don't care.
It's only because I come across this one
and we're, you know, we're talking and
stuff. Otherwise, I wouldn't I wouldn't
care either, bro. [ __ ] them. I don't
I don't give a [ __ ] either. Yep.
Do you like that autumn rose, Bob?
I would never [ __ ] beg some woman on
YouTube or flirt with a woman on YouTube.
The only way I'd get with a woman on
YouTube is if she come if she came on my
door begging for it.
Then I would
you come on my door, you know where I live,
you come on my door begging for it.
And um that's a different story. But in
in regarding flirting on Nah, [ __ ] that.
I would never ever do that, bro.
Why would anyone want to get with a
woman on YouTube?
Why the [ __ ] would anyone want to get you?
Unless they're at your front door
begging for you. I don't know why
someone would would the only thing I
reason I could think. Yeah.
But no, but the thing that don't make
sense is L. Yeah. He simps over this and
that, but he doesn't realize that even
if this singing on white light and
worked, it would end in disaster. Even
if you met a woman on this community, it
would end in tears. So,
it don't make sense
when you just meet a woman off YouTube
and keep it private like what I'm doing.
But they can't do that because they
can't cold approach women because
they're ugly. They ain't got no life.
I've had a woman beg for me once.
Well, once proper beg for me.
She's like, "I really want you, but I
don't think you want me."
And she sucked my dick in the alleyway.
Yeah, I have I've had it.
Yeah, he is a s, bro. He is a s
cuz he can't talk to women. He can't
Look, he went to that place the other
day, that club. He didn't even get one number.
He didn't. He's I think he's scared to approach.
Christian is his nice man. Yeah.
I'm not Christian. I'm atheist.
Yeah, I've had it once where like
someone's begged me. Yeah.
Well, obviously USA is he begged me as
well by coming on to me. But yeah,
I've been approached but not many times. No. Well, obviously
there's a lot of women that have found
Peter B attractive.
There's a lot of women that have found
Peter Bell is a decent looking fellow.
What would you do if you if you look
like nons legs? Oh, [ __ ] that, bro. Nons
legs. Money mike.
[ __ ] that, bro.
You know, some people, you know, you can
you can help yourself, but some people you can't.
Oh my god. Like rice. Oh, [ __ ] that,
bro. [ __ ] looking like that.
I think if I look like that, bro, I
would never ever approach a woman.
If I look like that, bro,
I would never approach a woman if I look
like [ __ ] rice. Oh my [ __ ] god.
Cuz I would have a different mindset.
Oh, this some weirdo. If I look like any
even Monty, bro, like I would think that
like there's no point me approaching I'm
ugly in it and everything they're going
to say they're just going to use
excuses. I'm just ugly in it. [ __ ] it.
There's no point me talking to people.
There's no point me trying with someone
if if I know I'm ugly.
That's I would never I would never speak
to anyone if I look like any of them
bro. Even like Laura Jane. Nah.
Some people can help themselves, some people can't.
If you're average and that, you can just
like get a good body and whatever, but
if you're ugly like them, nah, [ __ ] that, bro.
No way. I just feel now. Nah, bro.
I could do it.
Imagine looking like them, bro. I'd hate
to be ugly like them. Bro,
what would you do if you was butt ugly?
I know this guy. Yeah. He is He's from
Wales. Yeah. And he just looks weird.
It doesn't matter what he does, he just looks weird.
I would hate to be ugly, bro. Like these
people. I really would.
Cuz I know that women will just [ __ ]
say no cuz of the way that I look and
[ __ ] and give me the runaround. So,
I just would give I just wouldn't date
in it. It's as simple as that. I just wouldn't date.
It's as simple as that. What's dating if
you're ugly, bro?
So, if I was them, I wouldn't.
Yeah, I can have kids.
I was actually talking about We was
actually talking about babies.
I said, "Who do you reckon they'd look
like?" And she said, "For [ __ ] sake, probably you.
Probably you." She said,
"We're just getting to know each other and stuff." Yeah.
Let me see. He's there.
Yeah, I can see. But
Yeah, let me join. Let me join.
Yeah, I'm going to go on there, bro.
No, they wouldn't. Dusty.
Yeah, I'm gonna go on I'm gonna go on
Mix's panel. Yeah, everyone go on mixes. One sec.
Yeah, he's not letting me in, the [ __ ] [ __ ]
>> He won't let me in, bro. Yeah, I'm
trying to join. He won't let me in.
You want to let me in, man?
Let me try again, bro. I tried. Yeah.
Let me try again.