this. So, see what these people think about it.
This is what I think most of most of
these people do to be honest. They
didn't even take a fee that time as well.
Yeah, bro. [ __ ] me. I think that's what
a lot of these people in here do to be fair.
And to be honest with you, I don't
understand what is the point.
What's the point of letting someone
Yeah. One second.
What's the point of letting someone play
when you're just going to rig the
roulette? To me, it just seems
pointless. What's the point of letting
someone play a game when you're just
going to rig it and cheat? I don't see
the point of that. What is literally the
point of that, bro? I don't see the
point of it. I don't see the point in
letting someone play a game you're just
going to fix. I just don't I just really
really don't understand it, you know?
No, I just put 100 pound on roulette.
Nope. there. There's no women trouble in
my life, bro. Why would there be? No, I
just put £100 on roulette. It's doing
the same thing again where it keeps
missing every number. Every single
number that you bet on, it misses. The
first number I hit was eight. Yeah, I
got it to 137. And as usual, you think,
"Oh, you're going to win this time. You
missed three, four times in a row and I
covered 18 numbers. [ __ ] out of it. Eat
a dick." This is exactly why I didn't do
it in [ __ ] This is exactly why I
didn't do it for like three weeks, bro.
[ __ ] dumb, bro. And I only put 100
pound on it cuz it's [ __ ] It's fixed.
It's fixed as [ __ ] bro. I only put 100
pound on it. It's so fixed. It loves
that [ __ ] left side of zero. Same
story. It loves it, bro. It loves it. It
loves that pedo area. That pedophile
area for some reason. Yeah.
Yeah. It's fixed as [ __ ] bro. It's
fixed as [ __ ] I only put 100 pound on
it. It's [ __ ] fixed.
It is so so so so fixed. That's exactly
why I stopped playing it. That's why I
stopped playing it because it's fixed as
[ __ ] bro. The only reason I'm not going
completely mad, there's a reason for it
as well. I'm not going to I'm not going
to say why. I can actually feel my blood
boiling, bro. It's [ __ ] pissing me off.
What's the point of letting someone play
something you're just going to fix?
It's [ __ ] It's pointless. What's the
point if you're just going to cheat and
make it go on losing numbers? You did
make it go on losing numbers, mate. You
know, I had done about three or four
spins and it missed and I had half the
board covered. [ __ ] off, mate. You stupid wanker.
Yeah. Same story with it, isn't it?
Only £100, bro. Only £100.
Only £100, bro. That's all.
And why would there be any women
trouble, bro? I don't say my women [ __ ]
on this community. What's their tr what
trouble is there to have?
No one asks for advice. No one needs any
advice. Why Why would there be any women trouble?
They're Why would there? They're all the
same. They're all [ __ ] What more needs
to be said about it?
So yeah, this was my house, bro. I would
smash everything in that in this house,
bro. I swear to God, I would smash
everything in this house right now, bro,
if this was my house. It's [ __ ]
annoying. Oh, it's so [ __ ] annoying.
It's [ __ ] bastard annoying, bro. It's
so [ __ ] annoying, isn't it, bro? Even
if it's just £100. It's so [ __ ] annoying.
They shouldn't let people deposit money
if they're just going to cheat. It takes
all the fun out of it. If they're just
going to cheat. Yeah. If they're just
going to cheat, which they do cheat
because they're cheap bastards. They
can't offer a fair game. What's the
point of letting people even play it?
Yeah, it was just online roulette. I
only put £100 in it. Not the point. It
doesn't matter how much it is. It could
be [ __ ] 10 p. I'd still react the
same. I don't give a [ __ ] Something
that people with no life experience
don't understand. But yeah,
[ __ ] madness, bro. What the [ __ ]
Yeah, it was just online rude that bro.
That's one of the reasons I've gone
live. I would have went live if it
wasn't for that.
[ __ ] so annoying. It's so fixed.
Like I'm not even chatting [ __ ] bro. It
is so [ __ ] fixed. I don't even know
why I [ __ ] even played it 3 weeks after.
[ __ ] knows, bro.
Definitely fixed though. Definitely fixed.
Definitely fixed, lad.
It loves that loser. It loves that
loser, Mr. B. It loves that loser, don't it? Yeah.
It's a bit [ __ ] in it. Oh well. Yep.
I only put £100 in it for a reason.
Why can't you win? I don't understand.
Why can't you win anymore, bro? What the [ __ ] Damn.
Yeah, I'm not addicted. Yeah, I'm not
addicted. But thank you, bro. And no,
I'm not prepared to lose. I'm gambling
to win. So, when I put 100 pound in, I'm
wanting to win. I'm not wanting to lose. Yeah.
But yeah, I'm not addicted anyways. But
thank you. Cuz I wouldn't have money if
I was addicted.
Oh, you're just a [ __ ] You're using
the word skin. Oh, yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
There's no point trying to explain to
someone with a low IQ then. Oh, you're
using the word skin. Yeah. Well, I'm not
addicted. So, yeah. Thank you. Thank you
for the advice, though. Anyways,
see, this is what these people think.
These people in this community think or
or people in general, they seem to
think, dusty, that you need to be skinty.
They need to think they think that you
need to lose all your money or a big sum
of money for in order for it to affect
you. They don't understand. They got no
life experience. They really really
don't. Like trying to explain it to
these people is is is is stupid, bro. To be honest.
Well, I'm not prepared to lose because
I'm gambling to win. So, I'm not
prepared to lose. I'm not prepared to
lose. And you don't even think about
whether you're going to win or you just
put it in hoping that you [ __ ] win.
It's as simple as that. You put it in
hoping that you [ __ ] win.
And you can go away, Indigo. You
two-faced [ __ ] disabled [ __ ] I've
seen you [ __ ] comment so much [ __ ] on
other people's channel. Yeah, you ain't
got anyone's money stopped and I've got
more money than you and your [ __ ]
boyfriend. You stupid little [ __ ] You
disabled little prick. Don't [ __ ]
come on here. You can have a timeout for your two-fac
[ __ ] There you go.
You [ __ ] disabled [ __ ]
Yeah, proper two-faced [ __ ] ears, bro.
I've caught him on so much [ __ ] Not not
recent, not um today, but I caught him
the other day, bro. Like days and days
and days ago. Yeah,
I'm fed up, bro.
I'm really really fed up. That's so
annoying, bro. It's so so so [ __ ]
annoying, isn't it? This was my house, I
would smash this whole house up, bro.
Smash up £500 worth of [ __ ] Yeah,
they seem to think that just because
it's not uh
they seem to think that just because you
have money, it's okay. It ain't okay.
Doesn't matter how much money you have,
doesn't matter how much money you lose,
it doesn't matter. Losing ain't an
option. It's as simple as that. You're
gambling to win. You're not gambling to lose.
So yeah, I feel like seriously harming
someone badly, bro.
I need to I need to be quiet though cuz
someone had like a funeral next door and
stuff and they're still like crying and
that. So they don't want to hear my
[ __ ] do they? So you don't know what
I'm like. You really really don't know
what I'm like, bro. Trust me, you really
don't know what I'm like. Honestly, you don't.
Trust me, it's [ __ ]
It's absolute rigged [ __ ] That's
what it is. Rigged [ __ ] bro.
They think just because it's £100, they
they don't understand anything. The
people in this community, bro, they're [ __ ] thick.
See you later, disabled [ __ ]
I've got more money than you'd ever
have. See you later. So, yeah, this is
what I'm trying to say. Um, you can't,
Dusty, you can't talk about gambling to
anyone, be it Reddit, be it YouTube,
because they think, right, that if
you've lost a small amount of money and
you've still got money, it's okay. It
ain't okay. None of it is okay. Losing
is not an option. It's as simple as
that. It is as simple as that, bro. If I
if I lost, right, say for example, I was
out and I and 200 fell out my wallet,
I'd be like, "Oh, [ __ ] 200 fell out of
my wallet." If I lost 50 pound, I'd
smash up every single establishment.
It's as simple as that, bro. Yeah. And
that's how I'm like. That's literally
I Okay, let me put let me let me use
this analogy. I could lose I could drop
£200 out of my wallet
and have 900 left. Let's just say for
example, I'd be like, "Oh, [ __ ] Lost 2000.
See you later." Disabled. You laugh at
yourselves. But anyways,
um Oh, I could lose £100 and have five
grand left and I'd smash up the whole
base, bro. I tell you something, Dusty. Yeah.
You know what I mean?
I'm so glad I got banned from them
casinos, bro. V actually done me a favor.
But I reckon if I kept going, bro, I
would have seriously hurt one of them
managers, bro. I'm not even joking.
It's annoying. That's what it is. It's
>> with an E and I don't know. How about
that, bro? Yeah.
And they seem to think just because
you've got money, it's okay. I don't
know why they seem to think that, Dusty.
Just because people have got money, it's
it's not okay, bro. It's not okay. Yeah.
You saw what I done to the old house.
You saw what I done to the old house,
bro. Doesn't matter what I'm planning.
That's none of your business.
My life's none of your business.
That's got nothing to do with you. We're
talking about gambling.
See you later, lad. Two-faced [ __ ]
Yeah, but I won't be on here long anyways.
So, yeah. You have the urge to go live.
Every time you gamble, Dusty, you get
the urge to go live. Yeah.
There's certain things you can't say on
Reddit. There's certain things you can't
say on um YouTube and stuff. There's
certain things because people would never understand.
Like me, I'm not addicted to gambling. Self-projecting.
Self-projecting. White Knight. See you
later. Um, there's certain there's
certain like say for example, Dusty, I
went on Reddit now and said this, they
would think that you're addicted to gambling,
but you've made about five accounts,
bro. Get a life already.
Five. You've already made You've made
five accounts, bro. Get a life. [ __ ] me.
Yeah. So, you can't go on Reddit. You
can't ask anyone anything because they
they would just say that you're addicted
when you're clearly not addicted.
He's uh what you call addicted is people
like Timmy. Timmy
um I mean there's people that gamble
every day. I mean that's addiction.
You're not addicted, bro. I'm not
addicted. But they think because you
don't react the way that they want you
to react, you're addicted.
You want Does that make sense, Dusty?
Because you're not reacting the way they
want you to react. Oh, it's all right.
Oh, it's only £,500. No.
What the [ __ ] are you talking about, you
idiot, man? That's the fifth sixth
account you've made now, bro. Get a
life. Seriously, get a life.
See, no such thing as gambling responsibly.
No such thing, Dusty. There's no such
thing. If you don't react the way people
want you to react, they'll say that
you're addicted. They'll say that you've
got a problem. And it's clear as day
that I kind of [ __ ] don't. Do you
understand? I don't have no addictions.
I don't even have a Coca-Cola addiction anymore. Mad.
That is mad, bro.
That is depressing as [ __ ]
But secular slot says, "Oh, well, if
it's money you could afford to lose,
sick account now, bro." Yeah.
Oh my [ __ ] god.
Bro, you people are [ __ ] weirdos over
here. Is there anyone in here that can
have like a normal conversation? This is
why people don't go live anymore. None
of you people can have a normal
conversation. You're just all [ __ ]
weird low lives.
I saw Monty copy my sayings again the other day.
Got people messaging me. I don't even
want to talk to them.
I don't even want to talk to them, bro.
Dusty, that's how bad it is. That's how
it literally gets you, bro.
Doesn't matter if you got money. Doesn't
matter if you gamble, you can afford to
lose. Just losing and them having the
last laugh is enough to put anyone into
a depression. And I don't care if I
gambled. Simple. I don't care if I chose
it. Chose to gamble.
I don't care what I chose to do, bro.
Yeah, of course you got 200 accounts cuz
you got no life. You're a fat ugly [ __ ]
that ain't got a life.
You're a little low life and it proves
it. Making accounts just to get blocked.
You're a low life. You're laughing at
yourself. You [ __ ]
200 accounts cuz you're some fat ugly
old man that ain't got no life. Probably
in a wheelchair. Yeah, bro. Come on
another account. Get blocked again. Simple. Yeah, man. Mad madness.
But as they say,
as long as it's money you can afford to lose,
what are you talking about, bro?
What the [ __ ] is this?
Um, one sec. Incel.
Do you not find it weird?
Isn't it weird how an incel like me has
had more women than you do though?
Yeah. Isn't it weird how you claim I'm an insult,
but I've had more women than you? Isn't
that a bit embarrassing, lad? Isn't it
mad how someone you've called an incel,
right, isn't a virgin like you? You not
find that a bit strange? Yeah. Oh, you
say you got kids. Oh, you're from the
other day, aren't you, bro? You're from
the other day. You were supposed to come
in and show us what you had, wasn't you?
Isn't it mad how an incel has been with
more women than you? I'd start looking
within, bro. If someone's an incel and
they've had more women than me, you
might just be the incel yourself.
You might just be the incel. You're
calling someone that's been with more
women than you would ever have an incel.
Make it make sense. You might actually
want to look up the definition of what
an incel is. It's not someone that's
been with more women than you, bro.
Trust me, it really, really isn't.
Yeah, man. Another one.
Yeah, you're not going to bother anyone,
Red Star. You're just a gay loser that
needs to come out the closet. Get a life.
Yeah, you need to you need to get a
life, lad. You don't bother no one. You
don't trigger no one.
I hope you're being paid a lot of money,
bro. I couldn't sit on YouTube for Hey,
do you know what I was doing yesterday?
Um, early UK asylum.
Do you know what I was doing yesterday, bro?
Jesus Christ. You get life. Do you know
what I was doing? Uh, earlier I say
earlier, I was looking on my messages.
Yeah. That I sent to my friend and guess what?
Okay. Do you want Do you want to join
now then? Fair enough. Do you want to join now?
Yeah, that's I was looking on the
messages, bro. And people like this Red
Star and stuff. Yeah, they've been doing
this for years.
Imagine that, bro. Being sat on YouTube
for years stalking men and you're trying
to tell me you're not a gay jealous
bastard. You're actually going to look
you're going to look someone in the
face. Yeah. So, some of it was from like April
20 20 23, bro. So, you're sat on YouTube
being a gay bastard for three years and
you really are telling people you're not
jealous. Oh, come on. No one. Bro,
listen. Like, listen, bro. Let Let me
explain this to you. Yeah. Even listen
to me. Yeah. UK signing. Even if
somebody said to me right now, "Yeah,
you have to sign this contract, right?
Just use this analogy. You've got to
sign this contract and we're going to
give you 2 million pound." Yeah. And but
you have to stalk some man every day on
YouTube for three years. I tell him to
[ __ ] off. Isn't that not telling you
everything that you need to know, bro?
These people are willingly doing this
every day. They're gay and jealous, bro.
And they don't they don't get paid to do
it. Like, they don't get paid to do it.
Obviously, they don't get paid to do it.
They are jealous. These people should be
stalking [ __ ] women. These people
should be trying to get with [ __ ]
women, bro. These people should be out
living their life. Am I lying? Yeah. You
You call me a troll and stuff. Yeah.
Listen, listen to me, bro. Yeah. You
call me a troll and all of this stuff,
but tell me I'm lying about what I'm
saying right now. Yeah, I've only gone
live because I'm pissed off because I've
lost this 100 pound gambling. But tell
me I'm lying, bro. Tell me I'm lying.
You can't. Cuz I'm right. I'm [ __ ]
right, bro. You can even pay someone 23
million to do this for years, bro. Let
alone do it for [ __ ] free. You know
what I'm saying? Say yeah. Yeah,
bro. Your mom must be the biggest slag
ever, bro. Because I don't know what
you're talking about. My mom's be My
mom's being robbed by random men. Bro,
that must be your mom cuz there's
nothing to do with my mom. But okay. But
yeah. Do you understand what I'm saying,
lad? Like uh
it is a truth though. No, no, no. But it
is. You take the piss. But it but it is
though cuz think about it, bro. Yeah.
They have to sit on YouTube from the
time they wake up to the time they go to
bed stalking and recording men. You
think that could ever be me, bro? Do you
literally literally think that could
ever be me?
Do you think I could throw away years of
my life stalking men online? I couldn't
even do it to women online, bro. So, let
alone men. Do do not see the weirdness,
the gayness, the jealousiness, if that's
even a [ __ ] word. But if it isn't,
I've just made it up. And that's why
Monty man says what I say, bro. See,
look. This is exactly what I'm saying.
It proves my point, bro. They don't get
a reaction, but they can still do it,
bro. It just goes to show that they're
jealous nobodyies. It proves my point.
The more years they do this, the more it
proves that I'm right about them.
You know what I'm saying, lad?
Do you understand? It just shows that
they've got nothing in their lives. Cuz
if you couldn't pay me 2 million to do
this for 3 years, how are people
casually doing it every day for years?
Unless they're gay and jealous. That's
why Monty man says these things. He gets
it from me, bro. Everything Monty Man
says, he he copies from me. Ask him to
elaborate one day, he can't do it. Ask
him to elaborate one day, he can't do
it, bro. He can't elaborate. He just
says things for the sake of saying [ __ ]
You know what I'm saying, bro? But he
doesn't know. You know what I'm saying?
You can never have me on YouTube
stalking no man for years, bro,
recording [ __ ] Hell no, bro. I've got a
life to live and I've got places to be,
which is why I'm not on here much. Am I lying?
Am I lying, bro?
Am I lying? Come on. Yeah.
If you had the live, you would not be
doing this every day. If you people are
alive, you wouldn't be doing this every day.
I don't know. No, they don't even troll
me. They just self-reflect. And yeah,
there's a few of them.
But I'm talking about like, yeah,
you look at this, bro. He's gay. They're gay, bro.
They're [ __ ] gay, lad.
That's why Monty man copies me. He's a copycat, bro. M.
Yeah, you could never have me sat on
YouTube every day stalking men
unless I was gay and jealous. That's the
only thing I could I could think of,
man. And have I gotten all I'm not
talking about my life on the uh Wister,
my love life and people and and and
stuff like that. I'm not I'm not talking
about it, bro. But I gambled just now
and I lost £100. I went [ __ ] I went
mad, bro. But I had to calm down a
little bit. I was saying I don't know
why they let people deposit if they're
just going to rig it. What's the point
of letting people play if they're just
going to cheat? What's the point of
letting people play if they're just
going to cheat?
First time in I think it was like two
and a half, three weeks. So, yeah, done. No more.
Anyways, I'm going to put the link up so
you can join and show us what you've
got, Wormsy, cuz you were supposed to uh
come on the other day. I do remember
you. Yeah. So you can come on the live
stream and show us everything that you've got.
Your looks, your money, your house, your
car. Let's Let's see all of these things
that you've got. Come on.
Come on, bro. Come on.
I don't know, bro.
I just find it strange how men can
casually come on here every day for
years stalking other men for years.
Got to be jealous and gay, bro. I don't
know what else it could be unless they
were jealous and gay. Cuz the real
question is why are they not living
their life? The real question is why are
they not out with their misses?
Yeah, that's self projecting. Go away, lad.
Bro, you can you can come on here right
for another 13 15 years repeating the
word skint m, but it's not going to
change the fact that it's you people.
That's probably why you can't come up
with new sayings because you're talking
about yourselves. Okay, let's go by the
evidence, right? You people are on
YouTube 24/7, right? No lives. Am I
lying? No, I'm not lying. So, you're on
here. So, that means you got no money,
no misses, nothing going for yourselves.
It is [ __ ] proof. And then when
people have got channels dedicated to
people, it proves what I'm saying about
you even more. The shovel pushes even
more. You're gay and jealous. It's as
simple as that. Why do you think Monty
man loves my words, bro? Cuz I'm right
about it. Coming on here every day
stalking people cuz they're better
looking than you. That's what it is. A
lot of these people in this community,
bro, they're old, fat, and ugly. And
they hate you're better looking than
them. They hate God that you're better
looking than them and you can get women.
You got more money than them. That's why
they do all of this weirdness cuz they
hate that you're better looking than
them. They try to bring you down to
their level. Ugly skinn sat on YouTube
every day. I guarantee you, bro, Lord
J's going to be live in a bit and it's
going to be the same people that ain't
got no life. Am I lying? Tell me. Tell
me, bro. Tell me. Tell me. Tell me, bro.
Tell me. Come on. Come on.
Tell me if it's not, bro. Come on.
Yeah, that's it. Anyways, I'm not
talking about these little weasels anymore. Bad.
See you later.
I just never known people in my life so
desperate to get stranger men's attention.
Never, never have. To me, it's strange.
But to me, it's very, very strange.
To me, it's very, very, very strange.
Very, very, very strange, lad.
Obsessed with men that they don't know
for [ __ ] a million years. Mad,
mad, mad, mad.
Obviously, I've been on roller coasters,
you idiot. I'm [ __ ] 28 years of [ __ ] age. >> Yeah.
Losing that£100 [ __ ] pissed me off. I
get money every week anyways. I've still
got money anyways. But see,
I was going to do a video earlier.
No, not stealth. I know what it is. I
haven't been on that. I was going to do
a video earlier say and I was going to
title it UK asylum.
There's no point asking for dating
advice if you're a man.
See, you think I troll, but I don't
troll. I'm serious. And then it seems
that you can't even ask for dating uh
for advice if you gamble either.
So, from anyone,
I can write on Reddit right now about
gambling and guess what they're going to
come back and say to me? You're
addicted. You're not addicted
cuz you're not going to react the way
they want you to react. You're You've
got a problem. That's the way they see
it is you've got a problem because
you're not reacting the way they want
you to react.
Do you get me? That's it.
Someone's texting me. I can't even I
don't even want to reply. I don't even
want to talk to anyone. So yeah,
that was only £100 as well. Jesus Christ,
[ __ ] hell, man. You really can't
gamble, can you?
You really can't gamble, can you?
By you, I mean me. You really can't gamble, huh?
So so depressing in it, bro.
It's so annoying me, bro. So annoying me, man.
You're not coming in, you little virgin.
You get banned.
No one want that need to get off of
YouTube and go get laid.
There's quite a lot of these people in
here that need to do that to be honest with you.
There's a lot of them.
I went on um Is anyone still watching? I
went on Actually, I went on uh Lord
Jay's uh yesterday, bro. Or a little bit.
Was anyone else on there? Now, don't
worry, bro. I'm not going to talk about
anyone else. Yeah, because I mean, no
one else was really saying anything,
bro. So, bro, I saw this Jo on there and
every single comment was about me,
brother. Listen to me. You're not
getting my ass. I don't want you. I'm
not going to date you. You're not going
to [ __ ] shag me, right? So, I don't
know why every single comment of yours
is about me, you little gay boy. Every
single comment as well. No one else was
doing it, bro. But him. He's gay, bro.
He's a [ __ ]
He is an absolute [ __ ] Him. nonslegs,
Red Star, Jamie Thompson, they need to
literally book a room, bro, and and and
[ __ ] each other. Come out the closet
once and for all. Like, honestly, bro,
really, really, really, really.
Every comment, I don't even go on about
women like this.
For [ __ ] sake, that's when you know
there's a problem, bro.
That's when you know there's a problem.
That's when you know that like, yeah,
this is dodgy, bro. Proper proper proper dodgy.
When a heterosexual male is not as
bothered as women.
Oh, I don't need more luck, bro. I've
had more women than you'd ever have
women. I've had I've had more hot I've
had more women than you've had hot
dinners, lad. No, I know. I don't care,
Dustin. I'm just saying every single
comment was about me.
And when you're het When you're a
heterosexual male and you don't go on
about women the way they go on about
you, then Yeah, bro. This is dodgy. You don't understand.
He was he was writing some silly self-p
projecting comments saying about how how
I can only get big boobs if I paid. And
I'm thinking, bro, really? Everyone
knows my history and all of the people
that I've been with. Yeah, the guy's
gay, bro. The guy's simply gay. And no
one else was talking about me, only him.
He's simply gay.
No, I was going to do a video, but then
there's just like no point
cuz there is no point because the thing
is right in the end there's no point
because and then no what I was saying to
myself no actually what I was saying
actually what I was thinking I was
saying is that listen bro I'm not trying
to bring trouble to to this door yeah
I'm really really really not but the
thing is yeah if this guy is talking
about you on every single comment then
why don't he come and sort it out like
I'm not I'm not trying bro seriously I'm
not trying to start trouble Yeah, but
I'm just saying if you're really
obsessed with someone like that and
you're making every single comment about
me, then bro, you talk about people
sorting LT out, you talk about people
sorting Monty out, why don't you come
and sort it out, bro? You know where
people live. Like that's like what else
do you want someone to say, bro? Like,
if every single comment is about someone
when they're not even talking to you,
then bro, like you you you would have thought that [ __ ]
What the [ __ ] is going on out there?
Yeah, sorry about that, but it's [ __ ]
making so much noise. But yeah, bro, if
like every other com if every comment is
about someone, then bro, like why
haven't you comment out? Why haven't you
comment sorted it? It's as simple as
that, bro. Like, I'm having to [ __ ]
see your stupid little gay comments. Yeah.
Yo, I lost 100 pound on roulette.
Depressing, isn't it?
>> Yeah. Depressing as [ __ ] it.
Yeah. That one, man. question.
Someone's messaging me on WhatsApp. I
can't even talk to them, bro. So depressing.
You It literally It actually feels like
though you're like gobsmacked. Like you
can't even say anything, bro. It's so depressing.
It's so [ __ ] I don't give a [ __ ] if
it's only 100 pound. I don't give a [ __ ]
I don't give a [ __ ] if it's 20,30, 10 p.
I don't give a I don't give a monkeys.
[ __ ] How about that one? Yeah. You're
playing to win. You're not playing to lose.
And you're not even thinking before you
actually actually You're not thinking
before you actually play it.
You're not coming in Kevin Murphy. This
is 2026, lad. [ __ ] off. All I can say to
you, Kevin Murphy. I say this to you.
You know where I live.
You all right? I went to Liverpool. You
didn't show up. [ __ ] off. See you later.
How was that one for you, G? Simple, bro.
It's 2026, mate, and I've not seen you
in London calling anyone out. So, shut
the [ __ ] up. Go away, bro. You're done.
Bye. See you later, lad.
How these people can sit on here and do this, lad.
In 2026. It's mad.
2026. For [ __ ] sake. Was gay.
It's like that Jo. Every comment's about
me, but you don't see him coming on
people's door sorting stuff out. You get
me, bro? Think about it realistically.
Yeah. He talks about people not sorting
this out, not sorting that out. When
this guy, every single comment is about me,
but he hasn't come and done nothing about it.
So, what the [ __ ] bro?
Yeah, I lost 100 pound on roulette. Got
a so depressing in it. So so so depressing.
But people think it's okay just because
it's £100 and you've got money. No no no
no. Trust me. No no no no no no.
I'm having to be quiet, bro.
I'm having to hold it in.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no. That's not
the way it worked, bro.
Okay. Should we let this Kevin Murphy in?
Okay, let's see what he's got to say. Hello.
You're an ugly big.
>> See you later, Virgin.
Wow. Virgin boy is very desperate for my
attention, isn't he?
Very, very desperate for my attention. Gay boy.
Just like he's Master Joe. They're
[ __ ] gays. I'm telling you, UK
asylum, they're [ __ ] gays, lad.
Like I said, if they had a life, they
wouldn't be on here doing this.
Yeah, it's as simple as that. Bro, I
wasn't on here yesterday. I've only just
come on here now
because I because I lost money. I wanted
to talk about gambling cuz it's a
gambling. It's supposed to be a gambling
community, you see. Yeah, bro.
really you should ignore these people.
But bro, it's so like it's kind of
entertaining at the same time how they
can sit there and be obsessed with men
every day. It's mad, isn't it?
Madness, bro. Madness.
You know, I can kind of see why that
19year-old turned out to be a [ __ ]
Mr. B. I used to ditch her and I used to
lose money and stuff. I used to ditch her and
[ __ ] I was actually looking back on
some of the messages. I was like, "Oh, I
can actually kind of see it now." To be fair, bro,
I can actually kind of see it to be fair. Damn. Yeah.
Again, all gambling responsibly. mad.
Just fed up to be honest. Yeah.
Yeah. So, it's not the amount then, is it? No.
No. It's definitely not the amount.
No. The amount is irrelevant.
Losing is not an option. It's as simple
as that. Losing is not an option. You're
playing to win, not lose. Simple
friend in Amsterdam. Yeah, I'm a big
crybaby today. Yeah. Yeah. Today I'm a
big crybaby. I'm a big fat stinking
and I love it. Yeah.
I'm a big fat stinking crybaby. Mr. B.
That's what I am. Yeah. So, yeah.
Yeah. They didn't take no fees, so it
was literally just £100. Yeah. Doesn't matter.
Good old coding.
You know what? I've actually been
gambling responsibly for years. You know,
is that supposed to make anything better?
Doesn't matter what it is, bro. I can
get four in the lose right now with a
ticker main if I wanted to. There's no
point saying what it is.
There's no point saying what it is.
I'm on I'm on a diet anyways. I had some
chicken today and I went for a walk. Yeah,
I don't need to spend it on rent.
I don't need to spend it on rent. I
don't pay rent.
Yeah, I'm not getting a curry today. I
think I'm going to get a takeaway on
Friday or Saturday, bro.
I'm already looking healthier to be fair. So yeah,
gambling just [ __ ] up everything. Every
time, bro. Every single time.
Just ruins everything. Doesn't matter
how much the money is. Doesn't matter.
The worst is when you lose. Yeah. I
think the worst is losing in a casino.
That is the worst.
Doesn't matter where I, bro. That's none
of your business. My living
circumstances have got nothing to do with you.
That's literally got nothing to do with
you. My living my living circumstances
have got nothing to do with you, lad.
Don't you worry about where I live.
Focus on your own life. I'm only here to provide content
and talk about gambling
and talk about these people that ain't
got a life.
Yeah. Worry about your own life, lad.
So, mate, I think it's weird. Do you
know what I find even more weird? You
people sat on YouTube every day in your
40s, but you don't see me complaining.
I think that's even more weirder.
grown ass men sat on YouTube stalking
other men every day. I think that's a
bit weird to be fair, but you don't see
me crying about it.
Yeah, that's very, very weird. Focus on
your own life. Sort you out, sort your
own problems out before trying to judge other people. Simple.
I know I didn't cover number seven.
I hit eight. Yeah. And I got it to 137
and I lost it. I was 100 pound in 137
which is typical is it soon as you up
the ante or you keep repeating you lose
lose lose lose lose lose and you know
it's fixed as well you know it's fixed
as well because you don't hit any
numbers like any numbers at all it's so fixed
double six oh yeah it was it was double
yeah double Six.
Yeah. Double six.
Double [ __ ] six. Yeah, of course it
was. [ __ ] off. Yeah.
Yeah. I'm not having a curry for a
couple of days. Uh,
well, that just goes to show you ain't
got no life experience because most
people that live in London live with
their parents or they live in a room.
So, that just goes to show you've got no life experience.
That just goes to show that you've got
absolutely no life experience.
Why would someone It's actually the
smart thing to do. So what you want
somebody to go to work, right, and pay
most of their wages on rent. Why not?
Why Why not just live with your parent?
So you want somebody to go to work and
spend more money on rent and then
they're going to be more stressed about
their finances. What does that do? I
mean I mean what the [ __ ] does that do?
How how's that going to help anyone?
Most people in London live with their
parents or they live in a room.
Yeah. And I'm in a better better
position than you people. Yeah. I'm in a
better position than you people. I'm
going traveling soon, which is why I've
saved money. I'm I mate. I'm traveling
soon. So, you know, that's why I've
started saving money up and stuff. So,
yeah. Which this allows me to do.
Yeah, bro. So, yeah. It's better than
[ __ ] going to work and spending more
than half your wages on rent. That's not
solving any problems.
That's not solving any problems, you
know. You got to be smart about this
[ __ ] you know.
You got to be smart about this [ __ ] Yeah.
Yeah. So, I'll be traveling soon anyways.
And I wouldn't move and I wouldn't move
out unless I met someone and I was in a
relationship. I wouldn't move out. I'm
smart. I'm not stupid,
right? I'm smart and not stupid. That's the thing.
Um, so unless you met someone and you
was in a well you was in a relationship
with someone, it it's pretty pointless
to go to work just to pay most your
wages on rent to be fair. But yeah,
I mean this this is 2026.
It's literally 2026. Yeah. No. Mm-
No. Just you could just split the rent.
You could just you could just find
somewhere and split the rent. I wouldn't
rent somewhere anyways. Well, I'm saying
I wouldn't even I probably wouldn't even
rent somewhere. Renting somewhere is a con
to be fair.
You might as well [ __ ] put money down
for a [ __ ] a house deposit, you know?
Yeah. Why are you so concerned anyways, lad?
Well, I wouldn't rent.
I wouldn't rent, lad. Simple as that. I wouldn't rent.
So, I don't even know why we're talking
about my living circumstances to be
honest with you. Jesus Christ.
I find what you people in here do every
day very weird. But you don't see me crying.
You know what is is the weirdest thing
about you people in here yet? It's the
fact that like you are what
and that's it. Yeah. So you do what you
do and that's it. People in law J and
whatever. So you do all of that. Yeah.
Okay. But then you try to talk about
other people that are better than you.
That's what makes me laugh. You try to
bring people down that are better
looking than you, have got more than
you, that's got more of a life than you.
That's what makes me that that's the
whole funny thing about it.
That's like the whole
thing that makes me die, bro.
That's the thing that makes you [ __ ]
like little [ __ ]
If you definitely wasn't jealous of
anyone, you wouldn't be doing it. You
wouldn't be doing what you do.
Should I get a curry today?
I don't know if I should get a curry today, bro.
I shouldn't, bro. I should I should I
need to really cut down on what I'm
eating, you know? Yeah.
Yeah, I probably won't to be honest.
Save myself for Friday.
I don't know what takeaway I'm going to
get Friday. Maybe
I I did have some I had like some food
today. It wasn't even that healthy. Just like chicken.
I don't need a job. I've got enough
money. I get enough money. I don't need a job.
I don't need a job, lad. Thanks for your
concern, though. I don't need a job.
I'm actually in a good position with money.
Got some savings.
Got to do Got to do get to do what I
want when I want. I don't I don't I
don't I don't need a job, lad.
I don't need a job, bro.
I can afford to take people on dates. I
can afford to go waxies. Yeah.
No responsibilities, no tenants. It's
lovely. Absolutely lovely. Oh, Dusty,
you never guess what? Yeah. Somebody
messaged me yesterday on Instagram.
Yeah. Someone who I used to see in
O'Neals. I've only seen him like a
couple of times. We kind of know know of
each other. He messaged me said, "Oh,
have you got £50?"
And I'm thinking, bro,
and I'm thinking, what is it with these
people looking at me for money? He
probably still thinks that I've got
loads and loads and loads and loads of
money like I did before because
obviously but no, he wouldn't have
because he wouldn't have seen my money.
But what is it with people always
looking at me for money? It's so [ __ ] annoying, bro.
Yeah, women see this, women see that.
You don't know anything about women,
lad. You don't know a damn thing about women.
You have no clue, you little white
knight. You little s. Yeah,
>> you keep defending women, bro, and see
where that gets you in 50 years. Keep me updated.
It's like I said the other day. Yeah,
these white knights will still be defending women
at 90 years of age. They'll be like
they'll be on their deathbed
not being able to breathe. And women
hate them and women don't like them. But
they still defend them. They still
defend women even though women don't
like them. [ __ ] mad.
And And you need to ask yourself, UK
Asylum, why do they do it? No, no, no,
no. Let's just have this debate. Yeah.
Why do they do it, bro? Cuz whether I
was in a relationship, whether I was
single, if I was a virgin, which which
I'm not. If I was banging [ __ ] every
day, I'd have exactly the same opinion.
Do you know why? Do you know why, Dusty?
Because more women are bad than good. So
even if there was good women out there,
mo most are bad. And the way I see this
is they're not kids, bro. They're not
innocent. They're not babies. Most of
them are [ __ ] [ __ ] That's
that's the way you describe them. But
yet you get all of these people that
don't get women defending them. It's
just something that will never make any
sense. It it it's just something that
will never ever ever make any sense. And
I'll say it to I'm blue in the face.
Even if I was a relationship
for 50 years, I'd have the same opinion
because let's face it, most are [ __ ]
It's as simple as that. Most are
absolute [ __ ] If they were if they
were if they were defending children,
Dusty, I'll be like, "Oh, well, children
are innocent." But do do you get the
point I'm trying to make? Like, women as
a whole are worse than men, and there's
women that will tell you that as well.
But then you get all of these white and
simps defending them that don't get
women. What the [ __ ] You know,
madness. And they still defend women.
It's [ __ ] mad.
And most of them are [ __ ] Most of them
are just [ __ ] [ __ ]
And they still defend them. I'd love to
know why they do it. I would love to
know why people that get no women will
sit there and defend these [ __ ] I
shall never [ __ ] know.
What? You think just because I'm talking
to Christian Izzy and I'm going to meet
her. Oh, I I don't have the same
opinion. No, I've still got the same
opinion. That tells you all you need to
know. What? One person that's normal in
four or five years. [ __ ] off, bro.
They're they're idiots. They're [ __ ]
I don't know why they do it. I seriously
don't know why they they they do it. cuz
it's not like they get anything out of it.
So, I'm trying to see like the motive.
You know what I'm saying, bro? I'd love
to know why they do it.
Defend the women, bro. They're [ __ ] idiots.
Actually speaking to someone off Tinder
as well, Dusty.
It's not like Yeah, Dusty. Like we're in the 1980s.
We're in the 19 [ __ ] '9s. Yeah. Where
women are good, women are feminine.
There's not even that. So why they would
sit there and continuously defend them
is very baffling.
It's very baffling, lad. Very baffling.
very very baffling that >> Yeah.
Wonder why they didn't take a fee this time.
Yeah. I wonder why they didn't take a
fee this time. Hey,
it's strange, isn't it?
Oh my [ __ ] god. Will you just [ __ ] off?
Leave me the [ __ ] alone.
Can you just leave me alone? What do you want?
>> Hey, Porky. How are you, my lip?
>> Porky, bro, you're the one that's obese,
lad. Nothing porky about me, matey.
>> You just said
because you need to watch,
>> you know. Yeah, because I want to be
healthy, bro. I want to have a better
body. Everyone needs to improve, bro.
You could have a worse body. Have you seen
>> Bro, even Yeah. And I'm not obese like
you. I have seen myself.
>> None of your t-shirts are strong.
Put your put your put yourself on camera.
>> Uh, no.
>> Yeah, cuz you're a fat ugly gun. Cuz
you're a fat ugly bastard.
>> So, Robert, you're so fat and ugly. You
can't even get a woman. Do you see you
sniffing around all you can't even get
yourself a woman? You [ __ ]
>> I have a woman.
>> You don't? Let's see her then.
>> Why did I show you my partner?
>> Okay. Do you know what? Yeah. Put the
camera on and show us your body.
>> Why? Gay.
>> Come on. No, no, no. Just don't show
your face. Just show your body. Come on.
>> Are you gay?
No, but show us another guy's body.
>> Show show us show us you're not fat.
>> Okay, I will.
>> Yeah, go on.
>> Once you show me your you and show us your body.
>> Once you show me you with your Stone
Island jumper on, I'll show you my body.
>> Um, well, I'm going out next week and
I'm going to be wearing my Stone Island
jumper. I'll show you if you want. Yeah,
>> you're not cuz it doesn't fit.
>> I will do I mean I I will do it on my
own terms. I don't do what fat ugly
people tell me to do like you. I already know.
>> I don't I don't do what virgins tell me
to do. But I'll be going out next week
and I'll show you. Yeah.
>> Why next week? Why next week?
>> Because I want to go out next week. I'm
meeting somebody next week.
>> You're not?
>> Yes, I am. So, do you want to see next
week then? Yeah.
>> I know you're not meeting anybody.
>> Okay. Well, we'll see, won't we?
>> Why did you have to take 10 days or
eight days off YouTube?
>> Uh cuz I've got a life on like you. You
should try it sometime. Get yourself a
little life. Are you sure it wasn't
because your mother was afraid of LT?
>> No. No one's afraid of LT and no one's
afraid of you. You're the one that's
being racist to people, but you will
never meet anyone. You're the one that's
scared of LT.
>> Are you not racist? >> Nope.
>> No, I'm not racist at all.
>> So, there's not a video of you running
away from Venom after calling him a monkey. No.
>> What was you What was you calling
people? Somalian pilot. You're the one that's racist.
>> No, I called him a Somalian pirate. Not a pilot.
>> Yeah. So that's racist.
>> How is it? He's a Somalian pirate.
>> Yeah. See you later anyways, lad. Sorry, bro.
See you later, lad.
I'm a me. Yeah.
What a sad bastard. I don't even know
why that comes up on my [ __ ] page, but
just sat on YouTube all day waiting to stalk men. Bad
foodie food foodie food food. I live
Yo, this community is so [ __ ] weird, bro.
This makes me [ __ ] laugh my ass off,
bro. Mate, I've not eaten my dinner. Seriously,
coming from someone that's a fat, ugly
bastard, fat and uglier than you. This
is what I'm saying, bro. They don't,
these people on here don't just live
their lives on here and just be them.
They try to talk [ __ ] about other people
that are literally better looking than
them, younger than them, in better shape
than them, and and has got more money than them.
This is what makes the whole community
disabled as [ __ ] Cuz everyone that they
talk about, they're worse off than them.
Like, yeah, literally [ __ ]
worse body, worse looks, worse
life. You know what I mean?
Strange people. Strange people.
I can't say too much on here because we
got stalkers and grasses. But yeah,
don't even want to tell you what I feel
like doing, bro. Yeah,
Where's greasy today?
like doing some [ __ ] bro. Really, really bad.
I just feel like doing some [ __ ] [ __ ] bro. Yeah.
But it doesn't matter though, does it?
Cuz it's only £100. So because you still
got money and that that's completely fine.
This phone does this weird thing where
Sorry, I had to reset my [ __ ] phone,
bro. It's [ __ ] dodgy, this phone,
man. Have to get a new one soon. Going
to wait for the eight to come out. And yeah,
not had it that long this far, have I? Yeah. Yeah, bro. Bam.
I feel like just being rude to this [ __ ]
that's messaging me, bro.
Feel like just being like plain like
rude to them.
That's how I get, bro. I don't like
[ __ ] [ __ ] bro. Here
we go. Fake smoky bee.
>> You fat bastard. You fat bastard. You
fat bastard. Who at all the pies? Who at
all the pies? Month at all the
>> you did cuz you're the one that's fat
and obese, lad. Stop selfjecting.
Anyways, on to what I was saying. Yeah.
So this person that's messaging me, I
feel like just messaging them back and it's [ __ ]
know what I mean, bro.
You know what I mean, bro? Think
it was two days ago. Yeah.
[ __ ] fed up, lad. [ __ ] fed up.
Yeah, I'll probably eat today again.
Does anyone else feel like they lose
their mind whenever they play roulette?
You just feel like you're lose you're
just losing your mind.
That's how I feel like. I feel like I've
lost my mind.
No, I just lost 100 pound on roulette.
[ __ ] depressed, bro.
Yeah, I just played roulette. I lost 100
pound, bro. It's [ __ ] depressing, isn't it?
I have quit, bro.
Obviously, I've quit, bro. That was the
first time in weeks, isn't it?
Yeah. I don't know why I done it.
I actually feel like going outside and
really hurting someone, bro. I shouldn't
even be saying it to be honest with you,
bro. There glasses.
I feel like really really hurting
someone, bro. I'm not even joking.
I've got money. Get enough money. Whatever.
I just feel like seriously injuring
someone, bro, and putting them in in
hospital. I'm not even joking, bro. I
swear to God.
It's the same [ __ ] every time, bro. I
got the 100 to 137 and then after that,
lose lose lose lose lose lose lose lose
lose. You can't win. What's the point of
letting someone deposit if then if
there's no way of someone winning? It's
pointless, bro. That's why I was like,
"Oh, let me just try a quick hundred."
What's the point of letting someone play
something if there's no chance of them winning?
That was the first time me playing
online roulette in No, that was probably
a month to be honest. Online roulette
was probably a month to be fair. More
than maybe more than a month.
What's the point? I don't understand.
What's the point if there's no way of winning?
80 90 numbers, nothing. Bro,
I'm having these women message me. I
don't even want to message them back.
I'm pissed off, bro.
I don't usually bother. I mean, would
you would you would you really class
£100 as bothering? Not really.
I gamble so small. Well, it's small to
compared to the money that I have that
it doesn't even count. It's not like
you're gambling half your money or like
say 40 35 40% of your money
then obviously I don't know I feel like
where I gamble so small
it doesn't like count. Does that make
sense? I done£10 on the football. I just
done 100 on roulette. That was the first
100 in [ __ ]
Yeah. Well, over a month.
So, obviously if I gamble like 5600,
7800 then and I lost then obviously it's
Yeah. You know,
I don't do it like Timmy, bro. I don't
gamble every day, every other day. It's
more like every other few weeks if that.
You get me? So yeah, bro.
I was just so bored.
Yeah, I don't even have an issue, bro. I
rarely gamble. I actually do rarely
I've got my bills paid.
I eat Well, I'm on a I'm I'm kind of
cutting back on food cuz I want my body
to be a bit better. So, I'm going to
start training soon. But
yeah, um I want to I want to get a
vindaloo today, but nah, I want to cut
back on takeaways and stuff, bro. I
really need to start saving money and
looking better as well, bro. I'm not
getting any younger. So,
the more you go without a takeaway, the
more you enjoy it when you do get one as
well. It's I'm going to cut it down to
like once or twice a week. I'm going to
have like takeaways once or twice a week.
It's something to look forward to as
well. So, I'm going to have one on
Saturday. Friday or Saturday.
Yeah, I need to save some money as well, bro. So,
I've got money, bro. I'm actually in a
good position with money.
I really have, bro. You know,
I'm actually in a good position with
money actually, Bob.
I get money weekly as well. So, yeah.
Yeah. I'm in a good position, bro.
Like five, six years ago, I used to be
skinned, bro. Now I'm not skinned. Even
without the sublet and nah, I still get
money, bro. I still have money.
I'm too smart with money, bro. Trust me,
I prefer the not sublet to be fair, bro.
Cuz this way I don't have to beg people
for money. I don't have to chase for
money. I've got savings, so I prefer it,
bro. They're not subleting, to be fair.
I'd rather get half of what I was
getting and not have the responsibility.
I know it sounds mad, isn't it? I know
it sounds [ __ ] mad, but seriously,
bro, really, I really would.
I hate people. So, anything where I
don't have to deal with people is better
for me. It's as simple as that.
No, I'm not tempted to gamble again,
bro. I'm a [ __ ]
Yeah, bro. So, I'm not going to be
gambling, bro, again.
It's such a small amount of money. It
It's like it doesn't even make a difference.
So there's no way there's no gambling responsibly, bro.
I don't know, bro.
Maybe a couple hundred.
I would have maybe just went out
Thursday. No, I I still don't think I
would have went out this week. I don't
like drinking every week. I like I don't
like drinking every week, bro. And I can
afford it. I can afford it. I can go out
whenever I want. I just don't like
drinking every week.
I don't really like drinking much
anymore to be honest.
I have to be really bored for me to go
out and drink.
Maybe in the summer I might do more.
Maybe. I don't know. I don't know, bro. 500, 600.
I don't think I would have went out
regardless because I've got the money to
go out. So, I don't know, bro.
>> Yeah. About Yeah.
Gambling [ __ ] in it, lad.
Yeah. 100 pound, bro.
Yeah, I had some chicken earlier from
the chicken shop. I walked there, walked
back. I'm not eating again today.
I need to kind of lose some some of my
belly fat, bro. To be fair.
I don't need to, but I want to. I'm not
fat anyways, but I mean like, you know,
my belly and [ __ ] in it. So, yeah.
Take away Friday or Saturday.
I don't know what I was trying to win. I
don't even need to win money. I've got
money. I don't know. I don't know why
I've done it, bro. So, yeah.
Fancy a curry today, but sorry. Can't do
it, mate. Cannot do it,
bro. That was my first time in like a
month of playing it. Well, I played 60
pound like two and a half weeks ago.
Bro, I don't play it that much. Listen,
Timmy is the one that's addicted, not
me. If I was addicted, I would have no money.
I'd be gambling every day. Every I would
have no money, bro.
Do you understand? If I was I would have
literally no money.
Yeah. That was the first time in ages, bro.
I think I was just bored. I thought, oh,
let me just try it. But no, nothing. I
hit an eight and then after that, no man's land.
But at least they didn't charge me a
deposit fee, which was good. Some reason
that time they never charged me a deposit fee.
Or did they?
Let me have a look. How much did I have
in my account? No, I don't think they
did. One second.
What was it? I don't think they did.
Hey, they never That's weird that this
time they never
I had something 50 in my account and I
was just £100 minus. Yeah.
Yeah. It was only £100, bro.
Laney spent £50 on something today, so I
thought I I'll put £100.
Yeah, I'm speaking to some woman on Tinder
who's talking about [ __ ] yesterday and stuff.
We're talking about [ __ ] Steven Howard. But yeah,
we was talking about [ __ ] I was
talking to her earlier.
Uh, I had
1 pound 50. No.
Yeah, I had 1 pound50 on it. Sorry.
So, it got me to 137
and then after that I just lost. So,
when I was up in the stakes, lose, lose,
lose, lose, lose.
Someone was like, "Oh, yeah, like if
somebody wants to be your friend, you
could be their friend. I'll never be
friends with a woman. I don't want to be
friends. I've got enough friends. Thank
you very much."
Well, I don't like people.
The only people I speak to is
Christian Izzy, Ant-Man, my mom, and
like three other people. I don't like
people. I don't like people's ways.
You understand me? Um Bob, I just don't like people.
It's as simple as that.
There's, you know, Ant-Man and that like
that's my man in it, bro. We've been
been speaking for years and years and
years, bro. But like, I mean, generally,
I just don't like the way people are,
the way people move. I've got enough
life experience to know what people are
like. You know, I had somebody from
O'Neal, this guy used to see in O'Neal,
he messaged me yesterday on Instagram. I
barely know the guy. Oh, can I lend £50?
Sit with people looking at me for money
all the time. I'm sick of it, bro. I'm
sick of it. You know, when people talk
to you, it's always like there's an ulterior motive.
And I'm sick of it. I don't like people.
Simple. Like, it's as simple as that,
bro. And you know what? like the tenant
was trying to do the other day. I just
don't like people, bro. But now I ain't
got the house, bro. That's fine. I've
got money. I've got savings. That's
absolutely fine, bro. I've well
adjusted. Got more than enough money.
I don't have that headache anymore. It's
[ __ ] lush. [ __ ] lovely, bro.
And yeah, I just don't like the way
people are, Bob. Simple as that.
For [ __ ] sake, I don't even speak to
one of my sisters for [ __ ] sake. So,
at the end of the day, that's I just
don't like people.
Like I said, lad, the thing is if I was,
bro, if I was a if I was a bro, I'm
telling you right now, bro, if I was a
millionaire Yeah. If I was a millionaire
Yeah. I'd [ __ ] I uh if I was a
millionaire, I would just have a load of
dogs like what poor Grady had. That's
what I would do. Have a load of dogs. I
can see why he done that, you know,
had all them dogs. I I can see it. No, I
can actually see it, bro. Dogs are very
loyal. They Bro, I actually would, you
know, swear down. I actually I'd do
exactly what he done. Just have I'd have
three dogs. I tell you know, I'd have
three dogs. A Dalmatian, a Rock Riler,
and a Frenchie. Bam. And have them all
from puppies. I would have dogs, bro.
That's what that's, you know, in.
Yeah, I might get half the money now,
but I'd rather half the money, bro, and
not the stress
having to ask for money and then ask
again and [ __ ] all that, bro. The less I
need to deal with people, the better.
I don't need to if I, you know, I don't
want to deal with people if I don't um
if I don't want to if I don't need to. Sorry.
Like I said, I speak to Ant-Man and a
couple of other people and that's it.
And the other people that I meet,
they're acquaintances. I just call them acquaintances,
you know, people to go out with and stuff, but
obviously I do speak to people and
whatever, like, but yeah, [ __ ] I try
not to have anything to do with most
people to be fair.
Yeah. And he's asking me for £50, which
is strange because if you ask someone
for £50, you never hear the last of it.
You need to understand, bro, like
everyone's out for themselves.
Born alone, die alone, and that's it.
It's as simple as that.
So yeah, I would that's the doggies that
I would have.
See, dogs are good, you know. You look
after dogs, they'll they'll love you
forever. They'll never forget you. They
don't Trust me, bro. Like
Yeah. Just don't like people. Simple as that.
women. I don't like any of that stuff,
bro. Don't like the double standards.
I don't know. Like, obviously, he
probably would have gave the money back,
but I don't understand why he's messaging me.
But he probably was would have just gave
it back, but I don't know why you're
looking at me for money. This is the
fourth person that has done this now,
bro. I'm not [ __ ] minted. You know
what I mean?
No, he lives with my he lives with my
sister, bro. And I don't speak to my
sister. There's one sister I don't speak to.
So yeah, [ __ ] her [ __ ] Anyways, but yeah. Um yeah, man.
I don't see King anymore. I probably
will never see King ever again.
Well, we'll get our own dog anyway, bro. Like,
I think that guy Yeah, but I don't think
he ever saw me with money when I used to
have them 50 notes. That's what I was thinking. Yeah.
Yeah. But he would have gave the money
back. This guy would have, but the
tenant, he weren't going to give that
money back, mate.
I think this guy was just He just wanted
£50. But it was annoying that he was asking
it was annoying that he was asking me
because why? Where's everyone else? Why
are they asking you?
But yeah, they
Yeah, that tenant, bro. Oh, man. Then he
started getting racist.
[ __ ] stupid [ __ ]
He never replied back to that voice note
though, did he? No.
Never replied back to that voice note. I
had to put the [ __ ] in his place. So yeah.
Oh, here we go.
Um, he was racist because he was saying
about how like this is why white guys
die alone. And I said, "Bro, I'm pretty
sure white guys would rather die alone
than be thieving Pakistanis like you.
Stealing my after shave, stealing my um
um stealing my after shave, stealing my
t-shirt, and then not admitting it.
So yeah, cuz I knew what he was trying
to do. It's as simple as that, bro.
Like, so yeah, I'm glad, bro, about that
house. I'm glad. Very, very glad.
I'm very glad.
Yeah, you might only get half the money, but um yeah,
and them army guys started acting weird as well.
Them army lads started acting really weird.
So, I was messaging one, he doesn't reply anymore.
So, I'm saying people are just so weird.
People move so weird, bro. Like in
different ways. You get me?
>> You know what? Yeah.
You know, have you ever like understood
why people white knight and simp bob?
Cuz this I was going to do a video
earlier. I was going to be like there's
no point men asking for advice on women.
There's no point like whether it's
Reddit, whether it's real life.
Um, it doesn't matter to be honest because
there's no point asking for dating
advice if you're a man
because if you ask for dating advice
when you're a man, they're biased from
the get- go. There's double standards
from the get- go. They'll make excuses
for women. They will have all these
little rules that you need to follow
that they don't. So, why would anyone
even ask for advice?
You know, like I've said to you before,
bro, you want to meet a woman within
days of speaking to her. Oh, you're
coming on too strong. You're coming on
too, you're trying to meet them too
fast. But yet, when a woman wants to
meet you and [ __ ] you straight away, no
one's got a problem.
So, there's always going to be this
thing of double standards and biasness.
So, why would there you can't ever get advice.
You can't ever ever ever get advice from anyone
cuz no matter what you do, you'll be
wrong. Even if you took their advice.
Yeah. Let's just say you took someone's
advice, right? You you took their
advice, then they would tell you to do
something else. Like there's no there's no point.
And what I don't understand is Bob, most
women are bad. Let's just say that we
don't know all women. Yeah, we know that
most women are [ __ ] We know that most
women are [ __ ] Like, we've got the
evidence and everything. So, why do
people still defend them?
I'll have I'll do a podcast one day and
I want someone to sit and actually
explain it to me why people defend
women, right, when most of them are just
[ __ ] [ __ ] Like, they they
literally most of them are. Even if
there were some good ones out there,
most of them are not good. So why do
people defend them the way the way they defend them?
I don't know why they do. Why? Why do
they do that?
It doesn't make any sense.
No, it's not even just that though, bro.
But it's not even just that. It's like
you get these people defending them,
right? when bear in mind Bob I've met
more women than probably
most people probably most people right
and I've been with women and I've had
sex and I'm telling you straight they are [ __ ]
most of them are [ __ ] so why do people
defend them when most of them are [ __ ]
and they're not just [ __ ] to me because
when I was on my 3 month break when I
was on my 3 month break yeah I was
watching other people and they were
getting the same [ __ ] Ed Matthews was
getting the same [ __ ] [ __ ] in all of
these kick streamers. So, it's not they
can't even just say, "Oh, well, they're
like it to you." They're like it to
everyone. Most people,
so they're [ __ ] right? And then you
got that, but then you got people
defending them when they are worse than
[ __ ] men. What the [ __ ] Doesn't make
sense. I'll never defend them. I don't
care if Christian is talking to me and
she's going to meet me. I don't care.
I'll never defend them because I know
what they're like. I've had enough life
experience to know what they're [ __ ]
like. But how people sit there and
defend them is [ __ ] beyond me.
Kids, children. Oh yeah, I agree with
that. If you defend children, I can I
can get it. I get it. If you defend
children, cuz children are innocent. You
see what I mean, Bob? If people's
defending kids, then we can say, "Oh,
well, kids are innocent." But women are
very, very far from innocent. Yet you
get these people that defend them.
the leading on the piss taking on
purpose. What the [ __ ] bro? Where does
that come from? Them, you know? So,
so I don't know why they get defended
the way they do. Swear to God, bro. If a
white knight ever comes up to me again,
I'll break their [ __ ] jaw. I'm not
even joking, bro.
Like, I don't know how to explain it.
You might not be able to relate, bro,
because you haven't had the experiences
that I've had. But
it's hard to explain it, bro. It maybe
you haven't approached as many people as I have.
Do you get what I'm saying? Steven Howard.
Am I making sense what I'm saying?
Hopefully I am.
They're just [ __ ]
They are actually [ __ ] bro. Really
are. And I don't care if they gave me
sex. They didn't give me sex. They dated
me. Then I would still say the same
thing, bro. I'm blew in the [ __ ] face.
So, what's your plans anyways?
What's your plans anyways?
You know, I gave up for three months,
Stephen Howard. The last time I went
out, bro, two weeks ago. That was That
was three months. That was a long break, isn't it?
That was a long break, bro.
And if I get [ __ ] over again, lad,
I'll never be trying again. So that's that.
So yeah, bro.
I don't know why they defend them. Bro,
see the thing is, bro, like it's not
even like you're meeting people and
they're saying that they're not
interested in dating. Bob, it's not even
like they're like they're saying like
say you're approaching them and they're
saying, "Oh, they're not looking to
date." And they're being honest. then
you can't hate people, but it's actually
what they do. Like the entitlement, the
attitude, the leading on the game
playing, and then you casually have
people defending them every day. That's
the bit that baffles me, bro. Like, it
really really does baffle me. It's not
even like you you're approaching
someone, right, and things are not going
your way. It's actually what they do.
Does that make sense?
Just like Nodle Legs defends women and
women don't like him. Women hate him.
He's had less women than me. And he
still defends them. He will still defend women.
He will still [ __ ] defend women.
How does that make any sense? Can you
please tell me how that makes sense?
It doesn't make sense, does it? Yeah. So, yeah.
What content do you want to see?
What content do you want to see, bro? Yeah,
I don't know what content you want. I'm
hungry, bro, but I'm not eating today.
[ __ ] that. Can't be asked.
Not in a mood.
Yeah, but I don't want to do nights out, bro.
Why am I going to do nights out? Do not
understand. It's going to get me
depressed again, bro. Doing this night's out.
It's just going to It's just depressing
as [ __ ] Why am I going to do that? It's
depressing as [ __ ] Yeah.
Why do you think I gave up for 3 months, bro?
Why do you think I gave up?
No, I think we need to definitely go to Thailand, bro.
No, I think we definitely need to go. I
think we should go to another country
and start a new life somewhere, bro, for
like a couple of months.
Just book like a one-way flight and just
[ __ ] off. No, no. Like, I'm just
serious, bro. Because I'm done with all
of this this going out this [ __ ]
I'm done with it. Like, I I'll do it,
bro. I'm I'm I'm more than happy to do that.
I need to get the new fold when it comes
out. I'm done with all this night out.
I'd rather just like [ __ ] off to another country, bro.
Just do some madness. Just save a bit more. Yeah.
You know, I wouldn't have went out, bro.
I wouldn't have went out.
No, they don't. A lot. Most of these
women don't live long distance.
None of them live long distance.
Stop making excuses for them, bro.
They're [ __ ] I messaged someone the
other day. They didn't even reply back. Steven Howard,
I don't want to get back into the dating again, bro.
I'm pretty sure this Christian is uh
Christian is solid, bro. I don't want to
get back into dating again, bro.
Like, I've really made up my mind. I
went out the other day, two weeks ago,
cuz someone was annoying me, bro. Some
guy that owed me money. I really don't
want to get back into dating, bro.
I really don't want to get back into it.
I really don't want to, bro.
No, I don't want to get back into it
ever again, lad.
I don't know, bro. Yeah.
What's I don't understand what's the
point of trying to date in this country, lad.
Nah, bro. Not even much.
I don't think I will, bro.
I honestly don't think I will, lad. I
think I I will never I don't think I
will again, bro.
Unless it gets really I just don't see
the point in it.
Let's just say this Izzy doesn't go
anywhere, which I think it will. I don't
really see the point.
You might as well just [ __ ] off to another country.
I just don't really see the point on it
in it anymore.
Like you got YouTube, you got good
videos to watch, you can save money.
You've saved up one
[ __ ] idiot, bro.
[ __ ] [ __ ] was calling me.
But yeah, as I was saying, there's so
much to do, man. like,
you know, you can save money and,
you know, and just watch stuff on
YouTube and stuff. I don't see the point
in going out. What are you What are you
going out for, lad?
What are you going out for?
For what reason?
Someone's messaging me now. I can't I
can't even be bothered to reply to them, bro. No, Dusty.
I was getting really bad mood swings,
like psychotic mood swings, bro. Then it
went away and then I just like was fine
after that. That's the kind of impact it
has on you, bro. That's why I gave up
the whole dating [ __ ] and that. That's
why I gave up.
I gave up to get away from it. Just like
when ant like when Ant-Man went to
Thailand to [ __ ] get away from it.
You know what I mean?
No, I don't need an escape, bro.
And I don't want any more bad
experiences. It's completely logical.
If that guy didn't annoy me, I wouldn't
have went out.
You didn't see me go out last week, did
you? You didn't see me You don't see me
going out this week, do you? I've got
the money to do it.
But I don't worry, bro. It's as simple as that. Yeah.
You need a new life in another country.
That's what you need.
Isn't that right, Dusty?
just like I was already
Who is this [ __ ] bro?
So yeah, you hear me? Yeah.
Yeah. So that's that in it. Yep. My what?
Oh yeah. Defo, bro. Defo
just fed up, bro. To be fair.
What I don't understand last year is why
people still give people false hope when
it comes to dating.
Like I don't know why people on Reddit
still give people false hope.
You know Ed, right? Ed was um Ed's 23,
bro. And when I was 23, I was doing more
[ __ ] than him.
Would never go to Benador, even if he
paid me. And there would never be no
lads holiday, lad. Cuz I don't like
people. I only speak to a couple of
people. So that could never happen.
I don't like people.
So that would never happen in in any circumstances. One second. Yep.
Bro, there's loads of birds. English
birds that are not interested.
Yeah, westernized birds. Yeah,
I don't even meet people nowadays, bro.
Cuz I'm just I just don't like people.
His leg is still [ __ ] But yeah, I was
doing that [ __ ] Ed was doing when I was
like 23, 24. Not not in different countries, but
not in different countries. But the
point is I was still doing similar stuff
to him, bro. He's a he's a lot younger than me.
Yeah, right. Yeah. Yeah. I don't believe you, bro.
I don't believe you, lad.
I would never go to bed at all even if
you paid me.
Only place I'll go is Asia. That's the
only place I'll go is Asia. Simple.
Yeah. Asia, bro.
Go to Asia for two weeks or a month.
Yeah. But I'm going to go I want to go again.
Yeah. He's he's his he's his he's his friend. Yeah.
Yeah, we're not talking about them
places, bro. We're talking about
Thailand and Philippines. Yeah, bro.
Dating is so depressing in this country,
bro. Why do you think I gave up?
Still trying to blame people's attitude.
There's no getting through to these
people, is there, Dad?
You know, rat boy, there's there's no
point you ever asking advice about women
to anyone. Your mom, your dad, Reddit,
you know, there's there's no point ever asking advice.
You do realize that? But you can't ask
people for advice.
Yeah, a couple of people,
you know, you can never ask anyone for
advice, is it? Because of the um the
double standards and [ __ ] you couldn't ask anyone.
There's literally you could never ask
anyone, bro, for advice
cuz they just defend women.
No, no advice is good because 90 90% of
people will just defend women and make
excuses for them. That's why you could
never ask advice as a man. You could
never ask anyone for advice cuz people
like to make up rules
um for you that don't apply to them.
Oh, you're trying to meet him too quick.
Oh, you're coming on too strong. And all
of these little separate rules they've
got for men. So, I would never ask any I
don't think you could ask anyone for advice
cuz there's always going to be that
biasness. You understand, Dusty? They're
always going to be biased.
Like I showed about [ __ ] 10
screenshots of people that [ __ ] me
over and they made excuses for every
single one of them women. Oh, you're
trying to meet him too fast. No, no, no,
no, no. Like, so there's no there's
literally no point in it, bro. Because
they just always make excuses for them.
And the the an annoying thing is is you
know deep down that they're [ __ ]
We're not children. They're not
They're not children that are innocent.
Remember, women are not children that
are innocent. And that's the most
annoying part about it.
They know what they're doing and they
are [ __ ] That is the annoying part
with these double standards and people
defending them. If you were talking
about a kid or a baby, well, they don't
know any better. They're they're
children. They're innocent. You you get
the point I'm trying to make?
So there's no you can never ever get advice
cuz 90% of people are just biased.
So there's there's no there's no advice
you could ever take from anyone.
If a woman if a woman's [ __ ] you over,
if a woman's [ __ ] you over, they
changed their mind. If a woman lead you
on Oh, sorry. If a woman leads you on,
um, they've changed your mind. If a
woman's [ __ ] you over, you're trying
to meet them too fast. It's there's always excuses.
Yeah, but it's impossible nowadays.
Yeah, but in 2026 it's impossible.
And it doesn't even matter. I wouldn't
even put myself through it again. It's
as simple as that. So, if this Christian
Izzy doesn't go anywhere, we speak every
day. Then I am Bonito. I'm done. It's as
simple as that. I was done anyways, bro.
I only went out cuz someone was annoying
me and it'd been 3 months. Simple, bro.
I don't care. I don't need to deal with
people. I don't like dealing with people. Simple.
It's a very, very toxic thing, you know.
A very toxic thing to get into.
It's [ __ ] annoying as well,
you know. So,
so yeah, there's always double standards,
rat boy. There's always double
standards, lad. Because the thing is,
yeah, the thing is, right, is the only
reason I'm speaking to Christian Izzy
for as long as I'm speaking to her for
is because she's got exams. We speak
every day. She's genuine. Like, we she
sends me long ass voice notes, long ass
paragraphs. But on under a normal
circumstances, under normal
circumstances, I'm trying to meet
someone within four or five days because
that's how you know someone wants to
meet you and they're not wasting your
time, right? You meet them on a
Thursday, you want to meet them again by
the Sunday or the latest next week. They
can arrange it for next week. If they're
not doing that, people have got this
problem with it. Oh, you're you're
trying to meet them too fast or oh no,
no, no, no. Oh, no, no, no, no, no, no.
You never hear the [ __ ] last of it.
Do you understand? when that is the the
right thing to do because if if you've
spoke to a woman for 2 3 4 months,
right, they're not going to feel any way
about [ __ ] you over or [ __ ] you
off. So why is there we know me and you
both know that you need to meet someone
as soon as you possibly can.
You know, obviously there were
exceptions where people um you know
might might be abroad or like in this
case the person's stressed, they've got
exams, they're studying every day,
whatever. Some people like there were
rare exceptions, but even somebody that
works like say somebody has a job that's
not an excuse. So you need to be meeting
people basically as soon as you can. But
when I tried doing that, that was a
problem. But then when USA Izzy wants to
[ __ ] you as soon as he sees you sees
you, that's not a problem. There's no
problem with that.
Her first message was to me, let's meet
up on Tuesday. Didn't get to know my I
don't even think she even knew my
[ __ ] name for [ __ ] sake.
You know what I'm saying, lad? Yeah.
Yeah. But obviously Christian Izzy like
she's got exams and she studied. She
showed me her papers and everything. So
her she's she's legit. But yeah,
generally yeah, generally speaking,
yeah, unless there are some exceptions.
There are rare exceptions obviously like
this one. I woke up to 23 messages the
other day. So yeah,
but yeah. No, if I Well, I do Thursdays.
I don't know what what routine you have
when you go out drinking, but I go out
the Thursday and I try to meet them by
the Saturday, Sunday.
You get you get what I'm trying to say?
So you mid cuz you meet people midweek
and then obviously the Saturday, Sunday
for the day. Um
yeah, obviously there are exceptions but
yeah, you need to be being someone like
this person has literally got exams and
they are stressed. I've I've spoken to them
um and they wouldn't have been speaking
to you for this long. They would have
stopped talking to you a long time ago
as well. But yeah, that's it. But I
mean, generally speaking, um,
but her, I've been speaking to her every
day and when she's took over a day to
reply, she says, "Oh, I've just been
doing exams. I'm busy." No, no, no, no,
no, no, no. Like, she's genuine, bro.
She is genuine. But most Yeah,
I just hated people the way people were
as well. I I started seeing how people
were were as well when it comes to money
and stuff. Rat,
I had tenants trying to [ __ ] me over the
other day. I had somebody message me for
money yesterday. Just [ __ ] off.
Sick of people, bro.
I speak to Ant-Man, my mom, Christian Izzy, and
like a couple of other people, bro.
and meet people whenever I want, but
what's the point, bro?
You get what I'm saying, bro? Is it? Like,
people were just draining, lad.
Draining. Very draining.
But yeah, with her it's different, you know.
they study and um
yeah, she's got bad anxiety and that
she told me. So yeah,
but yeah, it made me think of Jo and
that Ricky Millington and there's other
people that said it. Oh, you're trying
to meet them too fast. What do you want
me to do, bro? Speak to speak to someone
for 10 years.
Like you know what I'm saying, bro? They
want you to speak to someone for [ __ ] 10 years.
And yeah, when I got five number I got
five numbers when I last went out, bro.
And I got the only one that replied was
her. So there you go. One reply out of
five numbers. What the [ __ ] bro?
Madness. I still like Thursdays, though.
I only go out Thursdays.
I don't like Saturdays. Too many [ __ ]
Sometimes I go out on Saturdays, but
normally it's Thursdays. So,
Thursdays are good, man.
No, I haven't seen it. Let me see.
Thursdays are the best days, bro. In
London, Thursdays are good because it's
busy, but it's not too busy and you meet
like more sort of like genuine people.
But sometimes I go out the Saturday as
well. Well, it depends, you know, but it
will always normally be a Thursday.
Always used to win money on the
Thursdays as well whenever I used to gamble. But yeah. Yeah.
But yeah, she's got like exams and and
stuff. I've spoken to her and whatnot. So
yeah, and then this other one I'm
speaking to from Tinder. So
I'm a [ __ ] going out tomorrow, bro. I'm
It's getting good money as well, Rat Boy.
And then you get all of these people
that make excuses. Oh, they won't date
somebody that lives with their mom or
oh, they won't date somebody that's not
got a job or
when we all know that's [ __ ] bro.
Don't say them. We all know it's all all
a load of [ __ ] rat boy.
Cuz I've lived by myself, lived with my
mom, had money, had no money, had a
normal amount of money. I've lived quite
different lives, you know, over the
years. That's that's another excuse for
women when they sit there and try to blame like
your situation and stuff like that's
also another excuse that they do
that they use. You know what I mean, bro? Like
because it's stupid because I've worked
I've lived by myself and what never made
no difference. I was meeting the same
person, bro. They always like to put
these emphasis on men. And I've had
money coming out my ass as well. I've
had money coming out my [ __ ] backside
and it still never made a difference.
I've still got money now. Whatever, bro.
But I used to have a lot more. I'm
talking about two and a half years ago.
But these are just excuses that they
use, you know, to try to put put the man
down. Do you get me, bro?
And I was legit. Yeah. It doesn't matter
if you were subleting the house, bro.
Theoretically, bro, it wasn't even
illegal to be honest with you. You know,
they had their chance to [ __ ] you
know, bring you get you to court and
whatever. Like, theoretically, you
wasn't even doing anything. You was in a
position to do it. Like, you was you was
put in that position to do it
and it wasn't really illegal really. If
you think about it, you couldn't get
nicked for it. So, you was doing
everything by the book
kind of. Yeah. So, all of my money was
legal. So, I mean, what when you're
saying to people you're a landlord, you
wasn't lying really, was you? You
offered to pay the rent. They didn't
want to put your name on the tenant. You
found a loophole. That's a smart person
if you think about it. So,
trust me, mate. No one lived, no one had
the money I had, bro, two and a half
years ago at that age. Trust me. So,
and it still never really made a difference.
It still never really made a difference, bro.
Obviously, I think if you're like a
millionaire, then it would. I feel like
if you was a millionaire or and you had
like a really nice car and you had
clout, then Yeah, maybe, bro. Maybe it
would. But like we're talking like
normally like just working and a couple
of thousand like No,
not really to be honest, bro. I'm
definitely going to go on holiday
somewhere, but where? I don't know.
But yeah, they just make so many excuses
for women. It's [ __ ] I don't get
these simps, Rat Boy. I really don't get these simps.
They sit there and defend women when
most women are [ __ ] and they sit there
and defend them. Makes no sense.
Makes no sense why they do it.
Why they do it, I shall never know.
But they defend them, bro. They defend women, bro.
Yeah, we're just having the same
argument anyways, bro.
You just have the same argument, lad.
Well, is it really though, bro?
Cuz it seems it seems the same everywhere nowadays. I mean
I mean where's supposed to be easier?
Well, yeah. Well, South America and Asia,
maybe. Maybe there's easier, but where else? America's not easier.
We have Americans here in London.
I don't think anywhere is easier, lad.
Everywhere is hard, bro. Everywhere is hard.
But Asia and South America.
Yeah, there are tourists, bro. But
there's also a lot of people that live
in London as well.
There is also a lot of people that live
in London, too.
And think about it, bro. Logically,
yeah. Say you met someone from Finland
like I done or you met someone from
Sweden. I mean, you could just go to
Sweden over a weekend.
And every time I go out, I'm always
meeting someone from England. So yeah,
there's tourists, but there's also a lot
of people that live here equally.
Depends where you're going, isn't it? But
you are meeting a lot of people that
live here as well.
You are meeting a lot of people. Yeah, I
met some. Yeah,
but it doesn't really matter though,
does it? because you meet people that do live here.
I mean, I do. I mean, the only two good
places to go out in London is either
central London or like Farington and Liverpool Street.
They're the only like places
that are like active
that are still active.
Brixton is uh me.
I mean, I used to go to the Swan in
Stockwell, but I ain't been there for
ages, bro. I'm thinking of going back
there and hitting it up on a Saturday,
you know, the Swan.
But I always just go Central, bro, because
it's just packed in it. So, well, yeah.
No more gambling, bro. Um,
but the thing is with shortage, bro,
like I went, last time I went there, I
went on a Thursday,
but it was dead
and there should have been more people,
but it was dead. But you can just start
off in shortage, then go found them.
That's what I used to do. But yeah, but
then you can just Yeah, I haven't been
fabric for ages.
Haven't been um the swan for ages.
I used to love that O'Neal was water
street, bro. [ __ ] That was the best.
The O'Neal was water street.
That was a vibe, bro. That was a vibe.
You ever been to the O'Neal's water street? Anyone
go there, man? when you're over in London. Um,
yeah, there's one in No, it's not
Leighton, it's Leighton Stone. I've been
there once. It was [ __ ] Yeah, it's
opposite the Tesco's in Leighton Stone.
Yeah, there's one in Leight and Stone. It's [ __ ]
You can't compare it to the central
London one, bro.
Yep, that's the baby.
Yeah, there's one in Ilford. Yeah, I've
been to the one in Ilford. Yeah,
I went to the one in Ilford a couple of
months ago. I started there and then I
went into central London. Yeah, there's
one. It's like opposite the trains division.
I met some Jordy lads,
but again, it's not like the central London one.
There's one in Ilford. There's one in um
there's one in King's Cross as well.
I've never been to that one.
I used to go to that Tesco to do my food
shopping prior co
um they never made it 24 hours again. I
used to do my shopping at like 2:00 in the morning.
Um but then when co after co they never
put it back to 24 hours again.
I bet it's not better than the water
street one though. I bet it's not better
than that water street one mate. That
water street one on a Thursday. Banging. Banging. Banging.
It's banging, bro. That Walder Street
one on a Thursday. Go on a Thursday and
come back to me. Go on a Thursday,
right? In April or May or even June.
Go on a Thursday, bro. Not a Saturday.
Go on a Thursday.
Go on a Thursday. Trust me. Trust me,
bro. Shocker block. It is. Um yeah.
Yeah. Wer street.
Wer street. Did you see that fight in
the O'Neals, Dusty? It's all over
Instagram. The O'Neal's one.
You must have saw it in it. Yeah, it was
on Instagram, in it. They were fighting
the bounces and the
two guys. I'm sure you have seen it.
I'm sure someone's seen it.
The mommy say been going there for a
while. One of the bouncers said dusty. Nah,
no. I'm never going to Birmingham again, bro.
Yeah, I used to do my food shopping at
2:00 in the morning because it was 24
hours and I don't and it was better to
shop when there was no one when there
was no one around.
Oh, do you know that Asda in Leighton Dusty?
I can't go in it, man. I can't go in
that Asda, bro.
Bro, that that store Yeah. gives me
anxiety, bro. I can't even go in it,
bro. I haven't tried for ages, bro. It's
[ __ ] huge. Have you been inside it,
bro? It gives me anxiety, bro. Just
looking at it. I swear to God, bro,
I can't even go in it, bro. That's mad.
Going anywhere else, I don't have
anxiety. But, bro, if I go in there,
bro, I will I would buy the KFC in it.
No, it's too big, bro. That g me that
gives me anxiety, lad.
That that ad is huge. I remember going
and that bro used to be 24 hours. Yeah.
I don't know if it still is, bro. I [ __ ]
myself, bro. I'm not even joking.
It's Bro, it's big as [ __ ] bro. It
gives me anxiety, man. Yep.
That Burger There's a Burger King.
Burger King next. I can't go in it, bro.
I can't go in it.
But any other shop I can obviously
Yeah. No cries for me today. No
takeaways for me. D lad. >> Look.
You need to give your tongue a rest as
well from that vindaloo cuz it starts
cutting your if it's too hot it starts
cutting like your your gums. So it's
kind of raw when you try having it
again. Does that make sense?
Don't know where that is lad.
I used to live in Leighton.
Yeah, I need to save some money as well.
I used to live in Leighton, bro. When I was younger.
I used to live in Albert Road.
I went back there the other day, knocked
on one of the big people's door. They
didn't answer it. I went to the dentist.
You're not far from Forest Gate. I used
to live in Maryland. What the [ __ ] Oh,
you're Oh, it's not far from Forest
Gate. Sorry, I misread that.
Well, you must be near me anyways since
you know so much. Yeah, I used to live in Maryland.
You know the admirals in Wolfenste, Dusty.
Good play stat. Good play stat. Good old
Admirals and Wolfenste.
Good old Leighton Blockbuster. Leighton Chester.
Toothpies are fine, bro. I brush my teeth.
Look after my teeth, bro.
They're completely fine.
That's another reason why um I cut down
on Coke and stuff. money. Uh, two fees, health. Yeah.
Speaking to this woman from Tinder, bro.
She's not the best looking, but we
talking about [ __ ] so we'll see.
Yeah, I ain't seen that. Have you ever
been to Sheffield, Dusty? There's a brothel there.
Yeah, I like East London cuz I'm from
East London, so I know everywhere in
East. But to be fair, I could get used
to West. If they if they gave me a house
in West London, I think I could get used
to it. West London's a good spot as
well, because think about it. Yeah. If
you live in Elen, you can get to central London quickly,
right? You can get to Shepherd's Bush
quickly. That's got a better Westfield.
And you can go to like Readen. And
Elen's a good place to live, you know?
Bro, I can get used to West even though
I don't like it. I just prefer east cuz
that's where I'm from. But, you know,
West. Yeah. You could actually um
you could actually um It's a good spot,
bro. Shepherd's Bush is Westfield's
better than Stratford. Way better than
Stratford. I've been to the Shepherd's
Bush Westfield. It's way better. Way better.
I don't really like West London. I'm not
used to it, but I would live there. I'd
get used to it.
Elen's one train on the Elizabeth line.
Just one train, bro. Just straight
through. I went on I went to Elen. Last
time I went to Elen, it was for a date.
Yeah. I went on a date. She was from
Maiden Head in it. So I said, "Oh, we'll
just meet in Ean."
It wasn't good, lad. Wasn't good. Have
you been to Sheffield, Dusty? There's a
good brothel there called Paradise.
It's a good laugh if you ever been to Sheffield.
There's that. Oh, it's a good laugh.
Sheffield. Sheffield's a good laugh.
I've been to most cities to be fair.
Where do you live, rat boy?
No, she's not a pig. No, she's not fat.
Her face is just not the best.
No, no, she's not a pig. She's not fat.
She's like a five out of 10 in the face.
She's not fat.
Just her face is Bro, if she was fat, I
wouldn't be talking to her.
Simple. Simple as that. Yeah.
Where do you
where do you live, rat boy?
Yeah, it doesn't matter. You can still
get a [ __ ] from it. So
simple [ __ ] [ __ ]
you know what I mean?
You live in Maiden Head, bro. I remember
one day I went out approaching. Yeah.
All day, bro. I ended up in Maiden Head.
I started off in Stratford, done central
London, done Shepherd's Bush, done at
Elen, [ __ ] ended up in [ __ ] Maiden
Head like 10:00 at night.
I think I've been to Maiden Head once
and that was that time.
I've been to Redin.
Yeah, I've been once to M. Is it once or
twice? I think once
I've been to Slow, bro. That's [ __ ]
Oh, I hate slow, bro. That's where
Fraser tried setting me up, bro. You'll
never know the story, dusty. He tried
setting me up, bro. I had to make a run
for it, bro. Then I had to get a cab and
then get a bus. Oh my god, bro. He You
tried to [ __ ] me royally, bro.
So, he's tried to [ __ ] me royally. I
made a break for it, bro. You You
weren't catching me. Trust me, bro. I
was I was a [ __ ] back then. But to be
fair, I was a [ __ ] bro. 3 4 years ago,
bro. I was a [ __ ] to be fair.
I was a [ __ ] to be fair, bro.
And then I had to like get like a cab.
I've never been to Luton, you know.
Never been there. And I don't think I'd
want to go to be fair.
Yeah, I know about looting. I've never been there.
I don't know how that Ali Law does them
climbing videos, bro. He's [ __ ] mad.
How does he do them climbing videos?
That is crazy. Oh, bro. I just [ __ ]
myself just looking at it.
I was watching some Adi law. He doesn't
post anymore, but some of his old stuff
and I've never been Southampton either.
There's a few places I've not been like main places. Blackpool, Glasgow.
I ain't been Southampton.
There's a few places. I've been to Bournemouth.
Been to Brighton. I've been to Bournemouth.
Been to Middlesbrough. I've been to Sunderland.
Yeah. Peter Belly used to go around,
didn't he, Dusty?
Where have my little legs take me? Dusty.
I'm thinking of like if I meet someone
to have kids, Dusty,
you don't like You don't like Ed
Matthews American mate then, do you,
Steven Nard? You don't like his mate.
What do you think? He's weird looking.
You think he's weird looking? Yeah.
his friend. Yeah,
stay of that puffy face. Alterly Pete
should stop blowing his pip on takeaways
and gambling and they said invest in a
hair transplant. He's like, "Bro, do you
know this is what I was saying earlier
with these people on here?" Yeah. You
know, you know all of these people that
are saying this Steven Howard Yeah.
They're just fat, ugly people that have
got no life.
That's what makes the whole thing so
funny is that they're literally just
fat, ugly people. Bold, ugly people that
have got no life.
You literally couldn't write this [ __ ]
bro. You couldn't write it. Honestly,
they're literally bold people
convincing themselves that I'm going
bored when I'm not even going bored.
But again, just projection. Just self projection, dad.
You I think you'll find that most of the
people in this community are bored. Yeah.
Why do none of these people show their
faces? Why do these people never come on
camera and show what they look like?
Strange, isn't it? They never come on
and show what other people look like.
They never come on and show what they
look like. Sorry.
And why are you telling people they
shouldn't gamble and get take and they
shouldn't get takeaways.
Like I said, Stephen, this is what makes
this community weird is that they these people, right?
They're older than you. They're uglier
than you. They're fatter than you.
They're skint. They haven't even got a
life. But then they talk about you.
That's the funny thing, bro.
That's the bit I find to be very funny
is they're in a worse position in life
than you could ever be. looks, money,
anything that you can think of. But then
they come on here talking about you
and telling you how you should live your
life. What the [ __ ] bro?
It's weird. It's so weird.
Look at it, Stephen Howard. All of the,
you know, all of the people that show
their face, tell me one person on here
that's better looking than me.
whether I'm below average, average,
above average. Like all of the people
now that show their face, name me one
person that's better looking than me.
You can't. You literally can't.
Strange, isn't it?
You can't, bro.
What's that telling you, lad? What's
that telling you?
That's why it's kind of jokes, bro.
And that Joe F. Yeah, I bet you he looks
like rice. He was talking about me on
L's yesterday, bro. Every comment was
about me again. Steven Howard weird
comes to jealousy with these people.
Steven Howard, it comes to jealousy. But
the whole thing is disabled because they
don't even know you.
The thing is, the thing is with this
community is that these people, they
don't even know you. Like, they don't
know you in real life. They've never met
you. And then it's kind of about, think
about it, bro. How can they sit online
for years and be obsessed with people
they don't even know? It's disabled,
bro. That's why we call it a disabled
community. Disabled, gay. I was on my
Instagram uh [ __ ] earlier, bro. And this
red star, I saw something that he was
doing from April 2023.
That's three years ago he's been doing
this. Steven Howard, so you tell me if
someone can come on YouTube for 3 years
stalking another man from the time they
wake up to the time they go to bed, what
kind of life do you think they have?
Nah, bro. I'm done with the Lego. I'm
done collecting the Lego. But what kind
of life do you think they could possibly have
if they're doing this? You get it?
I don't know. Alan Mountjoy, he's
disabled in it, bro. Think about it
though. Like seriously, bro.
That to me the whole thing is just weird.
I don't know about you lot, but to me
it's just weird coming online recording
and stalking someone every day. That is
very gay, bro. That is very weird.
And it shows they don't have anything in their life.
And that's it, bro. Pelly's right, lad.
Pell is [ __ ] right about these people, bro.
It's very weird.
And what you'll find with these people
is you're better looking than all of
them as well, which should tell you
everything. You're better looking than
them, and you can go out and meet
people, and you can go out and have a
life whilst they're sat on YouTube.
So, that's that's that's where that comes from.
To be fair, I watched one of that Jamie
Thompson videos yesterday, bro. One of
his videos. And to be fair, it made me laugh.
Even though it shouldn't have made me
laugh cuz he's a gay [ __ ] with no
life. It actually did make me laugh, bro.
Did you see it, Dusty?
He's like, "Why are you still ranting
about that American? I don't know why,
but he's disabled as well. So, yeah.
Shouldn't really laugh at it, but it did
make me laugh, bro. I can't lie to you,
man. I fancy a curry.
kind of fancy a curry. Can't lie to you
about it, but I can't.
Peter Belly needs to stack some money up as well.
When did I last get a takeaway?
What did I eat yesterday? I had a stew yesterday.
No, I ate uh chicken. No, yesterday I
had a stew.
I don't know. I think I might have had a
takeaway. I had a beef stew yesterday. I
know I didn't get a takeaway yesterday.
Yeah, but I don't have any coke.
And the Coke they give you is nasty, but
we got lemonade, didn't it?
I can't really do it, Dusty. Bro,
I'm just trying to cut down on them. I
just think I'm just trying to cut down
on them, bro. Just to do it, you know?
I had a beef stew yesterday. I know that
for a fact. I didn't get a takeaway
yesterday. And I had chicken and chips
today. I spent £7.
Went to Lakers, bro. Um
I don't know, bro.
What do you think, Steven Howard?
Take away. No take away.
Let me see.
I shouldn't have lost that 100 pound, bro.
Why would I gamble, bro?
Yeah, I need to get some coke though.
But they don't sell normal coke in these
places. I don't know why.
I shouldn't have lost that £100, man.
Even though it's nothing, but still.
It's [ __ ] annoying, is it? Yeah.
You know what? I'm not going to get one, bro. Nah.
Actually, I could do
I have to go out and get because of the coke. Um,
you know, I should know Yeah,
there's a place I like, bro, and I need
to leave for that. America Should
I get a takeaway or not, Grey? I've not
had one for two or three days. I had a
beef stew yesterday,
but obviously I'll have to go out.
cuz I need to get some uh
lost £100 on [ __ ] roulette. [ __ ] bullshitting it.
What do you think, Grezy? Should I get
it or no?
Have to run it by you first. Stay
with you boss.
Have to run it by this [ __ ] first.
Some lovely ticker and some lovely curry
and coke. Reevesy or nah.
Just a fucking£100 on roulette, bro. [ __ ] [ __ ]
No, leave it. Yeah.
What about Friday, Grezy?
How about Friday?
Can I get one Friday, boss? Yeah,
Monty man was saying that these people
um do what they do because they're fat
and ugly and they're jealous.
Any any opinion on that, Grezy? What he was saying?
Any opinion on that?
Uh, he's being a big fat stinking dirty
copycat cuz that's what I was saying.
Yeah, Greavvesy, it's better to get a
takeaway like every Friday or every
Saturday cuz A, it's healthier. B, you
save money and C, you enjoy it more.
Think about it, bro. There's only pros
to it. There's literally only pros to
Think about it, bro.
I'm sure I look healthier, bro. Look.
Look at me, bro.
I think I look healthier than I did,
bro. To be fair. But I didn't give up
for that reason. I'm just trying to like
save and [ __ ] bro. So, see,
none of these people can come on camera,
can they, lad? None of these people can
come on camera. Yeah.
Say no. car. Can they?
None of these people can come on camera.
Yeah, man. None of these people can come on camera.
Yeah, I'm sure I look healthier, bro.
I uh I've just been cutting down on
takeaways and [ __ ] bro.
See, I'm I went fat, bro. I'm not fat.
Just gained a bit of weight.
Just gained a bit of weight, lad, during
the winter Christmas and stuff.
You know what I mean, bro? Yeah. Yeah.
I'll get a takeaway on Friday.
We're not you get one every week now. We take away
Is that okay with you, boss?
Is that okay with you, Greasy, if I do a
little dating video?
I got some things I want to get off my chest.
I don't really do videos, but yeah.
Okay with you, boss. >> Yeah.
Yeah, bro. Look at me. Comp Look at me
compared to Jamie Thompson.
Look, bro. You can actually start seeing
my cheekbones. Look.
Bro, I really need to start I need to go
to a gym, bro. I look even better, bro.
Look, you can actually start seeing my cheekbones. Look, see,
Peter Bell is getting lean, bro. Look,
Peter Belly's getting lean. You can, you
know, when you see your your cheekbones, bro.
I'm getting lean, brother.
Yeah, tell these people to come on camera.
Yeah, I've cut down on the coach to be
fair, bro. I have cut down. I had
chicken and chips today, but I walked
like three or four miles. I walked four
miles today, bro. So, obviously. Yeah.
Yeah. I walked four miles, bro. So,
I started it.
I do need to drink some more water as well. Yeah,
I'd need to go to the gym, bro. To be fair, man.
I want to look good in the summer and that
damn army [ __ ] Greavesy,
remember the You made me laugh when you
said you nipped to the shop to get some
uh what? Eggs of milk, Greavvesy.
Some eggs and milk.
Was it eggs and milk you meant to get?
I don't know why that made me laugh.
Was he Was he trolling Greavesy?
You went to get eggs and milk.
I don't know why that made me laugh.
I'm just looking at the McDonald's menu though, Greasy.
Don't mind if I do, lad. Don't mind if I do.
Nah, I will never order from McDonald's
ever again unless it's nuggets.
So I order from McDonald's, I pay money.
I order and I pay money. Yeah. And then
it comes cold. Yeah.
So, am I b am I banned from takeaways
then? Have you put have you banned me
getting a takeaway today then, Grezy? Yep.
Yeah. And the nice sto takeaway is bro.
But the thing is where I keep having hot
food they they start cutting your gums
as well. Greasy.
Does that make sense? Like um it starts
making your like not your gum but you
know your what do you call it? Not on
your on your teeth like your mouth
like above your tongue. When you have
the vindaloo it starts where it's hot it
kind of cuts it. So if you have it day
after day, it just it's not good, man.
Where is he?
That's what I was saying when I was
watching Monty bro yesterday.
Yeah, I might do a little dating video.
I don't know.
I lost £100 on roulette greasy. Is that
okay with you, boss? Because it's not
[ __ ] okay with me.
It's not [ __ ] okay with me, boss.
Is that okay with you, boss?
Yeah, she's fine. We spoke once earlier
sending voice notes.
Yeah, she's good.
And I'm speaking to someone else from Tinder.
Yeah. I have to run things by you, don't I?
I might just cut some cheese and have
some cheese. Greavesy.
You know what I mean? Just cut a bit of
cheese. I had a cinnamon swirl earlier. Grezy. Yeah.
I'm kind of getting sick of women again,
we must tell you the truth. Yeah.
Them army [ __ ] was laughing at us. Mocking usy.
They were laughing at you. Mocking you.
Do you remember that one? Creepsy.
You remember that one? Greasy. Mocking you.
All right. So, um, can I can I make
myself a hot chocolate? Grezy,
is that okay?
Is that okay with you, boss?
Can I make myself a little milkshake?
Yeah. What have I got a little What have
I got a little collection of?
Huh? What have I got a little collection of?
Do you like my little collection? H
Did I get it?
Are you in a sink? We
>> What do you think of that? Oh, I like to
urinate in the sink.
My pec is too big.
So, we just lie it over the sink. It's better.
You get it?
Do you get it, Grezy?
Oh, to build a kettle up. What you What
did you do? You enter the shop to get
milk and eggs.
To get milk and eggs.
Or was you just strolling
to get milk and eggs?
I think you was trolling, didn't it?
My finger was trouble.
Have a slice of Can I have a slice of cheese?
I don't know. He's jealous of me, lad. Jealous. Jealousy.
Can I have a slice of cheese? Squeezy,
you have some things here.
I'm going to I'm going to cut myself
cheese. Is that okay?
[ __ ] I said the right one.
Milk and eggs.
You said you go to the shop to get milk and eggs.
Yeah. He's been obsessed with me for
years, bro. He's a homo.
You're a gay boy, bro.
He's a closet game.
I'm probably more more than likely a wheelchair user. User.
Um, more than likely a wheelchair user. User.
Yeah. The homosexual. He's been doing it for years.
You ain't got a life. Just some fat ugly
low life sat on YouTube
like most of these
myself a hot chocolate. Hello. He says
he says that I bled him but he's the
only one that bled.
Nothing bing about me. So I sort of full
head of hair must be projected probably probably
like what they what most of people out projection. Um, brie.
Um, what's your hairline looking like?
What's your hairline looking like, lad?
Yeah. Well, it's definitely definitely not, mate.
Not not any part of me is going bald, lads.
You know, my hair's not thinning and I'm
definitely not going bald.
Don't mind my haircut.
But the only people that are saying this
are the people that are already bull themselves.
It's just another form of projecting
like skin ugly. It's just another self.
No, not the re. I don't own that
channel. He's a homo. I don't go that
little gay boy channel.
I don't go that little gay boy channel.
Listen, how what's your hairline looking like?
Don't let them say anymore.
Yeah, that's self projection, lad. The
only bold ones are you people in this community, matey.
You're only saying that cuz you're
already bored yourself. Self projection.
Like, think about it, bro. Yeah. You
people in this community would love to
be young. You love to be good-looking
like me. You'd love to have hair like
me. And that's why you do this.
That's literally why you do this.
Like I said, I'm not going to keep
repeating myself, but we've seen what
you people look like when you get doxed.
And you're always bald, fat, and ugly.
So stop self projecting.
That's a good fellow.
Oh, I just made this lost hot chocolate.
Can I ask you a question then? No. No.
No. Yeah. Yeah. Can I ask you a
question? Can I ask Can I ask you a
question then since you want to ask me
Since you want to ask me questions
cuz no one's answered it. So can I ask a question?
Why is it that every single time, right,
one of you people get doxed, you're
always fat, bald, and ugly?
Why is that? Bomb hat,
Gray Cat. Nons is ugly. L is ugly. Does
that not like tell you something
that you're talking about yourselves?
No, no, no. Look, I'm I'm I want to
really like [ __ ] ask her normal
stuff. Like, think about it. Like, just
[ __ ] all of this name calling for a second. Yeah.
Answer me this then. Why is all of you
people that's done this in the past all
been fat, bald, and ugly?
I I want like answer me. Grievy, Steven
Howard, someone else. Do you not think that maybe, just maybe,
you're talking about yourselves?
Do you think it's Do you think it's
wrong to think that with the history of
your people you people when you've been
doxed? How you've always been fat, bold, and ugly?
Maybe projecting. Yeah, definitely
Because if I was really all of these
things, you wouldn't be obsessed with me
every day. Think about it, Stephen. All
Jay, if I was really bored and I was
really this and I was really that, they
wouldn't be obsessed with me, bro. They
wouldn't be wanting my ass. Think about it, lad. So yeah,
if you was really these things, they
wouldn't waste their life on you, bro.
Let alone 3 years plus of their life on you.
Think about it, Steven Howard. Yeah. Am
I Am I wasting my time on ugly people?
Okay, think about it. Yeah. Non legs.
Ugly as [ __ ] Do I waste my time on non legs?
Answer me that question. Do I waste my
time on nons legs? No. Why? Because I'm
better looking than him. I'm better than
Got more money than him. Got more of a
life than him. You get it? Do you
understand the point I'm trying to make?
I They For these people to waste their
time on you, they're jealous. It's deep
down, you know, it's jealousy, bro, with these people.
Just deep, deep, deep, deep jealousy
with these people. 100% jealousy with
these people. Why are they not speaking
to their misses, Steven Howard? Why are
they not living their life? Why are
these people not at work when they
should be at work?
Let's hear it, bro. What's the excuse?
That's a lovely hot chocolate, by the
way. But yeah, what's the excuse?
Come on, bro.
They're [ __ ] disabled, bro. Disabled as [ __ ]
You know what I mean, bro? Yeah, boy.
And you know it's jealousy deep down as
well. You know it's jealousy because
think of it Steven. Do you see people
obsessed with rice? Do you see people
talk about rice? Not really,
you know, because obviously look at what
rice looks like.
Look at me, bro. I'm better looking than
these people. I've got hair on like
these people. I've got more money than
them. And that's what that's what kills
them every single day for years. Am I
lying, bro? If I'm lying, tell me I'm
lying, bro. Tell me I'm wrong.
They say this. Yeah. They want to sit
there and talk about you. But what about
them, bro? Like they want to talk about
you. Yeah. But what about them? Just
what about them, bro?
Just what about them? Come on.
It's so like I don't think anyone on
this community can has the mental
capacity to understand what they're
doing. So weird.
That's why I don't think I think when
I'm explaining it, they don't really get it, bro.
You get it, bro? Like, well, the people
that are listening. Okay, put it this
way, bro. Who's better looking? Me or Nlex?
Me. Who's got more money? Me or Nlegs?
Me. Who's got a family? Me or Nlegs? Me.
Who's never had to go for a disabled
girlfriend? Me. You get it, bro? You
understand the point I'm trying to get at?
Yeah. You're better looking than these
people. You were younger than these
people. You've got more of a life than
these people. You've got more family
than these people.
I'm trying to get people to understand
it. How do I know I've got more money?
Because listen, at the end of the day,
yeah, if you people had money and you
had a life, you wouldn't be on here 24/7.
You wouldn't be on here 24/7. Simple as that.
I'm on here today cuz it's night. I
wasn't on here yesterday. I was off for
[ __ ] 9 days the other day. Because if
you had money and you had a life, you
wouldn't be on here doing what you do
every day. It's it's quick maths. It's simple.
You know, you wouldn't have channels
dedicated to trying to [ __ ] with people
every day if you had anything going on
in your lives. You wouldn't be making
accounts to get blocked. You wouldn't be
coming on YouTube hating on strangers if
you had anything in your life. It's as
simple as that. It's it doesn't take
it's not rocket science. It doesn't take
Albert Einstein to come from the grave,
bro, and and tell you. It's common sense.
Yeah. And that's it. That's all I wanted
to say, bro. Yeah. But yeah. No, I was
just saying it, bro. I was just saying. Yeah.
Like I said, Bob, these people can be
what they want to be. I don't give a
[ __ ] if they want to if they want to sit
on YouTube um you know 24/7 like they
have been doing for 15 years. They can
do what they want. I don't really give a
[ __ ] But then it's when they're trying
to talk about me, someone that's better than them,
you know? They can't even come on and
put their cameras on, bro. Like [ __ ]
And that's all I'm saying, is it, bro?
It's like it's when they're trying to
talk about other people that are better
looking than them, that are better than
them in life,
>> you know?
Anyways, [ __ ] all them. Yeah, I made
myself this hot chocolate anyways. So, yeah.
This hot chocolate is lovely.
Yeah, man. They can say whatever they
want, but these people can never come on camera.
These people can never ever come on camera.
Enough said. So, that's it, bro.
Yeah. I'm just I'm not talking about
them, but I'm just saying, is it, lad? Yeah.
It's not the same old sad song with me, lad.
Why can't anyone come on here and show their hairline?
You know, that's my hairline. Okay. Why
does no one come on here and show their hairline?
Come on, bro. Why does no one come on
here and show their face? You know,
they hate that they're them, lad. They
hate that they're them.
Oh, there's some new GTA videos
up here, bro. That's good, is it? Yeah. Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Yeah, man. No one really goes for rice.
Do you not find that mad? How if it was
really about things that people have
said, wouldn't you get people being
obsessed with ricey?
Think about all the mad stuff he's said
and done. Yeah. Why is no one obsessed
with Rice? Cuz he's not younger. He's
not better looking than these people.
They hate anyone that's better looking
than them. They hate anyone that's got
more money than them. That's what it is
with this [ __ ] backwards community. Lad
Monty said it, but he copies me. Why do
you think people don't go for rice? Cuz
Rice doesn't have a life.
Rice isn't decent looking. Rice can't go
out and get women's numbers. You You get
the point I'm trying to make?
You understand? Why do you think no
one's obsessed with Rice? And why do you
think no one's really obsessed with Monty?
Do you get it, lad?
You need to read between the big lines.
I tell you, bro, I'd be very surprised
if these people leave their house every
day. I would be very, very, very surprised. Very surprised. Yeah. Yeah, man.
Joe's one of the brothers, Stephen.
Joe's one of the brothers.
Yeah, Joe's one of the brothers, bro.
One of the non-legs brothers, more like.
He's one of the He's one of the non-legs brothers.
He's one of the nons
talking about me all
evening yesterday. Bro,
this guy was commenting, commenting,
commenting, commenting, commenting,
every comment was about Peter Belly.
Yeah, bro. It was about me, lad. Yeah.
There's no story.
So anyways, why don't you answer some of
my questions? If you people have got
this perfect life, this perfect money,
why are you sat on YouTube 24/7 talking
about the same [ __ ]
Why are you sat on here 24/7, no life,
and then think you can come and talk
about other people? One second,
Greavesy. One second. Now answer me.
Answer me that. Why is it whenever you
go on L J's when I've been in there in
the past, why is it always the same
people that should have friends, that
should have a life, that should have money.
Yeah. Okay. I'll put you know what?
Yeah. I'll put the link up and you can
you can join and show us what you look
like as well. Yeah. Mess of a man. Yeah.
Yeah, man. That's nice, man. That's
Thank you, bro. You can I'll put you on
a timeout for five minutes. Yeah. Why
don't why don't some of you people join
the hangouts and show us your hairline,
bro? This is all self-p projecting and
you know you know you're going to get
doxed as well one day, even if it's in 5
years. Anyways, back to what I was
saying. So, if you people have got this
perfect life, right? You're not ugly.
You're not this. You're not. Why are you
sat on YouTube 24/7 every day?
Does that somehow leave you gobsmacked
cuz you can't answer me? Why is that,
bro? You got this perfect life. You're
not ugly. Everyone else is a ma. So why
are you sat on YouTube 24/7?
Is that not a good question? Steven Howard
sat on here [ __ ] obsessed with men.
No, I mean that's a that's a good
question, isn't it? Isn't it not greasy?
Like explain it to me. Help me
understand, bro. Like I'm not blocking
people that actually want to talk. I put
the link up. Like the link is up. I want
somebody to explain it
cuz I might be mis, you know,
misunderstood, but I don't think I am
to be fair. You know,
have you been paid £3 million? Are you
saving for something? Explain to me why
you're on YouTube 24/7 obsessed with
people that you don't know.
This is a million-dollar question. I I
want to know, bro. Like,
if you actually had a life. Come on.
Come on, bro. Like, tell me.
Where's your misses when you're doing
this? Where's your job when you're doing
Do you get what I'm saying? Like, no. Is
what I'm saying? Like, is what I'm saying? Yeah.
Is what I'm saying lies,
Steven Howard. Like, if you if you're if
I'm wrong, bro, tell me I'm wrong, bro.
I don't mind being wrong. I won't block
people for being wrong.
Let's talk about you, bro. Let's talk
about you people. Come on.
The link's up, you know. Cuz
I'm telling you, right, I'm trying to
save these people's time.
You will never ever ever make me feel
ugly. You will never make me feel
insecure. You're never ever going to
affect me. You're literally just wasting
your life. Probably the only few years
that you've got left. You're not going
to make me feel ugly. You're not going
to make me feel insecure. You're not
going to make me rage. You're not going
to basically bring me down to your
level. So, you're just wasting your time,
you know. No, you answer my question as
to why you people on YouTube every day,
bro. Not been laid in a year, bro.
You've never been laid in. You haven't
been laid in your whole life.
You're still a virgin. Anyways, I
noticed that you're not answering any of my questions.
You're just dodging the questions. I
wonder why they're dodging the
questions, Steven Howard.
I wonder why do they keep dodging the
question? It's cuz they know I'm right.
It's because they literally know I'm
right. That's why,
you know. Same to you, Bob. You need a
good woman and you need a shag lad. Same
same thing goes to you, my man.
Yeah, I appreciate it. But same same to
you, bro. You need a good woman and you
need a shag. Right back at you, lad.
You know what? I was so tempted
yesterday, Steven Howard. Yeah. To um to
call this Joe out and just go to
Nottingham today, bro. Like yesterday, I
was thinking to go today, bro. But it's
always going to be the same with these people.
Bro, he would I would Bro, you don't
understand. I would knock the [ __ ] out
of this [ __ ] Listen, you know, he was
talking [ __ ] about the women that I was
I'm speaking to. Yeah, I'm speaking to.
Yeah, he was speak He was speaking [ __ ]
about the woman I was speaking to,
calling her a Bible basher. Bro, you've
got a fat ugly MS. We've all seen your
Mrs. Hands. I guarantee you, bro. Yeah.
the way that he showed his body, he
ain't going to show his woman's body,
bro. She's a fat healump.
And you're calling someone a Bible
basher because they're Christian, bro.
Have you looked at your own [ __ ] ugly misses?
That's what I was thinking. I was like,
"Bro, has this guy seen Yeah. his own
fat ugly misses when [ __ ] um um
what's it called? With [ __ ] droopy
ass saggy tits. Has he seen his own misses?
Bro, I shouldn't I really shouldn't get
too deep into this, bro. Seriously, bro. I shouldn't
cuz I would just end up going and just
knocking the [ __ ] out if he's got any
kind of sense, bro, to meet me, bro.
I'll just knock him out, bro.
I will literally knock his teeth down
his throat and put it all over YouTube,
bro. But he won't show. He will not meet
anyone. He will literally not meet anyone, bro.
Like, do you want me to put it to the
test? Yeah. Think about it, Steven.
Yeah. Think about it. We were saying
this earlier. Yeah. This guy has got so
much [ __ ] to say on YouTube. Every
comment, Bear in mind, bro, every
comment that he makes is about me. Yeah.
Just Just I'm not even trying to bring
trouble to this address. Yeah. But every
comment is about me. Why is this guy not
come on my door and sorted it? He's
always said to people, don't listen to
me, bro. Yeah. He's always saying to
people, "Oh, why have you not gone and
sorted LT out? Why have you not gone and
sorted Monty out? Why haven't you come
on my door and sorted me out, bitch?"
There's been nothing for like three or
four years of any excuses that you can
use why you haven't gone on someone's
door. If you're happy to comment about
someone every day, then bro, at the end
of the day, you can more than sort
someone out. You know, you say that
people will do something when when they
something's going to happen when we
least expect it. Hold on a minute.
Doesn't this guy know where I live?
And at the end of the day, bro, it's
very relevant. It's very relevant when
um they're talking about you every day.
You get me, bro?
And he's trying to [ __ ] stir. It's very
relevant. I mean, bro, why haven't you
come on someone's door and sorted it out?
You know, think about it, bro. I
actually think about it. Is Is that not
the truth? If you're talking about
someone every day, I was reading it,
bro. What the [ __ ] Then at the end of
the day, why haven't you come on
someone's door and sorted it out?
You know, you're talking about Monty.
You're talking about LT. But come on.
Why? Why haven't you? You know, you
can't use LT as an excuse.
Think about it, lad.
Think about it. You can't even use LT.
So, why haven't you gone on someone's
door and sorted it out? because you're a
little [ __ ] Simple. At the end of the
day, bro, listen. I went to Manchester.
Yeah, I dealt with Bomb a couple of
times. I went to Middles, bro. I went,
bro, you've seen me go all over. So,
what what is a valid reason if this guy
wants to talk about someone every day,
why he hasn't come on someone's door and
sorted it out?
Because we know that I'm not scared of
anyone. Nothing's happened for four or five years.
So, I mean,
it's just a bit weird, isn't it, bro?
because he's a little [ __ ] He's a
little [ __ ] And the only reason he
wants people to come to go to leads,
bro, is so he can sit there and say,
"Oh, I made you go there. I made you go
there. I made you go there." That's
what's going to happen, bro. That's why
he will never come to London.
Yeah. Well, LT's full of [ __ ] mate,
because I've gone live in many of these
places calling people out.
Yeah. Well, LT's talking a load of
[ __ ] because everyone knows
everyone I've tried to meet on here.
So anyways, if this guy is talking about
people that need to be sorted out, why
hasn't this guy come on this front door,
bro? I've had more boobs than he will
ever have, bro. This guy is an unhappy
closeted gay at the end of the day, bro.
Yeah, this guy this guy's misses is
probably the thing that turned him gay.
That's why he's talking about me and
this [ __ ] woman being a Bible basher.
Bro, you've got a fat ugly misses that
turned you gay. Why do you think you're
obsessed with me every day, bro? You
should be banging that Punani every day
instead of having a channel dedicated to
another man. Yeah. Well, he's wrong
about that one.
He's wrong about that one. So, yeah. And
and L's turn up unannounced many times.
Anyways, we're not going to get into that.
Yeah, LT LT talks [ __ ] LT talks a load of [ __ ]
so who cares?
A Bible buster. Have you looked at your
own fat, ugly misses?
Have you looked at your own fat misses
who turn you gay? Like that's that's
what I'm thinking, bro. You know what I mean?
You've got a fat ugly MS. Every single
woman that I have been with, bro. Yeah.
He went to my door unannounced. He went
on my door unannounced. And if I wasn't
in, you wouldn't accept that. So, we're
not even going to get into the bias list again.
He What if he went on my door and I
weren't in? Then what? You would have
all said that. Oh. Oh. Uh, he beat you.
He beat you. So, bro, don't even try to
use that excuse.
Steven Howard, should I just go to
Nottingham and knock the the [ __ ] the
[ __ ] [ __ ] You want me to just knock
this [ __ ] out if he agrees to meet me?
You want me to just go there and knock
the [ __ ] out
like a book a hotel, bro? If he even
thinks he's going to turn up, like, do
you want me to do it, bro?
Cuz I don't mind doing a video, bro, and
just and and just calling him out and
just slagging him off and everything, bro.
Yeah, I I really I really don't mind, bro.
I really really really really don't mind. Yeah.
But you already know what's going to
happen as I know what's going to happen.
You know what's going to happen as I
know what's going to happen. Yeah.
Why is that, bro? Why Why is something
Why do we know this is going to happen?
You want me to tell you? A because it's
happened many times before and B they
know where you live. So,
it's as simple as that. If you're
willing to be obsessed with someone every day,
mate, I've met more people in this
community than anyone,
you know? I've met more people in this
community than anybody.
So, have that one. Yeah,
it's a waste of money, bro. But like the
thing is, bro, I I will knock the [ __ ]
out of him
about the only boobs I've ever been for
is paid for, mate. I've had more women
than you would ever. And I'm not with
some fat ugly misses. I'm not with some
fat like, bro, I will break his jaw,
bro. You don't understand. I will break
the cunt's jaw, bro. And I won't stop.
You don't understand, bro. Yeah. And you
know what I'll do? I'll grab him and
I'll laugh in his face and I'll put it
all over YouTube.
Trust me, bro. Like, don't [ __ ] with me,
bro. Simple. Like, really, really don't.
It's the same with It's the same with
Kevin Murphy. Yeah. And I also want to
bring up the whole London Taylor [ __ ]
How many times have you told people that
they need to sort stuff out, but you're
not on this front door? You're not on
this front door. You know, that's not
causing trouble. That's that's speaking
facts. That is speaking facts. Think
about it, bro. Let's let's talk about
over the years people come. What
happened when Timmy and Tiger come on
the door? Yeah. Didn't I didn't I fight
them? Didn't Didn't I [ __ ] fight
them? Did I travel to fight people? Do
you understand? So, at the end of the
day, bro, we we need to understand.
Yeah. Why is this guy really not on
someone's door? Cuz he's a [ __ ] house.
He's a [ __ ] house, bro. He's an absolute
[ __ ] [ __ ] house. Because the first
thing people would do, right? Simple.
Yeah. Well, we're not talking about LT, lad.
Yeah. You are, bro. I'm special needs,
bro. You people are the biggest special
needers. Bro, only special needs people
would come online for 15 years repeating
themselves. You are definitely special
needs. Like, listen, you people say that
you've got an IQ. Yeah. But who's all
the ones on YouTube 15 years repeating
themselves? That is special needs to the
maximum. Like think of it, bro. None of
you have got lives. None of you have got
friends. None of you has got anything
going for yourselves. You are special
needs to the max. That is literally you.
Only special needs spastics would sit
online. Yeah. For 15 plus years
repeating themselves. Only spastics will
do that. Like no, no one else does that,
bro. Anyone else that's got stuff going
on in their lives, unlike you fat fat
people, don't do what you do. Like you
people are the biggest embarrassments.
And every single time you've been doxed,
you've always been fat and ugly. Every
single one of you has done ugly looks,
ugly lives. Every single one of you
have. You can't even tell me that I'm
lying, bro. You people are [ __ ]
You've had people's addresses for years.
You ain't done [ __ ] Yet you come online
for 15 years repeating yourselves.
You're [ __ ] Absolute [ __ ] Like
you actually are [ __ ] Not maggots.
[ __ ] [ __ ] You tell me right. What
is not disabled about coming on YouTube
for 15 years talking about people that
you don't know that are better looking
than you people? Come on, bro. You can't
even You can't answer anything that I [ __ ] say. say, bro.
But anyways, bro, it might be a waste of
money, but bro, listen. I'm I'm willing
to do it one more time, lad.
Yeah, but it's the truth about you
people. You ain't got a life. Yeah, I've
heard of Yeah. Yeah. You And you'll hear
it again. You people ain't got no life.
You're sat on YouTube 24/7. And you'll
keep hearing it. And you'll keep hearing
it until you get a [ __ ] life. Yeah,
bro. Yeah. And you [ __ ] [ __ ] will
keep hearing it.
until I say is enough. How's that? Is
that Is that good enough for you? You've
heard it before cuz it's the truth. You
haven't answered anything I've asked.
No, no, no. You people have got no
lives. You are on YouTube sat on YouTube 24/7.
Nope. It's definitely facts. You ain't
got nothing in your lives. No, it's not
speculation. It's facts about you ugly
Oo's ugly skin Oo. It literally is. If
you had anything going on in your lives,
you wouldn't be on here. Doing what you
do every day. Doing what you do every
day. Yeah. I' I've literally said doing
what you do every day. It's not
speculation. It's facts. Big difference.
Yeah. I've seen you people sat on here
from the time you wake up to the time
you go to bed. You sorry ass losers.
That's it, man. That's all I wanted to say.
That's it, bro. That's literally
literally literally it. ain't got no the
[ __ ] you do on here is is disabled. Do
you not understand? Every single day you
people are [ __ ] so disabled. That
would never happen in the real world,
you know? That would never ever happen
in the real world. Only this disabled
community, you know? It's not It's not
even real life, bro. Yeah. So,
but I'm just telling you anyway,
Stephen, now that's what's going to happen.
That's exactly what will happen.
That's exactly what will happen, lad.
Just so you know, bro. Just so you know.
Yeah, I lost 100 pound earlier. But
yeah, just so you know, that's um that's
what's going to happen, bro, with the Nottingham. Yeah.
No one's going to meet you on here, bro.
No one's going to meet you cuz then they
get docked. Their faces get out there if
they meet you.
If they meet you, their faces get out there. No,
think about it, Stephen. Yeah. These
people are ugly as [ __ ] So if their
faces get out there, they could never
Why do you think Bomb's not on him
anymore? And if he is, he's like behind
because his ugliness got out there. It's
the same with these people, bro. Once
their ugly faces get out there, they'll
run a mile, bro. They'll run a mile. It
happens every time. It happened with
Pat. Happened with Bomb. Gray Cat
stopped her [ __ ] So, if they're meeting
you, think about it. If they meet you,
their faces are going to get out there.
Their faces are going to get out there
and that's that, bro. So, they're not
going to do that, you know?
We've seen your ugly fat misses with
them fat ugly hands
and you're talking about people being Bible basses.
You [ __ ] closeted gay homo.
Know what I mean, bro?
You [ __ ] [ __ ]
about you've got a strong punch. I would
whip your ass, bro, with just my thumb.
It's not It's It's not even funny, bro.
Just my thumb. All I would need is my
thumb, bro. And that would be it.
Maybe we should ask him these questions
as to why he hasn't come on people's [ __ ] door.
You know, maybe he can answer some questions,
brother. It would not be a fight,
brother. Me and him, it wouldn't be a fight.
Yeah, it wouldn't it wouldn't be a fight.
It would never happen and it would never
be a fight. So I think yeah, there you go.
You still there, Grezy? You still there? Stephen Howard.
What's the day tomorrow? Thursday.
No, he's never coming back to London.
He's banned from London, mate. He's
never coming back to London,
mate. He's never coming back to London.
He ain't happening. He ain't going anywhere.
The only place he he'll be going is
Birmingham for Timmy. He's definitely
definitely definitely not coming to London.
He's banned from London. Yeah, man.
He's just jealous at Jo because he's too
ugly. He can't get any women, bro. He's
He's an ugly bastard. Did you see? He's
misses his hands. [ __ ] fat as [ __ ]
Bible basser, bro. What the [ __ ] You
little gay boy, bro. I really want this
[ __ ] to meet me, bro, so I can smash his face in.
You actually think there's no chance
you'll meet me at all? You actually
think there's no chance?
I might just do a video and just get so nasty, bro.
like and just show you what this [ __ ]
is once and for all, bro. Seriously.
Yeah. Show you what this little f and
and and what I'm going to do is I'm
going to humiliate him. Yeah. I'm going
to humiliate him. I'm not going to just
beat him up, bro. Yeah. I'm going to
beat him up. I'm going to laugh in his
face. I'm going to spit all over him,
bro. Trust me. I'm not going to beat
someone. I'm not traveling somewhere one
more time. Yeah. Yeah. I'm not traveling
somewhere one more time to to to fight
someone and then leave.
You you understand me, bro?
Yeah. And that's it. And I'm going to
put them all on my channel. Yeah. And
leave it up there for a year. That's
what I'll do, bro. Yeah. That's what I'll do.
I'll probably rob the [ __ ] as well.
You know what I mean?
You know what I'm saying? Look, because
where it's been going on for so long.
Yeah, Steven Hours with these people.
Where it's been going on for so long,
it's going on for so long with these
people. You're not just going to fight
someone and then just leave. [ __ ] that, bro.
You understand me? Fight them,
humiliate them, and rob them. That's
what I would do, bro. Yeah. Just to be a
nasty little [ __ ] And I'm not a thief,
but still, bro, because these people
need to learn. Do you understand? They
need to learn, bro.
And then you're saying that you laugh at
people, bro. Come and laugh in your [ __ ] face.
Right up in your [ __ ] face, you silly
[ __ ] You get me?
It ain't happening, bro. Is it? Because
they'll never meet anyone.
Why won't he come to Nottingham? Huh?
Why won't this little git come to Nottingham? H
why won't he come to Nottingham?
Cuz he knows he'll get smashed up
and he knows that he's not in control.
He can't say, "Oh, I made you go here. I
made you go there. I made you go here."
Because he's an ugly [ __ ] That's why
he's never going to show his face cuz
he's ugly as [ __ ] Just like Red Star.
Just like most them people. They're
[ __ ] ugly. Ugly as [ __ ] trying to
call Christian is your Bible basselor
when you've got a fat ugly misses that
turn you gay and you know it deep down
and you're calling people a [ __ ]
you're calling people a Bible bastard
you silly little [ __ ]
You never he will never show his face.
He looks Bro, he's he's another rice.
Trust me he's another rice.
He's another rice bro. Ugly as [ __ ]
Fat ugly misses just like nonslegs. Yeah.
You people don't do anything.
You people don't do anything though, do
you? You people just talk [ __ ] on
YouTube every day, bro, for [ __ ] 15 years.
I've done more than you people ever do.
How many of you people have met me when
I've traveled all over the country? How
many of you people have come on my door?
Exactly. So, shout out, man. Right. I
need to call this person Asian.
You little gay, ugly, fat wankers do
nothing but sit online and talk [ __ ] for 15 years.
You know what I mean?
I guarantee you, bro. Yeah. All of them
people on L J's are just some fat, ugly
people in wheelchairs.
What do you reckon the odds are, lad?
What do you reckon the odds are?
Just fat, ugly nobodyies that ain't got
no life for themselves.
It's true, bro. True. Yeah. Sad bastard.
How do I
Yeah, man. He's a gay bastard.
I hope he does meet me, bro.
>> No chance. If any of these people would
have met you, they would have just come
on your [ __ ] door, bro. If they can
sit there and be obsessed every day,
they can come on people's doors. It's as
simple as that. Yeah.
I shouldn't even be reacting to these
people. They're just jealous little low
lives. We should know better, bro. You
know, that's one of the reasons why,
bro, I I didn't do that video and
started this whole Nottingham thing
because deep down, bro, you're looking
as bad as them because they are jealous.
They're fat. They're ugly. They got no
life. They got nothing going for
themselves. So you kind of look bad like
you seem like you haven't learned your
lesson. Do you get it?
Because that's that is the reason why
they do this is jealousy.
Jealous. So when you you you start
looking bad when obviously he's running,
bro. He would never meet anyone. He's a keyboard warrior.
He's a keyboard warrior, lad. He's never
going to meet anyone. He's a keyboard warrior.
tried for many years, Bob. Tried for
many years. He won't meet no one, lad.
He's just a gay, homosexual, jealous
[ __ ] in a wheelchair.
I'll tell you what, next week, invite
people to someone's panel.
What are you talking about?
Yeah, they are jealous, bro. Look at
what half of these people on here look
like. Nope, it's not. Okay, then. Okay,
then. If I'm speculating, why don't you
come on right now and show us what you've got?
Okay, I'm speculating. Okay, why don't
you come on the panel right now and show
us what you look like and what you've
got. Yeah, you're right, bro. I
shouldn't speculate. Yeah.
Yeah, you're right. To be honest with
you, bro. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. You're right
to be honest. Yeah.
Yeah. Speculating. Yeah. Yeah. Why don't
you come on and show us what you got?
Prove me wrong. Yeah, bro.
Oh, but you don't think talking about
men every single day makes you gay? Come
on, bro. Okay. Well, why don't you show
us what you've got?
It's not speculating, bro. If you people
had anything in your lives, you wouldn't
be on here every day doing this.
Oh, [ __ ] bro. So, I'm speculating. How
How am I speculating? So I'm speculating
when I'm saying that you people right
that come on YouTube every day all day
every day has got no life. That's me speculating.
Do you think that's speculating? Really? Really?
Nah, bro. No.
No. No. No. No, no, no, no, no, no, no,
no, no, no, no, no. You can't come on
YouTube all day, every day stalking men
and have a life. Yeah, there's some
people on here that could have a life. Maybe Charlie,
maybe How Hard Can It Be, maybe Ben
Fury. I mean, yeah, I mean, there's
maybe 5%. But you people that go on L
J's don't have a life. Because if you
did, you wouldn't be sat on YouTube
making videos of men. You wouldn't have
channels dedicated to men. And you
wouldn't be talking and hating on men
that you don't know every day. That's
the people that ain't got a life. That's
That's the people that ain't got a life,
bro. That's serious. Because I'm trying
to put myself in your shoes. I'm trying
to I'm trying to really really put
myself in your shoes, you know, before I
say all of this stuff. Yeah. You know,
I'm trying to put myself in your shoes, isn't it?
And to me it just that's why we I I
asked you the question you know
you saw there Stephen
I don't know anyone that's got a life
that sits on YouTube stalking men all
I'm sorry. I'm sorry. I I I don't I
don't understand. I don't know where
that desire could possibly come from.
Explain it to me, bro. I'm trying to see.
As a heterosexual man, I'm trying to understand it.
Okay, I'll explain this one more time,
right? Since you want to keep bringing
this guy up. Red Star sat on YouTube
every day stalking men from the time he
wakes up to the time he goes to bed.
Okay. Now, even if you paid me £3
million, I wouldn't do that for 3 years.
You understand what I'm saying, right? I
You could pay me £3 million. Yeah.
No, you're not even trolling though.
You're just self projecting.
Yeah, you could pay me £3 million. I
wouldn't do it. I wouldn't do it.
No, it's not believable. Nothing you say
is believable. It's just self-p
projection with you people. And you
wouldn't be trolling people if you had a
life. That's another thing. You wouldn't
be sat on YouTube trolling people if you
had a life.
So yeah, it's it's common sense. It's
literally common sense. It's not about
speculating. It's common sense. For
someone to sit on YouTube stalking a man
all day, every day, you have got no
life. You are gay. That's not
speculating, bro. It's facts, right? The
truth hurts. But that's the truth.
There's There's nothing else it could be
other than you've got no life and you're
[ __ ] gay. It's as simple as that.
You people ain't got a life.
You people literally ain't got a life.
>> That red sword definitely ain't got a
life. Stephen Howard definitely ain't
got a life.
You need to understand what I'm saying
to you, bro.
Bro, you need to understand, bro. Yeah.
Someone that sits on YouTube stalking
men every day hasn't got a life. Doesn't
matter what they try to say to you or
what they try to convince you. They are
gay, homosexual, jealous people with no
life. Okay. Could you imagine yourself
doing it? Okay. Here's the thing, Steven
or anyone else. Could you imagine
yourself doing it? I couldn't imagine
myself doing it. So that's what I'm
trying to understand.
Would Okay. You reckon? You reckon?
Right. You reckon? So, like, you reckon
I would sit online every day recording
that skinned virgin or would I go out
and live my life? Think about it. You
need to put yourself in these people in their shoes.
Yeah. They don't bully people. They
bully themselves. But yeah, and none of
them have jobs. They don't have 95% of
the None of them have jobs. 95% of the
people on here don't have jobs.
No [ __ ] way, bro.
Yeah, you do. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
Yeah. You do. You definitely definitely
do. No normal working person would come
on YouTube trying to bully people. They
definitely definitely definitely don't
bully me. I'm still here. I'm still
laughing at them. No, no, no, no, no,
no. Dr. Echo, it's not speculation when
it's facts. No normal person who works
and is better than you would do this.
Facts. Not speculation. Facts. Big
difference. Okay, again, I'll repeat
this against you. Someone that's got a
life and a job don't come on here doing
what they're doing. It's not up for
debate. It's facts. It is literally the
truth. If anyone's got a life and
anyone's got a family, they wouldn't
have time to be on it. That if they had
a life for themselves, they wouldn't be
on it. Facts. Not speculation. Facts.
Every single time you people have been
doxed, right? You people have been
doxed, right? You've all been fat and
ugly. Everything I've said in the past
about you people has always been right.
Fat, ugly, bro. Everything I've said has
been the truth.
Yeah. You don't know anything, mate.
They don't have nothing. They literally
literally do not have nothing.
They've got nothing. They lit If they
had something, they wouldn't be on here
stalking me every day.
They literally don't have a pot to piss
in. Bullies. Yeah, they bully
themselves, but they don't bully me.
Nah, they definitely definitely don't
bully me. Yeah, they're trolling
bullies. They bully themselves. They
don't bully me. That's why I'm on here
laughing at them. Still on here. Still
got away with everything. Literally
everything I've done, everything I've
said, I've gotten away with. Literally
everything. Like, think about it,
Steven. Yeah. How many years have these
people tried [ __ ] with me and I'm
still here laughing at them and they
still think that they bully people even
though you're sat there laughing at them
on YouTube? What does a bully do, bro?
When when someone gets bullied, what do
they do at school, Steven Howard? They
tell the teacher and the teacher [ __ ]
gets involved. I'm sat here laughing at
him. But apparently I'm bullied. I'm
laughing at how gay and how [ __ ] they
are and how they know where I live and
they will never do nothing. That's not
bullying. That's the truth. Yeah, I'm
close to crying. No, definitely
definitely definitely not. You know what
it is, bro? It's like when when you're
trying to explain stuff to spastics like
you that ain't got a brain, it becomes
very very frustrating. Not crying, not
almost crying. It's just very tiring
having to explain stuff to spastics that don't understand.
you lose brain cells. But I can assure
you I'm not crying. Nowhere near crying.
But you people cry every day on YouTube
about people that's got a better life
than you though. But hey, that's on you. Yeah, man.
These people have definitely been
bullied at school, lad. Definitely
definitely been bullied at school.
[ __ ] the person who made social media. Huh, lad.
Yeah, you people ain't got a good life.
Cuz if you had a good life, you wouldn't
be on here.
You don't see me on here for You don't
see me on here 24/7.
You know why I'm not on here 24/7.
Stephen Howard, I don't even watch 24/7.
I just go live when [ __ ] go live. Is
because you know these people. Yeah.
They're [ __ ] retards, right? And then
when you watch retards Yeah. long
enough, you kind of turn into one of
them. Like I can't explain it, bro. Like
it they actually start where they're
such idiots and you're talking to
idiots, you start becoming like one of them.
You know what I'm saying?
You actually start like I can't explain
it, bro. Where they're so [ __ ] Yeah.
You actually kind of like lose brain cells.
That's why it's not good to go in this
place. It's It's a very disabled place.
Like sometimes I I listen to Timmy, bro,
and I actually lose brain cells.
These people will always be bullied, bro.
Yeah, you actually lose brain cells, bro.
You actually lose brain cells.
What the [ __ ]
I have had a job and yes, I have been to
Asia. Thank you very much.
You know what? I think people like you need to
I think you people just need to get a
life to be honest with you, lads. Oh,
where's that bit? I think you really
need to get a life.
Really do need to get a life.
Yeah, you really, really do need to get
a life. Why are you not out there
talking to women? Why are you not out
there working? Why you not out there
making money? Why you not out there
traveling? Why you not going to the gym,
bro? Why would you sit on an eggheads
[ __ ] panel? Because you ain't got a
life. cuz you simply ain't got nothing
going for yourselves. Simple.
And don't try and sit there and say,
"Oh, people do this when they've got
jobs because they don't." And let me
tell you something, Dusty. Do you know
how I know this? Yeah. Because when I
had to do this thing, right, where I was
sending money um to someone and I was
trying to multitask and it was very,
very, very [ __ ] hard. So, at the end
of the day, bro, these people can't have
anything going for themselves if they're
sat on the air every day on YouTube
doing this. Don't let them try and tell
you that they got jobs. No, they do not,
bro. Yeah, try and have a job and stalk
a man on YouTube 24/7 and see how far
you get. Yeah, you never got any of my
money stopped. But yeah, you keep
telling yourself that, lad.
Yeah, you keep telling yourself that.
And this is what I'm trying to say. You
really have got no life. You just weak
of hate and jealousy.
Yeah. You people don't have your own businesses.
businesses at all.
Yeah. Bro, you're not going to kid a
kid, lad. So, there's no there's no point trying.
You're not going to kid a kid, brother.
You're really really really not. Yeah.
But no, you really you people really
ain't got a life. I couldn't imagine
being like you sat on here talking about
men every day. I couldn't imagine your lives.
Really sad, is it, bro? You really You
know what? I actually feel sorry for you.
You know what, bro? I actually really do.
I actually, do you know what? I actually
do feel sorry for you, bro. You know,
it doesn't matter what part I went.
That's none of your business.
You can get back to it, but I'm not.
It's none of your business.
Yeah, you got businesses. cuz you got
money, but you're sat on YouTube 24/7.
Yeah, make it make sense. You're sat on
YouTube in your 40s and 50s trolling
men. Yeah. Okay, bro. Yeah. Okay. You
keep telling yourself that. Businesses,
money, but absolutely no life but YouTube.
Yeah. Okay, bro. Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
I mean, you you people are on YouTube
from the time you wake up to the time
you go to bed.
I mean, literally.
And it's actually 1000 p.m. [ __ ] not
12:00 p.m., so you might want to
actually get the time right. Um,
sad though, is it really? If you've got
all this money, you claim you got you
got this life, but you're sat on YouTube.
Weird, isn't it?
That is weird. So weird.
It's very very strange.
This is very weird.
But yeah, you ain't got a job at all.
Cuz I've tried multitasking when I was
sending people money before, bro.
Mate, the day I start stalking men on
the internet for years and years and
years, I will I will generally seek help
when I'm like one of you people. When I
get to literally when I literally get to
like 5% of what you people are like, I
will generally seek help. Yeah.
I don't need a job, mate. I've got
money. And I'm not on YouTube 24/7. I've
got money. I've got enough money to do
what I want to do. And I don't need a
job. And another thing is I'm not on YouTube 24/7.
But do you know the thing is Dusty?
Yeah. Let me tell you something, bro.
Why don't you people have a job?
Why don't you people get off of YouTube?
That's another thing. Why don't you
people get a life, get a job, get off YouTube?
Same question to you little self projectors. Um
um yeah, but you know the thing is
Dusty, what did I do when I was on
YouTube, bro? I lived my life on YouTube.
Lord J never. None of these people
Yeah, they've ruined me so much. Yeah.
That I'm still here. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
Uh, bro, your little self-p projecting
comments are not going to work, bro.
Bro, your little self-reflecting
comments aren't going to work because
let's just say that you was just about
to get to me. All we need to do is
remember what you people look like. Fat,
ugly on YouTube 24/7. Just remember that
it's the people that are saying this.
You know, you people are fat and ugly.
That's what people always need to
remember about you people.
That you are fat and ugly and that's why
you do all of this.
Tell me I'm lying, bro.
Pile the weight on. Nope. Not unckempt
and I'm not overweight. I I'll repeat
myself. You people are fat and ugly.
Look at yourselves.
Fat and [ __ ] ugly. If I look like you
people, I would kill myself. You know
what? No wonder you people come on here
every day doing this because you're so
ugly that you can't even live your life.
No girlfriend, no family, no mates.
You're so ugly. This is all you've got.
You're [ __ ] ugly as [ __ ] most of
you. That's Bro, why do you why do you
think none of you people can come on
camera and prove me wrong? Cuz you know
you're ugly. That's why you hide your
faces, bro. I'm better looking than all
of you people. And you know it, bro.
I'll put the link up right now and prove
me wrong. You can't do it, bro. You're
[ __ ] ugly bastards. Bully victims.
And you know why? Yeah. You talk about
people being bullied. It's cuz you've
been bullied all your life at school.
You've been bullied your whole life for
your ugliness. That's why you're on here, lad.
Brother, isn't your boyfriend in his 40s
on YouTube every day repeating the same
[ __ ] Dr. Echo,
do you not maybe think your Isn't your
boyfriend already doing that? Your
boyfriend, Lord J, you little Ly Mong.
Yeah, stop talking about yourself,
brother. I will never be like you
retards. You fat ugly 40year-olds. Stop
injecting your life onto me, Dr. Echo.
I'm not like you. I'm not like your
boyfriend. This is what I mean with you
people. It's just self-p projection
every time. You're in your 40s. You
ain't got a life. You're ugly.
Everything you say is about yourselves.
Do you even realize, bro? Do you even
realize that you're talking about yourselves?
You are 40year-old ugly people. I've
said this now 20 times now and you and
it has not gone through your head. Yeah.
You are You can't live without YouTube,
Dr. Eko. You're on YouTube every day cuz
you ain't got a life. And then when
people tell you that, oh, they're
speculating. Oh, they're speculating.
No, it's facts. It's not speculating.
It's facts. No person that's got a life. Yeah.
No person that's got a life would be sat
on there 24/7.
Solid advice. How can any of you people
give me advice?
How can any of you people that ain't got
your [ __ ] together give me advice? You
literally can't give anyone advice. You
can't even get off of YouTube for one
day. How the [ __ ] are you going to give me advice?
Yeah, I own Monty. Yeah, cuz you kept
talking about me, bro.
How can someone that can't get off of
YouTube for one day give me advice?
You're not You're not setting a good
example, are you?
You're idiots, bro. You're absolute
[ __ ] clowns. I wouldn't have went on
here today if I didn't lose that 100
pound gambling. That's how sad it is. Do
you know? That's how sad it is that if I
didn't lose money gambling today, £100,
I wouldn't have been on it. For some
reason, whenever I lose, I feel like going live.
Don't know why, bro, but I just do. If I
didn't gamble today, I wouldn't come on
here. Swear to God, I wouldn't come on
here. Let me just They just escalated.
Yeah, but LT's biased.
Yeah, but LT is biased. So, yeah.
I don't give a [ __ ] about LT. I don't
like LT. He's biased.
Yeah. Still on here.
And you're also on here as well. Yeah.
No, I don't like LT. He's biased. I
that [ __ ] again. No.
Yeah. He was starting that girlfriend
[ __ ] wasn't he? Uh Steven Allen LT.
That's how that all the whole madness
thing started again.
Now he's a troll, bro. That LT is a troll.
Yeah, that LT is a troll, bro. So, yeah.
No, no one can give me advice, bro. Trust me.
You need to give yourself some advice.
You know, you people need to give
yourselves some advice
to be fair. Yeah.
So, apparently these people work.
I don't need a job, mate. I've got
enough money. I get enough money. You I
don't need a job. Maybe you should get
yourself a job.
Isn't it funny that you people tell
people to get a job yet you are the ones
on YouTube 24/7 with no job? Huh? Bro,
is there anything that you say that
isn't about yourselves?
What do you think, Steven Howard? Is
there anything they've ever said that's
not about themselves?
Get a job. They've never had a job. They
don't They don't have a job. Ugly,
they're ugly. Fat, they're fat. Skin,
they're skin. No life. They ain't got I
I generally don't think there's one
thing they've said that isn't about themselves.
Telling people to get a job when you
ain't even got a job yourselves.
Bro, come on, man. That is some 2012 [ __ ]
No normal person would be on this
community. No. I like I said, that's why
I'm not really on here anymore.
I'm not on here anymore really.
I went live today cuz I lost Buddy
Gably. I was pissed off. Other than
that, I would have been on here.
Bro, you don't need to know what any
women want to hear.
You're a s. You're a white knight. You
don't know about women. I know more
about women than you do.
And if you think that getting a job gets
you a woman, bro, keep thinking that.
And you know, this is how you know that
these people ain't got no life. just the
way that they talk about things. They
just have got no life experience.
You know, normal people wouldn't come on
here every day if they had a life, bro.
Trust me, if they had a life, they
wouldn't be on here. Okay, think about
it like this. Yeah. I'm saving money.
I'm saving money at the minute. Yeah.
Stephen Howard. Yeah. So, I don't go out
drinking as much. Yeah. Right. And these
people are on here more than me. Think
about it, bro. So, I'm saving money. Yeah.
Well, you're very, very wrong, doctor,
because no, not many women ask me if I
work or I don't work.
So, you really don't know anything about
women. And I'm not here to be convinced.
I know more than you, bro. I'm not
talking about women. If you want to
think what you think, that's on you,
bro. I'm not here to argue when I know
I'm right. It's stupid. I know more
about women than you. I've been with
more women than you and I've met more
women than you. That is not even
bullshitting. That is facts.
You don't know about women, bro.
But I said I'm a gambling addict. I
never said I'm a gambling addict. The [ __ ]
So yeah. Like, so if I'm doing that and
I'm just chilling, bro, how are these
people on YouTube more than me?
Is that not saying something?
Is that not really saying something?
You come on here. Come on here at 8 9:00
in the morning. Yeah, Stephen. I They'll
be on YouTube. They'll be straight on
YouTube. They will literally be straight
on YouTube as soon as someone goes live,
right? They'll be straight on YouTube,
bro. And they'll be on it all day.
They'll be on it all day, bro.
Not even like certain times. Yeah.
So, I don't get why they don't just live
their life and do what they do on
YouTube and not judge others.
You know, they were on a Christmas for [ __ ] sake. Yeah.
What they do is so weird on here, bro.
They are [ __ ] weird as [ __ ]
They are so [ __ ] weird.
They are weird. Very weird.
You can't ever tell women your full name
in case they Google you.
That's never going to happen.
Well, you can do Well, actually, Grezy,
you could do after months.
That's none of your business. What I've
got to be um what I've got to be proud
of. Grievy. Yeah, but you do realize
Yeah. At the start, no. But if you was
meeting someone for like 6 months to a year,
then the chances are they're just not
going to leave you.
You get it? But if they haven't met you
yet or they've met you once, then yeah,
you're [ __ ] But I mean, like, if they
they met you for like 6 months to a year,
they wouldn't it wouldn't
it wouldn't really matter. Do you get it?
You get what I'm saying, bro?
That 19year-old never found out anything
about me, bro.
She would She never found anything about me.
Yeah, you are a virgin.
Then you know how I know you are a
virgin by the way you speak about women.
Oh, if you get a job, you'll meet a
woman. Only virgins do this. Only
virgins white knight and simp. The only
people that do that are virgins now come
to think of it.
The way you defend women and thinking
that if people live by themselves they'd
get a woman. Only virgins would say that. Yeah.
That 19year-old never found out anything about me.
Yeah. Two kids. Yeah.
Is it It's very immature. Ah,
is it? Well, have you been on Launch
Legs's channel, Dr. Eko?
Cuz he calls me a virgin all the time. I
don't see you calling him immature.
So, is it only immature when I say it?
I think it's very immature calling me a
virgin even though I put a porno up and
got people's channel banned. Been in
women's beds naked, been with multiple
different women and I still get called a
virgin. Strange that.
No, I think it's strange that, isn't it?
But I still get called a virgin.
That's interesting that.
Yeah, that's interesting. That
Yeah, that's interesting how someone
could be called a virgin
who's done all of that stuff.
That's interesting, bro. Very interesting. H
Yeah, that's interesting. that.
I don't know. The virgin greasy.
No, I didn't know I was a virgin, bro.
That's That's news to me.
That's strange. Strange. That is
That is strange.
Never you mind if I'm traveling anywhere
abroad this year? That's never you mind, lad.
Next time they say, "Yeah, how can
somebody with a girlfriend be a virgin,
Steven?" Yeah. All you got to say is
there's no proof that that is actually his girlfriend.
At the end of the day, bro, if if if a [ __ ]
and me and all the [ __ ] I've put up is
not proof, then some random woman is not
proof. Could be his carer, could be his
cousin. Like we can really get into
this, bro, about this whole virgin thing
if you want.
We don't know. That that might not even
be his girlfriend.
I don't know, bro.
This Joe is really starting to w me up.
But at the end of the day, bro, just ste
like Steven Howard said, they're never
going to meet you. He's not going to
meet you. This Joe's not going to meet
you, bro. By you, I mean me.
No, he [ __ ] didn't invite me, mate.
No, he [ __ ] did not. Not to
Nottingham. He didn't. Yeah.
No. Yeah, but that he that's not
Nottingham. Yeah. He told me to go to
somewhere, but not Nottingham. I'm not going there.
I'm not I'm not going all that way
because I know what he's going to do.
I know exactly what he's going to do.
Grievy. Oh, we control you. We made you
go there. It's so obvious, bro. You
can't kill a kid, lad. If he was serious
about meeting, he would come to Nottingham.
It's 150 mi away from me and 70 mi away from him.
Simple as that. Simple as that. What's
that? 70 mi like an hour and 20 minutes.
Hour? Hour? Simple
cuz that is exactly what's going to happen. So yeah,
and it's not just going to be a fight, Greavesy.
It won't be a fight. I'll headbutt him.
I'll [ __ ] knock him out. I'll laugh
in his [ __ ] face like a nasty little
[ __ ] and put it all over my YouTube. And
then I'll rob him. I'll pro, Do you know
what? I'd probably, bro, I'd probably
take his clothes off, bro
home walk home naked. I'm not I'm not
going again for just a little fight. I'm
not having a little fight then coming
back. Yeah. How long has this come been
winding people up now?
It's not going to be a little fight.
It's not going to be a little fight,
bro, at all. You know, and then I I'm
just going to come back. No, no, no, no,
no, no, no.
You know, I want it I want it on my channel.
You know what I mean, bro?
Does that sound lovely to you, Grezy?
Does that sound lovely to you?
I'm not strong enough to pick up a a bus ticket.
Do you even hear what you're saying,
bro? Do you even hear what you're saying?
A bus ticket. Are you [ __ ] mad, you silly [ __ ] Yeah.
And I never had an obsession with Sher
Co. I just said that people used to say
she was attractive to fit in.
to answer your question. Yeah. So what
they did do it to fit in.
I saw people I saw about three people
today, Greavvesy, wear them Canada Goose coats.
Everyone wears these Canada Goose coats now.
And what is that, Greavesy?
That everyone wears the same coat now. A
lot of people. A lot of people
What do you think of that?
But I don't know why people follow
trends though, bro. I don't follow no
trends. I wear Vapor Maxes, no one wears
it. Ami jeans, no one wears it. Six silk
coat, no one wears it. I don't follow trends.
I don't follow a trend, lad.
Nah, not me, bro.
I had Stone Island,
but I don't really see people wear it
like that. You don't really see people
wear Stone Island anymore.
So greasy was liking real a trend.
What do you think of that, Greavvesy?
Me paying £200 for a pair of jeans.
They're lovely jeans though, aren't they, Greavvesy?
They're lovely jeans, lad.
So what you want me to you want me to do
a video in Nottingham Reeves laughing Joe's face
and knock him out. Yeah,
he'd love to see that content.
The only thing about not eating as much
now is you're not going to be as big.
That sounds lush, doesn't it, Grezy?
That sounds lush.
[ __ ] a little virgin.
I might go back on roulette.
Like [ __ ] will I grievy?
Like [ __ ] will I? Yeah, right.
Press one if you think online roulette's
rigged. Press two if you don't think it is. I'll start.
Oh. Oh, it doesn't let me comment.
This [ __ ] phone has almost had it,
Grezy. This phone has almost had it.
It's just going to You're just going to
open it one day and it's just going to
break. I need to get the new fold. Greavesy.
going to be getting a new fold in July.
Would you like an unboxing, Greavvesy?
Yeah, online roulette is definitely
fixed, bro. They still haven't closed my
account, you know, even though I asked
them to do it,
they won't close it.
What? You really think it's You think
it's fixed UK asylum as well? Really?
Yeah, it is fixed, bro.
It is definitely fixed.
They don't let you close your account
now, bros. Dodgy, isn't it?
You doing a football on Saturday, Stephen?
I guess I want some money today, bro.
Just wouldn't keep [ __ ] going with it.
Why is online roulette rigged, Steven
Albert? Why is it so rigged?
We're going to make
We're going to make a baby with this Christian. Izzy.
Yeah, but do you think the roulette's
fixed on um
on the UK sites?
No, it's not a crypto site. It's just an
site that's not regulated by you, the
UK. But they didn't charge me a fee this
time when I deposited.
Yeah, but even the Lad Brooks roulette
is probably fixed, isn't it?
It's all fixed, bro.
I'm going to try and have a baby with
this person, Steven Howard.
Hi, Greavvesy. Are you still there? I I
had I knew I had something to tell you.
What do you mean stricter regulations?
I knew I had something to tell you, Greasy.
What kind of stricter regulations?
This woman said that this Indian woman
said that if I was nice to her and
treated her good, she said that she
would lay me on her belly every night
like I was her baby. Greedy.
She then she put me on her stomach and
put me to sleep like a baby. Grieves it.
Why is it stupid?
I might buy some more Lego Grezy.
We're missing Chew Becca with a crossbow
gqueezy. We need a Chew Becca uh figure.
It's [ __ ] fixed, bro. I was playing
at this site called Brick Casino.
It's [ __ ] fixed.
It's so fixed. So, at least with Lad
Brooks, you get your money instant.
Yeah, but they are on the on the UK
sites they they ask you for proof of um
proof of income, don't they?
They ask for proof of income.
I'm sure they do at some point. Yeah,
they asked for proof of income, I think.
He needs to do some football bets, man.
Yeah. Is it [ __ ] Is it [ __ ] to do with
money laundering, bro?
They've got no problem with people
losing thousands and thousands and
thousands in the casino. Yet, as soon as
you win, they want all ID and all this
and all that. It's [ __ ]
They just don't like paying. Exactly. Yeah, Dusty.
I'll never forget that time in
Nottingham, bro. Yeah. When I was with
Ant-Man, I was 150 in. I got it to 350
after like an hour.
[ __ ] ages, bro. And then I tried to
cash it out. There's like, "Have you got
anything with your name on it? Have you
got anything with your name on it?
Have you got anything with your name on it?"
Yeah, but even casinos are dodgy, dusty
nowadays trying to pay people. They'll
do anything to get out of paying people.
Even casinos do it, bro. Why do you
think you go in and the [ __ ] ticket
the the the ticket machines are all out of order?
Yes, you [ __ ] do,
Dusty. Yes, you [ __ ] do. They were
asking me for ID for £350. And when I
used to go into the casinos, Yes, they [ __ ] do.
In casinos they do.
No, in casinos they do. Bro, I used to
go to the Empire though and they used to
just pay I think I won £1,600 before
they paid it after a while.
I won £1,600 from 500. Yeah.
Is would you say Lad Brooks is a
well-known site, Dusty?
Yeah. I used to go Empire all the time.
I used to win there. I used to win money
in the Empire.
I'm on 1600 before and I gave it in 50s. Yay.
I won four grand before from 150.
Happy days, bro. Good times.
Is Lad Brooks a trusted site, Dusty?
four months. I think the worst the worst
I've had is like four days for them to
pay out. Yeah, but the roulette on Lad
Brooks is fixed though, isn't it, Dusty? It's fixed.
Yeah, but it's fixed though, isn't it?
I went with I I echo I went in the
casino with 150 before I walked out with four grand.
I hit 11 with a multiplayer.
I used to go casino all the time.
Yeah, I used to go casino all the time, bro.
So Dusty, if I if I put 500 pound on Lad
Brooks now and I won six grand, they
will ask for ID now.
They won't ask for ID now.
Really? So, so I can't win on there then, Dusty.
So, I can't win then. No.
Yeah, but I can't show bank statements obviously.
So what? They wouldn't pay you then. If
you won five, six grand, they wouldn't
pay you know.
So they wouldn't Yeah.
[ __ ] gambling, bro.
Yeah, I used to play golden bet. I used
to win thousands on golden bet. Yeah.
If I went to the hippodromeome now,
Dusty, and I'd w I win, they wouldn't
pay me out cuz I'm banned in it.
I'm banned from the premises.
So, I'm actually trespassing now. If I
go into any of them casinos, I'm actually trespassing. Yeah,
I used to love
probably for the best to be honest. Yeah. Yep.
I used to go casinos every Thursdays and
I'd always win, bro.
Casino then O'Neal was dusty.
I've done more than LJ in his life, bro.
And I'm younger.
I'm younger, bro.
I've done more than he has in his life,
bro. Trust me.
Believe that. [ __ ] believe that.
But yeah, I I they wouldn't pay me, Dusty.
They wouldn't pay me at all, Dusty. Nope.
No, they wouldn't pay me, bro.
I used to love winning them£50 notes.
No, Dusty. It was lush. It was lush. Yeah, man.
When did you last play roulette, Dusty?
>> Yeah. So, so does Lad Brooks.
I don't play slots.
I don't play slots, lad.
Do you think gambling's worth it, Dusty?
Do you think gambling's worth it or not? It doesn't.
It's so hard to win nowadays, isn't it?
It's hard to win in it nowadays, bro. Oh, bless.
Do you like my little women collection, Grezy?
Yeah. So, I'm going to meet this Christian Izzy,
but I'm going to get with other people
at the same time. Is that all right, Grezy?
Is that all right, Grezy? Is that okay
with you, boss?
I want to be a cheater. Grezy's
all right and a grievy. Yeah,
she's all right. Dean's okay.
I think it's all right.
I think it's all right, mate.
is Matthew's live.
Yeah, Ed's [ __ ] legs [ __ ] in it.
You know what? Me, Greasy, Dusty,
Steven, we all need to meet. We all need
to meet up for a tea party.
What do you think, Grezy?
Nice little tea party.
A little chimpanzees tea party.
So Greasy, do you think Red Star is
still going to be stalking me after 10 years?
What do you think, Steven Hour? Do you
reckon after 10 years he's still going
to be stalking me?
Or do you reckon he would have got a life?
Jesus Christ. You should go in this Red
Star channel, bro.
[ __ ] you hell, lad.
Been doing it for years.
Years and years and years.
It's [ __ ] quite sad, isn't it, bro? These people Yeah.
Yeah. But they've been doing it. Yeah.
But they've been doing it for years, Greasy.
They've been doing it for absolute years. That's mad.
Jesus. Imagine that. Years. Years. Greasy.
Someone said, "Listen back to his
suicidal stream. He has 650 to his
entire name. He is one skinned mun."
This was from a year ago.
This was from one year ago.
And these people don't even have 650.
They're [ __ ] broke.
I'd be surprised if any of these people
had 50 quid.
I'd be surprised if any of them had 50 quid. Lad
Grezy, you said you said being skint is
having£300, didn't it?
What did you say?£300, didn't it? Um, Greezy,
isn't that what you said, Grezy?
It was £300, wasn't it, Grey? H. Yeah.
But you said six But you said 600. Okay. Is it?
Yeah. And by emergencies, you mean like
your phone could pack up?
Like something could pack up like your
phone, isn't it?
Your phone could pack up a minute.
You said 1300's good though, ain't it, Grezy?
But you said 1300's okay, ain't it, Grezy? 1300,400. Yeah. Hey.
So, how how much would you say is like a
solid amount then Greavesy?
15 1,500 2,000 in it. Yeah.
line up, bro.
Yeah. 300 pound.
It used to be back in the day.
Back in the day, 300 pound used to be something.
10 years ago, it did grieves.
10 years ago, it used to be something.
Did you know that?
Yeah. A few years ago, it used to be um
it used to be a lot, bro. Feel the pound. Yep.
Why he Joe's being mean about Christian, is he?
He's being mean about Christian, is he?
He said that she's a Bible basher.
He said that she's a Bible basser. Graves.
He's just jealous.
Yeah, he's jealous, bro. Oh, [ __ ]
Bless you then, Grezy, if you saved £400 this month.
Bless you if you saved £400 this month, Grezy.
That's cute, isn't it? Bless you.
Bless you, Grezy. Bless you.
Greavvesy skin. Everyone,
your skin in it, Grezy.
Your skin, lad.
Where is his skin? Yeah.
What's the day today? What's the date today, bro?
I'm getting a bit hungry now, Grezy.
I fancy some McDonald's.
I fancy some McDonald's nuggets.
Yeah, Grevy doesn't go out. Yeah.
Who? Virgin boy. Virgin boy absolutely
is skin. And that money that he showed
was his daddy's life savings.
And yeah, you are absolutely skinn. If
you had 13 grand and you had all that
money, you wouldn't be in a bedsit with
no life experiences.
Yeah. He showed 13 grand of his daddy's
life savings about 5 years ago, bro.
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. He lives in a bedsit,
no life experiences at all. That's not
someone that's got 13 grand, bro. Make
it make sense. Someone that's got 13
grand doesn't live in a bedsit with no life experiences.
Make it make sense.
He doesn't have money, bro. He doesn't
have no money because you know how you
know he's got no money, Stephen Howard.
Yeah. Remember that time, right, when I
was showing that um well that money I
was showing different amounts of money?
Yeah. 5.7 grand, 2 grand, three grand.
Who Who come on here and showed me any money, bro?
What person come on here and showed me any money? No one.
I was thinking about this earlier, you
know, when I was actually walking to the
shop here. I was thinking, "Hold on a
minute." Yeah. These people claim that
they've got all this money, but no one
ever ever played the money game with me.
Cuz they ain't got none, you know?
Why are you so invested in [ __ ] Why
are you invested in [ __ ] ugly
disabled women? You skint [ __ ]
that can't even consent to sex, which is
why you're still a virgin and you're
going to die one.
You [ __ ] stupid [ __ ]
Why are you invested in [ __ ] disabled
girls that won't [ __ ] you?
But no, you ain't got money, mate. I
remember when I was showing that money,
no one could match it, mate. Not one
person could show me money. Not one
person. Not one person. Dusty mate, you
show daddy's life savings from four or
five years ago. Your skin, you live in a
bedsit. People with money don't live in
a bedsit with charity shop clothes. You
can't pull them all over my eyes. You
ain't got no [ __ ] money. You're [ __ ] skinned.
You're [ __ ] skin.
[ __ ] skin, mate. [ __ ] absolutely
skin. Skin to the eyeballs. Bed boy. Bedshet boy
Why Grezy? I'm really hungry, bro. Can I
get some chicken nuggets?
Can I get some chicken nuggets? Greasy.
I'm actually really hungry,
mate. You're saying that I'm skint? I
don't live in a [ __ ] bed like you,
you [ __ ] virgin. Greavvesy,
are are you sure that's okay with you? Greavesy. Yeah.
Obviously have to run it by you first, mate. that it
one second please bro can you hear me yeah
it said Boy,
that's it. Boy,
what's up, bro? Bedshit, boy.
Skinny little bed [ __ ] with no money in it.
Yeah, Porky Pete brother self projecting again.
We've seen you fat ugly bastards and
you're not going to make me feel like
you. How long have you ugly fat people
been on this shitty community for?
You little low lives. You little low
How long have you low lives been on this
community? You ugly fat people. No
girlfriend, no friends. Tell me, bro.
Yeah, but do you not remember that?
Anyway, Stephen Howard, when I was
showing these people money, did you
notice that not one of them showed me anything?
Do you remember that, bro? During that
summer, not one person showed me any money.
Nah, I'd rather live with my mom in a
house than a shitty bedset. I'd rather
live with my mom in a house than a
bedsit. No, no, no, no. I'd rather live
with my mom in a house. I'd rather live
with my mom in a house than a [ __ ] shitty bedit.
100% would. I literally 100% would.
I'd rather live with my mom in a in a
house. A house where people should live.
You people are so boring. You just say
the same [ __ ] over and over and over
again. This is why people don't go live anymore.
This is literally why people don't go
live anymore, bro. It's only cuz I lost
money to This is why people don't go live.
Cuz it's just the same fat, ugly
self-projecting loners. That's why no
one goes live anymore,
Greezy. That's why you do remember when
you messaged me on Instagram, bro.
Uh you messaged me on Instagram. I was
done with this [ __ ] Why do you think, bro?
It doesn't matter what I'm going to do,
bro. We'll cross that bridge when we
come to it.
Yeah, that's why I don't I don't really
come on here anymore, laddy.
£14 now for [ __ ] nuggets and a Coke.
Yeah, well, she's doing fine.
We're doing fine.
One second, bro. Bro,
£1 for some nuggets and [ __ ] coke. [ __ ] sake. No. No.
Mad is it. Greasy,
what do you reckon the cheapest you
could eat for in a week? Huh?
What's the cheapest you could eat for in a week?
What's the cheapest you reckon you could do?
Ah, you'd be like [ __ ] Virgin boy Grezy.
Yeah, but you'd be like [ __ ] if you
Yeah, but if you done that,
if you done that, you would just be like virgin boy.
Greavvesy doesn't go out
and spend money, do you? Bless you.
Bless you in life, Greavvesy.
put this [ __ ] in.
Yeah, I'd say about5 a day. Yeah,
I kind of [ __ ] it, bro. Gambling
today. Now I'm [ __ ] ordering McDonald's.
It's not good, is it? Bro, I've done it.
I've lived on £5 a day
when I was saving and [ __ ]
I'm still saving now, but
you'd be very depressed doing it, bro.
You'd be very depressed.
How much money do you think having in
your bank account account is skin? Bob,
how much would you class as is skin?
Greavvesy says if you've got three only
£300, you're skin. How much do you think? 150. Uh,
I know a certain person who's skint
and he's a [ __ ] virgin. Steven
Howard, he's the biggest virgin you'll ever meet.
There's no way someone that's got 13
grand is living in a bedsit with no life
experiences, mate. Sorry, mate. It's one
or the other. You're either into
traveling, you're either into designer
clothes, or you have some sort of asset
or something. No one has money and does
nothing. Trust me, bro.
Doesn't matter if it's not 1 million. I
done a lot with four or five grand.
I've done a lot with uh you can do a lot
with 13 grand.
So, it's not a million. And your point is,
your point is, we know it's not a
million. It's 13 grand. Can still do
lots with it. Yeah.
I've never even had 13 grand. I think
the most I've ever had is 9 grand.
I think 9,000 is the most I've ever had.
And I was living a whale of a time. So,
you explain to me how you've got all of
this money, but you're in a bedsit with
no life experience.
Can you explain that, mate?
Can you, mate? Your little cancelled
shitty bedsit ain't even yours,
mate. That [ __ ] old bedsit in the out of
London that you live in,
that's not yours. It's the councils.
Isn't that right, Steven Howard? Belongs
to the council.
belongs to the [ __ ] council.
Yeah, I know what a bedsit is. It's what
you're [ __ ] living in.
A [ __ ] shitty little bedset.
A shitty little bedset.
A little virgin bedset.
Your little virgin bedset with no bed in
it. Is your big virgin.
Isn't that right?
You little virgin.
Are you a little virgin?
You a little virgin.
You a little virgin. Are you a little
virgin? You [ __ ] virgin.
You [ __ ] virgin. You [ __ ] virgin.
You look like a virgin cuz you're a [ __ ] virgin. Yep.
You get yourself a little job.
Stop saying Sher Cole is attractive to
fit in. Have a mind of your [ __ ] own.
Do you know what I'm going to do? I'm
going to buy you a um mind of your own
for your birthday.
What do you think of that, Grezy? Oh,
it's your birthday in a couple of days.
I'm going to buy you a mind of your own. Stop copying.
What do you think, you little copycat?
You little copycat. Are you a little copycat?
I'm going to buy you a mind of your own.
What do you think of that for birthday present?
So you can stop copying copying the
crowd. Oh, my McDonald's is on its rail
way already. Oh, it comes so fast.
Yeah, I had £9,000. Yeah. So,
yeah. And I've got more money than you
now. What's your [ __ ] point? Do you
know what, bro? Why are we even talking
about money, bro? I've got more life
experience than you. I've been to more
places than you, been with more women
than you, had better clothes than you,
got more family than you.
I've literally got more life experience
than you, you [ __ ] virgin.
You went to Amsterdam because I did.
Little copycat. Copied my holidays. You
copy my holidays. You little copycat.
You little copycat. And no, I never show
nine grand because most of it was in my bank account. So yeah. Yeah.
Yeah, mate. Yeah.
Yeah. That's nice, mate. At least my mom
never starved me. And at least my dad
weren't a nons.
People die, mate.
Your dad's a nons and your mom starved
you. And I don't have a full brother. I
got a half brother who I met once. So yeah. Yeah, mate.
Your mom starved. You and her boyfriend
beat [ __ ] out of you.
They've beat the [ __ ] out of you, mate.
Beat the fat [ __ ] out of you.
You ain't got a mom. Your mom starved
you. You little [ __ ] You little [ __ ]
virgin [ __ ] It's the star of you.
I UK sign him. I'm thinking of buying
his virgin for his birthday. A mind of his own.
What do you reckon? A mind of his own.
What do you think of that? A mind of
your own. What do you think of that? A
mind of your own. What do you think of
that? A mind of your own. What do you
think of that? A mind of your own. What
do you think of it? A mind of your own.
What do you think of that? A mind of your own.
Why? How am I trolling UK asylum? He
said Cheryl Cole was attractive to fit
in. You didn't want to feel left out.
It's tough for you to a college and you
didn't want to
you didn't want to, you know,
you didn't want to feel left the [ __ ]
out, did you? Oh, she's attractive. I
won't deny it. I won't deny it. It's the
name. It's the name. It was all in the
name. Nothing to do with the person. Virgin copycat.
Are you a little virgin copycat?
You a little virgin copycat.
>> Yes, you [ __ ] are. Little virgin.
>> Oh, man. 16.
>> One six.
Oh, I got myself some nuggets. I
couldn't help myself. I literally
>> I couldn't help myself. Oh.
You can't deny it. You can't deny it.
>> Yeah, it was quick though because it's
the time is it? M m.
So, I'm going to ask you this one more time. Yeah.
So you sure that
the only reason he was saying that if
you don't find Sh attractive, you're gay
is because the name.
So it was 100% about the name, right?
Not the person. It was just about the
name, wasn't it?
Oh, I don't get any source with it.
So it was definitely the name, right?
You're not the not the person.
Well, that's what said.
That's what chat said.
I used to get bullied.
Um, I used to get teased cuz I didn't
find her attractive. Music.
I got teased because I didn't find her attractive.
He said if I didn't find her attractive,
Dusty, I was gay.
When I used to meet nonss,
he said that I can't deny that she's attractive.
He said that I can't deny it. And if I
said that she's ugly, um, I'm gay m's
a bit dodge, but m
I only get the nuggets from McDonald's.
It's the only things that don't come cold.
Dusty, why was you saying that I was gay
if I don't find her attractive?
I'm not gay, Dusty. I promise you I'm not gay.
Nons said that I was gay. I'm not gay.
I swear I'm not going. You said I was
going. I don't find her attractive.
Well, I don't find her attractive. Stop bullying me. M
I'm enjoying my little nuggets here.
[ __ ] UK asylum saying I need to stop
trolling. I don't troll. Never troll.
No, but nonsense said that if I don't
find her attractive, I'm gay.
Yeah, I think that's a bloody good idea, Grezy.
That's That's certainly okay with me.
I reckon you should do exactly the same.
Yep. Damn right. Yes. Yes. M Yeah, treat yourself.
I want to live with Greasy.
Yeah, there's one sister I don't talk to.
There's one sister I don't talk to. Yeah, Dusty.
But I'm sure there's a sister you don't
speak to or whatever.
Yeah, there's someone I don't speak to. but
They're using it as an excuse. You know
the things I said in the past, Dusty,
they're using it as an excuse.
Like I'm an easy target, right? It's so
easy to bring up my past. Like, oh,
things you've said and said, you get me?
As opposed to people that are actual
pedophiles. You get me, bro? So, yeah,
it is an excuse. Yeah, definitely, bro.
Like what you said might be [ __ ] up,
but bro, like it's just words at the end
of the day
and it's years later. So, I mean, think
about it. Yeah. Look at all the [ __ ] me
and Monty went through like what we said
and whatever and we met up and we was fine.
So, it is an excuse, bro. In 2026, it is an excuse.
Like, and it's just easy to use my name.
You get it? Uh,
of course, of course.
So yeah, I haven't.
Did you order it?
I remember when I was having that steak
with USA Izzy. It was lovely.
Oh, did you get did you get did you eat
did you order it?
Did you order it?
Your little nuggets.
I've almost finished mine. Excuse me.
Did you order it?
>> So, what you've ordered the McDonald's nuggets?
What? You've literally ordered it?
What? 20 nuggets and what? What? A Coke?
What? You've ordered 20 nuggets and what
seriously what was what did you order
for McDonald's? Can you tell me the exact order?
What's your exact order? What is it? H Meow meow meow.
You copy cat.
You eat more than me, you fat [ __ ]
[ __ ] large fries as well.
Greasy, for [ __ ] sake.
How do you like chicken ticker? Greasy.
I love chicken ticker. Do you like chicken ticker?
Chicken ticker with some onions. Oh,
do you like it?
[ __ ] hell. We will, mate. We [ __ ] will.
It's only right because I copied your
order last time, did I?
I copied your order, didn't I? Yeah,
but next time get an Indian, Grezy. I
never hear you getting Indian,
Grezy. I never hear about you getting an Indian.
You don't really get Indian, do you, Grezy?
Oh, I love Coke. I love curses. Okay.
You need to have an Indian boozy. It's [ __ ] rough.
It's how I get my vitamins.
I agree with you this year.
You know, nonsense.
Be honest. Do you think he knows about
the copying trend
and he's just playing stupid
when he's like, I'm saying that people
used to copy each other? Be honest.
Be honest. Yeah.
Do you think he knows about the trend?
He knew about it in it.
He didn't know what was going on.
She must have kn
the crowd. No. Do with me?
You need an Indian, bro. Chicken cha
binderoo pa rice and some cheese naan.
Did you see that guy there that was climbing
that channel I sent you? That's [ __ ]
mad, is it? What the [ __ ] bro?
I could, but it's hard to watch, is it?
If you to watch it,
did you did you watch some more of the videos? BG that
[ __ ] off. I'm not having a [ __ ] with
that [ __ ] virgin.
Sarah's [ __ ] ugly.
[ __ ] ugly, [ __ ]
No, [ __ ] that, mate. Disabled. No.
What do you think of that ginger guy channel?
Why? What do you think of that channel I
sent you? Greasy.
That guy is our age. He's been to like
80 countries. Imagine he come in this community. Yeah.
What could anyone say about him? Even
though they would still try and talk [ __ ]
Imagine that Greavves. Yeah. He's our
age. He's been to 80 countries. So
imagine he went on a law J's panel.
Yeah. And he can be like, "Yep, I've
been to all of the countries.
I've been to all of your countries and
I've been to more countries and I'm 29
and you can't tell me nothing." But they
probably still talk [ __ ] in it. Uh,
it's a L l y l a w. Yeah. Actually,
them people have been all around the
world, bro. And they're they're young.
They're our age.
He doesn't upload anymore, though. I
grieves. He had a kid in that, but he
used to do madnesses, bro. Like climbing
[ __ ] running away from police.
I don't know how we climbed that bridge,
bro. [ __ ] that.
Yeah, you'll be waiting for an upload,
but he's not going to be uploading. He left YouTube.
Look at you. You'll be waiting and
waiting and waiting, but nothing's going to happen.
What did you say? What did you say,
Greasy, that you you miss?
You You'll wait.
You You wait.
I I'm not I'm not understanding. You wait.
Wait for what?
Yeah, bro. But he's been to like 80 countries.
So if he went on LJ's panel,
what could they say to him? But they
would still talk [ __ ] They would still
talk. This is what I was trying to say.
Like bombing L. Yeah. They think they've
been to loads of countries, but they
really really haven't. If they're making
it a competition, they really haven't.
There's people our age that's actually
traveled the world, you know.
I'm pretty sure my sister's been to more
countries than Lord J. She's been to a
lot of countries.
Greavves never crossed the pond, have
you, Griezy? You've never crossed the
pond yet, have you, lad?
Well, you're just happy collecting your
little DVDs, aren't you?
You're just happy collecting your little DVDs. Bless you.
What do you think of Christian? Is he grievy?
I'm scared of falling in love again in
case I get hurt.
What if I get hurt again? Greavves.
You know, I've been thrown pillar to
post, pillar to post, pillar to post.
Found a new mama. That mommy abandons me,
you know. Then what, Greavvesy?
What if I get hurt and abandoned again? You know
then what greases
you'll always be here to pick up the
pieces. I'm hoping
You'll be here to pick up the pieces, it Oh gosh,
I'm under my little blanket now. Grezy,
I want to make a baby. grievy.
I was saying to this woman on Tindy
yesterday, I said, "We should make a
baby and [ __ ] the system over."
I said, "If we had a baby, we could get
money from the government and get a house."
She said, "I'm not sure that's the right
reason to want a baby."
I said, "It is."
I said, "If we have a baby, we can [ __ ]
the system over and get some extra cash. We
can make some We can get some more money
from the government. We
What's your opinion on me having having
kids, having a baby?
What's What's your opinion?
Be cute, isn't it?
It's quite cute.
We can get some money from the government
for the Bubba. Yeah,
that'd be cute. Why not?
Why not, lad?
You actually think I'm a troll? We
cuz this UK asylum keeps calling me a
troll and I'm not a troll.
I'm not a troll, bro. I don't get nothing.
Why wouldn't I have a Why wouldn't I
have a good upbringing?
Why wouldn't it have a have a good upbringing?
No, but I'm being we
No, but I'm being serious about the baby and stuff.
I do want to I do actually want to have a baby,
you know. I want to see what it looks like.
You didn't hear that, did you, Greasy?
I do want a baby Grezy just to see what
it looks like.
Is that cute? Yeah.
I want to have a baby with multiple
people though, Griezy. Like three
people. Three different people. Griezy.
I have a baby with three different people.
What's your opinion on that?
I think that'll be the best.
No, don't say that.
I like your picture, Greavvesy. It's got
Stitch on it and it says Greavvesy above
it. You're such a [ __ ] troll. You're
a proper troll. You are Greavvesy.
I love the greasy bit above.
You're a [ __ ] troll. You're an
absolute troll. I agree he's a troll.
I'm I'm going to have a baby soon, Dusty.
Yeah, I'm going to have a baby soon.
So, you're going to be an uncle. You and
Greavves is going to be an uncle.
How does that feel?
You get to see the bubba.
You get to see the bub chin. Greasy. Dusty.
I come back cuz I didn't want to deprive
you of content. Did I grieve the poor [ __ ] Poor [ __ ]
No, it wouldn't it wouldn't be in care.
It wouldn't be in care. The baby
No, the baby wouldn't be in care.
No, don't say that.
Seaside Mark used to make me laugh. We
he said that Bob sniffs his daughter's knickers.
Do you remember Seaside Mark?
Bob sniffs his daughter's knickers. Oh no.
Why Seaside Mark made me laugh, bro?
He used to do like so many YouTube
videos, bro. Do you remember when he
went to Kent to see that woman Greavvesy?
He saw post. He's like, "Oh, no. Of
course, he ran away, didn't he?
Yeah. Well, that thing went on with the
great guys obviously. Yeah.
You know, I never used to watch him that
much. Sees Mark,
he went to Kent to see some women years
ago. Greavesy. a few years ago.
Yeah, it used to be all right. Suicide B.
No, I don't know who it was. It was some
woman from Kent.
You used to love Seaside Mark, didn't you, Grezy?
The seesaw mark was a troll though.
Grezy, you got bipolar.
I'm going to be talking to uh Christian
Izzy tomorrow. Greavvesy,
we'll be speaking.
I wake up thinking about her. Is that normal? Quezy,
is that cute?
That's cute, isn't it? Grezy,
I can get attached again, can't I? Now,
Grezy, that's when it becomes dangerous getting attached.
Is that right, Grezy? That's when it it
gets dangerous when you get attached again.
What do you think?
Peter Benny can't get attached anymore, Dusty,
because he's already found his mama.
Sometimes I think about that, you know,
greasy like I'll be walking there and it
pops in my head.
He belly can't get attached anymore
because he's already found he's mama.
Them army [ __ ] were laughing at you.
Mocking you crazy.
Them [ __ ] were laughing at you. Mocking you.
That's why I stopped coming on YouTube
for a while cuz that account just kept
mocking me. Greasy.
Greasy. Do you remember? Stop saying my name.
I used to say your name all the time. Is it?
Stop saying my name. No.
No. Because what it is is you people
just laugh at yourselves.
You take the piss out yourselves. Think
about it. Yeah. You are the ones that
are on this shitty community 24/7, 24
hours a day. You take the piss out yourselves.
You laugh at your [ __ ] selves. Really?
sat on YouTube 24/7. No life
in it, bro. In it. Yeah,
you still there, Greavvesy.
I miss Triple H's little voice.
I think you're a bit gay, Grezy, lad.
I think you're a bit gay.
100 250 on casino. What are you talking about, lad?
So, what should I do with this? Um,
Christian is greasy.
But most people are Christian, aren't they?
No, I'm not putting any more on rigged roulette.
Why am I going to put money on something
that's fixed? Pointless.
Oh, Greavvesy. Um, most people are
Christian or Muslim though or Catholic.
They're either Christian or Muslim,
aren't they? Most people
they're either I'm sure they're one of
I'm sure they're one of them. They're
either Muslim or Christian, I'm guessing.
But that's Timmy.
Oh, that's Timmy. Hello, Timmy. Bye-bye.
Oh my god.
I'm a I'm a Muslim. Greasy.
Yeah, I'm a Muslim, but why am I going
to put 100 pound on roulette, bro?
That's [ __ ] fixed as [ __ ] I'm not
doing that. It's fixed.
Oh, Timmy. I'm going to put the link out for Timmy.
Timy's a [ __ ]
greasy. Most people are either Muslim or
Christian, aren't they?
Hello, Timmy. I played I played I put
£100 on roulette earlier and I lost
Timmy. It's fixed.
>> You should know it's big boy now. For [ __ ] sake.
>> They were making it go on other numbers. to me.
>> You know it does. This doesn't want to
pay. It won't pay.
>> It hit eight and then I lost four or
five spins in a [ __ ] row.
>> I can believe that. Believe it or not,
I've covered 28 numbers and I've still
lost five spins in a row.
>> Yeah, cuz that's it's a fix, isn't it?
>> It's called rigged, right?
>> Have you have you you gambled today in
it? I saw like a video.
>> I've made eight quid, believe it or not.
Eight lousy pounds.
>> Eight. Oh, bless you then. If you made eight pound,
>> it was a little bit of a battle, but I
made eight [ __ ] pathetic quid.
>> All right, Timmy, you have to admit you
are a bit of a copycat sometimes, though.
>> Dude, I am the original artist. You all copy me.
>> Yeah, but you're a little copycat. Come
on to me.
>> Come on. You all copy me, dear lads.
Let's be real.
>> So, so what you're saying, would you
would you say it's a it's a copycat community?
>> Well, it's been like that for the last
10 years. You should know that question.
>> What? What's it been?
>> A copy Captain Mooney as you call it.
>> Yeah, you know that. Yeah, but you know
copy me. Let's be real about the situation. >> Yeah. >> No.
>> What you do? What you do? What are you doing tomorrow?
>> Saying oh [ __ ]
>> It's my birthday tomorrow.
>> It's your birthday. >> Yeah.
>> Happy birthday, Peter. Can you Can you
send me £100?
>> Might send you a drink if you apologize
to every female. You've been a dickfest.
>> No, just send me £100.
>> Why are you so angry with women, dude?
No, don't cut me off. Let's have a genuine
>> Simmy. Stop it, man. You're a virgin,
>> dude. I've had more sex than you've had
up cakes, mate. I've had Okay. Okay.
When did you last me anymore? Sorry.
When did you last have sex?
>> About a week ago. >> Yeah.
>> Where did you meet her then,
>> Peter? I'm not fussy. I just get my
hands into something. Even if it's got
six legs, two [ __ ] eyes, you name it.
I'm a bit like Freddy Bean in that way.
>> How do you get all of this sex to me, man?
>> Dude, all you got to do is go in a rough
boozer. Don't be fussy. You know, just be yourself.
>> I might have I might have to come to
Birmingham and you can show me how to do it. Man,
>> thing is, dude, you can't be frigid.
>> If I come to Birmingham on Saturday,
will you meet me?
>> If you say sorry to every female. Yeah, I will.
>> We can go on a pool together and you can
show me how it's done.
>> But thing is though, dude, I'm scared
you're going to lose your Wagner female.
I'm going have to put your head down the [ __ ] toilet.
No, we can go beat that horrible Monty
man [ __ ] up, can't we? Oh,
>> I'm up for that one. Yeah, I am up for
that one. That That [ __ ] does, my so
[ __ ] far left, that bastard. It's untrue. Oh,
>> we can we can do a We could do a tag. We
could do a tag team, is it?
>> He thinks that that Natty G is going to
fight his battles. He's that pathetic. It's be
>> You know what I like about you, Timmy?
You're a proper like war lad.
>> Dude, get it right. Wolampton.
No, but you're originally from Warsaw.
You're a Warsaw lad.
>> No, I was originally from Soleie. Hold your penis.
>> No, but on your thing on the um you know
when you were showing that gambling
thing, it said you are from Warsaw.
>> Yes, because that's what you tell the media, Peter.
>> Oh, so where were you? Wait, where you
originally from? Where you originally from again?
>> I just said it solely. You penis and but
I thought you was a little yum yum.
I am a yam yam.
>> You are a little yum yum.
>> Nutcase. All yum yums are nut cases.
What beat up virgins like you?
>> Didn't me. Have you ever been to Southampton?
>> Yes, I have. And I've c and I've gone to
the ferry to the aisle of white to Newport.
>> I've never been to Southampton.
>> You're not missing much.
>> Okay. What's the shopping center there called then?
How the [ __ ] am I supposed to know? I
haven't been to shopping. I drive
through it to get to the fairy port, you penis.
>> But did you go gambling in Southampton?
>> No, I gone gambling in the aisle of whites.
>> I tell you where it's a good place to
go. You you you'd love you. A good place
to go is um Middlesbor is a lovely place.
>> Are you for real? Are you that it's a
lovely I've been there. It's lovely
place. Pete, it's a [ __ ] hole. That's one.
>> Well, I've been there. You You remember
I went there, isn't it?
>> You remember I went there, is it? I done
a couple of videos. It's a lovely place. Middle work.
>> Are you blind or you haven't been to Spec Savers? >> Huh?
>> Are you blind or haven't you not been to Spec Savers?
>> No, I went Middlesborough. It was
lovely, lovely place. Go, you go on holiday.
>> When do you get bullied on here if you
call [ __ ] Middlesbrough a lovely place?
That's a lovely place, man.
>> Are you actually for [ __ ] real?
>> And Stoke on Trent as well.
>> Are you trolling me or are you actually for real?
>> No, Timmy. I don't troll.
>> Well, you bloody well are trolling me
cuz you say Ms was a lovely place and
you are more [ __ ] spasticated than I thought.
>> Why? It's just a place Middlesbrough. >> Sorry.
>> It's just a place Middlesbrough.
>> Yeah, it's a [ __ ] hole, Peter. That's
why the dosses live there like ponty.
>> Trevor Dawson lives there too.
>> Yes. And that's why Trevor Dawson goes
on about Lisa's [ __ ] skirt 10 years
down the line cuz there's nothing there to do.
>> [ __ ] hell, Timmy. Man, have you been
to Stoke on Trent?
>> Uh, loads of times.
>> That's a sh you know.
>> No, it's not. It's got [ __ ]
>> It's got what [ __ ]
>> But you get more [ __ ] there than
middles, bro. Do you know what Timmy? I
miss Seaside Mark, man. >> Really?
>> Yeah. Me and Greasy miss him. We used to
like the content, isn't it?
>> It gets a lot of [ __ ] on. I don't find
the G too bad. I think he's a bit of a
[ __ ] nut job, but he's all right,
man. Deep down. He's not a bad.
The internet misleads people in it. You
get me? And that they they look at a
screen that I met Mark, right? And I
I'll explain. Mark is not as hard as he
says he is, right? He's he's he's a shy
man deep down, but he's all right, man. He's harmless.
>> Yeah, he's he's a he's a good guy, Mark.
>> Better than you, SH.
>> But you got to understand, do you know
what's so weird, though? Yeah. They go
for Mark. Yeah. People are here. Yeah.
Because of like because of that girl
they were saying. Yeah. But they don't.
They should go for lunch.
No, they go for Mark because Mark does
not [ __ ] help himself. Let's be
honest about the situation. But Mark is
not scared of trolls like you, Peter. >> Really?
>> No, he ain't.
Mark Mark doesn't go on about Shan Sean
long legs for 50 hours a week like you. Mark
>> Yeah. But what I'm saying is what I'm
saying is people should go for [ __ ]
nons legs like they do Mark. You know,
>> but we've had this conversation many
times. The reason why they don't go for
nonsle because it gets to you and
everyone doesn't like you.
>> Yeah, I know. L don't like launch legs.
He sometimes goes forever.
>> Nobody likes [ __ ] long nons apart
from the American Nazi community, right?
But my point is what I'm saying is
right. Well, Nazis will always defend
Nazis. Let's be honest about the situation, right?
>> Yeah. But so I can't defend you cuz you
are a bit of a bacon. The [ __ ] you said on here.
>> I'm a bit of a what?
>> Well, you are a bacon, bro. You said some horrible
>> a bacon. A bacon.
>> Well, you are do. Let's go down memory
lane. I'm not going to repeat cuz it's disgusting.
>> All right, Timmy. You know there's I I
don't speak to one of my sisters. Is it?
>> Yeah. Go on. Where are we going from here?
>> So, say say like we we was related.
Yeah. and you and you heard some of the
stuff that I said on YouTube. You'd
still talk to me in it if we was brothers.
>> Dude, the only reason why I'm tolerating
you because you got autism and you're in
the dark and you're full of [ __ ] and you
ain't deny you are autistic.
>> Yeah, I'm very autistic.
>> So, at last you admit it [ __ ] finally.
>> I'm I've got anxiety, too.
>> So, why are you why are you trying to
impress some people on screen and just,
you know, accept who you are, dude? I
only come on YouTube to impress you.
>> You don't need to impress me, Freddy.
Look after your [ __ ] self.
>> All Timmy, do you remember when you used
to played the um Bob Te's when they were
100 pound spin when you was with with Charlie?
>> I can't forget about it, mate. It's been
that long I've been playing them, but
what's your point?
>> Yeah, but it was funny, wasn't it? No,
>> when when I come to Birm I'm going to
come to Birmingham to me. We're going to
meet and we're going to we're going to
find some women to get pregnant. We uh to me
>> what the [ __ ] you on about? Find someone
to get pregnant. What this in a clear
sentence, man. I'm drunk, but what what
the [ __ ] are you on about?
>> I'm going to come to Birmingham and we
can go and get some women and hopefully
we can get them pregnant and have some
have a baby.
>> Don't do that. No wonder you're a [ __ ] virgin.
>> You don't What do you mean you don't do that?
>> Say you want to pregnant. Are you that
stupid or what?
>> It's lovely to me.
>> No wonder you're a [ __ ] virgin if
you're going to say [ __ ] like that.
>> Well, you don't want a baby.
>> No, I [ __ ] don't.
>> Why not?
>> Because it's responsibility. I could deal without
>> Yeah, but then maybe the baby would stop
you stop you gambling as much to me.
Yeah, you definitely are autistic.
>> No, it's true though, isn't it? Isn't it
Grievousy? Yeah, if Timmy had a baby, it
might keep him off the [ __ ] Tes.
>> Well, I'm going to go in a minute, dude.
Cuz I'm going to play some tunes. But
listen to me. Well, the reason why they
don't troll Sha cuz they hate you more than Sean.
>> Oh, okay.
>> But if you went on the community, Long
Legs would be the target. If I left for
like six Triple H Yeah. No, listen.
Triple H said to me, "If I left YouTube
for six months, then they'd start going
for him." Is that true?
>> Well, possibly. Well, let's be honest
about the situation, right? Let's be
honest about there's two reasons why
they don't go for long legs. One,
because he doesn't give a [ __ ] He just
laughs it off. And two, he doesn't get
rattled like you.
>> So, if I left for six months, would they
start going for him? Yeah.
>> Yeah. But he wouldn't give a [ __ ] He
just [ __ ] laugh like me, Pete. He
doesn't get rattled over a fiberactive
cable like you sunshine.
>> But no, he used No, he Yes, he did.
Yeah, he did used to get triggered,
Timmy. Do you remember my mom was legal?
He used to shout and that
>> your mom said they're only trying to get
a reaction out of you and you should
start listening to your mom, Peter.
>> I think Timmy, we need to quit gambling
and become a parent.
>> No, I think you need to quit gambling
and sort your [ __ ] head out before
you become a parent, lad.
>> No, Timmy, we need to become a parent. Bro,
>> come on. Seriously, Jimmy, it's time to
grow up now.
>> I was [ __ ] autistic to [ __ ] but you're worse.
>> Why are you calling me names?
>> I didn't call you among I was referring
to Jamie. I'm saying you are worse, man.
Because you need to learn real manhood.
>> Why? Cuz I want to have a baby.
>> No, it's more. Okay, you live with your
mom. You're 28. You're scared of a
[ __ ] bunny called Bron. How you going
to look after a baby?
>> Scared of a what? You're scared of a
bummy called Prime. Who's
>> What's that got to do with me having a baby?
>> How do you look after a baby? You run
from a [ __ ] bummy?
>> So what are you saying? Brumies are soft then.
>> No, they [ __ ] own you. London, let's
put it that way.
>> No, I came to Birmingham and I owned you,
>> bro. All you do is m out your heart and
then say you got autism so you don't get
nick like pasta boy.
>> You learned.
>> No, that's what you done, Timmy.
Timmy, that's what you done when Ben
caught you. He said that you was using
your autism. You're projecting.
>> But don't [ __ ] use an excuse to go
around and say, "Oh, I'm going to Nick
Sweets. Oh, I'm going to be Be honest."
Yeah. Be honest to me. Yeah.
>> Don't use Be honest. Be honest though, Timmy.
>> That Ben Gregory would have had you in it.
>> What's that?
>> Ben Gregory would have had you in it.
>> No, the only one who had me was Welsh.
It was the only one. What happened to
that Ben Gregory? Drunk or not? Drunk.
To be fair, he had it in. And
>> what happened to that Ben Gregory?
>> Okay. It was a bit [ __ ] wise. Welsh
could have him when I wasn't so pissed.
He could have
>> No, but Timmy, Timmy, what happened to
Ben Gregory? Where was he?
>> At least the Got Balls.
>> Timmy, what happened to that Ben
Gregory? Did he leave?
>> I don't [ __ ] know, Peter.
>> And that Liam Sutton used to be on your
case, didn't he?
>> Bro, they're all [ __ ] The only geese
who had it in him was Welsh.
>> Yeah, but they left though, is it? A lot
of people left.
>> He got me when I was drugged. That was a
bit cowardly. At least he still had some
sort of minerals. I like the
>> I could put the baby in a stitch baby
grow. Greavves. I could put the baby in
a stitch baby girl. What do you think to that, Greavvesy?
>> Yeah, Mike's going jail, isn't he?
>> I generally think you need serious help, dude.
>> No, but seriously, no, no, no. But
seriously, to me, yeah, he's actually
going to jail on it, Mike.
>> What the [ __ ] are you on about, dude?
>> Money. Mike,
>> what about money? Mike,
>> he's going to be put he's going to he's
going to be get sent down.
>> What? What the heck are you on about?
Can you explain in English? Not Pakistani.
>> Money. Mike is going to get sent down, isn't he?
>> No, he's not. Cuz he hasn't done nothing
wrong and he's free as a bird.
>> There's your question.
>> A lot of people on YouTube say that he's
got a case against him.
>> Ask him direct yourself. He's got
nothing to do with me.
>> Are you sure?
>> Yeah. Yes, Peter. Yes.
>> Well, a lot of people saying that he's
he's he's raped someone.
If somebody told you to overdose
yourself, would you do it? Yes or no? >> No.
>> Exactly. So, take one out the other, you pratt.
>> I agree with you. What did you think of
Sig when I was talking about babies with
Sig? Was that cute?
Why are you so obsessed with this grimsy?
>> Boot is my little friend.
>> No, he's not. He's [ __ ] rolling you
up and he's doing a great job to be honest.
>> What do you think of me talking about
babies with Sig? Was that cute?
>> Nobody's friends on here.
>> You know, you know if you want to get in
a Hey Timmy, you know the best way to
get into a woman's knickers is start
talking about how you want to have like
a baby with them and stuff.
No, Peter, because you were a virgin.
That is not the answer.
>> What the [ __ ] Yeah, but no. What? [ __ ]
man. Full of [ __ ] constant [ __ ]
>> So, Grevy, what? Wait, what? Grievy,
what you're trying to say is I troll
some of these women. I don't troll
>> I'm being serious and stuff when I talk to them.
>> You need some [ __ ] help with your
pulling skills. You do some
>> I don't troll them, do I, Grezy? Never.
I never have. Never. I'll be wasting my
time, be wasting their time.
Timmy, do you know who Crush Bandicut is?
>> What are you [ __ ] on about?
>> Crash Bandicut, do you know who he is?
>> No, Peter. Cuz I live in the real world
with your friends, not [ __ ] You
[ __ ] fiberactic cable. I'm a troll.
>> Look, who's this? That's Crash Bandicut,
>> dude. I wouldn't have a clue cuz I'm not [ __ ] six.
>> Yep. His name is Crash. It's a lovely little chap.
>> I sleep next to him. I sleep next to him every day. >> [ __ ]
>> I sleep next to him every day. He's a
lovely little fellow.
>> Imagination of a six-year-old. >> Sorry.
>> 28. The imagination of a six-year-old.
>> Why is Money Mike raping people? That's
kind of sick.
>> Yes, he hasn't. M you say that to his
face, P. You won't be like [ __ ] tired
of putting the mattress. He will put you
in hospital better.
>> But you would turn,
>> mate. He's about He's about 5 foot. He's
>> When he likes toughened up, I've taught
him to toughen up over this [ __ ] Yeah.
But if you saw him and said that, Matt,
you know the real reality, mate. You
would not be standing.
>> Nah. The only one that can beat me up is Tiger.
>> You run away from your own reflection.
You are how why did he do it anyways,
dick? What? Why did he do it? Why did he
actually do it though?
>> You ain't do anything. Why are you a
[ __ ] virgin and no woman wants you to
answer that question?
>> Yeah, I'm a virgin to me cuz uh I'm a
virgin because I don't know how to have sex.
>> You're a virgin. It's not It's not
[ __ ] hard to work it out.
>> Yeah, but you said Monty and Nons is a virgin.
If I say N leg is a virgin, you just
agree you're a virgin. Yeah.
>> Yeah. But yeah,
>> the end of the [ __ ] world if you're a
virgin for crying out loud.
>> And and Monty man's a virgin as well.
>> If I say everyone's a virgin, will you
agree you're a virgin? Yeah.
>> No, I'm asking you. You don't have to
agree with anything. All right.
>> I'm going to charge up my phone. I'll be back.
All right then.
Yeah, I get sexually frustrated, but
[ __ ] I don't go around doing that,
dick. Well, I don't get sexy frustrated anymore, but
you just [ __ ] use an escort.
Is that still true about Mike Dusty Greavvesy?
Is that true?
Is it true or are you pulling my leg?
I've been hearing that story a lot.
So, how comes he's been bailed out then? That's sick. very sick.
Why are these sisters not disowned him? now?
Well, his sister still talks to him. Yeah.
It's weird, isn't it, bro? It's [ __ ] weird.
How's the nuggets, Grezy?
So what? I'd get money for the baby and
I'd gamble it greasy. No.
I like I like Christian and Izzy Greavesy.
I think we'd make a good couple.
We'd make a good couple. We
finally ready to settle down. Greavvesy,
I'm finally ready to settle down. What's
your opinion on that, Greavvesy?
I'm finally ready to settle down. Grezy.
Nope. I am.
I finally found someone.
I I can I I can make you laugh with this video. Greavvesy,
look. Watch this video. Graves there.
That guy's a weirdo, bro. That guy's a [ __ ] weirdo.
That made me laugh. That video
that made me laugh. That's funny. Crazy.
Did you watch it? Greavvesy,
do you know Christian Izzy's got some
big boobies as well?
What do you think of that, Grezy?
He's got some big boobies.
That's good, isn't it?
There'll be some more milk for the baby. UK asylum.
I haven't showed her my Lego yet.
I actually didn't bring it up.
Oh gosh. Well, I will do at some point.
Bring the Lego up.
Yeah. More nutrients for me and the baby.
How cute is that?
You called me a troll, didn't you? UK asylum.
You call me a troll, don't you?
I'm not a troll. I'm ready to settle
down and have kids.
Yep. I'm ready to settle down.
How cute is that UK asylum? Alive.
Oh, what's going on here?
All right, I think it's past my bedtime. Grievy,
you chewing on your little nuggets.
So, is is Ali Law on the same website
that my house got broken into, Grievy,
or is it a different website?
That's kind of weird.
So, how comes he's not dead yet?
Yeah, but how comes he's how comes he's
not dead then?
You're waiting patiently, aren't you?
Yeah. Do you remember what he said? Do
Do you remember what that Do you
remember what he said that? Why he said
that? Triple 8 said that Grezy
I said are you going to go for a couple
of drinks with Anon Deck
when you're next to Newcastle in it. And
he says be realistic.
I said I am. You and Neck you get on a
session in it. That's what And he's like be realistic.
Why is that not realistic?
Ant and deck.
Do you even know who they are? Grievy.
You don't know who they are, do you?
You know they are grievy.
Right. I'm going to bed now anyways.
I'm going to watch Ed Matthews and I'm
going to go to bed.
In a bizzle. In the Bizzle.