Yeah, I'm not going to be live long.
Just wanting to see if it's just the
same people straight on YouTube
[sighs and gasps] first thing in the
morning or did they get a life
or are they at work? Yeah, just checking
cuz obviously people should be at work,
shouldn't they? [gasps]
They're not on my live stream. So, I'm
just going to check quickly
to see see where people watching so far,
which is good. [snorts]
I'm going to keep it that way. Just keep
That's good. It should be like that for the whole
20 minutes or so I'm on to be fair. Oh,
one person's on YouTube and they should
be at work.
There we go. One person. Why are you not
at work, Mr. One person watching?
Straight on to YouTube.
Straight onto YouTube.
Come to think of it, yeah, Monty man is
he was a copycat with the Christmas
thing as well.
Oh, he's just one big copycat, isn't he?
Two people that's not at work that
should be at work. That's two people on
YouTube at almost half 9 in the morning
when they should be at work. That's
almost That's four people now on YouTube.
That's four people on YouTube.
I won't be long. Won't be on here long.
I'm just checking see if it's the same
people or did they get a life in 2026.
Four people straight on YouTube. [ __ ]
me. Absolutely [ __ ] me. Six people.
Six people on YouTube.
Why aren't you at work? Why aren't you
people at work?
Why the [ __ ] aren't you peeps at work?
Shouldn't you little idiots be at work? [snorts] Yeah.
Next thing will be playing roulette.
Seven people on YouTube.
Yeah, seven people should be at work
today, but they're not.
Why are these people [ __ ] working?
Yeah, six people watching that should be at work.
It's mad how the people in this
community tell other people to get a
job, get a life when they're sat on YouTube 24/7.
Mad, isn't it? It's a madness. It's a [sighs]
you know, [clears throat] sat on YouTube
from the time they wake up to the time
that they go to bed.
Sad sad individuals, sad people.
Give him a Oh [ __ ] Virgin boy.
These people just come straight onto
YouTube when they wake up. [snorts]
Sad bastards on this community.
Proper proper sad bastards. They wake
up. Yeah. This what they do. Yeah.
They're such sad bastards. They wake up.
Yeah. And then they come on YouTube.
Literally come on YouTube with their
screen recorder and then they keep
refreshing the page. What gay bastards.
But I don't think people on YouTube have
the mental capacity to understand how
weird it is. If you explain how weird it
is, they don't where they're so [ __ ]
dumb. They're so disabled they don't
even realize like they sit online with a
screen recorder refreshing YouTube
refreshingly YouTube paid for content.
They got no life. They got no jobs.
Don't listen to anything that these
people claim that they've got. Cuz if
they really do have any of these things,
tell them to show it. Tell them to show
their job. Tell them to show their
money. They can't. They ain't got nothing.
It's not speculating to accumulate. It's
facts. It is absolute facts.
That's it, bro.
[ __ ] screen recorder cuz they got no
life stalking men cuz they're gay bastards.
You couldn't pay me £3 million to do it.
So, there you go.
But you're you're trying to explain
stuff to disabled people, so
they're not going to understand obviously. Yeah,
it's true. It
Yeah, it's true. That is definitely
Oh, that's cute.
That That baby is a Marvel fan.
That's cute, man. I don't think I can
share it to someone. No.
A lot of people blocked, man. Nine
people watching. No one's coming.
nine people that should be at work,
should be out making a life for
themselves, but they want YouTube.
Strange, isn't it? Strange.
They tell [snorts] other people to get a
job, but these people have never had a
job. They never They've never had a job,
but they tell other people to get a job.
I think they need to give themsel advice
before trying to give anyone else
advice. They need to give themselves >> Yeah,
[clears throat] that Marvel thing is
[ __ ] cute, man.
So thingy it even got the Spider-Man coat.
That is even got the Spider-Man coat.
That is so cute, man.
No, that is cute, bro.
>> [clears throat]
>> woken up in a foul mood.
A foul foul foul foul mood. A foul mood.
That always seems to happen. You calm
down during the night and then you just
wake up in a bad mood again.
>> [clears throat] [snorts]
>> That's what happens. And you just wake
up in a bad mood again. [clears throat] Yeah. [snorts]
It's supposed to be a form of entertainment.
If you don't react the way if you don't
react the way you if you if you don't
react the way people want you to react,
you've got a problem.
Another thing you can't discuss on
Reddit. Another thing you can't discuss on anything
cuz if you don't react the way they want
you to react,
[snorts] they start assuming things. You
see, they think everyone should react
the same. [snorts]
Woke up in a foul, dirty, vile mood. [snorts] Yeah.
Form of entertainment. My ass. [snorts]
Is this Does this guy still does do
gambling videos? Yeah. 14 hours. [sighs]
I've actually woke up feeling worse than
I did when I done it yesterday
to be honest with you. Yeah. I don't
give a [ __ ] if it's only £100. I don't
give a [ __ ] if I had to have a million
pound. It ain't the [ __ ] point.
Simple. It ain't the [ __ ] point at all.
Doesn't matter whether it's 10 p, £5,500. [snorts]
You don't gamble to lose. You You're
gambling to win. And you're certainly
not trying to lose. You don't want to
lose. Do you get me?
And man said, "Same old then." Pretty
much same old.
Left side of zero six. All them
horrible, nasty, dirty numbers.
Them old dodgy men numbers. We won't get
into that. Yeah, them old dodgy men
numbers. It likes to keep branching and seeking out
cuz it loves the loser. It loves the
loser numbers. M yeah. Yeah.
I don't think I'll be doing anything today. [snorts]
Yeah, I definitely won't be doing anything today. Yeah. [ __ ] [snorts]
The [ __ ] is this group been added to? Man, [snorts] [sighs]
that's kind of scary.
Sucks, bro. Sucks. Shut up. >> [snorts]
>> That's funny as [ __ ]
Put all on. That's funny. Yeah. Yep. >> [snorts]
>> Why does so many people right
have cheating exes? is I find that to be very strange.
They seem to have these cheating exes,
but you never hear about people going
with cheating women.
Find that to be very strange. You know,
they must be picking these people that
cheat and then cry when they cheat. >> [snorts]
>> So, why do we never Why do you never
hear about people getting with women that cheat?
That's a bit strange, isn't it?
I find it so strange
why they have so many
so many people they they cheat and stuff.
Don't hear about people's girlfriends cheating ever. Strange, huh?
Strange that, lad. Strange that.
I don't know, man. Ask yourselves. These
are the ones that are on YouTube 24/7. I
don't know, bro. Ask yourself that question. >> [snorts] >> Hm.
What is this weird chat?
This [ __ ] weird chat they've added me into. [snorts]
You know how so many of them end up
cheating? That's to that's very strange
to be honest. Yeah.