Timmy's a proper [ __ ] in he man. So he
mentions people's name starts all that
[ __ ] just to run away again.
You couldn't make it up could you?
Just to run away again.
[ __ ] stupid [ __ ]
Stupid [ __ ] [ __ ] in here.
Let's see if people on YouTube today or
are they at work? Little tester.
Are they at work or are they on YouTube?
Hope it stays to zero.
I hope it stays to zero.
Almost one minute and it's still zero,
which is good.
Oh, one person. Yeah.
It's the same old with this Timmy
Eldridge, isn't it?
It's the same old with this Timmy Eldridge.
Draws people out. People tried to meet
him and then he runs away. Another thing
his boyfriend does, his skint boyfriend
in a bedsit who has got not a penny to
his name, let alone a couple of quid.
Same [ __ ] with these little retards on
here. This is why people don't come on here anymore.
This is exactly why people don't come on
here anymore. Well, I don't. I don't
know about why other people don't.
That's the reason why I don't. Is this
the same [ __ ]
Same [ __ ] with these little low lives. Yeah.
Even when you beat them, they pretend
they've won. That's what they do on
here. That's a big thing with these
[ __ ] retards on here, bro. Yeah.
I'm coming here. I'm coming there. No,
no, no, no, no. He's not meeting me. He
said he was going to come to London.
He's not. Now, this is what he does. He
draws people out. He mentions people and
then he and then he runs away. He always does this
bit like he's skid boyfriend. Oh, just
Timmy mentioning my name yesterday and I
had enough of it. Keep mentioning my
name time and time again. self projects
[ __ ] time and time and time and time again.
And your boyfriend nonslegs don't have a
couple of quid cuz if you had a couple
of quid you would have kept letting me
show thousands and thousands the way I
did for so long. You would have been on
it like a bottlefly on [ __ ] on a
summer's day beating me out the money
gave me if you had it which you couldn't
have done it and he couldn't have done
it cuz you ain't got it. So, in the
future, when you're making your little
stupid videos, refrain from using my
name because you're not going to meet anyone.
Come to London today. What's the excuse?
You're only what, an hour and 20 minutes
away on a train, on a fast train. You
got all this money. You say that you're
comfortable. Come on, let's go. What are
you waiting for?
Bring your mate from Birmingham as well,
who I assume is [ __ ] that stupid albino Mike.
What? What you waiting for, man? Come on.
You know what I'm saying?
Yeah. I messaged his family yesterday. I
said, "Yeah, and I'll do and I'll do it
again. I'll [ __ ] do it again, bro,
until this guy learns." Simple.
Yeah. [ __ ] [ __ ]
I just ate two cinnamon swirls.
Two cinnamon swirls.
I never said I was leaving.
It doesn't matter what I said, but I
messaged I messaged these message his
family. You shouldn't be taking the piss
out of people, lad.
You shouldn't be taking the piss out of people, bro.
people. You can't even take a day off of
YouTube. I wouldn't be taking the piss
out of people if I was you.
Yeah, I wouldn't be trying to take the
piss out of people if I was you, lad.
You can't even take a day off of
YouTube. That is chronicle scenes.
That is chronicle chronicle scenes, bro.
I wouldn't be taking the piss out of anyone.
Yeah. Does he? [ __ ] I told him to come
to London today, bro.
What makes me laugh is he still calls
other people out for fights, but every
fight Yeah. that he's been in, he's
lost. He's lost every fight.
Every fight he's been in, he's actually lost.
That's the funny thing.
Well, I I I I [ __ ] will. If he keeps
mentioning my name, then I will.
Obviously, you can mention my name today
and meet me. Obviously, that's that's
I'm not saying that, but I'm saying
don't make your little videos trying to
draw me out in your drama,
cuz that's what he's doing. He's trying
to draw me out
if that makes sense.
So that's it. Yeah, man.
And it's the way he's mentioning me as
well. It's annoying, bro. You know,
and your boyfriend on legs don't have no money either.
He couldn't answer me as well. If you if
you both have got all this money, right,
and people are skin, how comes you've
been beat at the money game multiple
times? He can't answer me. He can't
answer me. How comes last, I think it
was. Yeah. How comes last February when
I showed you £1,300, you ran away?
You ran away with nothing to show.
Timmy, that's Timmy, by the way. It was
actually shown to Timmy. Where was your
Where was your two grand? Where was your £2,600?
And then you're asking people to show
you 20 pound again. It's not called an
autistic community for nothing.
It's not called an autistic disabled
community for nothing.
And he's the worst. He's he's the biggest one. Oh [ __ ]
He's live now.
No, he's not live now.
And he can join my panel.
He can join my panel. I'm not joining
his panel. He can join my panel. Why is
it not letting me? Well, I'm not joining
his panel. He can join my panel. I'm not
leaving my live stream. [ __ ] that. One second.
Yeah, that's Monty, man. Yeah.
Why Why is it not letting me put a link
up for [ __ ] sake? Why
happens sometimes? I tried to put links
up, it doesn't let me.
Yeah, Mony's live. Yeah. Not Timmy.
I can never get a bird like that. Gee, that's nice.
Yeah, that's good. Good friend. Tell him
does he want a medal? That doesn't That
[ __ ] doesn't annoy me. It's what Timmy
does that annoys me. Greavvesy. Yeah,
he'll have attention on him. Yeah,
people will be going for him. Then he
starts bringing me up in these videos
when I'm not even talking to the [ __ ]
and I haven't even gone live. So, I was
like, "Okay, I'll message your family."
Simple as that. Then, if that's the only
way you're going to stop, I'll message
your family. Simple as that. I think
it's quite a clever idea to be fair. Yeah.
Yeah, I know. I see it, bro. I see it.
I know. What the [ __ ] bro? Where's he
getting this information from? That's
what I'm saying. It's projection. That's
what he That's what it is with him UK
signing. He doesn't have 20 pound to his
name. Do you understand? It's self
projection with these people always and forever.
Always. And even when you show them
money, bro, they still talk [ __ ] Just
like when you show that you've had sex,
they still talk [ __ ] They're a waste of everyone's time.
Well, we're supposed to be meeting
today. Yeah. Bro, where does he get this
information from? I haven't been skinned
for about 6 years.
Makes up so much stuff. He thinks
everyone's got the same life as him. is
disabled as [ __ ]
He says, "Oh, oh, he thinks what I think
he means is, yeah, because I lost 20,
right, and I was annoyed." Yes. Yes.
Because it's not about the money a
million times. I've explained the same
thing million times. It's not about the
money, you [ __ ]
It's not about the money.
See, that's what I'm saying. And that's
how you know it's an autistic community
because you repeat the same [ __ ] over
and over and over again trying to
[ __ ] draw people the [ __ ] out, bro.
[ __ ] off, man. Yeah,
I agree with you. You know what made me
laugh yesterday? Monty commented on
Timmy's channel. How does he know
Timmy's channel? Greasy.
I don't know why that just made me
laugh. How does he know um Timmyy's channel?
I don't know why. That made me laugh.
I mean, that's it's a I mean, what do
you want me to do with that? You sent me
a question mark. I mean, what what bit
didn't you get? I find it funny. I mean,
I don't know what what what bit don't you understand?
I find it funny that he went on Timmy's
channel and commented because Timmy
can't spell. Timmy can't uh sorry, Monty
can't spell. How did he find his
channel? It's It's not hard to understand, lad.
So, with that question mark, stick up your ass.
Stick it up your backside.
Stick where the sun don't shine, matey.
Everyone knows. Yeah, but no, it's just
[ __ ] stupid. Timmy was pissing me off yesterday, bro.
He's so throw up nonslegs's [ __ ] ass
as well. Oh, was he watching these videos? Anyone?
Oh, he's smart. That's why he's got
money. He doesn't have money. Just like
you don't have money,
you know. And that's what I mean by you
never win with these people, bro. So, it's pointless.
You never win with these people. So, you
know, you want to talk [ __ ] on a video,
someone's called you out. Where are you?
Nons doesn't have any money. I don't
know why you're going on about like
you're going to rob people and stuff and
all of this [ __ ]
You just don't never win with these
people. This is why I didn't go live
yesterday, bro. I didn't I I technically
didn't even go live yesterday
because you can never ever ever ever win
with these people. Never ever ever win
Show more money than them, they pretend
they beat you. showed you've had sex,
they still call you a [ __ ] virgin.
Call them out a million times, they
don't meet you. You can't You can't win
with these spastics.
You really really cannot win with these
spastics. Show you're better looking
than them, they still call you ugly. You
can't win with them, bro. You [ __ ] literally can't.
So, is he coming? Is he coming to meet
me today or what?
soon to be Rit the Bear Grezy.
And the reason I said he can bring
London Taylor with him as well because
we know that like he's going to try and
get himself involved.
We know that he's going to try and get himself involved.
So, you might as well just say it there.
Say it say on that video if you think
about it, bro. Just to show I'm not
[ __ ] scared. I'm no [ __ ] [ __ ]
Bring who you want when you want. I don't care.
I don't give a [ __ ] bro.
You know what I mean? Yeah.
UK silent United work today, lad. Day off.
Day off work.
It must be your little day off today, isn't it? Nice.
What's day today? Monday, is it? Yeah,
you must have a day off Monday or something.
Must be your little day off.
Yeah, I had peppes. I had peppers
yesterday. A whole chicken and chips.
I I I mean, I do worry about my own
money. I've got plent I've got I've got
enough money. I I I don't I do worry
about my own money. I'm not the one on
YouTube calling people [ __ ] skint lad.
So I I I don't need to worry about my
own money, bro. I've got I've got my own
money. I'm not the one telling people
they've only got 20 pound like Timmy
when he doesn't know what people have.
When he doesn't know what people have
and he says, "Oh, you showed that money.
You showed that money to me ages ago.
Doesn't matter if it was shown ages ago.
Why didn't you show money ages ago when
I showed you money? It's the same
argument. It's the same autist. That's
why we call it an autistic community. It's autistic
[ __ ] talking about how your boyfriend
nonslegs has got money and how you've
got money. Bro, how many times have you
been showing money and both of you have
run away? Should we should we count?
Should we literally literally literally
literally count? It doesn't matter if it
was ages ago, you know? It's like
someone It's like someone taking an L
ages ago. It still It still counts. If
someone If someone took an L ages ago,
right? Say someone took an L a year and
a half ago. Does that mean that they've
not took an L because it was because it
was because it was a year and a half ago, you know?
Simple, bro. So, the prime thing doesn't
count then. All of these things that's
happened to me in the past, if it's if
it's ages ago, then it doesn't count,
does it? Yeah, exactly. That's what I
thought. Shut the [ __ ] up, bro. Jimmy
got shown £1,300 in in a pub, bro. When
I lived at the old house, £1,300
he got shown and he ran away and he's
coming back asking people to show him
£20. What the [ __ ]
And then you show them money, then they
ask you to show money again, and then it
goes round in circles again. And then
your your brain fries again. And that's
why we call it the autistic community.
It's not called autistic for no reason.
You know what I'm saying?
What has Timmy and Nodle's done in their
life? What life experiences have they
got? They're not traveled. They haven't
been to nice restaurants. They don't
have nice clothes. They don't have no
assets. All these two that's got all of
this money. What life experience have they had?
I can tell you all the things that I've done.
No, I just don't like him talking about
me. No, no, no, no, no. It's not the
comments that he made. I just don't like
him talking about me trying to draw me
out. No, no, no, no, no. It's not even
the comments because it's self-
projecting. It's it's what he's doing
trying to draw me out because the
attention's on him.
So, you tell me what assets and life
experiences both of you have got cuz I
can tell you the things that I've done.
And I know you don't like designer
clothes because you call it
materialistic. Okay. Well, I can tell
you all the places I've been. I can tell
you all the hotels I've stayed at. I can
tell you all of the all the restaurants
I've been to. Can you and non-legs do
the same? Mr. Couple of quid. Mr. Got
this cup of quid. Could you do the same
thing or could you not? We could
exclude. We could ex we could exclude we
could exclude we could exclude the um we
could exclude the designer clothes.
Can can you name like stuff you've
actually done? You can't cuz you ain't
got it. You ain't got no money. You
ain't got one quid, let alone a couple
the quid. It's the truth. You know what
I'm saying? It's the truth.
Stop sucking your boyfriend Nons's dick.
I've shown more money than [ __ ] both
of you multiple [ __ ] times. Stop
sucking your boyfriend's dick.
Yeah. Okay. So, list You should be able
to list life experience that you've got.
You should literally be able to list
experiences you've got. You've got all
this money, this couple of quid. Let's
hear all of these experiences that you've had.
Like I said, I can tell you the ones
that I've got.
I can tell you the ones that I've got.
No, I'll react and I'll message his
family just like I did. No, no, no. I
will react and I'll message his family
because it's annoying.
PJ, PJ, PJ, Rose, Rose, Rose, Rose,
Rose. Every time I get I get mentioned
in one of your videos now. Rose is going
to get contacted. It's as simple as
that. Rose, Rose, Rose, Rose, Rose,
Rose, Rose, Rose, Rose.
Lovely Rose. How about that one? Rose
Eldridge. Simple as that.
And then he said he's gonna message my
mom. Bro, you can message my mom. I
don't even speak to my sister. And And
I'll say, "Yeah, I I've told this guy
multiple times to stop dragging me in
his [ __ ] on YouTube, and he keeps doing it." So yeah.
So yeah, you should be able to list
experiences that you've got, Mr. Cut the
Quidd. I can tell you the restaurants
I've been, the hotels I've stayed at, um
the clothes I I've had and have the
clothes I still have that look brand
new. Someone that's got a couple of
quids should be able to should be able
to answer this.
You [ __ ] [ __ ]
You [ __ ] little [ __ ]
Stupid [ __ ] [ __ ]
Yeah, it does. Yeah, it does make a man.
Yeah. Yeah, it does. It does make a man.
Yeah. So, you you say you got all this
money, but you got no life experience.
Yeah, it does make a man. Clothing does
make a man. Yeah. Yeah, it does.
He lies so much, bro. Oh, I get my I'm
comfortable. I'm comfortable. You're not
comfortable at all.
He talks so much [ __ ]
Him and his boyfriend Nons is absolutely
skint. He mentioned two skint people in
one video. Skint as [ __ ] Like I said, I
go back to my point. If any of these
people had money, they would have beat
me at the money game when I was showing
money multiple times. You've got no
excuse. You can't say that, oh, it was
ages ago and you've literally got no
excuse. It could be 10 years ago and it
would still and it would still count.
This is him trying to get out of it.
This is their way of trying to get out
of it when they take L's. You see, this
is what they do when they take L's. This
is their way of getting out of it.
And I never said it's just them as well.
It's multiple people. It's not just
them. It's Joe F. It's LJ. It's loads
and loads and loads and loads and loads of people.
There's loads of people that that's
that's been beaten at the money game.
They run away every time you show them money.
They've done it a lot of times as well.
A lot of times no one has ever beaten me
when I've show money. That is a fact,
bro. That is a [ __ ] fact.
And do you know how you know that? You
know how you know that L is skinn? Think
about it, bro. He showed his win. He
showed his win, bro. Like when he won
money, he showed money. That I said to
my mom straight away, that's how you
know the guy's skin 99 times percent of
the time. 99% out of 100 because nine
times out of 10 because if if you if you
want money, I don't know about anyone
else, but I don't show money whether I
have it, whether I don't have it,
whether I've won it. I don't show money,
bro. I what I do on here is I do not
show people money. You think I I can go
You think I can't go to the bank, pull
out money, and show it? Of course I can.
But I'm not going to do it because I
know what happens on here. I know what
these little retards do.
He's another one. He's another one. The
fact the fact that he was showing 800
cuz he's showing it because if he
actually had money, he he just wouldn't
bother showing it.
I never show money, bro. Never ever ever ever.
Nope. No, I didn't. And I already
explained that as well. You're asking me
things I've already explained.
Yeah. And it wasn't £80. And And I've
already explained this, so get your
facts right. I've already explained
this. So you're And then you're showing
800. And you could just tell the guy's
got no money. The way he was going on
about £700, how he's so quick to show
800, bro. You could just tell that the
guy has got no money,
you know? At least when I've show money
before, it's been a [ __ ] big amount.
Yeah. Go away. self-reflector talking
about yourself. See you later, lad.
See you later. So yeah,
that rings a bell that name.
draw people out like Timmy and then they run away.
What's the point? You know,
stop saying your [ __ ] boyfriend's got
[ __ ] money. Your boyfriend ain't got
no [ __ ] money. If your boyfriend had
money, you would have beaten me long
time ago, bro.
As soon as you got shown three grand,
you would have shown [ __ ] six. As soon
as you got 5.7, you would have shown 10.
Why was no one able to do it? Don't say
it was ages ago because the same thing
would happen now if someone showed the
same amount of money.
The same the same thing would happen again. You know,
you know what I mean?
It's not called an autistic community for nothing.
Yeah, you might have won the money game
about two and a half years later, but
you're missing a point. I showed money
for a period of about 18 months every
day, and no one showed me nothing. So, I
mean, my my that's the end. That's the
end. It doesn't matter if it was if if
it was ages ago, if it was yesterday, if
it was today. L's don't work like that.
You took an L. You took an L. It's as
simple as that. It doesn't matter how
long ago it was.
It's like the prime thing. That doesn't
matter how long ago that was, it still
gets brought up. It's the same thing
when you've been showing money and
you've all ran away. Every single
[ __ ] one of you. It wasn't just
Timmy. It wasn't just nonslegs. So why
are we still talking about showing 10
pound and showing 20 pound?
Why are you still asking people to show
you money when you've been shown
a [ __ ] mad amount mads amounts of
money and you've all run away? So why
are you still asking people to show you
money so you can run away again just
like you done last February?
Are you trying to kill the community completely?
Pointless, bro. Pointless.
See, look at Timmy. I'm going to meet
him. There's no trains.
It doesn't matter if I won the money or
mate. Listen, I've got plenty of money.
You do not know how much money I've got.
I've got plenty of money. The only
reason you're calling me skin is cuz
you're skint yourselves. That's why you
so know so much about people being skint
because you're talking you're basing
your own life because you are the skint
ones on YouTube every day. That's why
when you say stuff like skint and stuff,
it doesn't bother me because you're just
talking about your skinelves sat on
YouTube 24/7. Just like Timmy talking
about his skin self on that video. You
call people skint, it's because you
skint yourselves on YouTube 24/7. We've
already got the evidence, bro. No one No
one cares. No one cares.
You know, you call people skint, it's
because you're skint yourselves. It's
your own life projecting. Just like what
Timmy does, just like what Nons does.
You all self-reflect your skin lives.
We've all seen the real you when you've
been shown money and you've all ran
away. We've seen the real you. There's
no arguing now. Doesn't matter if I won
it. Doesn't matter if I saved it.
Doesn't matter if I stole it. Doesn't
matter if my mom gave me it. We've seen
the real you when you've been shown
money, right? You can't You can keep
saying that, "Oh, people won some money
ages ago and that money ages ago was
enough to show what you ski people were
running away." Yes. Yes. Ages ago. Yes.
And you still took took me out. Yes.
Yes. And there's And there's a reason
And there's a reason why it was ages ago
as well. You know,
so are you going to can you answer the
question then or not?
Right. So, if I won money ages ago and I
showed it, why did you all run away?
You've got all this money, you've got a
couple of quid, whatever. You say all of
this, don't answer me. Why when you were
showing money did no one come in and beat me?
You can't answer the question. You just
go back to resorting to, oh well, you
won money ages ago. You can't you can't
even answer the question. You literally
can't even you can't even answer the question.
So now what you're saying is So now what
you're saying is wait so now what you're
saying is that if it's ages ago it
doesn't count. So now you're
contradicting yourself because now
you're saying that if things are ages
ago it doesn't count. Okay then the
prime thing doesn't count then. Then the
LT thing doesn't count then. So you know
you're not making no sense. If you're
trying to say that things ages ago don't
count then none of that stuff counts
then does it?
If you being beaten at the money game,
beaten to the eyeballs don't count
because it was ages ago, then none of
this stuff counts then, does it? None of
this stuff counts. Nothing counts then,
does it? Day by day. Okay. Yeah.
None of you people have ever beaten me
out of the money game when I've showed
money, bro. I can say that for a fact.
Not one of you people beat me out of the
money game when I showed money. Not one
of you. Not [ __ ] one of you. Just
like you ain't been seen with women.
None of you. This is what I'm saying. We
can't win with you autistic people.
Autistic people you won't win with.
That's why you're best off just getting
off this shitty community, which is what
I've [ __ ] done. And this [ __ ] [ __ ]
Tibby keeps bringing up my name. I don't
want no part of this autistic biased gay
delinquent [ __ ] [ __ ] community.
You know, gay ass [ __ ] weirdo
community. And you know what? I was
thinking about it yesterday as well
before I went live. It's so weird. This
community is so [ __ ] weird the [ __ ]
that people doing it. They argue with
people, you know. Yes, I do have more
money than him and I've shown more money
than him. Yeah. I've got plenty more
money and I've shown plenty more money
than he has and we're not getting into
this again. So, the [ __ ] that you people
do Yeah. that the fact that you people
can be in your 30s and your 40s. Yeah.
And you talk about people every single
day. And yes, I do have more money than
your than your [ __ ] boyfriend, bro.
Yeah, I do have more money than your
boyfriend. He ain't got no money. People
that live in a council bedsit with no
life experience ain't got money. Their
life their life gives them away, bro.
Their life gives them away. No one in a
council bedsit with no life experience
has money. Let's start talking about
life experience. No, he doesn't have
more money than me. No, he does not have
more money than me. Not even at any more
than me. I have shown [ __ ] six grand.
I had him running, mate. Mate, when I
was showing £6,000, yeah, this [ __ ] was
showing £800, acting like he's won.
That's what I'm saying. You can't win
with them. You can't win with these
disabled ugly people. You can't win with
them. You beat them at the money game,
they pretend that they've won. You show
them women, they call you a virgin. You
can't win with them. Like, bro, you
literally cannot win with them. You
can't win with disabled autistic bias
people. You give yourself a headache.
Not one of these people. Right. Listen,
Smoky B. Maybe you didn't see it. Maybe
you didn't see it. Yeah. Okay. Maybe you
didn't see me show money. I find it a
bit hard to believe that you wouldn't
have show seen me show money for 18
months, but Okay. So, you didn't see see
me show money. Okay. Yeah. Okay, bro.
Yeah. Okay. So, you didn't see me show
money. Okay. Okay. But other people did,
bro. L J did, Jo did, Non Legs did,
Timmy did, loads of people did. No one
came on here and showed money. Not one
person. That's the evidence you need
that they're skint. There's no getting
out of it. You can keep saying that, oh,
oh, it was ages ago. Oh, you won the
money. You can keep deflecting
undercover deflecting, but it doesn't
change the fact that you got shown what
you are, right? Just like if someone was
to start traveling all over the country,
right, and calling you [ __ ] out over
and over and over and over and over
again, and three years has passed. Oh,
it was ages ago. Okay, it was ages ago.
And And does that make it any more Does
that make it any more less relevant? No, it doesn't.
Yeah, and I showed 5.7 grand.
Yes, uncle. And I showed 5.7 grand.
That's not the way the money game works.
The money game does not work where you
get shown five times the amount you show
and then you come back with less
thinking that you've won. It doesn't
work like that. The money game don't
work like that. It don't work like that.
Only you people will think that you've
won by doing that. But in the real
world, it don't work like that. Oh, I do
have money. I've got plenty of money.
You don't know what I have. You don't
know. One second. Doctor. Doctor.
Doctor. One sec. One sec. One sec. One
sec. One sec. You don't know how much
money I have. You don't know me. Just
like you don't know what color boxes I'm
wearing. You don't know how much money I have.
You literally don't know nothing. You
don't know me. You don't know me. I'm
I'm I mean, I'm explaining to you why
I'm not showing you money again. I have
more money than you and and your
boyfriend. I've got more than both of
you. I swear to God, on my mom's life,
I've got more money than these people on
my mom's life. But I'm not playing their
silly little autistic games. Yeah, you
have been shown money multiple times and
you've run away every time. We don't
waste our time on you anymore. Just like
we don't go to meet you people. No, it's
not speculation. Again, doctor, you've
been shown money, right? You have been
speculated. No, it's right. Facts are
not speculation. I'll put the link up
again. You want me to put the link up
again and prove it again? You're telling
people You're telling people right about
speculation? They're right about you.
It's facts about you. You have been
shown money multiple times and you've
run away. There's not speculation about it.
There's no speculation about the facts.
Facts about you people.
Fat ugly little low lives. It's facts.
It's not speculation because it all
speculation prove we're speculating. Then
I've got more money than you. Not I've
got more money than you. I swear to God
in my mom's life, I have got more money
than these people. I don't live in a
council bedsit. I've got designer
clothes, right? I've got life
experience. I'm not sat in a council
bedsit pretending I've got money.
Listen, bro. You're a flexer if you had
cash, bro. No. No, I wouldn't. No, I
would not. No, I would not. You don't
know me. You don't know how much money I have.
If you was if you people weren't fat and
ugly, you'd show yourselves. You'd show
your faces. Same thing to you then. Same
thing to you people then, right? If you
weren't fat and ugly, you'd show your
faces. You'd show your faces. If you
weren't fat and ugly, you'd show your faces.
See you later anyways, lad. See you
later anyways, lad. And this is why I
don't come on here, Grezy. This is
exactly why I do not come on here with
these fat, ugly, autistic, jealous
people. This is why I came away from
this community, bro. All them eight,
nine days. Cuz I don't want nothing to
do with jealous, ugly, disabled people.
Like, every time you come on here, bro,
it hurts your brain. middle-aged, ugly,
biased people. What kind of community is
this, bro? Why do you think people got
away from it?
No, it's not guess work. It's facts
work. Because if you wasn't any of these
things, you'd show your faces, lad.
You'd show your faces. Nothing I say
about you people have ever been guess
work and been wrong. I said what Timmy I
said what Bomb was. He was that.
Everything I'm saying is facts about you people.
It's not guesswork. It's factual work.
It's hard work and it's facts. That's
why you don't show your faces cuz you're
fat and ugly. It's not guessing. It's
facts. End the story, bro.
Every time you've been [ __ ] shown to
be [ __ ] fat and ugly. Yeah. It's not
guesswork. It's facts work, lad. Yeah.
[ __ ] [ __ ] This is why I don't come
on here anymore, bro. This is exactly
why I don't come on here anymore. Yeah.
This is exactly why I don't come on here
anymore. It's so weird the [ __ ] that
they do, bro. Like, even on other
people's channel. [ __ ] 30
40 year olds talking about people that
they don't know every day without a
life. What the [ __ ] is this community,
bro? A bunch of people on YouTube 24/7
projecting their life onto other people
and the ages of these [ __ ] people as well.
It's a [ __ ] disabled community. It is
literally a disabled [ __ ] community.
Yeah, I went live yesterday. I'm on here
today cuz it's Timmy who kept mentioning
my [ __ ] name. Keeps trying to draw me
out. Keeps trying to [ __ ] draw me
out, lad. Now he doesn't want any of it.
Typical Timmy. Now he doesn't want any of it.
[ __ ] [ __ ] You know,
bro, these people might they actually
they actually hurt your brain, bro. They
actually give you a headache. They're so
disabled. Like is they actually hurt
your brain, bro.
You can't You can't win. You You
seriously, Mike, you cannot win with
these people, bro.
You show that you've had sex, they still
call you a virgin. You show more money
than these people, they show you less
and still think that they beat you. They
they they literally, bro, they can't you
can't win with these people.
That's another thing that you need to um
remember. Uh uh it's just Fruit Madwell
like it always is, bro. He's under the
same name. Like you literally cannot win
with these people.
Uh you can't win with him, lad. There's
no way of winning with these people.
You show more money, they still think
they beat you. You show more women, they
still call you a virgin. You show you're
better looking than them, they still
call you a ma. It's pointless. It's
weird. A, it's pointless. And B, what
they do on here is so weird. It's
[ __ ] freakyified, bro.
Proper proper freakified.
It's proper freakified.
What they do on here, lad. So so freakified. Yeah.
And I said to him, "Meet me today. He
won't do it." So he started [ __ ] again
cuz I would have hurt him today, bro. If
he come to London, I would have
seriously seriously seriously hurt him,
bro. Yeah. I was I was ready today.
Yeah. Stop mentioning my name in your
stupid little videos. It's as simple as that. Yeah.
You know, and you can see what he's you
can see what he's doing as well. You
know what I'm saying? I don't want to be
on this loser community with these
little Mongs, these little low lives,
these little projectors,
these little jobless skimp people that
have got nothing. You say that we're
speculating, but it's not. It's not
speculating when it's facts. Facts are not speculating.
Cuz if you people had a life, you
wouldn't be on here talking about other
people every day, would you? Come on
now. Let's be real. Straight, bro. Straight.
Yeah, that's fine, bro. Don't put your
[ __ ] on to me, though. Don't draw me out.
Yeah, that's fine. Don't draw me out.
Don't [ __ ] draw me out in your stupid little videos.
He was talking about me smoking me. I'm
thinking, why the [ __ ] is this come
ringing me up saying that I've done my
balls in and I've not got 20? Is this
guy mad? So, he's trying to draw me out.
He's trying to get me in a mood. I'm in
a mood now. Now he's run away. So, I
message his family.
So, I messaged his family, bro. So, I
messaged his family.
So, I messaged the cunt's family.
Then he was sucking his [ __ ]
boyfriend nonslegs his dick again,
saying how he's got money when he does
not have money. This is the last time
I'm saying this. If you had any money,
if any of these people on here had any
money, you would have you would have
long beaten me. You would have long
beaten me over that summer. You would
have loved to beat me, but you couldn't.
And you didn't.
Yeah. And that's it, bro. You ain't got
money and your [ __ ] boyfriend ain't
got no [ __ ] money. Just like you
ain't got no [ __ ] life experiences.
What? because you got your housing
benefit and you showed everyone your housing benefit.
There's no gains to drawing out money
and showing these people. There's no
gain to it. There's literally no gains.
There's lit I could go to the bank right
now and take out two grand. Show these
people and they'd still pretend they
won. There's no gains to it, bro.
There's literally no gains to anything.
Yeah. Okay, bro. I'm skinn. You keep
telling yourself that, bro. I'm skinn.
If that makes you feel better about
yourself, then that's fine. Yep. I'm
skinn. Yep. Yep. Okay. If you keep
telling yourself that, bro, you keep
thinking that everyone's got your life.
You keep thinking that everyone's got
your life, bro. That's fine, man. If it
if it Do you know what? If it makes you
feel better, right, then that's a good
thing. I think I've done my job, bro.
I've done my job. I've done a good deed.
If you projecting your skintess onto me
makes you feel better, keep saying it,
bro. I love it. I'm not even going to
I'm not even going to ban you.
Yeah, bro. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah,
man. That's nice. Yeah. Yeah. I'm skinn,
bro. I haven't got a penny. I'm not
going to eat today. Does that Does that
give you a boner? If everyone agrees
with you, does that does that give you a
boner? Does that give you a boner? H
Does that give you a boner, lad? But
yeah, we can't all be like you people,
bro. Millionaires, all this money, sat
on YouTube talking about people every day.
Yeah. Yeah. I'm so skinned. I can't eat, bro. [ __ ]
I've already done it. No. No. No. No.
No. No. What they'll do, what they'll
do, what they'll do, what they'll do.
No, no, no. I've already shown money
before. Smokey. Smokey. I know how the
cookie crumbles. All what will happen
is, this is exactly what will happen if
you show them money, right? You will
show them money again like I've done a
million times. They won't show you
anything. So you've got money there. So
you've withdrew money. Yeah. Right. So
you show money then you show money. I've
got nothing to gain. I've got literally
And you people haven't show me money yet. Yeah.
Yeah. Simple as that. And another thing
is uh what I was saying is um what will
happen before I was rudely interrupted
is what they're going to do is say you
withdraw two grand right now. Yeah.
Right. Or say say for example two grand.
What these people are going to do is
they're not going to show you nothing.
They're going to continuously run away.
Then the next day you're going to show
them money again and then you'll show
them money again and then you show them
money again for the period of about two
weeks. This is what happened over the
summer. You put money in and then they
ask you to show money again. It's the
same cycle. They do it every time. It's
an autistic community. There's no point
showing them nothing. Nothing. Even if
these people had not £1 to their name,
bro, I wouldn't even show them £10.
That's how bad it is. I will never ever
show money ever again. They can keep
saying I'm skint. They can keep saying I
don't have anything. I mean, think about
it, bro. I don't have any bills. I don't
gamble that much. How can I be skinn?
How could I be skinn? I don't I don't
have no al Well, I have one phone. I've
got one phone bill and I don't gamble
much. How could I be scared? Just think
about it, bro. Like, think about it
logically. How could I run out of money?
Think about it. Just just think about it
for one second. Try try to be realistic about this.
Yep. And I've also shown money as well,
multiple times, which no one could uh no
one could have doubled. So,
yeah. And also, Mike, I've also shown money
in cash as well, and they still run
away, and they still didn't show me
nothing. And they still come back like they've won.
I mean, think about it, right? I went on
Nons's thing earlier, and he's bringing
up this Timmy thing.
I'm not showing you nothing.
I am not showing you [ __ ] all. I'm on a
I was on Nonsex's channel.
Nonsex's channel. And he's talking about Timmy.
Skin, big-nosed, immature virgin. The
word The word virgin. The The word
The word virgin, bro. The word virgin.
A virgin. A virgin. Really, bro? Really?
Okay. And that's what I'm saying. You'll
never win with these people.
You'll never ever win with these people.
You could show them a million pounds.
You could show them sticking your dick
up a million women. You could show that
you [ __ ] was a model. They would
still talk [ __ ] bro. That's why no one
wastes their time. That's why literally
literally literally no one waste their
time with these people. And they do the
they try to get away from these people.
This is why I try to get away from these
people, bro. Cuz you can't win with
them. That's the main thing. You can
never ever win with these people. A B
like you only speak to like a couple of
people on here, so you might as well
just make a new channel anyways.
Do you know what I'm saying? There's
they're jealous. What you got to
understand with these jealous people is
they're never going to leave you alone.
They're fat. They're ugly. They got
nothing in their life. They're waste of
everyone's time. They're just losers.
That's why I don't come on here much.
Yeah. Okay. I would be flexing. Okay,
bro. You keep telling yourself that we
Okay, bro. Whatever. I've already flexed
more money and it and it didn't make a difference.
I've been flexing money. I've been
flexing money and you all run away. You
run away. We're not We're not making the
same mistake for you people to run away again.
Okay, bro. I've got no money. If it
makes you feel better, I'm skin. Okay,
whatever. I've got nothing to my name.
If that makes you feel better, then I've
done a good deed. Simple.
You've been [ __ ] shown [ __ ]
thousands. Not Lord Jay has shown
anything. Not Joe has shown it because
they ain't got it. You've already got
the evidence right to show that these
people are skint. The evidence is there
just like you Joe. Joe L Timmy ngs.
The evidence is there that you're skint
there's no talking out of it. You've
been shown different amounts of money
and you're still thinking that you've
won. So there's no point. There is
literally no point. Everyone seen the
five grand clip. Everyone saw the four
And that's why no one waste their time.
Yep. No one waste their time because
they know they can't win with autistic
bias people. That's why they don't waste their time.
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. They would say that.
Anyways, we're not talking about this
anymore now. I'm moving on. I've said
what I've had to say. I've shown more
money than these people for a long
period of time and they've not shown me
nothing. We're moving on now. I'm moving
on now. Anyways,
so we're moving on now. Anyways, it's
just just the same argument with these
people every time.
So, yeah, we're moving on now. Anyways,
I'm I'm moving on now on my channel. So, yeah.
So, is this guy not um coming to London
today then? No.
All right. See you later.
So, he started all of this [ __ ] only for
him to not come.
Can you show uh I'm not showing you nothing.
Uh see you later, lad. I'm not showing
you nothing. I'm not showing ugly biased
people nothing. I've said this multiple
times. I'm not showing you nothing. No
stonies, no money, no nothing. Simple as that.
We don't argue with autistic biased
people. It's a waste of everyone's time.
Isn't that right, Joseph Ferrar?
And Skint doesn't mean zero money. Well,
it [ __ ] well does.
Get a life, man. How long have you
people been on this shitty ass community
doing this? 15 years. 12, 13, 15 years.
You would have thought that if people
like you right has got all this money
and you would have made a life for yourselves.
Can one okay what can one people stonies
are all sold. Nice try mate. No one
showing you nothing. When I said I'm not
showing you autistic biased people
anything I meant it. Yeah I s I sold my
stonies. Okay bro.
Yeah. No no no. Joe you are definitely
definitely skinned. I got more money
than you lad. I've not got a 300 pound
phone. I'm not skin like you and launch
legs. You're both skin. No, no, no, no,
no, no, no, no, no. I've got more money
than both of you, bro. Think of it. If
you had money, if you had money, you
would have beaten me at the money game
with cash. You ain't got no money. The
fact that you show a pension proves you
got no money. Cuz think about it, a
pension is not disposable money. The
fact that you're trying to use a
pension, it shows that you're poverty.
It shows that you're poverty, bro. It
shows that you are completely poverty.
Yeah. You do not see millionaires,
people with all of this money showing a
pension. It does. What do you mean? How
does it make sense? Of course it makes
sense. The money game, the money game,
right, is to show cash, not a pension.
Pension is not disposable money. A
pension is not your money until until a
certain time. What do you mean? How does
it make sense? It makes perfect sense.
You know, poverty eye Joe with a 200lb
phone. You're poverty. Joe, I have lived
more of a life than you have in three or
four years. I got more money than you.
The only one living in poverty is you. I
do. Okay. Okay. Go to the bank right
now. Same. This is This is exactly why I
don't come on anymore. It's the same
argument again. Show us £10,000 cash.
Right. Okay. Okay. Show us £10,000 cash.
Don't make excuses. Go to the bank
tomorrow and get £10,000 cash out and
show us the £10,000 and then go back.
Simple. I don't want to hear any excuses
that you can't do it. No excuses. Okay.
Show us £10,000 cash, bro. What I did
have. No. No. It's what I do have. Yeah.
I've still got designer clothes. I've
still got more money than you. Again,
I've I've stated again. I've got more
money than you. Open your ears. You do
not know how much money people have and
what people don't have. I have got more
money than you. I don't have to show a
pension. I don't have a 200 pound phone
like you. It's what I do have. Yeah.
Yeah. Simple. It's not what I did. It's
what I do. And it's not a 200 pound
phone like you, poverty boy. Yeah. Simple.
Simple, bro. Yeah. I've got more money
than you. You poverty ridden ass. Bro,
you only get about three grand a month
and you're flexing like you got money.
You ain't got no money, bro. Do you know
how easy three grand a month gets to live off?
Yeah, you're living under poverty
yourself. You poverty ridden northerner.
Poverty is your name. Poverty is you.
Poverty Joe with a 200 phone. They don't
call you that for no reason. Why else
would someone, bro, only be able to show
pensions, pensions, pensions, and
[ __ ] pensions? You wouldn't be
showing pensions. Think about it, right?
Yeah. If you argued with a millionaire
right now, would they be showing you
pensions? If you argued with somebody
that had loads and loads of money, would
they be showing you pensions? It's
because you ain't got money. Just like
nonsense, you ain't got money. Joe,
listen. You have been shown money,
right? And you've ran away. It doesn't
matter if it's 2 years ago. It doesn't
matter if it's 10 years ago, it doesn't
matter if it's 25. You have been shown
money and you ran away. The facts don't
change. It doesn't matter how. It
doesn't matter how long ago it was. It
doesn't matter how long ago it was. You
got shown what you was about when you
got shown money. Yeah.
Simple as that. It doesn't matter. It
does not matter. It does not matter. Yeah.
Simple. It does not matter.
It literally does not matter. Yeah.
Think about it. If you and your
boyfriends had all this money, why
didn't you mug me off when I was showing
you money? Huh? Because you ain't got
it. That's why you keep That's why you
keep ignoring me, bro. You keep ignoring
me, right? You keep ignoring and
ignoring and ignoring because you know
I'm right. You know I'm telling the
truth about you and not legs. You've
been showing multiple money and you all
run away. You kept running away from me,
bro. And you still come back like you've
won. You will always think you've won.
Even when people show you money, even
when people show you women, you come
back like you've won. There's no point
with you. That's why I do not get into
any [ __ ] with any of you people
anymore. Any of you jealous
self-reflected skint people. I don't get
into it anymore.
I don't get into it with biased skint
self projectors. It's a waste of
everyone's time and you just have a you
just have a sore head.
You don't have the mental capacity to
understand what is what someone's saying
to you. What's the point? You know,
just like you're never going to meet
anyone, Joe. You're never And think
about it. Yeah. You come up with all of
this [ __ ] You come up with all of this
[ __ ] but you I don't see you on my
front door. Think about it, bro. I don't
You You go on about how people are this,
people are that, people are this, people
are that. I don't see you on my front
door. And there's no reason for it.
Every single comment is about me, you
little gay boy. And I don't see you on
my front door sorting me out, Giza. Like
you keep telling people that they need
to sort LT out. Why don't you sort me
out, Gizer? You know where I live. Don't
use my mom as an excuse. Don't make me
bring up Albert Square again. Don't make
me bring up Albert Square again. Geyser
who sorts people out. Think about it.
Come on. How many times has me Yeah, I'm
not even going to use Ali as [ __ ] cuz
he's biased. How many times have I had
to go here, go there, go here, go there,
go here, go there, go here, go there.
We've never seen you on anyone's [ __ ]
door sorting anyone out, big man. So
don't come on here telling people that
they need to sort people out when you
can't even come on someone's front
[ __ ] door. And at the end of the day,
it's very valid when every comment is
about someone. I'm thinking, bro, why
didn't this guy just come and sort me
out? Cuz you ain't got no balls, you
skinny ugly man. You skinny ugly man
like your boyfriend. You ain't got a
pair of balls. You understand, bro?
Yeah. You ain't got a pair of balls. I
would [ __ ] knock you clean out with
one punch. Oh, I r Okay. Yeah, bro.
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Just like I call
the police on Timmy and Tiger. You can't
win with these people. You can't win
with these disabled people.
Yeah. Like I like I wrong the police.
Yeah. You've always got excuses. That's
why people don't bother anymore. And you
know what? I'm I'm I'm hoping Monty Man
does the same thing. I'm hoping he
rarely goes live. I hope he doesn't go
live much now as well to be honest with
you. People need to starve these biased
low life jealous people. That's what I
was doing for N. Just starve the low
lives. Starve them. They've got nothing
in their life. Poverty. Poverty. [ __ ] Joe.
H brother. I live by myself and you
Okay. Okay. Okay. Yeah. Okay. My mom.
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Well, I was
living by myself and I still didn't see
you. What about when I was living by
myself? Why don't you come and sort me
out? Like you keep talking about how
people need to sort this out and sort
Monty out. Why didn't you come and sort
me out, you [ __ ] stupid Norman [ __ ]
I would have banged you straight in that
ugly rice face of yours, bro. I would
have I would have laughed at you in real
life. I would have took the piss out of
you in real life. But you're never going
to meet anyone. Admit it to everyone
you're not even going to meet me in
Nottingham. Admit it to everyone now
that you're not going to meet anyone in
Nottingham. You're not going to meet
anyone in Nottingham. Tell everyone that
you're not going to meet me in
Nottingham because we know your game,
you little gay boy. We've been dealing
with you little gay [ __ ] losers for
ages. I'm I will do nothing. Bro, like I
said, you've had my address and you've
done nothing. So, you've done nothing
despite knowing my address. You've known
it and you have done nothing and you
will continue to do nothing. Yet, you
know where I live. Remember, Joe, you
know where I live and you continue to do
nothing. Yeah. Simple as that. So, so
okay. Okay. [ __ ] the addresses. [ __ ] the
addresses. Anyways, [ __ ] all all of this
address. So, if I if I tell you that I'm
going to go to Nottingham a week in
advance, are you going to are you going
to meet me?
Are you going to meet me or not?
You're in Harriet tomorrow. Uh, good for
you, bro. Good. Good for you.
So, you're not So, are you going to meet
me in Nottingham so I can punch your
ugly face in and spit all over your
face? cuz it's not going to just be a
normal fight. It's not going to just be
a normal fight.
Are you going to are you going to do it? Like,
listen listen. Are you going to come and
meet me in Nottingham or not?
I'm asking you. If it's a no, then I'm
done with you. It's as simple as that.
I'm done with you. Yeah. I've already
been to Sheffield. I've already been to
Leeds and you was quiet like a good boy.
You've known where I've lived and you've
been quiet like a good boy. Are you
going to meet me in Nottingham or not?
I'm not going to Har because I I've
already explained the reason why I'm not
going again. I've already explained the
reason why I'm not going. Right. You've
known where I've lived. You've done
nothing. I've gone to Leeds. You've done
nothing. I've gone to Sheffield. You've
done nothing. You've never done nothing.
I'm trying to arrange a meet with you
and you're not doing it
because you will continuously do nothing
yet you know where someone lives. And I
am and I am saying that now. And I am
saying that now cuz that is the truth of
you little weasels. I am saying that
now. You know where people live and you
continuously do nothing. You don't sort
anyone out. You haven't done anything.
You didn't come on my door when I lived by myself.
When I live by myself, you continuedly
done nothing despite knowing where I
live. You ain't sorted me out. Like I
needed sorting out. Do you understand?
I'll say the same thing to you then.
Yeah, I know. It's proper bad. It's It's
a proper bad. He is bad, bro. He is.
It is proper bad, bro. It is proper bad.
Cuz if anyone's serious, bro, they meet
they'll just meet people halfway.
If people are serious, they'll just meet people halfway.
Shouldn't you be sucking your [ __ ] boyfriend's dick?
Shouldn't you Shouldn't you be sucking
your boyfriend's dick?
You know what I'm saying, bro?
I'm I'm calling him a virgin. You got to
cry some more about this girlfriend. I
think he's a [ __ ] virgin, Joe. Go cry
some more. [ __ ] stupid [ __ ] I think
your boyfriend Nunchle Legs is a [ __ ]
big virgin. Are you going to cry some
more? Oh, he's in a relationship. Oh,
he's got a girlfriend, bro. He is. He
is. He's a [ __ ] Do you know what he
is? He's He's undercover gay, bro. Did
you go on Did you go on Lord Did you go
on Lord Jay's? Did you go on Lord Jay's
the other day, bro? Every comment was
about me, rat boy. Every comment was
about me, but he won't come on anyone's
door. He won't meet anyone. He won't
sort it out like a man like he tells
other people to sort things out. Do you
know what I'm saying?
Do you know what I'm saying, bro? Jesus
Christ. Oh, don't say that about him.
He's got a girlfriend. You want to suck
his dick some more, gay boy? A
girlfriend doesn't mean someone's had
sex. What I've shown is is having sex.
Being in women's beds naked, [ __ ]
that's more than an ugly girlfriend.
That's more than an ugly girlfriend. I'm
certain it's more than an ugly
girlfriend with special needs that can't
consent to sex. I'm pretty sure I put my
money on that. To be honest with you,
I'm pretty sure I put my money on that.
I'm pretty sure someone showing [ __ ]
and them bed naked all women is more
than a disabled girlfriend. I put my
money on that. And I don't really I
don't really gamble anymore. But go cry.
I'm calling him a virgin. Go bring up
Oh, don't say that about him. I can't
understand it. He can't be a virgin.
Well, you're probably a virgin your
[ __ ] self. A closeted [ __ ] virgin at that.
But no, seriously, you are a bad troll.
Everybody knows what you're trying to do
when you're trying to get people to go
to Yorkshire. Oh, I can troll you. I
made you do this. I made you do that.
The fact that you can't even come and
talk on a panel proves it. The fact that
you can't even come and talk on a panel
proves it. You're just a little nonslegs
lover. You've all got the same traits.
Skin, poverty, cowardly. You've got the same traits.
You've got the same traits as your
[ __ ] boyfriend. It doesn't take
Albert Einstein to come to be digged up
from the [ __ ] grave to say what
you're doing. You're just like your [ __ ] boyfriend.
You're just a little chicken [ __ ] like
your virgin boyfriend. And you know
what? Every single time you bring up the
girlfriend, I'm just going to keep doing
it now. I'm just going to keep saying
that he's a virgin. He's a virgin. And
I'm just going to keep ignoring it and
keep going on like he's a virgin because
I'm sure you'll live, Joe. I'm sure you
will live. You're not going to die.
Nothing's going to happen to you. I'm
sure you'll live, lad. I'm sure you'll
live with me calling someone a virgin.
Yeah, that's fine. No one's meeting you
in Harriate. Answer. Ask yourself, why
haven't you come to London and come on
my door and sort me out? You've had two
addresses of where I've lived. I've
lived by myself. Why haven't you come
and sorted it, big man? Sorted it.
Sorted it like a big man. Why haven't
you come and sorted it? You little
skinny little [ __ ] Northern ugly
little poverty ridden [ __ ] Why haven't
you come and sorted it out? You're
talking about people coming and sorting
Monty Man out and this Haven't you have
two addresses where I've lived? Why
haven't you sorted it out, big man? You
keep avoiding the question because
you're not about to nothing. And the
only reason you want people to travel
that way is so you can say, "Oh, we made
you. We laugh at you." It's not going to
work. Joseph [ __ ] Joseph [ __ ] It's
not going to work. If you was about
anything, you'd agree to meet someone in Nottingham.
Joseph [ __ ] It's not going to work.
Poverty [ __ ] with 200 pound phone.
Joseph [ __ ] Poverty eyed [ __ ] Joe
with a 200 pound phone.
You're not going to meet anyone and
you'll never meet anyone. You will never
ever ever meet anyone. You would have
been on someone's door. You'd agreed to
meet someone in Nottingham. You would
have agreed to meet someone in
Nottingham if you were serious about
meeting someone. [ __ ] little fanny.
You're not meeting no one.
You're not meeting [ __ ] no one. Go
suck your boyfriend's dick and go cry
some more that call him a virgin. You
got better things to be doing. You got
You got better things to be doing.
Bro, bro, bro, listen. I told you the
place. You've backed out of meeting me
again. You will continuously do nothing.
You've had two addresses. You won't come
on my door. We're done with you now.
We're done. We're past that now. We're
done. You're not beating no one. You'll
continuously do nothing. We're done with
you now. We're done with you, keyboard warrior.
[ __ ] hell. You just like your
boyfriend whose dick you like to suck
every time I call him a virgin, yet he's
not proved he's had sex. You are so
similar to your Are you sure you ain't
already sucked his dick? I'm saying all
of this stuff to you and you're not
meeting me. You won't come on my door.
You won't come on my door and sort me
out, Gizer. Sort me out, Gizer. Sort
Monty man out. Suck this person. Now
tell everybody on YouTube why you come
and sort me out. You big [ __ ] You big
Joseph [ __ ] Tell everybody why you
haven't come and sorted me out. Ger like
you're telling other people to sort
people out. You little fatty.
Yeah. Because Joseph [ __ ] Farra
with a 200lb phone living in poverty
showing fake wins will never meet anyone.
And that's it, bro. That's it.
Poverty Joe with a 200lb phone. I got
more clothes than you. I got more money [ __ ]
And no one's ever had to pay for stuff.
Most of the women I've been with is
free, bro. I bet you any money jokes
that that your MS, if you even have one,
is fat and ugly. You're too ugly to get
anything. Just like your boyfriend legs.
You're all the same. You're just like
You're just like your boyfriend legs.
Both skin, both scared of me. It's the
same. You're the same.
You're literally the same. You know all
about Nottingham and you know exactly
where it is. We're not getting into this.
We're not We're not getting into this.
Yeah, you know where Nottingham is. You
know about Nottingham.
You're not meeting anyone. You never
have and you never will. Yeah.
And you never will.
He's never going to meet anyone. Greedy.
Stop it with this weirdo. He's never
going to beat anyone.
He's not beating no one.
He's not beating anyone.
Isn't that right, Joe? You've known
where people have lived, but you ain't
come and sorted it. Sorted. I love that.
I love it when you say that. Sorted.
You're not going to do anything. You
poverty ridden skinned [ __ ] showing fake
wins. Poverty jolt with that 200 lb f.
They don't call you that for no reason.
They don't call you They don't call you
poverty eyed Joe with a 200 pound phone
for no reason. That hasn't come on
anyone's door. There's a reason for that, bro.
Um why am I on here? Because um I was
supposed to be meeting Timmy today.
That's the reason why I'm on here. No, I
don't even get bored. No, I was supposed
to be meeting Timmy today and he shhat his pants.
He tried drawing me out again and look,
he's run away again.
Yeah, he's run away again. He's tried
drawing me out again with himself
injecting on these videos. And he was
supposed to be meeting me today and as
usual, nothing again.
Nothing. Absolutely nothing.
Complete [ __ ] spaz.
Get my name out your [ __ ] stupid [ __ ]
toy mouth. I don't even know why I'm
even wasting my time. You I don't even
know why I'm wasting my bloody time on this, bro.
I guess I just thought you was just
going to meet me to be. I mean, what is
the point? You're all [ __ ] ugly as
[ __ ] You ain't got no life, which is
why you come here talking about people
every day. Just like the poverty eyed
Joe with a 200lb phone. Poverty eyed Joe
with a 200 phone.
Trust me though, I've got more money
than you and your boyfriend will ever
have. Will ever have. Yeah. Meet me
instead. Okay, bro. Yeah. Yeah, I'll
meet you. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. I'll
Yeah. Yeah. I'll meet you. Yeah. Yeah.
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. I'll meet you. Yeah.
This is why I don't come on here.
So you get deprived of content, Grezy.
Sorry that you get deprived of contact content, lad.
Sorry you get deprived of content. But
this is exactly why you can blame these
people, lad. You can blame these people
and hear why why you don't get content
anymore. You poor [ __ ] You can stop,
you can stop naming these people.
It's what they do on here is so weird.
Anytime you want, any place you want
and this is exactly what I mean. It's
got no life in it. Generally have got no
life on here
really. Really? That's nice of you, man.
Um yeah, meet me in meet me in Stratford.
Yeah. Yeah. Meet me in Stratford. Yeah.
And this is the same thing every time
with these people, bro.
It's the same thing with these jealous
people. Do you understand why I'm not on
here now? Um Grezy, do you understand
why I don't come on here now? It's the
same atmosphere every time you go live
with these people. It's the same thing
with them. Do you see why I don't go live?
Do you see why I avoid this place now?
Do you understand now? Do you understand
why I avoid this place? Because of these
jealous ass ugly people with no life?
Wasn't Timmy supposed to be coming to London today?
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. I was Yeah. I
was on 6 and 1/2 hours straight. I was
talking to someone. Yeah. And do you
know what I was doing? I was speaking to
someone that could actually have a
conversation. I was speaking to someone
that's had a that Yeah,
bro. This guy Ben Yeah. He was giving it
the big, bro. I swear to God, I was I
was watching his video yesterday cuz I
thought, "Oh, he's going to put some
down. He's the only one I'm subscribed
to." Yeah. I went on his video. He
starts self-projecting his skin onto me.
He keeps bringing me up. He kept talking
about [ __ ] nods legs. I thought,
"Fuck this, bro. I'm gonna go live.
Yeah. And I messaged his family. I said,
"Bro, you keep talking about me. Every
time you do a video talking about me,
I'm going to message your family. That's
how it's going to go." I messaged Auntie
Rose and I and I messaged Chris. I said,
"You keep talking about me, I'll keep
messaging your family. That's the way
it's going to work now until you stop."
Yeah. Because what he does, right, is
when the attention is on him, right, he
likes to start bringing my name up to
try to get out of, you know, what people
are doing to him on here. Wasn't talking
about him. Didn't go live yesterday.
Didn't do any videos. I didn't do any
videos. Why is this guy bringing me up,
bro? Don't stop mentioning my And it's
the way it was so obvious what he was
trying to do as well. It's not like he's
saying, "Oh, PJ or just throwing you in
there." It's obvious what he was trying to do.
the guy like and like I just said, bro,
like every time you do it, every time
you do it now and you don't meet anyone,
that's what I'm going to do. You think
about it then. Yeah. This guy is never
going to stop. How many times this guy
got beaten up? You know what's so mad is
this guy has actually been beaten up and
he still hasn't learned. He still has
not learned. I'm not drawing him out. I
might I've tried to get away from this
place and he keeps bringing me back into
it. You know,
you know what I'm saying, bro? You don't
have money, Timmy. Just like your
boyfriend nonslegs don't have money.
You've already been outed what you are
when you've been shown money. You You've
already been outed. You nonslegs Joe [ __ ]
uh LJ a lot of them. You've all been outed.
You've all been outed of what you are
when you've been showing money. Why are
you still doing this in 2026? Why are
you still asking people to show you stuff?
Oh, it doesn't count though, Ben,
because it was ages ago.
This is this is this is the thing, Ben.
You won't you will not you will not win
with these people ever. You will never
win with these people. You will never
ever ever win with these people. That's
one of the main reasons why it's
pointless coming on here. And the fact
of what they do as well on here, it's
just so creepy and freakified, which is
why I don't think you come on here much
while you're not on here much cuz I
don't see you much. Doesn't matter, bro.
Who reacts, who doesn't react. They of
course they're biased, bro. Listen, I
was stating both. I've you know the
thing is when you're trying to explain
this you you're giving yourself a
headache. I've explained multiple times.
I have shown these people money time and
time and time again. And every time
they've done it, they've run away.
They've run away, bro. And it shows that
they don't have no money. No one needs
to show NGS anything more. No one needs
to show Timmy anything more. No one
needs to show Lord J anymore. And you
know what the excuse they come up with,
Ben? Oh, it was ages ago. Oh, it was
ages ago. Don't these people talk about
things from years ago, bro? Don't they
every day talk about things that
happened years ago? It doesn't matter if
it was years ago. It could be it could
be hundred years ago. You've been show
money and you've all run away every
time. End of. End of. There doesn't need
to be a repeat. There doesn't need to be
a rematch. Well, until you show more
money than what I've shown. That's what
I'm saying, bro. Like, it's it's the
same with them. You [ __ ] show women,
they still call you a virgin. You show
you're better looking than them. They
still call you ugly. They're [ __ ]
It's a waste of everyone's time, bro.
It is a waste of everyone's time.
Everyone's time. Even getting into it.
But I just thought Timmy would have met
me today. But no,
I weren't even in a bad mood yesterday.
I was just chilling, bro. I was watching
some GTA videos. Yeah. Just chilling,
bro. Didn't gamble yesterday. I was just
chilling. And I see this little prick
keep talking about me, bro. Yeah.
You know what I'm saying? Yeah, they are
biased, bro. They are biased.
We got [ __ ] some [ __ ] nons calling
me a virgin. When I when I've got their
channel banned for porn Ben, I got I got
the channel banned for porn
pornography. Ben, I got I got his
channel banned for pornography. I was in
but he was but he's still calling me a
virgin. Can you please explain to me how
that makes sense? Not that he cares. I
don't not that I care. I don't care who
calls me Virgin. I'm saying can you
explain to me how that makes sense.
Can you explain to me how that makes
sense? Yeah. Timmy, come to London like
you said you was going to come today.
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. You said you was going
to come with your mate today. Yeah. To
London. Come on then. Come on then.
Yeah. Skin. Yeah. Again calling me a
virgin again. Even though I proven I've had sex.
You people just must be jealous of me in
it. You really, really, really must be
jealous or something, bro. To to to sit
on here. I know you don't like that
word. I know you're scared of that word,
but you must be, bro. To come on here
for years, every day doing this, you
must be must be seriously jealous of
something. That's the only thing that
could explain the biasness
um and and and the [ __ ] that you do
every day. You got you got to be
seriously jealous of something, you
know? I'm I'm bringing that word back,
you know? I'm really really bringing
that word back.
You must be really, really, really
jealous of something.
You know, calling someone a virgin
that's already proven that they've had
sex again. Second time you've done this, right?
You must be seriously jealous of
something, bro. It's got to be jealousy
with you people. No, no, no. No,
seriously, bro. It really, really,
really, really has.
It's not letting me put a link up for
some reason. One second. I need to
restart the live stream. Two sex. 2 seconds.