Timmy's talking [ __ ] again, making excuses again.
Timmy, I will pay for your Uber to come
here and go back. Yeah. Go to Birmingham
train station or wherever you are in
Birmingham. Tell me where you are and I
will literally pay for your Uber. No
problem at all. I will give you my email
and I will pay for your Uber. So, you
have no excuses. It's £180 there, £180 back.
Call it £400. Not a problem. Come on.
Let's do it, man. Come on. Come on. Go
to a location. Tell me I will book your
Uber and I will give you the registration number.
Come on. You've got nothing better to
do. You keep making videos on YouTube.
So, I mean, I I I will pay for your Uber
if you want.
Not a problem at all.
200 max there. £200 back, £500. Not a
problem. Let's do it. Come on. You know,
keep making excuses. Oh, if I had a car,
oh, what if I had a car? Mate, I'll pay
for your Uber. It's not a problem. I
will literally pay for your Uber and
I'll give you the registration number as well.
Yeah, let's do it. Come on. Let's do it.
Yeah. Let's see what excuse you come out with now. Come on.
You talk some [ __ ] don't you, mate? If
I had a car, if I had this, you're not
meeting no one. You're just a skin
self-reflecting gambling mess that's
self-p projecting your skintess onto me
like always. And then you're talking
about toasty and what the [ __ ] are you
even talking about?
You [ __ ] stupid little [ __ ] I'll pay
for your Uber if you want.
Not a problem, bro.
Only cost about £400 maybe. Damn back. I
don't mind doing it, you know. Come on.
You said people are skin cuz you know
how much people have apparently cuz
you're skin. So, let's do it then. Let's
do it. Come on. Let's do it. Come on.
Yeah. 100% serious.
Come on. the links up. Come on.
Wherever you want to go from, come on,
you stupid [ __ ] [ __ ] If I had a car,
I would drive. Oh, you're so full of
excuses. Just get off of YouTube and
stop calling people out. Stop mentioning people's names. Yeah,
I'm on the links there. What you waiting
for you little [ __ ]
What did he say? People can't afford a
[ __ ] Big Mac, wasn't it? Oh my. What
the [ __ ] is he going on about now?
[ __ ] nine [ __ ] grand. You've never
shown nine grand.
Oh my god. Anyways, the office there
with the Uber. I said to him, I'll pay
for his Uber. I'll pay for his Uber if he wants.
I'll pay for his Uber. Yeah, I know. No.
I said I'll pay for his Uber. It'll be
about £400 return. So, he's got no
excuses now, does he?
I'll pay for his Uber if he wants.
I'll pay for the Uber cuz he said that
if he had a car, now he's using more
excuses. I'll pay for his Uber if he wants.
if that makes it a little bit easier.
Come on then. I I don't mind paying for
the Uber, bro. Yeah.
I'll pay for the Uber. It's about 180
there, 180 back. I've just looked at it.
Say £400. Not a problem at all. Come on.
He's so sure people are skin because he
seems to know everyone, but he doesn't
know anything. Let's do it. I'm I'm
happy to do it. Me? Yeah.
He's saying that Trael showed money and
Toasty showed money and all of this.
What is he even going on about? What the [ __ ]
What the [ __ ] is he going on about, bro?
I was watching some [ __ ] Spider-Man
and a video popped up. PJ from Fruit
Man. From Fruit Man. World Grezy. I was
watching Spider-Man and Mary Jane.
And this cunt's trying to draw me out.
I'm watching some Spider-Man.
And this cunt's trying to draw me out. [ __ ] off.
Now, do you see what Hey, do you know
what these people are doing now as well,
Greavesy? You know, people, they're
pretending to like me because they don't
like him. They're doing exactly what
they're doing to non-legs now. Thumbs
up. Everyone's going at him. Yeah. See,
they're pretending to like me because
they don't like Timmy. Do you get it?
They're doing now what they do to
nonslegs. Didn't you Didn't you clock on?
>> Yeah. They're doing what they're
Yep. I was watching some lovely Peter
Parker Greavvesy and I've been interrupted.
Been [ __ ] interrupted. Griezy.
Yeah, I've been interrupted, bro.
There is no 2001. It's 2002, 2004, and then 2007.
It started from 2002.
It started from 2002, 2004, then 2007.
So I was five when it come out.
Yeah, that's Peter Parker.
I said I'll pay for his Uber.
Of course I know about Spider-Man, bro.
I used to watch Spider-Man when I was a kid.
You know, Super Oh, you know
Spider-Man's been going since 1962.
Yeah. And Superman's been going since
1940. But he started off on comic. They
started Spider SP Superman on comic books.
Before there was DVD plays, they just
used to make comic books of him,
dude. Yeah, he's he's older than uh
Superman's older than Spider-Man,
but I prefer Spider-Man. I never really
like Batman, but I like Joker. I like I
like Joker in Batman.
I might start a comic book collection, Greavvesy.
I might spend some money on comic book collections.
Is that cute?
So, that must mean Spider-Man had a baby
with Mary Jane. Oh,
that's the mommy of the baby then, I'm
guessing. That's really cute.
So, that's the baby then, isn't it? Oh,
that's really cute, isn't it, Grezy?
Yeah, that's really cute. Bless Grezy.
That's really cute.
So, I said I'll pay for his Uber, Ben,
and he's gone silent.
He's gone silent. Hm. [ __ ]
He's a [ __ ] bro. [ __ ] mentioning my [ __ ] name. Yeah.
He's saying that Toasty showed money and
Trol's never shown money.
Why is he saying Tremodell's shown
money, Ben, when he hasn't?
Why is he Why is he saying that Trael
shown money when he hasn't?
And And apparently Toasty's shown 100
grand. No, he [ __ ] hasn't.
He hasn't shown 100 grand.
Toasty shown 100 grand. Yeah, I don't
think so, bro. 100 grand.
Yeah. Okay, bro.
Guy's a [ __ ] idiot, bro.
I don't know what to eat today,
Greavvesy. I can't get an Indian because
the chef's not there.
I wish I had like a macaroni cheese or
like a lamb hot pot I could just put in the oven.
You could just put in the oven, you
know. M Chinese is closed.
Chinese is closed, bro.
Bye. Greasy. Bquest.
Greavvesy. Greasy. Bquest
to fit in. Greasy. Bquest. Bar quest.
Bless him. Barquest and Lee. Bless him.
Barquest said that he was saying it to
fit in. Greasy.
Barqu said he was saying it to fit in.
Do you remember
to fit in? We griezy.
That sound funny coming from Bar Quest, didn't it?
Bless him, dude. Bless him then if you
didn't want to feel left out.
No, I'm sick of hearing it. I'm sick of
talking about it, bro.
There's nothing funny about it, bro.
There's nothing funny about people that
copy other people.
It's very boring, very lame.
Trends are boring. Trends are lame.
Canada goose coats are lame. All the
trends in the past have been lame.
In it, uh, in it, Grezy,
it's just all lame. Copycats are lame. Boo.
Throw eggs at them. Is it? Yeah, bro.
I was watching um Dickerson's Real Deal downstairs, Grezy earlier.
Big up Dickinson. He's a legend.
Big up David Dickinson. Eh, he's a legend. Yeah.
Giza, he's from stock. He's from
Stockport. Bless him brie. He's from Stockport. Bless.
Mr. Dickinson. Bless him. And his little
fake tan. Greasy.
Him. And his little fake tans.
That's cute, ain't it?
What are you going to eat today? Greasy boss.
What are you eating today, Captain?
Don't know what I could eat, bro. Like,
I don't know what I'm going to eat.
Let me have a little look.
I had peppers yesterday, didn't I?
What about a vindaloo, Grezy? Can I get a vindaloo?
I need to stop getting food in and
cooking, but I'm so lazy, bro.
I'm so lazy.
>> Yeah, I'm not that that hungry, but I'll
have to have something, won't I? Remember
that Tik Tok? That's enough Tik Tok for
today. Rey the little cat. That's enough
Tik Tok for today.
That's enough Tik Tok for today.
That made me laugh.
It was going mad, isn't it?
It was going mad. Greasy, wasn't it?
The little cat. That's enough Tik Tok for today.
probably what they were like when they
used to watch the X Factor when they
used to copy each other.
Ant-Man said, "Oh, I don't think people
used to copy each other. I think people
generally wanted her." Nah.
Nah. She ain't that good, bro. She's not
She's not that good, Greasy, to make
everybody want her and talk about her
the way they did. Think about it, bro.
No one is ever that good.
Nah, no one ever looks that good to make people. Yeah.
She wasn't that good for people to talk
about her and start questioning people's
sexuality. You understand? Greedy.
I didn't see it. Anyways, maybe other people did.
Yeah, you can see the westernity in their eyes.
But men don't have it in their eyes,
Grevy. It's only women. If you see men's
eyes, there's no westernity in it. With
them, you can see it. It's like MP.
They're like NPCs
that they've got that look in that eye.
It's just nothing there. It's just dead.
And the eyes never lie, Grezy. The eyes never lie.
The eyes never lie, Grezy. The eyes never lie.
I am I don't know what I'm going to eat today.
The eyes never lie. You can see the
westernity in their eyes.
Did USA have westernity in our eyes? Grezy.
I had peppers yesterday.
I had a whole chicken and chips.
I already had that yesterday.
I had a whole chicken and chippies.
I don't know what I'm going to get, bro.
Maybe like a chicken burger.
No, I'm not in the mood for pizza. You
have to really be in the mood for pizza.
No, not pizza.
I'm very rarely in the mood for pizza,
Grezy. Maybe three times a year.
Maybe three times a year, bro.
I have to really be in the mood for
pizza. Like really?
I'm not in the mood for KFC either.
It's fried chicken. I don't know. Maybe
a curry. I don't know.
I don't know. No, I don't fancy a KFC.
I'd probably get like a Subloin chips,
but where you getting the Subloin chips from?
Do you know what I mean, Bloomsy?
Yeah, probably like a ser, but you can't
get it cuz the place ain't open today.
>> All right, send me some money in this
Uber thing and I'll be down within the
next 3 hours.
>> Do you realize it will cost you? No,
I'll pay for your I'll pay for your Uber.
>> £250 quid back.
>> I'll I'll pay for your Uber.
>> Yeah. Have you got £500? Yes or no?
>> I've got more than £500. So, you can pay
for my return there and I'll put you in
hospital and you can pay for me back. Yeah.
>> Yeah. Yeah, that's fine.
>> Yeah. Okay. So, can you show me on your
Uber app that you're going to book it?
>> Yeah. You What do you mean I'm going to
book it? I'm going to book I'm going to
book the Uber. Yeah.
>> I want I want you to provide the
evidence. Well, you to give me the
address to order it to and I'll order it.
>> Peter, all you've got to do is go live
on your tablet, show the booking.
>> You give me You give me the address and
I'll book it.
>> You haven't got any money, have you?
Okay. I haven't got any money to have
you. Anyway, I haven't got any money. Okay.
>> You're at the same
um bangers, mate. Daniel,
>> what should I eat today? Get Arnold Lane
to come and meet me and I'll own you before.
>> Byebye. I'm kicking you now. See you later.
See you later, kid.
Do you know what could be nice from the
Chinese? Like a curry or something?
Yeah, I think like a Chinese maybe.
But an actual Chinese curry. That would be nice.
No, not noodles. No
salt and chili ribs.
I need to stop this takeaway [ __ ] man.
>> What do you want kick me out the
hangouts for? Is it cuz I'm owning you
again cuz you got no money?
>> Because you're talking [ __ ]
>> All you got to do is provide the
evidence, Peter. It's not rocket
science. And anyway,
account is a nons.
>> See you later. Get kicked.
>> Yeah, that's what I'm thinking. Yeah,
Chinese beef curry. Yeah,
just like a little curry, you know, a
Chinese beef curry would be lovely. Grievy,
I haven't had one of them for ages. Nope.
But you people are judging by your weight.
Well, you you you want to see a fight,
Greavvesy. Well, you'll be waiting a
long time because Timmy will never meet anyone.
Why do people care if you got Because
they haven't got no money. Because
they've got no money. So it's self
projecting. So that because they're
skint, they like to tell other people
that they've got no money. Same as nonslegs.
Yeah. It's because they're skint
themselves and they like to self-project
and tell other people they've got no money. Anyways,
seafood, chicken, beef.
Yeah, it's just self-reflecting. Basically,
it's because they're skin. Timmy's skin.
So that's why he's saying that I'm skin.
Oh, here we go. Curry. Chicken curry. Beef curry. Oh, lovely.
No, I don't have a fast food problem,
but judging by your weights on this
community, you people definitely do.
There's a pork curry, but I don't really
want that. Okay. What about rice?
Steamed rice. Yeah, we want steamed
Yeah, I'm not I'm not cooking food
today. I'm not going out.
Beef, curry, and steamed rice. Don't
mind if I do, Captain.
Don't mind if I do, Captain. £1683.
Is that okay with you, Greasy?
Yeah. I got a beef curry and steamed rice. Yep.
There you go. Just ordered a takeaway
that cost £17 basically. But Timmy said I'm skint self projecting.
But yeah, Bob, to answer your question,
it's because they haven't got no money
themselves. That's why they call people
skint cuz they're skint.
So you you know this five pound you know
this£5 challenge you wanted to do,
Grezy, where you um
you you you live off£5 a day. I reckon
you could do£3 pound a day.
I reckon you could
if you ate pork.
I had six nuggets from Chinese. My mom
bought nuggets. I had six nuggets. Yeah.
So what? So what?
I reckon you could do £3 a day. Well, I
had pork chops before. I bought three or
four pork chops. They cost like 2 pound50.
I reckon you could have a meal free 3
pound50 a day.
Yeah, I reckon you definitely could, lad. Yeah.
I'm going to try and I'm going to have a
lamb pot tomorrow.
I'm going to try and live off £3 a day
for a month. Greavesy. Imagine that.
Live off 3 to5 a day for a month.
Do you reckon you could do it? Yeah.
For a month. I think I'm going to go out
drinking again. Greavvesy. Um,
St. Patty's Day.
I think I'm going to go out St. Patty's
Day, I think.
Yeah, I think so, bro.
Maybe. Which is the 17th? I think St. Patrick's Day.
if I got Yeah, probably maybe
before. I don't know.
I don't really normally go out events, but uh
>> why do you
>> Yeah. So, you are you coming are you
coming to London?
>> You're going to provide the evidence.
You're going to pay for this taxi.
You're just full of [ __ ]
>> You You said You said I'm skin, but I've
just got a take away.
>> Are you full of [ __ ]
>> But you you said that I'm skinn, right?
But I've just bought a takeway.
>> Lee Green has to phone the police cuz he
got exposed for being a bacon.
>> Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait. You said
that I'm skinn but I just bought a
takeway on Facebook.
>> You said I'm skinned but I just bought a
take account is Lee Green.
>> One second. You said that I'm just
bought a takeaway.
>> You [ __ ] up there, haven't you, Lee? Anyway,
>> one second. One second. You can go and
cry to Yorkshire Police. You big fat waster.
>> Timmy, you said I couldn't afford a McDonald's burger.
>> Me today and provide this [ __ ]
evidence or not.
>> You said that I couldn't afford a
takeaway. Are you coming to Are you
going to pay for this tax? You just
>> Yeah, I am. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Give me
the Give me an address to order it to.
>> Put the evidence up. Go get off live.
>> No. You order You
>> 7 quid to get me there and back.
>> No. You give me your address and I will
order it to you. Okay. Listen, listen.
Okay. Okay. Okay. Okay. One second. One
second. Right. I can't talk cuz of this
[ __ ] Right. Okay. Timmy, go to
Birmingham train station. Birmingham
Mall Street. Listen to what I'm saying
now. Stop typing. Go to Birmingham Mar
Street and I will order the I'll order
the taxi to Mar Street. Yeah, it's the
smaller train station in Birmingham and
yeah, uh I'll give you the registration number
and obviously it's just my name. Okay,
then go to More Street then and I'll
order it. Simple.
Yeah, you go to More Street. More street
and then I'll order the T and I'll order the Uber.
Simple. Yeah, that's it.
Put the link back up now. It doesn't let you talk.
500. It doesn't matter, bro.
Timmy's [ __ ] skin. He said I can't
afford a burger, but I've just ordered
food and I'm prepared to pay £500. [ __ ] [ __ ]
These people are so [ __ ] on their greet.
So you want to do that challenge then
greasy try to live off three to5 for a month
a day for a month. Think of how much
Think of how much money you'd save.
You want to try and do it?
try and do it for a month in it.
I've lived off like seven pound a day
when I was saving money. But yeah.
>> So yeah, go to Birmingham Mar Street and
I'll order the Uber.
>> Let me show you when I come to 55 and
take you off.
>> Yeah. Yeah. I'll order you the Uber when
you're at M Street. Yeah.
>> You can't even p
>> I'll order you the Uber when you're at M Street. Yeah.
>> I want to see the evidence, Pete. I'm
not wasting my time in you. What do you
mean the evidence? I'm going to order it
when you're there, you [ __ ] idiot.
>> Show me your bank statement and I'll go.
>> My bank's What the [ __ ] are you talking
about? You're a [ __ ]
>> You got no money. I think you're skint as [ __ ]
>> Yeah, because you're skint yourself.
That's why you're in London.
>> The only one that is skint is you and non legs.
>> The only one skint is you and nonslegs.
You know the only skint one.
>> Show me your bank statement online right now.
>> The only skint one is you and nons
>> and I will make my way to more street. I promise you. you know.
Oh, look. They've already got the food.
Um, Grezy, it's 22 minutes away.
>> So, are you
>> Timmy? The only one that is skint is
you. You know that's why you call people
skint cuz you're skint yourself.
>> All you got to do is show a bank
statement. It's not rocket science.
>> It's cuz you're skint
>> a bank statement. I told you I'd ordered
the Uber to more street. What the [ __ ]
>> Hold on.
Tim, be quiet a second. Be quiet. Be
quiet a second, Tim. You two are going
around in circles. I'm not going around
>> Tim, listen. Wait,
>> Tim, listen for a second.
>> Tim, listen.
>> [ __ ] hear PJ kick him out for a
second. He doesn't He won't [ __ ] up.
>> I said I would order the Uber to where he goes.
>> Tim saying you show me your bank
details. Tim, unless you're going to dox
your new address to PJ, how can PJ order
you an Uber?
>> That's why I said go to Mar Street station.
>> Tim, he's saying you go to a train
station and then he's going to order the Uber.
>> Tim Street is smaller. Mar Street is
smaller than um New Street as well. So,
it's a small train station.
>> I don't know,
>> but it's a smaller to
>> Yeah, Tim. So, go to the train station
and then he's going to order the Uber. It's [ __ ]
>> It's £186.
>> Yeah. So, you two are going around in
circles arguing about the same [ __ ] thing.
>> Yeah, because he won't do it. I've told
him where to go and he won't do it.
That's why I keep kicking him.
>> Where is Tim?
>> Right. Anyway, please. You fighting or not? >> Why
your bank name? All you got
>> Mr. 500 quid in your account and I will
get that Uber.
>> Timothy Mr. No, no, no. PJ, it's very
[ __ ] easy to do. All you got to do is
show a bank balance balance.
>> Just go and fight him.
>> You're using [ __ ] mommy street.
>> You're using mommy's Uber.
>> You're absolute embarrassment.
>> See, he's he's making any excuse.
Tell the truth.
>> He's using any excuse.
>> Anyway, so PJ, right, you came on
talking to yourself. Banger. So Peter
find this evidence of showing £500 in your bank.
>> Grezy, go to the [ __ ] Grezy. Timmy,
go to Mar Street Station and I will
order the Uber. Stop. Stop. I'm not
going around in circles. I'm not going
that you've got money.
>> I'm not going around in circles.
>> PJ, all you got to do is go online, click
>> Show us your [ __ ] balance and I'll be there.
>> Tim, shut Timmy. Timmer, you don't need
to see people's balance. He's just using
excuses. He's just using McDonald's cuz you're skint.
>> Yeah, he's using excuses.
>> No, no, we do know.
>> PJ, don't kick me out the house because
I'm only so right now.
>> Timmy, you're you're saying people are
skinned cuz you're skinned. Do you not
understand? You don't know how much
money people have.
>> You don't know how much money people
have. This is coming from within. You are begging.
>> This is coming from from within, lad.
>> You are skinn. Yes, we know your skins.
>> You listen. If he wasn't skin, he would
come to London today. If he wasn't skin,
he would come to London today.
>> Oh, you are.
>> He would come to London today.
>> No, I'll come to London if you show me a
bank statement, PJ.
>> Oh, for [ __ ] sake. A bank statement.
>> He's not about it, man. Show me the evidence.
>> I'll pay for Timmy to go. If someone
said to me, I'm playing Timmy, you going
to go fight or not? I'd
>> show it. This is tragic.
>> It's not hard. It's not hard.
>> I ordered myself a Chinese curry.
>> Yeah. Is that Is that off mommy's
[ __ ] Uber? Is that mommy's [ __ ]
bank account, PJ?
>> You know,
>> is that off your mom's bank account, Dad?
>> Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Totally.
>> Mommy's paid for that, PJ. >> PJ,
>> I don't know why he wants people to show
him money when he runs away every time
people do. I don't know why he
[ __ ] bullying your mom for that take away.
>> Yeah, I want to see some cash.
>> He's got to bully his He's got to bully
his own mom for a takeaway. [ __ ]
>> have to show Tim.
>> Yeah, go. Okay, let Okay. Show Timmy
money and see if Timmy shows you money
back then. Go on. >> Yeah.
>> PJ, if I said I'm going to pay for your
Uber and you said show a bank statement, I could
>> go on then. Yeah, if he's got all this
money, then he will show it, won't he?
>> Uber. So why can't you show a bank
statement? You did this last time and
you cost me an hour and a half. My [ __ ]
>> Because because the last time I showed
you money, you ran away, knobhead
>> because the last time I showed you
money, I ran you ran away.
>> You can't provide your business because
you haven't got any money.
>> You're a [ __ ] You're a [ __ ]
>> No, you're the [ __ ] cuz you can't
provide the bank Uber. It's
>> so embarrassing. Is it?
>> No, you're embarrassing. You said you're
going to pay for my Uber. I'
>> think I won't play up. I'll wake you up.
>> And you can't even pay for my Uber cuz you're that little nap [ __ ] Uber.
No. You're a virgin. Virgin. Virgin.
>> You are a virgin. Yeah. Just like your
boyfriend on legs. Just like you're both skin.
>> Just like you're both skin.
>> Mommy's account to get food. You would
Who's more skinny?
Who's more Who's more books?
>> Timmy, who's more sk or him? I literally
I can't I I don't know who's more skint.
Maybe it's you.
>> PJ, are you going to provide the evidence?
>> And the only reason you call me a virgin
is cuz you're one yourself. You're the
biggest one going.
>> Press Press one if you've seen Timmy
with a Woman. Press two if you haven't.
>> Press one if you've seen Timmy with a
Woman. Press two if you haven't.
>> I don't believe
>> I don't mind starting. I'll press
[ __ ] two, bro. I ain't seen this [ __ ]
with no woman.
>> But you can't provide the bank balance cuz you're two
two. No one's ever seen you with a woman
because you're a virgin.
>> Pay back your mom.
You're a bra virgin.
>> Are you going to pay back your mom for
this curry today? >> Um, no.
>> So basically, you're a freeloader.
Timmy, why do you keep projecting your
skddness onto me?
>> Why Why are you lying that you look like nons?
>> You're another nonss.
>> No, you're a nons legs, bro. You're the
one who says you want to go and grab
children. No one else is another nons.
You're skin like him. You're a virgin
>> Peter, it's all about the
>> Maybe they're brothers.
>> Grab children.
>> N when you said the [ __ ] you
>> Maybe they're brothers. Maybe they're
>> So anyway, Peter. Anyway,
>> he's just like his boy. He's not
boyfriend. Both skin, both virgins.
Literally going to provide this evidence
that you're going to get a taxi. All you
got to do
>> Yes, I will. When you go to the train
station, I'll order you a taxi. And
look, I'm not going around in circles.
>> Going to send the bus.
>> Listen, I'll see you when you're at M
Street station. I'll see you when you're
at M Street train station. Do a video at
the train station.
Yeah, do a video at the train station.
Greavves. I woke I woke lady up lady up.
That's funny, bro.
That's funny. That's funny. Is it?
That's funny, isn't it? That's [ __ ] funny, bro.
Did Mr. B get involved? Grezy, are you
fighting or what? He will never fight.
He's full of excuses.
He is full of excuses.
He is full of [ __ ] excuses.
Full of excuses.
Isn't that right? Graves H.
All right, Mr. B. What did you say about LT?
What did you say? He's a mad man or something.
What did you say? He's the bad man, isn't it?
That's funny. He said he's a [ __ ] isn't it? >> Um,
>> are you on your way to more street? Right.
I've got a better plan.
>> Are you on your way to more street?
>> I will. Right.
Right. If you are Oh,
>> you on your way to street?
>> I will go into Shirley and you can get
an Uber from Shirley.
>> No. No. See, he's twisting [ __ ] around again.
>> So, you're going to get me one from Wall
Street, but Shirley's even closer and
you can't get me from Shirley.
>> Why? Now he's Now he's twisting [ __ ]
But not Shirley.
>> Now he's twisting [ __ ]
>> No, no, no, no. How about How about
this? I meet you halfway. You get you
get a taxi from North Street, but you
can't get one from
>> How about How about I meet you halfway? That
>> you're lying.
>> How about I meet you halfway? How about
>> You're talking, but you're not moving anywhere.
>> Talking [ __ ]
>> You're talking, but we still don't see
you going anywhere.
>> You're talking, but we don't see you going anywhere.
>> We don't see you going anywhere.
>> We don't see him going anywhere. >> [ __ ]
>> We don't see you going anywhere. See,
look. There we go.
Just talk talk talk talk.
That's enough Tik Tok for today.
The cat went mad, didn't it?
It was rolling, isn't it? Like them
westernized women. Grezy, that's enough
Tik Tok for today.
That's enough. Tik Tok.
You can see the westernity in their
eyes. As that man said, you can see it
in their eyes. The dirty western eyes. Look,
you can see it in their eyes. The eyes
never lie. Like that one you showed me
trying to hit the man Grezy.
I wonder how many men she's led on with
them eyes. Them devious eyes.
them devious eyes. Greasy.
>> Hello, Virgin.
>> I'm going to Shirley now to meet the
lads. And Shirley is cheaper to get to
London than Birmingham. So, if I go
virgin boy by Uber, are you going to I'm
going to prove to you that you've been
owned again in your skins.
>> Hello, virgin boy.
>> No, you're the virgin. You've never been killed.
>> Yeah, I'm the virgin. Anyways, are you
going to be every person on this? You
wouldn't even know how to get up
someone's vagina, lads. Anyway.
>> Yeah. Okay. Are you going to Mar you this Uber?
>> Okay. So, you've had sex. Okay.
>> Wait. You always know when Timmy's done
his balls in there yet because you start
self projecting. He's skinless and his
virginity. This is how you know he's
done his balls in. This is how we know
you've done your balls in.
Okay. Let me ask you this question. When
I showed you, 1300 last year, why didn't
you show anything back? Huh?
So is it every woman's eyes you see the
westernity then greavvesy?
Is it every woman in this country the eyes
proper proper wester that westernized look?
Cuz when I watch like vintage porn, you
don't see it. It [ __ ] is every
woman's eyes. Greasy. Every woman's
eyes. You can see the westernity in it.
Of course it is.
Of course it is, bro. You don't see it
in vintage porn back when there was no
Tik Tok or anything.
I I've seen it in all of their eyes.
Oh yeah. May Yeah, I was just about to
say that though to be fair. Yeah. Yeah.
Maybe older women don't. Yeah. Yeah.
Maybe. Baby. Yep. Yeah, that is true.
Oh, you know what? I was just about to
say that to be honest. Maybe if
someone's in their 40s or 50s. Yeah, but
people our age, they've all got it in is
the eyes. The eyes never lie, Greavesy.
The eyes never lie.
>> And why do you keep kicking me out the
gaps? You big baby.
>> You are baby. I said Charlie, which I
will within the next hour. Right. Oh,
>> and I guarantee you you won't pay for
the taxi because you are skint.
>> You're giving me a headache.
>> You know, you probably like, "Oh, mommy,
I put all my money in laps. I can't
cope. Can you buy me a co? I've got a
shaft and a bunch of spastics on YouTube."
>> This guy so disabled.
Why did my bow? I said I would pay for
his taxi. I said I would pay for his
Uber£500 return. And he won't he won't do it.
>> He won't do it. I believe how I mean no
wonder your sister hates you. You're
taking all this away off the [ __ ] family.
>> Yeah. Yeah. I said I pay for his return
Uber which been about4 to500 and he
won't he won't do it.
>> You're so selfish that your your
sister's got a family.
>> He will never meet anyone. He will never
>> So you can get a takeaway.
>> He will never meet anyone.
>> PJ, I will beat you. Trust me. I am
coming mates. I will
Yeah. Yeah. PJ, it will happen.
>> Taylor, he took you by surprise and you
shhat your pants.
>> Yeah. Yeah. Well, why don't you and him
both meet me? Why don't you both meet
me? Why don't you both meet you and then?
>> We all know that you are a lefty [ __ ]
>> Yeah. Why don't you both meet Why don't
you both meet me? You
>> are you going to pay for this taxi?
>> Yes. When you go to Birmingham Street, I
will pay for your taxi. Yes.
>> When you go to Birmingham Street second
time, sunshine. So, I'm actually
generally going to Shirley for a drink.
That's actually actually a real fact.
>> What the [ __ ] are you talking about?
>> Taxi from Shirley to London.
>> Okay, whatever. Okay. Well, show me the journey.
>> Okay, then go to Shirley and I'll order
the Uber. You show me where you are.
>> Have you got £530? Yes or no? Simple.
>> I've got more than that. Yes.
>> No, no, no, no. You've got more than £530. >> Yes.
>> You do talk shite, don't you?
>> You don't know how much money I have.
You don't know me, Timmy. Just because
you don't have any money.
>> Mommy is buying the take away.
>> Timmy, just because you don't have any
money. Just like nonslegs don't have no
money. It doesn't go for the rest of us.
>> On your mom for a takeaway.
>> Just because you and Nonss don't have
money. It doesn't go for the rest of us.
Just like you are both a virgin. It
doesn't go for the rest of us.
>> Afternoon. Your
>> you and Nle seems to think we have your
virgin skin life. And you're laughing
cuz you know I'm correct.
>> You know, mommy's boy to take away. I've
got the evidence. sister just told me
that you rely on yeah
>> you've got the password to mommy's Uber,
haven't you, Peter?
>> Yeah, yeah, yeah.
>> The family are not very happy that
you're taking all the pip inheritance away.
>> Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah. Just let
me know when you're at M Street.
>> No, no, no, no, no. I will let you know
because I know you haven't got the
money. I know you haven't got 550 quid
to get me there back. I can actually put
>> Okay. Yep. Okay. Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
>> So, you haven't got 550 quid.
>> Yep. Yep. Yep. Okay.
>> I know that. Okay. Yep. Yep. You know
everything. You know how much money
people have. You know everything.
>> Yep. Yep. Yep. Yep. Yep.
>> Are you going to meet him or not?
>> Banger. You [ __ ] bullshitt.
>> He's offered to pay your taxi. Stop
coming up with excuses. You're not a
He's offered to pay your taxi. Show off
the goodbye. YOU [ __ ] SPARK NO
FRIENDS. No [ __ ]
go to spoon by yourself. You've got
nothing in life. Now jump on ginger
pubes. No one's interesting your
[ __ ] Go and take your fake news and
your fake drama elsewhere.
>> Who Who's the root cause of this today?
Greasy. It's Timmy, isn't it? Tiby's the
root cause, isn't it?
>> I am on my way to Shirley. Okay.
>> From there.
>> Okay. We'll see. Yeah. Okay. Okay. Yeah.
And let us know where you are as well so
I can order the Uber. Who's the root
cause of this?
Oh, my curry will be here in 2 minutes. Lovely.
So, how comes there's no westernity?
Look at my eyes then, Greavvesy. Is it
because I don't watch Tik Tok?
My eyes just are just green eyes.
How comes there's no westernity in my eyes then?
There's no westernity in my eyes.
They're just normal.
Just greeny brown.
Oh, you sent me an email.
You know what I think is weird? Yeah, no
offense. That LJ's got people
WhatsAppapping him about Timmy. I think
that is [ __ ] weird.
I agree. I don't know about you, but to
me that's weird. Yeah. You got this good
vibes WhatsAppapping people about
[ __ ] Timmy. They actually WhatsApp
people about that YouTube.
You sent me an email. I don't know, bro.
That's weird to me.
You didn't send me an email, lad.
I got an email from Steven Howard.
One second, bro.
Oh, I've seen it now. Yeah, this one
come the other day.
Yeah. Yeah, you sent me an email the
other. It goes into spam. When you email
me, it goes in spam.
Oh, there we go. Hurry.
This is how I get my vitamins. Where is he?
I ordered this place before.
Got my curry here.
>> Oh gosh.
Easy. They were mocking you,
laughing at you.
Yeah, it's all right.
There you go.
I got some rice to have it with.
Then I've got some rice. It looks a bit watery, but
that's what happens when you order it.
The rice is nice, though. I can smell that. Yeah. Oh gosh.
>> All right, bro. Yeah, [ __ ]
see how I'm getting my vitamins.
But apparently I'm skinn.
You can't beat a nice Chinese curry with
mushrooms and onion.
Oh. Oh, I should have put the [ __ ]
rice in first. That's what you're
supposed to do.
Do you know what I don't get about these
Indian places, Greavves? Yeah. They'll
give you a lot of curry. Yeah. And then
they're so stingy with the rice. Like
the rice is always smaller than the
curry, you know, like in the container.
And you would think, what the [ __ ] Rice
is like the cheapest thing to make. And they
um they're so stingy with the rice.
This doesn't really make any sense. Mhm.
This is nice. That gym. M coming H M.
It tastes so different.
I'll give you a link in a minute. I'm eating.
Why do you need a link? You should be on
your way to mall street.
You should be on his way to more street.
You should be connected from You should
be going to more street. More street.
Isn't that right?
H probably nice.
Oh, sorry about that, lad.
I was just eating. See? Hey, Grezy.
Stig not Peter Belly's mama.
Stig not Peter Belly's mom. Mama. Is
that right? Is that right?
Signal Peter Belly's mama.
It's never your mama.
Remember, Grezy Sig was never your mama.
Just a forgettable one night stand.
Oh, that account that used to come on
and egg me on Grezy,
she wanted to keep it a secret. Remember Grey,
that curry was lovely. Oh gosh,
that was a lovely curry.
That was bloody lovely.
>> Right. Right. Are you on your way to
street? Why can't you show me 550 quid?
Cuz the fight will happen if you can
provide to me the evidence that you got
the money for the taxi. I'm not on your
way to more street over a bunch of
spazdics who are on your way to street
game donating money when he ran away
from a 21y old.
>> Are you on your way?
>> The evidence where bangers shatters his
pants. Are you on your way to master? The
>> deal Chicago summers. I'll delete my >> Chicago.
Banger is a big Chicago summer. >> Right.
>> What's his name? What is it? Chicago Summers.
>> Let's be honest here. I think Banger has
been owned more than anyone on here.
I've been by a 29y old. Anyway, the point, right?
>> Chicago, are you going to provide this
evidence, Vang? I want to fight PJ and I
want to FIGHT YOU.
>> STOP BRINGING ME UP FRONT.
When you're arguing with him,
>> you're [ __ ] pathetic. You're not going nowhere.
>> You [ __ ] tragic. Get off YouTube. Get
off Grinder. Get off Guys.
>> I'm just going to I'm just going to move
my my bangers battles.
>> Chicago Summers.
>> So So why did you get owned by a 21-y old banger?
>> Delete your Tesco's at banger. You're finished.
>> Chicago Summers.
Tilly, you're Tesco's at Bang.
>> I think you homage on here. The biggest
L in 12 years.
>> PJ, you're second, right? >> Timmy.
>> Timmy, what's what's his name?
>> Cuz I am going for a drinking me. Will
talk. I'm not. No, but what's his name?
What's his name?
>> Can prove to me you've got 550 G. You
did this last time, Peter, and you let
>> Timmy I showed you£1,300 before you ran away.
>> I've got the evidence on that, Peter. Someone
>> mate for [ __ ] sake. M
>> if you're gonna pay my taxes, I will
100% go because I know you got money.
>> Listen listen. PJ's already told you if
you want to get an Uber to London, he
will pay for it.
>> But he won't pay for it.
>> I will pay for it 100%. I will. I swear
to God. He told you I will pay for it, bro.
>> Come on, Smokey. I will pay for it.
Hasn't got a
>> It's 180 each way. Timmy, you don't know
how much money I have. KJ doesn't have a
lot of money probably. Fair enough. But
he has more money than you.
>> Yeah, exactly. Exactly. Timmy, you don't
know how much money I have.
>> Listen, Tim, if you if you go to London
today and I'll pay Listen and there'll
be no taxi.
>> Listen, if you go to London today, I'll
PayPal you 500 quid.
>> Taxi. Now, if you like the taxi, Smokey,
I know you've got money. I will
>> Timmy, but you don't know. Hey, listen.
Oh, for [ __ ] sake. I've just told you
if if you go to London today, I'll pay.
I'll give you 500 quid.
>> You never ordered it. >> Yeah.
>> If you had money, PJ, and you weren't
full of [ __ ] I'd take your
>> Timmy. I've got more money than you.
[ __ ] sake. It's embarrassing.
>> You're broke as [ __ ] You couldn't even
>> Oh, Timmy, you don't know what I have.
You don't know anything.
>> Show 20 [ __ ] pounds last night, Peter.
>> I showed you £1,300 last year and you
didn't show nothing back.
>> I will 100% go and you know I will.
>> Right. Okay, fair enough. You got 70
quid, that'll get
>> If you've got 70 quid, that'll get you halfway.
>> Who's full of [ __ ]
>> 70 quid will get you halfway. If you go to London,
for God's sake, got money cuz you're not
trolling me a second.
>> 70 would get you there and back with a train, bro.
>> Exactly. You dare back.
>> Yeah. If he goes to London, I'll pay him
500 quid and he can go back on the >> FBS.
Okay, then I'm going to be on my way to
Shirley, have a couple of points, and
we'll go from there,
>> right? Get to London then.
>> And then he left. He left.
>> What's the point?
>> [ __ ] He's just
>> I said I I would pay for his Uber, bro.
He doesn't know how much money I have.
He doesn't He really doesn't. This is
what I mean. Huh?
>> I mean, he Well, you can't trust the
word of someone who's He's got his TV in
pawn, his phone's in pawn, his [ __ ]
life's in pawn. He's He's got no money.
>> That's why he's saying that I'm scared.
I said to him, I'll pay for the Uber. I
was serious. I was serious.
>> James [ __ ] broke as a joke.
>> I was serious.
>> You know,
did Smokey B get involved, Greavvesy?
Did Smokey be get himself involved? Greavvesy.
Did Smokey be get involved, Grezy?
soon to be soon to be Retar.
How can How can Ret the Bear be
president of this country? I don't think
it makes sense. He's not even real.
How can it be R the Bear? How exactly?
He's a [ __ ] salt. He's a projector in it.
There you go. Smokey be just said he'd
give you £500.
He just said he'd give you £500.
Do you know what? Yeah. I'm Bro, give me
[ __ ] £500. I'll [ __ ] go.
Simple as that. You give me £500, I'll [ __ ] go.
How about that one, Greasy?
You give someone gives me [ __ ] £500,
I'll [ __ ] go. Yeah, you know.
But no, let him do it. Let him do it.
Let him do it because he's he's the one
that said he was going to come. But if
he doesn't come and you want to give me
£500, I'll [ __ ] do it.
I'll 100% do it.
Sorry about that, matey.
Yeah, it will cost me about the whole
day. It will probably cost about 100.
There you go. I made £400 in a day. Simple. Yeah.
Yeah. 70 to Birming from Birmingham
about it probably cost you about 4050.
Even if you booked it now, it's not it's
not expensive to go to Birmingham and
back. They're all random prices. It's always cheap.
It's cheap to go to Birmingham. But
Manchester, you know, if you go
Manchester and back, it's always the
same price. £67 there and back. It
doesn't matter how advanced you b how
long advance you bought you you you
booked it. It's always the same price.
Manchester, but Birmingham's a lot cheaper.
Birmingham's always been cheap to get to.
Let me look it up.
I can actually look up the prices if you want, we
[ __ ] hell, bro.
70 70 quid his name. Yeah. All right.
All right. He called Chico Summers. Chicago Summers.
Chicago Summers. Grezy. Oh man.
And he calls London Houston. London
Houston, one second. Let me look up
these um trains. Yeah.
So it's only £15 each way.
So you don't have any excuse.
He doesn't really have any excuse, does he?
Do you remember Greavves? I love you all.
You remember that when I went out the
house that day and I was like, I love you all.
And that account that account used to
come in and copy me in it. I love you all.
I love a lot of you. I love you all.
That's what I'll [ __ ] do. I'll call
out Bonnie. Whatever. Listen, if you
give me £500, um, Smokey, I'll do it.
I'll give it a whirl.
Give it a little try. I'll do if you
give me £500.
You know where I live as well, so I
mean, it's not like I'd scam you or anything
cuz this guy's been winding me up. He's
been [ __ ] winding me up, bro, with
his videos. Yeah.
Okay with you, boss.
Yeah. You give me You give me £500,
mate. I'll do it.
Come on. Set, bro.
How about you give me half
and half when I get and half when I do
it? That sounds fair. You know, that's a fair offer.
And when I'm on my way to Birmingham,
um, Reevesy, will RJ see it? Do you
think Money Man will see it? Will they
all be on my channel like a butterfly on [ __ ] I've [ __ ]
What do you think, Greasy? Do you reckon
I'll be there?
Yeah, they would be.
He's not meeting anyone, mate.
He was supposed to come to London today
in the car. Then he said, "Do you want
me to come today, tomorrow, or
Thursday?" I said, "Today." Then there
was another excuse. "Oh, if I drove, I'd
come." Then I said, "Okay."
Uh, then I said, "Oh, okay." I said, "Okay.
Um, I'll pay for your Uber." Another excuse.
[ __ ] me. Absolutely [ __ ] me, bro.
Another excuse. She's not meeting Oak
[ __ ] bro. Anyone that's really going to
meet someone, he would he would have
been here today. He would have been here
today, bro. Trust me, he would have been here today.
Or he would be going to Mar Street. He's
doing anything but meeting. He's
talking, but he's not meeting anyone.
He's doing anything but meeting anyone, isn't he?
[ __ ] me, bro. [ __ ] me.
70. [ __ ] hell.
He lies so much [ __ ] He lies. He said,
"Oh, he he he he's got a comfortable
little nest, Mr. B." He said he's got a comfortable nest.
like money and that does he [ __ ]
said he's got a comfortable nest and he
has other people look after his money
does he [ __ ]
does he [ __ ] bro
he does this every time bro show us
money show us money you show him money
he runs away and doesn't show you
anything same [ __ ] bro they want you to
show what they wish they Yeah, quiet.
Yeah, I'm saying.
What does Monty man say about this community? Greavvesy.
>> if he keep if he keeps mentioning me on
these videos. Yeah,
that was nice.
That was lovely.
Nice coffee. Nice coke. Yeah.
>> Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
>> Yeah. He's run off, bro. He's not
coming, is he?
>> Are Are you going to go to him?
>> If you If you g If you gave me half the
money, I would. Yeah. Listen, I'll give
you if you show me your own way, I'll
I'll PayPal you 100 quid and
>> Come on, man. Seriously,
>> I got to go all the way to I will go. I
will 100% go. If you if you give half, I
will go. I will go.
>> You just looked it up. It cost less than that. Cost
>> Yeah, but obviously I want to Yeah, of
course. Of course.
>> Yeah, of course. But I want I want more.
Like I want to know that it's been worth
my time, bro, because I know exactly
what's going to happen. Yeah, [ __ ] listen.
>> I said to you, if you show me your own
way, I'll send you 100 quid. Then if you
meet him, I'll send you the rest. I'll
send you 400 quid.
>> Okay? And what if he doesn't Okay. What
if he doesn't show up?
>> Then that's on him. And then I'll send
you another 100 quid then just for your
troubles. You've got 200 quid. It cost
you like less than half of that for the whole trip.
>> Yeah, but that's Yeah, but that's not
that's not worth it.
>> Well, [ __ ] me. You're the one calling
them out then. It's up to you. Yeah, cuz
money. No, no, no. Cuz you No, cuz you
said to him that you'd give him 500,000
if he comes there. Yeah. >> Yeah.
>> I'll do it. I'll do it.
>> I said I said that to Tim cuz I know for
will not [ __ ] leave Birmingham. That
is just the end beyond end all. He's not leaving Birmingham.
>> And I told him I would pay I told him
I'd pay I tell him I'd pay the Uber,
bro. I would I would actually pay it.
>> Yeah, I know you would probably to be
fair. Like I said to him, I said, "You
don't have that much more money than
[ __ ] the average Joe on the street,
but you've got more money than him." And
you would pay that if he was going to come,
>> bro. He doesn't even He doesn't even
have a £100, bro. Imagine that.
>> He's got 70 quid, his name, he doesn't
want to spend [ __ ] 50 quid get.
>> I was chilling yesterday. Yeah. Do you
know what annoys me about this guy? I
was chilling yesterday. I was watching
his video like cuz he talks about
gambling. I think it's interesting. He's
the only one I'm sub to, in it. Yeah.
So, okay, I'll click on it. And he's
mentioning me, bro. What the [ __ ] I
didn't mention him. I didn't do no
videos. And he's my name up.
>> Since Since Lur J won his football bet,
Tim has been on it. He's been triggered
as [ __ ] He just doesn't like to see
anybody win or anybody get subs or
anyone get any views or anything like
this because Timmy cannot handle YouTube.
>> Yeah, it does it doesn't it doesn't
bother me. I don't I don't care if
someone's won. I don't care if someone's
lost. You know what I'm saying, bro? I
don't know why he reacts like that. I
don't know why he does, but it's weird to me.
>> You do whatever you do. just [ __ ]
repeat every day and rage on everything.
>> Yeah, but I don't get I don't get
triggered. I don't get triggered if
someone's [ __ ] got money. Do you get me?
>> Well, I know that's cuz you're just
[ __ ] used to losing. But
>> it's like Timmy expects to win when he
goes to [ __ ] hit the fies and hit the barrel.
>> I mean I mean I mean I mean I I mean I
expect to win to be fair.
>> Yeah, you can't expect to win when you
spend 20 quid. Timmy does his
>> Yeah, but I put I Bro, I lost I've lost
like a couple hundred the past month.
>> Yeah. What? In one sitting. How much
have you What's the most you lost in one single session
>> online? Was two grand? That was once. >> When?
>> Uh maybe two years ago.
>> Yeah, that's what I'm saying. Two years
ago. I've lost two grand the last few weekends.
>> And it's like No, but no, recently I've
lost like maybe 300, 400 maybe like last
month. I don't know. Yeah, but unless
you're spending like a couple hundred
quid in a session, you can't even call
it gambling really, can you?
>> Not really. No, not that's what I'm
saying. If you do£10 a week on the
football, you can't really call that
gambling. That's what I said.
>> Exactly. So that's why that's why Banger
just sticks to doing that. Then he has
to go on the clubs if he wins and he got
lucky and he won 800 quid and 10 to
listen listen. To be fair, to be fair
though, the odds on the football has
gotten worse. It's it's so [ __ ] They're
so [ __ ] It's [ __ ] now. Yeah, but if you
if you play in any of the bookies, it's
like they've taxed them harder, so
they're obviously going to pass it on to
you. So, you're [ __ ]
>> You put 150 on two teams, you're only
getting 350 back now. That's [ __ ] Like,
both teams have scored. That's bad.
>> Well, I mean, you you before you put 150
quid on, you know how much you're
getting back. So, it's up to you. So,
>> unless it's like four something to five,
it's what? Yeah, that's what I'm saying.
It's pointless, isn't it really? But
regardless, the thing is Timmy goes and
does his absolute boss on spends 300
quid on a 100 pound jackpot on 25
>> spins. No, but seriously, have you noticed
>> But have you noticed it's been about the
past six months the odds have got worse.
Is it me or they have? They have it.
>> I don't play I don't play fog and [ __ ]
like that to be honest.
>> No, it's defin It definitely has though.
It definitely definitely has.
>> Well, but anyways, you're getting off
[ __ ] topic here. The thing is
>> Timmy is not coming to London. He's
trying to call you out to Birmingham the
same way you try to call everybody out
to London because you don't want to
leave London. He doesn't want to leave Birmingham.
>> Yeah, but neither.
>> But I've met people though. But I have
met people though. He has He's been
doing for years. He's been doing this
>> When you sort of have you when was the
last time you left London to go and meet someone?
>> Bro, I've been all over the country
partly because of YouTube. Well, when
was the last time you went left London
to go to meet someone?
>> You um
>> I gave up ages ago. Yeah, I know. Ages
>> saying. That's what I'm trying to say.
If one of you has the balls then to go
and meet the other person, I'll [ __ ]
sweeten the day.
>> Yeah, but you're you're going on like
I've never have met tried to meet people
before, but he hasn't. That's what I'm
trying to say. He he the only time he
shows up yet is if he's got backup. And
that's one in a blue moon, bro. No,
[ __ ] Tiger Dave so much back up.
>> Yeah, but still No, but what I'm trying
to say is that Yeah, but No, but what
I'm trying to say is he got Tiger Yeah.
to to fight these battles. Technically,
that's still what he done. Even though
he's he's he's little and he's he's a
[ __ ] and that he I never had a You
don't understand. I've never had a
problem with Tiger. I never argued with Tiger ever.
>> Tiger stuck your head in the [ __ ] mattress.
>> Yeah, bro. I slipped. But I don't care
anyways. It's not the point. It's not
the point anyway.
Yeah. So, the point is he tries to get
like other people to do his because like
I said to you before, bro, I've never
argued with um Tiger ever.
>> So, how's he all of a sudden got a
problem with people, you know what I mean?
>> Look at the runaround that Tim had
whenever [ __ ] Monty moved to
Birmingham. That just shows you the
caliber of a man. It's like he was running around.
>> They were they were going back and forth
for like they were going back and forth
for like two weeks before they met.
>> Exactly. Not a single one of them could
meet and they were about 15 minutes
apart from each other the whole time.
>> I know. I had to stop watching it. It
was annoying me to be honest. It was
annoying to be honest. That's why I
stopped watching it. They would just
kept going around in circles and it
Oh, he left.
Yeah, he left. Bro,
[ __ ] hell, bro.
Has anyone else noticed? Yeah. that that
the football bet the odds have gotten worse.
Yeah, it's gotten worse, isn't it? It
has gotten worse.
Yeah, it has. It has gotten worse. Come on.
Is he uploading anymore now?
Has he uploaded anymore? Nah.
The channel's gone quiet now. Greasy,
that's enough. Tik Tok for today. Oh,
that's enough Tik Tok for today.
I love that. That's like one of my favorite memes.
I want to watch it again.
enough Tik Tok for today. Yeah.
Yeah. I've done it a lot of times, bro.
I've done it a lot of times.
Do you remember Grezy? P stuck in his
ways. Remember Greavesy Pete stuck in his ways. Oh,
Well, I'll put the link back up.
Yeah, he said be realistic. Do you
remember why he Do you remember why
Triple H said be realistic, Grezy?
Why did he say? What did I What did I
tell him to do?
What What did I tell him to do, bro?
What did I What did I tell him to do?
Do you remember?
I said, "Oh, you live?" Yeah. He said
that he lives near Newcastle, in it. So
I said, "Do you want would you go on a
session with Anand Deck?"
He said, "Uh, be realistic."
Why is it not realistic?
You go on a like on a night out.
No more Tik Tok for today.
Oh, I love that. It's cute, isn't it?
What animal is it, Grezy?
What does that What does that animal
remind you of?
Oh, I love that little cat. Grezy,
if if if the phone didn't get snatched
from the um cat grievy, how how many
more hours would have it been on there for?
How many more hours if the phone didn't get took crazy
how how long
how long would have the cat been on
there for on the phone? Bless it.
No, it's funny, bro.
Yeah. Go for a night out with Alan Neck.
He said, "Be realistic, P. Be realistic,
Funny, bro. That is funny. [ __ ]
Are you waiting for Timmy to go live? Greasy. Oh [ __ ]
Munt is heavily disabled and has no life
experience. Has never been in a
relationship at 28.
Yeah, man. You keep telling yourself
that. If it makes you feel better, D lad.
Just like I'm skin. Just like I'm a
virgin. Oh, bless you.
You keep telling yourself that
be and Smokey B is going to work together.
No, Smokey B.
No, Greasy. How long was the cat going
to be on the phone for if it wasn't took off it? How long?
Like another hour or what? That's enough
Tik Tok for today. That's my favorite.
Okay. And but what about when it Yeah,
but what about when it wakes up in the morning? Grezy?
That's enough Tik Tok for today. No.
So, what about when it first wake up?
Would it eat Greavesy or what?
Oh, there was this Harry Potter meme
where um that uh Dobby got kicked down
the stairs. Greavvesy. Poor Dobby.
He got kicked. Yeah. Bless
enough Tik Tok for today.
Stay on Tik Tok.
He might be on his way to London now.
Smokey be greasy. He might be on the
train to London now, lads.
Yeah, he might be on his way to London now. Yep. Oh gosh.
Oh gosh. Yeah.
I can't stand that Northern Irish
accent. Can you, Grezy? There was
someone on the chase the other day. He's
from Northern Ireland. It grinds on you.
It grinds on you, mate. You know when L
J when I when I first discovered LJ J I
couldn't understand him for about two weeks.
I needed like subtitles.
I needed subtitles, bro. And there was
there was no subtitles to be seen. I
could understand the [ __ ] when I first discovered.
Nah, bro. I could understand pattern
that but not not bro. What the [ __ ]
Yeah. What do you think of that, Grezy?
They're on the same website. Yeah. Ian Bill.
What do you mean Ian Bill? What happened to him?
He died in East Enders.
Didn't he die a long time ago?
He died a long time ago, didn't he? On
in East Enders.
Nope. It's not as strong as L J's. [ __ ] hell.
Do you remember when he was crying? He's
like, I've got nothing left.
Do you remember that scene? Greavvesy.
I've got nothing left.
Bless you, Ian.
You know what you should do, Greavves?
Go on a session with um Dickinson. David
Dickinson. That make a good video. It grieves.
You and Dickinson going on on on the drink.
No, I [ __ ] don't.
Do you remember what Monty man said
about Pat's kids? He said, "I'm going to
let you join in." Do you remember
Greavves? He said, "I'm going to let you join in.
I'm going to make you watch and join in." Mad.
No, he didn't die.
No, he's not dead. You're probably
watching some AI [ __ ]
Yeah, he was a nons to be fair. Yeah,
Harry Potter and Tim Al's on the same
website. Grieves. There was a there was
like a video of Harry Potter. Yeah. When
he was like nine like they were doing
like the cast behind the scenes and it
was it was killing me like the
thumbnail. It was killing me the
thumbnail. Greavves. The same website
you can watch Money Man on. No way.
No [ __ ] way. No way.
Do you want to go for a drink or do you
want to do it dirty?
Oh, [ __ ] hell, man.
>> All right there, Peter. My lid.
>> See you later, lad. You get kicked.
You get kicked for that, lad. That's
what I'm saying. See you later, lad.
We want Timmy on here.
Smokey B, what's the What's the What's
the most you've ever won from gambling?
Me. Four grand.
No, I don't want your win, V, lad. We
know what Timmy is. We know what Timmy
does. We know he's a [ __ ] house. You
don't need to give me any wins, matey.
Yeah. Me for a grand lad.
It's most I've ever won.
The most I've ever won was four grand at
a time. I'm saying at a time.
Please don't tell me you gave it all
back on the same trip.
Don't tell me you gave it all back on
the same trip. [ __ ] hell.
What would you even do though if you won
16 grand on the first night? Probably
you'd probably do something like gamble
like two grand of it in it I guess
and then just do other stuff I'm
guessing. What would you actually do if
you won that money on the first night?
Yeah, probably gamble like two.
Imagine that. Coming back a winner. You
can't you wouldn't be able to Yeah.
Coming you don't want to come back a loser, man.
[ __ ] that. I don't know what you would
do. What would you do? Imagine you went
to Vegas. Yeah. For for for 10 days.
Yeah. And you gambled and you won 20 grand.
And you won 20 grand like the first
night. Like what would you actually do?
Cuz you're in you're there in it. So
you're you're in a gambling place. Maybe
gamble like five grand and take 15,
something like that. I I don't know,
bro. Cuz you wouldn't you wouldn't want
to lose all of it, is it?
It's a hard one, is it, Greasy?
Yeah. Most I've ever won was four uh four grand.
Four grand, me. But I used to win f I
used to win like a thousand every week
when I used to go to Empire. I used to
go hippo drive on Thursdays. I used to
win. I used to win every week when I
used to go Thursdays. I used to go to W
Street, Smokeoky B,
W Street Casino, O'Neals. So yeah.
Yeah, I used to win on I used to go out Thursdays.
I used to drink on Thursdays. So yeah,
going to do a nice football bet on
Saturday. I'm really going to study the
teams. I really want to try and win some money, bro.
I've got money. I've got enough money
and [ __ ] but you know
still it' be nice.
See me, bro. If I'm gambling, I want to
win like life-changing money. I don't
know if it's just me, but I'd want to
win like or or or win enough money to
like that will last me at least 6 months.
You get me?
just win a nice amount of money to last
you like six months.
Do you get what I'm saying?
Yeah, I used to love roulette as well.
Maybe like if I could win like 30 grand.
I was having this conversation with
Ant-Man. He said, "Oh, but if you win
it, you'd give it back." I'd be like,
"Nah, nah, no, no, no." What I would do
is I would spend if I were like a big
amount, I'd probably give half of it
back and the other half well over time.
Like I wouldn't like if I was to give it
back, it would be over a period of time.
It wouldn't be like you won and then you
just giving it back. It would be over a
period of time.
Trust me. Trust me. I wouldn't give it back.
If you want like 60 grand, 50, 60 grand,
you're not going to give it back, are you?
You get me, bro. So, yeah. Oh, [ __ ]
It's hard though. It's hard to [ __ ] I
was looking up the odds for a double
both teams to score Saturday. 340 from
150. I'm not doing that.
Hardly anything back, isn't it?
Hardly anything back.
It's not worth it.
What do you mean? Like move to another country? Yeah.
What do you mean by leave the UK? You
mean like move to another country?
That's what you mean, ain't it,
mate? If I want if I want like 50 grand,
I'd start my own business. I don't think
I'd even buy designer clothes. I already
got some. I think I would just start a
business and just start traveling
and go into restaurants and [ __ ] That's
what I would do if I won.
That's what I would do. Yeah,
that's what I would do. I would travel.
I would travel and live life and try to
start some kind of business.
I wouldn't buy designer stuff. I've got
designer stuff and I wouldn't I just
wouldn't do it anymore. So,
not until I come back. Maybe if I came
back after traveling, I would. But I
wouldn't I wouldn't buy. Do you know
what I don't understand though? Tri
Timmy just like dresses like a [ __ ]
This is what I don't understand with
him. Yeah, you don't need designer
clothes. I mean, I've got Ammani jeans
and vapors cuz I like them and I just
like save money to get like I like them
jeans. I like trainers. But bro, you can
you can you can wear cheap stuff and
still look good.
No, like you actually could. All you
would need is like a decent pair of
trainers and that's it. You don't need anything designer.
You don't need anything designer at all.
He dresses like a [ __ ] [ __ ]
There's other people as well, like you
see some people on YouTube, you know,
they've got money in that and they'd
still rather dress like a [ __ ] Doesn't make sense.
And they've got they've got money as well. Easy, bro.
You could get jeans from somewhere like
Jack and Jones. You get plain Levi
t-shirts. They're dirt cheap. get like
two for 25.
Yeah, I prefer decent clothes as well.
But I'm saying I'm saying to you is is
you can you can you can you can wear
decent clothes and they don't have to be the best.
Do you get what I'm saying? Like, okay,
I'll give I'll give you an example,
right? So, you can get these two Levi
t-shirts for about 17 to 20 and they're
two pack. They're plain, but they're
Levi. Yeah. But they're good. It's good
quality. Yeah. Um, and you can buy 4050
pound jeans and a nice pair of trainers.
You That's good enough, bro. That's good
enough. If you wanted to be like awkward
about, if you wanted to be difficult
about it, that's good enough. No,
I like All Saints. I like All Saints t-shirts.
I like All Saints t-shirts. I like Ammani jeans. Um,
you know, I've only got about, you know,
I've only got about four pairs of socks.
I don't like socks.
I've got about four. No, I think I've
got more now. Maybe I got like 15, but
there was a time I had four pairs of
socks. I hate socks, so I never bought them.
Yeah, Fred Perry's all right as well.
Yeah, I've had a Fred Perry t-shirt, not a polo.
But yeah, if I what I'm saying is if I
want life changing amount of money, I
would just go traveling with like five,
six pairs of clothes. Simple. I wouldn't
be buying like mad designer [ __ ] until
maybe I come back or something. I
wouldn't, bro. I wouldn't.
Even if I won, like I would I wouldn't
do it, bro. I'd do other stuff with it.
There you go. That's what I'm saying.
Yeah, boss. That's what I'm trying to
say. Boss Levi,
my Marley jeans, Smokeoky B, cost me
£200. My jeans cost me £210. That's £400
quid right there.
That's £400. Over £400 just on two things. But um
but no, if I won money, like say it was
like May or something. Yeah. Buy two
Levi T-shirts, shorts, couple of things.
I'll just go traveling, bro.
I I'll just go traveling and I wouldn't
give a [ __ ]
There's some people out there that don't
have never worn designer clothes.
I like Amomani jeans, bro. They used to
be like 130. I [ __ ] paid 200 quid for them. You know?
Yeah, exactly, bro. Yeah, I know. I
would just buy them Levi T-shirts,
couple of packs, buy some shorts, bro.
I've got Amazon shorts that cost me
about £10. Last for ages. A couple of
basketball shorts. I don't give a [ __ ]
about designer stuff, bro. If I was
traveling in the summer, not at all.
I've had designer stuff. I've still got
I've got a Ralph Lauren jumper in my
wardrobe. Cost me £200.
I got stony [ __ ] I got I got Reese
clothes. Reese clothes are nice in the
summer as well. Reese clothes [ __ ]
expensive, bro. I spent about £400.
I spent about400 pound.
That was like two summers ago. I bought white vapors.
Yeah, man. White vapor and [ __ ]
I had black vapor, white vapor. Jeez.
I used to have money coming out my
[ __ ] ass, matey. Yeah, I don't care
anyways, bro. I've still got money and
[ __ ] but I'm just saying, bro. Like,
I think that's everyone in life, in it.
You've had more money than you have
before and that.
Yeah, I might go to Reese in the summer, actually.
Buy some more clothes.
So yeah, there's no reason to dress like
a [ __ ] you know.
No, when you get to a certain age or
even some people that are younger, you'd
rather the experience than like the than
the clothes, if that makes sense.
Yes, but then I don't get time then,
Smokey B. Then I lose my time.
Then I lose my time, bro.
You get me? Then I don't have no time
to go [ __ ] to [ __ ] around or if I want
to be lazy.
Do you get me, bro?
Well, I'm I'm going to stop be going out
from next month. I chilled in F. Well, I
went out once this month. Um because
I always spend a month well every year I
spend a month or two saving money and
then I'll just go out again. I'll be
going out from March so I'll be busy.
Got this person to meet as well. I've
got stuff to do. So I just Yeah, just I
don't know. March I'll be going out
probably every week to be fair.
Maybe not every I don't know. I don't
know what I'm doing. Yeah. Okay.
If you if you want if you want 200
grand, would you quit work?
Yeah. But come on, bro. Like even if
you're doing nothing with your life, like
you'd still prefer not to work in it.
Yeah, she is. Yeah, but be honest, bro.
If you if you didn't have to work, you
wouldn't. And it cuz think about it. I
know I know what you're saying. I know.
Listen to me. I know what you're saying.
Yeah. When you're saying about like if
you're doing nothing anyways. No. No. I
get it. I understand what you're saying.
But I'm But like I know what you're
saying. Yeah. But it it say you had the
money. Yeah. And you had free time, you
just do hobbies. You could go to the
gym. You could do stuff. There's other
things you Just because I'm not doing
anything right now doesn't mean you
can't do. You know what I'm saying?
You'd still prefer not to work in it.
You I think you would still prefer not
to work though. That
if you if you like obviously you
probably could, but like yeah,
there's other things you could be doing, bro.
You could go to your gym. You can go to
new places. There's other things you
could be doing if you're not working and
you got money, bro.
Yeah. I remember when I was doing that
Uber thing, bro. My eyes were out of my
[ __ ] head for like two days after.
Oh, it was hard, bro. Not hard. It
wasn't hard, but like your body would
ache and [ __ ] bro. But I used to work
like 11 hours, bro. Like every other
day. It's mad.
But that was like a strenuous job in it.
He never stopped working.
Yeah, that was hard, bro. On Peter
Benny's little body. Yeah. number.
One second, bro.
So, you work 70 hours a week?
[ __ ] hell, bro.
Well, most of the people in here don't
work. Maybe 10% do, bro. But most of
them don't. No.
Some do. Maybe a few. Very few do. But
most of them don't know.
Obviously, bro. Obviously, most of them don't. No. Uh,
but yeah, that's what I would do if I
won money. I would just go traveling
again, bro. To be fair, own business,
traveling, done. I'd go traveling and
then I'd try to start some sort of business.
When I come back, that's what I would do.
sort out my wardrobe, then come back and
then try to start a business or some
guy. That's what I would do. Yeah. Well,
buy some more clothes, I think.
I've got lush clothes, bro. Lush.
So, if you've got Okay. Okay. So, would
would you would you pay would you pay
two grand for a phone, Smokey?
Would you would you pay £2,000 for a phone?
Oh, little pups.
Would you pay that for a phone?
Believe it or not, bro, the tips are not
as good as you think.
Believe it or not, mate, in central
London, the tips are not as good as you
think. I know loads and loads and loads
of like bartenders.
When I used to go into the places and I
used to ask them like, "How much tips
did you get? How much tips tips did you get?"
What? I bought a and have a sim. Yeah.
How much was the 16 Pro Max?
They don't get as many tips as you think, lad.
Not in Not in central London.
They don't get as much as you think. Trust me.
I don't know about waitresses. I don't
know about them. But I know the
bartenders don't they don't get as much
as you think, mate.
Yeah. I don't think I'd ever get a contract again.
No, I was thinking of getting a Samsung
phone and it was £180 a month for a
year. Yeah, that's not too bad.
Yeah, £180 a month for one year. Then
after a year, the phone's yours. Yeah.
What's wrong with that? If you want a
Samsung Galaxy, if you want a flagship
phone, that's how much it is.
Well, that that was that. Yeah.
100. It's 180 a month. Yeah. But the
thing is, you either pay the phone for
two grand, which I'm not paying two
grand for a phone even though I have it.
Or you get a 2-year contract, which is
like 60 70 a month, or you pay 180 a
month for a year. It's only for a year. So yeah,
cuz what what else can you do?
You can't I can't justify two grand for
a phone, bro. That's [ __ ] ridiculous.
Don't matter how much money I had.
That's ridiculous, bro.
Yeah, but I don't want to be tied. And I
don't want to be tied into the contract
for as long for longer than I need to be.
2 years is fine because I wouldn't
upgrade the phone every year because
what's the point of that? So yeah, it
would you could do one year, two year, three year,
but then obviously you're you're stuck
on a contract for three years if you do
three years. That's the thing. So
yeah, the cheapest one would be 3 years.
I don't think the last the phone would
even last 3 years.
So maybe two years.
I get unlimited everything. I've got a
phone. I've got a SIM contract.
No, it's not 100. No, no, no, no. It's
not Bro, listen. It's not £180 a month
for three years. It's £180 a month for a
year if you do a year contract. If you
do a year, if you do two years, I think
it's 6070 a month. And if you do 3
years, it's like probably like 4050.
No, if £180 a month is for the a year
contract, not for three years.
So after you pay the year, it's yours,
isn't it? You're done, you know.
Uh, well, this phone I've got now is
blocked. Well, the thing is, bro, the
phone I've got now is blocked and the
screen's [ __ ] I've got I've got a fold six.
I've got a I've got a fold six and the
screen's kind of not [ __ ] [ __ ] but
one day I'm going to open it and it's
going to break. One day it's going to
happen. It's kind of like it's got lines
on the where I've like open it and that,
but it's block. It's blocked. Yeah, long
story. So, yeah.
And I would I would use it until um
until it broke, obviously. Yeah. I just
love the fold phones. They're [ __ ] lush.
I only like this phone cuz it's a fold
phone and it opens up like a tablet.
I've just like these phones, bro.
One grand's not that much, bro. If these
phones was £1,000, I' i'd pay £1,000.
If the new f If the new fold coming out
in July was £1,200, I'd pay it.
I'd pay it. Yeah. But it's not that
much. It's [ __ ] like two grand, bro.
I'm not paying that.
But even one grand is stupid. I get your point. Yeah.
Yeah. I like I like the flagship phones, bro.
I like flagship phones.
>> They're flagship phones.
>> Phones are [ __ ] sexy.
>> Wear cheaper clothes.
Get more expensive phone. Trust me, bro. Yeah.
You get me, bro. No, no.
So, you still got that same iPhone? You
still got that same iPhone 16, Smokey?
Nah, it's not a trend. No, it's not a
No one. I have never met anyone else
that's got the same phone as me, lad.
It's not a trend. Uh-uh. It's not a
trend, bro. I've never ever ever met
anyone that's had the same phone as me.
And I've met a lot of people. I used to
go approach him all the time, bro. My
friend's got iPhone 12 and he still uses
it. He's got an iPhone 12
and he said he will never upgrade. No, I
don't follow trends. No one has this phone, bro.
Yeah, but I wouldn't get any flagship
phone. I I only like the fold phone.
No, I only like I only like [ __ ] the fold phone.
If If there was no fold phone, then I
wouldn't I wouldn't get a flagship phone.
There's a big difference, bro.
Big difference. People that like several
cole, that was a trend to fit in.
This phone is not a trend, bro. It's not a trend. Yeah.
Yeah. It is good. It is good. I've not
had I've not had an iPhone since I was 14.
I've not had an iPhone since I was born.
Yeah, but I know what you're saying,
dude. I know what you're saying, Smokey
Be. Yeah, you don't need a flagship
phone. So, say there's not there's not
this fold phone. Yeah, I'd just probably
get a 400 phone. Well, a £350 phone,
like a moderate range one. Yeah, that's
good enough. Yeah,
you don't need a flagship, but you don't
need like a really really [ __ ] one. You
know what I'm saying? Maybe 350 400 and
that's like on sale. Like the one I had
for Uber. That was perfect.
That was £400.
It was perfect.
Obviously, it was it's not as fast as
this phone, but yeah, that's fine. A
moderate phone's all right, but you
don't want a cheap cheap cheap one,
dudly. You know, you can get Samsung
from Argos for like 150. They're [ __ ]
bro. They're [ __ ] [ __ ]
You get me?
Yeah. They're [ __ ] [ __ ] You just
need a a moderate one.
Like a moderate range. Yeah.
Yeah. Just a moderate range phone.
They work perfect. I I when I like I
said, when I use that one for Uber, it's perfect.
Probably £400, but yeah.
Yeah, I used it for four 400 pound it
cost me, but it was fine, bro.
It done the It done the Uber fine. It
done the work fine. Smokey B.
Yeah, to be honest, if I didn't to be
honest with you, if I didn't have this
fold, it's going to take you it's going
to take time to not get used to the
fold. But if this phone wasn't blocked
and like I would never I would never get
a new one until it broke. So I don't I
don't I wouldn't get a phone every year
or two years if I didn't have to. I I
would I would do it. I'd get the latest
one if it broke. You get me? I wouldn't
just get a new phone when my other one's
still working fine. Never, bro.
But one day I will open this phone and
it will break. Trust me, it will break.
One day it will break.
It will break. One day, lad.
You can tell by the screen, isn't it?
Yeah, you you can tell by the screen, bro.
But yeah, where's Timmy gone anyways?
Says that I lost my last 20 pound.
[ __ ] hell. You wouldn't believe this
guy, Smokey B. I haven't been skint for
like 5 years.
I haven't been skint about 5 years, lad.
You know, maybe longer. May maybe
Poor [ __ ] £70 a week. Poor [ __ ]
Greasy. Poor [ __ ] Yeah.
I ain't been skinned for about 5 years, lad.
I haven't lost my all my money for about
five, six years. No,
that's how you know this Timmy is a
proper self projector. I don't gamble
every day. I don't gamble every other
I gambled quite a bit last month.
Then that was the first time in like a year.
So just Timmy is just a self-reflector lad. Yeah.
So, you don't follow trends, do you,
Dusty? I don't follow trends. You'd
never You'd never see me dead in a
Canada goose coat.
You'd never see me um
you'd never see me dead in a [ __ ] um
Canada goose coat.
Not dead, bro.
>> O there, M. I just like to say,
>> see you later, lad.
You've not seen me dead in one of them coats. No.
So, what do you think about these
streamers, Hyperlink, uh, Smokeoky Me?
Do you reckon they use fake money
like Rock and Roller and stuff? You
think they use fake money?
I reckon they do. I I think they all do
about I don't think Seven Neighbors
does. I don't think Hyperlinks does.
What do you think?
Okay. What do you want?
>> I just want to say well done on your
first W on YouTube.
>> First W. It's one of many, lad.
>> Why? What other ones have you got?
>> Come on. You know exactly the other ones.
>> I don't.
>> You know exactly. You You know,
>> well, Shaunie owns you. He showed money. >> Prime.
>> I've showed more. I've showed more money
than him, but Okay.
>> Yeah, but you said the pass doesn't
count. Shaunie showed £1,100 just last week.
>> Well, the pass doesn't count then. It
don't count then.
>> Okay. So,
>> show show it now.
>> So, congratulations won your first £11,000.
>> Anyways, I don't give a [ __ ] Anyways, I
don't know why you're bringing this up.
>> Well, you asked.
>> Okay, whatever. Okay. So, Porky P,
congratulations on your first win.
>> You shouldn't call me Porky, bro. I'm in
much better shape than you, lad.
>> You're not
>> much better shape than you'll ever be, lad.
>> You said the other day that you need to
stop eating takeaways because you're
getting too big.
>> Yeah, I need because because it's
unhealthy and it's a waste of money.
>> No, you Stone Islands don't even But you
know, the thing is if I ever got like 1%
of you people, bro, I would go straight
to that gym. Yeah, you are. He also said, >> okay,
>> he also said that you have been show
years, but last Christmas you £25.
>> Okay, let's let's let's see let's see
what you look like.
>> Why would I show you what I look like?
Are you gay?
>> No, just show us what you look like.
>> Well, if you're not gay, why did you
offer to suck Mongo's [ __ ]
>> Well, that's completely made up.
>> It's not. It is.
>> Were you not meant to meet a gay guy during lockown? No.
>> Were you not talking to a transgender
guy from Glasgow? >> No.
>> You sure?
>> You see, Peter, the more you lie, the
more people are going to realize that
you are actually gay.
>> Oh, really? I'm not the one stalking men
every day on YouTube like you. So, I mean, talk.
>> See you later, lad. Yeah, he's a self-reflector.
And Stone Island was a trend. Yeah, it
was a trend back in the day.
I do you know what the reason why I wore
that stuff because I just wanted to look
good. That's why I just wanted I just
thought it was going to help my chances
with the approaches and it did to be fair.
That's why I bought that Stone Island stuff
because where it was like people was
wearing it and [ __ ]
Um, you know, and obviously if you're
looking good, looking like you've got
money, cuz I have I had money, then obviously
self-improvement, isn't it? If you got
the money to spend, then you got the
money, isn't it? That's why I done it. I
done it because of the approaches and [ __ ]
And it [ __ ] worked to be fair. I
remember the first time I bought a stony
and wore it.
I met USA
and I was convinced ever since that.
Yeah, Stony, bro. Get the [ __ ] in there.
That's why I bought it to be fair.
I bought that stuff.
If I didn't approach, would I? Probably not. So,
So mine was kind of different,
but people like when people was talking
about like um celebrities, that was just
to fit in.
Dusty, that was just generally just to
fit in with the crowd.
Chat GBT says it as well.
None of these celebrities are anything
worth questioning someone's sexuality
over. You get what I mean, Dusty?
There's not one of them that think, "Oh,
fuck." Like, there's not one of them you
look at that makes your dick hard.
So, not one of them. Not one of the any
of these celebrities you could look at
and they'd make your pee pee hard.
So, they're definitely not uh anything
to question someone's sexuality over,
if you get what I mean, Greasy.
It was so evident. It was copying when
they were putting these average
celebrity when they were putting these
average celebrities on pedestals.
They're not even real beauty. They're
not they're not anything. You know, if
you watch some vintage Porn Dusty, you
will actually see like some really
really good like women back in the day,
back in the 70s, back in the 80s.
There's one that I'm familiar with
and I watch some of the videos. She's
old now, but that's what beauty was back
in the day, not [ __ ] trends, people copying,
you know what I mean, dusty,
you know? So, but yeah, if I didn't
approach and stuff, I would never have uh
bought them them them stone islands and stuff.
Oh, Smokey B wants to join. One second.
You have to wait a bit, man, before I
let you on. I don't know why your does this
one second lad
showing up but it's not letting me
I just because I just don't understand
why people had to copy each other that doctor
just cuz it's just copying
copying the crowd you know
definitely Nothing worth questioning
someone's sexuality over.
It's not letting me add you in, bro.
Why? It's smoking. It's showing your Oh,
here we go.
Bro, have you got something or something?
>> Can you hear me? Can you hear me?
I'm echoing echoing. Hello. Hello.
Bro, you got you got Wi-Fi. You really do.
>> You must be using your [ __ ]
>> phone. Internet, bro.
>> It always happens when you join join this.
>> What was the answer saying? Indigo,
>> what was the chat GBT answer saying?
I was looking at some memes about her
and she's nothing more than average.
Nothing more than average. Definitely
nothing to question someone's sexuality over.
It's not like they had a big ass and big
tits and they were insanely attractive where like,
you know, that's just No, just it's just copying.
It's just copying
because you even you either like ass or
tits in it. So, if someone had both,
right? Then you can kind of say, well,
you either like ass or tits, but then
still them people could have a preference.
Oh, little snooze blesser. It is.
It is draining.
Definitely would kick her out of bed.
She's not my type.
She's There's nothing good about her. No
ass, no tits. There's nothing about her.
If you completed I've already completed
school. Thank you very much. You would
use those type
Yeah. It was just It was just copying.
Yeah. For not liking FIFA. Yeah. It's
just cop It's just copycat trends.
People used to say shovel cole was fit
to fit in. Yeah. They're just trends.
There's a lot there was a lot of trends
going about going about back in the day
copying. People used to copy. >> Hello.
>> Yeah, there's something wrong with your
Wi-Fi, man. Yeah, I can hear you.
>> It's [ __ ] Yeah, it's [ __ ] in it.
>> Is it It's your Wi-Fi, is it?
>> I think so. Well, it's just a
Everything's Bluetooth on my [ __ ]
computer and phone and everything, so
it's Oh, [ __ ] Yeah. So, what's what's
what's the business?
>> [ __ ] what's happening? What's the business?
>> He's not We haven't heard from Timmy.
>> You're never going to hear from Timmy,
are you? He's He's [ __ ] hiding under
the bed trying to phone Tiger at the minute.
>> So, you you you want us to work together? Yeah. >> Huh?
>> You want us to work together?
>> Why? What the [ __ ] What? No.
>> No. like work like work like work
together you know
>> what the [ __ ] do I have to work with you for
>> you said you was offering me a job in it
>> well I mean I can give you a job you won't
>> yeah so I'd be work so I'd be working with
>> you [ __ ] so >> huh
>> probably have to sack you after about a week
>> why you I mean you've never worked a job
in your life
>> yeah I have
>> yeah you stole food off [ __ ] Uber Eats
>> I've done other jobs
>> yeah What?
>> It doesn't matter. But I have worked.
Doesn't matter what it is.
>> So I have worked. You said I haven't
>> Yeah, but come on. You haven't worked a
proper job in your life.
>> Get yourself down to waxies, lad.
>> I have actually had a proper job. I had
I'd done removals.
>> Well, you lifted some [ __ ] into the back
of a van.
>> Yeah, but No, no, no. But it was a
traveling one where we travel everywhere.
>> For travel?
>> Like the whole like we would go everywhere, lad. No,
>> you don't know that kind of job where
you you remove when people are moving,
you remove their furniture, but it's
every you go everywhere in the country.
You get it?
>> Yeah. Do you not think I've moved house
PJ? I'm from Northern Ireland. I live in
England. Do you not think I've had to
employ them type of people before?
>> Yeah, but you got here by aeroplane.
>> Yeah, but how do you think the rest of
my [ __ ] got here?
>> With a van, right?
>> Yeah. Exactly.
>> So, how how much how much did you pay?
How much did you pay them?
>> I think it was like two or three grand >> really. >> Yeah.
>> DJ like it's just normal [ __ ] normal
people [ __ ] you know?
>> Yeah. Yeah. I think if I moved far away,
I'd probably just I don't know. Depends
how new the stuff was. I'd probably just
buy again to be honest. Like buy a new
bed, you know? Depending on like how you
know what I mean. depending on what
stuff you get me.
>> I mean, a lots of people do stuff like
SPG, but it's just like that's just
normal life stuff. You know what I mean?
It's like you've just lived with your
mom all your life.
>> So, you're you're 40. You're 40 odd, isn't it?
>> 40 odd. [ __ ] off.
>> [ __ ] I'm nowhere near [ __ ] 40 odd.
>> You're near 40, is I? >> No.
>> You're not the same age as me. >> No.
>> You tried saying that before, huh?
>> Huh? I'm not too old saying that you're
my age before.
>> I'm not too far away from the same age
as you to be fair.
>> Couple years older.
>> Yeah. A couple years older than you probably.
>> But that's the thing. That's why I said
too, PJ. It's like
>> people like you think everyone on here's
>> what happened?
Oh, he [ __ ] left. What the [ __ ]
But yeah, I would kick her out of bed.
Definitely kick her out of bed. Disgusting [ __ ]
>> There we go. Yeah. Sorry, man. You got kicked.
>> My [ __ ] phone is in my pocket there.
Here. You think everyone on here is some
[ __ ] who's over 40 years old who has absolutely no
>> not all not all of the people but majority?
>> No, not the I wouldn't even say the
majority to be fair.
>> Like V and [ __ ] good vibes and them
sort of pe Oh, man. Come on.
>> No, to be honest, Var is not. He's
probably younger than me.
>> Have you seen what he looks like?
>> I haven't. I've never seen what these
looks like, but I've heard things about
him and I would say
>> you're one of these. You're on these
WhatsApp [ __ ] groups and [ __ ] is it? >> Yeah.
>> Like, and that's kind of Do you not
think it's a bit weird though, bro?
Like, like being in WhatsApp groups
talking about like YouTube. Come on.
It's a bit weird, is it?
>> Why? Why? What if you spend I mean, you
literally think of you. You spend six to
seven hours a day. Every day on live.
>> Not every day, bro. But yeah.
>> Nah, come on. Come on. We can look back.
There's an account that like uploads
every single Why? Okay. Why am I
>> on here? 6 to 7 hours in.
>> And do you know why? Why am I Why am I
on here? Why am I on here today? Oh,
he's done a video. Yeah. One second. I
Why did I do a video today? >> Why?
>> Why did I come? Cuz it's Timmy. >> Yeah.
>> Did you not You was asleep yesterday. We
was going back and forth yesterday. You
were sleeping, wasn't you?
>> Oh, you can say this [ __ ] You can say
you're bored or whatever. But then you
got people who are on here like the odd
couple of hours every day. Like the people
>> One second, bro.
>> What's this?
>> One second. to me. Yeah,
>> I'm in now. PJ, I'm actually
>> Yeah. Where where what? What? Where are
you? Are you at the train station?
>> I've just done a video. Smokey's not
paying for the taxi. You're paying for
>> Yeah, I am paying for it. Yeah, I am
paying for it. What?
>> He's the one who said he wanted me to
come down. I didn't say I was coming
down. So, I am not deleting my Tesco's
app when I said something I didn't say.
He wanted me to come down.
>> Yeah. Yeah. Yeah, I do. What? What train
station are you at? Can you can you
>> What train station are you outside the
train station? Yeah, >> PJ.
>> Hey, Timmy, go to London. I'll give you
400 quid. 50 had a quot. I want to be
back here by 11:00 tonight.
>> Smokey's talking to you.
>> I'm not talking to Smokey. I'm talking to you.
>> Okay, you outside M Street, right? I'm
having points. I'm having a quick beer.
Right. I'm having a quick beer. You're
in the taxi. Not Smokey. I'll have a chat with
>> And you're not in M Street. You're in
New Street. You got yourself more
street. on attack. You don't plan.
>> Okay. You want the MTO as well. Anyways,
yeah, I will do. I will do. Yeah.
>> One second, bro. Hold on.
>> If if if Timmy comes to London, I'll pay
for his tax. He don't even know.
>> No, I'll pay for you. No, no, no. I'll
pay for it, bro. I'll pay for it. And
he's not he's not at Mall Street. He's
at New Street.
>> Of course he's not.
>> He's not He's at New Street, bro.
>> He's nowhere. He's [ __ ] Nowhere.
>> He's He's bro, he done a video in New
Street. I go to North Street and I'll
order it. Done.
>> He's He's chatting [ __ ] He's not going [ __ ] anywhere.
>> Well, he doesn't understand that. I know
Birmingham. I've been there multiple
times. You know, there's free there train stations.
>> To be honest, I don't know. Like, but
he's he's not going.
>> Have you been there?
>> To Birmingham? >> Yeah.
>> Twice, I think. But that's it. I've been
to the [ __ ] ports of Birmingham. It's
>> Yeah, that's free train station. So, go
to I ordered the taxi. I don't give a [ __ ]
>> Hey. No, I've been to Birmingham a
couple times, but [ __ ] hole.
Yeah, you need to stop this YouTube [ __ ] man.
>> But that's what I'm saying. It's you you
go online and just call people out, but
then there's people on here who just
enjoy it for a laugh and that's all the
people who's in the WhatsApp groups
>> and we just have chat and just chat [ __ ]
>> do you know what I mean? It's like
there's a whole other side to this. You
take it far too serious.
>> It's obvious Timmy done his balls in
yesterday. It's so obvious he done his
balls in yesterday, bro. It's so
obvious. He he peed on his balls in the
day that Lord Jay won [ __ ] 900 quid
or whatever it was.
>> Yeah, I remember I remember going on I
remember going on Lord J's video. I
remember going on LJ's video. Yeah. And
everyone was saying, "Oh, Snug's
jealous." And but no one really said
anything about me cuz they know I don't
care, bro. It know I don't care.
>> If it doesn't matter, you gamble 20
quid, 30 quid here, there and [ __ ]
>> Yeah, it's annoying. I'll be honest
though. I just don't I just don't like
losing on the fobies. I don't I don't I
don't You know what I'm saying? I just
don't like losing on the FB. on the FBI.
Doesn't matter what you play, but if you
if you play the FB, you've got to
realize that like if you spend [ __ ]
20 quid, 50 quid, 100 quid, you're
potentially going to lose if you win.
>> Obviously. Yeah. But I think you don't
want you don't want to lose in it. Like,
do you understand? Like
>> who who wants to stick 20 quid in 100
quid and lose on the FBI? Nobody. >> No.
>> So, it doesn't matter. So, it does it
literally doesn't matter. But it's like
the people just handle it and then
people like you who [ __ ] lose their mind.
>> So you so you so you you you speak to LT
off it isn't it?
>> I was spoken to him a few times just on
the side but not that much but it's just
like just normal chat. He's just a
>> So you going to like meet him and that? >> No.
>> No just LP is just a normal fella to be honest.
>> Yes. So why don't you meet him then?
>> Then why do you have to?
>> You don't have to robot. I was going
down for a fight and he was going to be
in Tottenham for a fight and that was
it. And if I say to him, if I'll bump
into you, then we can go grab a beer.
But it's like
I didn't see
>> Yeah, man.
>> Well, you went to the same boxing you
went to that same boxing match.
>> Yeah, but there's about 20,000 [ __ ] people.
>> Yeah, obviously. Obviously, obviously.
But I'm saying like
>> obviously obviously you weren't just
going to like run into, but I'm saying
like you could have planned something in it.
>> No, but that's what I said. says, "If I
bump into you or if I see you or
whatever, give me a shout and we'll
>> Yeah, but how you But how's that going
to happen? You know what he looks like?"
>> Yeah. No, but that's a different thing.
I know what he looks like and he knows
what I look like. So,
>> that's what I'm saying. Yeah. So, like
>> Yeah. So, yeah. But it's not everybody
speaks like we speak on YouTube, you
know what I mean?
>> You like Do you like boxing then? Yeah.
>> Yeah. Of course.
>> Yeah, man. It's better than football,
but I don't like football, man. It's
[ __ ] isn't it?
>> But anyways, you need to just like if I
don't [ __ ] don't know what you're
going to do with your YouTube channel,
to be honest. You're absolutely [ __ ]
at this point.
>> We have to put some content in it on this channel.
>> You are [ __ ] for content to be honest
at this point. >> Why?
>> Cuz you just get trolled into oblivion.
>> Why don't Why don't Why don't Why don't
me and you meet for a drink?
>> Who? Me and you?
>> Yeah. Get Go to Waxies in it. I'm not
even trolling. I'm being serious.
go to waxies in it.
>> I don't think I would meet you by myself
to be honest. >> Why?
>> I don't know.
>> If if
>> that doesn't really make sense, is it?
>> If Banger or any of them boys ever came
over here and then we was going to have
like a proper meet up and then they
wanted to invite you along just either
for like to troll you or like whatever.
But I'm just pretty sure like someone
would end up just smacking you.
>> Yeah. But who would that Who would that
be? Well, it depends. There's like one
of about [ __ ] five different people
might want to end up smacking you. So,
>> yeah, but I mean like we could just go
out for a friendly drink.
>> Nah, you've just you've said too far too
much mad [ __ ] on here to be honest to be
>> Yeah, we can we can leave it in 2025, you know.
>> I mean, yeah, but it's difficult, isn't it?
>> No, it's a new year, isn't it, lad?
>> Nah, it's just don't think it would ever
happen to be honest.
>> We can go to the swan. We can go to the
swan, you know.
>> But that's the thing. The only thing you
can do is try and redeem yourself by
like see people like Tim and stuff like
this. If you can try and like just
squirt off with them, the only thing you
can do is not say [ __ ] not say mad
[ __ ] Number one, obviously don't say mad [ __ ]
>> and just square off all of the [ __ ] that
you said with anybody. You know, people
on here said worse stuff than me,
though, and they don't they get away
with it. Like Rice, and there's been there's people
>> Listen, listen. Nobody's said worse [ __ ] than you.
>> Rice has.
>> Nah. Who the [ __ ] Rice? Some fraud content.
>> Yeah, but he said no. He has said stuff.
>> Who gives a [ __ ] He's a
>> No, I'm just saying he has said stuff
and no one goes for him in it.
>> Yeah, but nobody gives a [ __ ] who he is.
>> You know, you get Tim in here. You get
[ __ ] Lord Jay in here. people who
come want to come in here and speak to
you. Nobody goes in to speak to Rice.
>> He's a [ __ ] [ __ ] So
>> yeah, I guess so. Yeah.
>> If you're want to squash any of the type
of beef that you have,
>> then you need to like face it like a man. >> Okay. >> So,
>> all right. You said I've made my way
smoky. I'll leave out my speakers crap
on this. You said you're going to pay
>> you in more You Station. Yeah. Lord Jay
is trying to get money out of dead
drama. Banger's not about it.
>> Okay. So, let's get to the Let's get to
the point. I talked to him smoker. I've
had a bit of bone smoker. I can
concentrate more. You said you're going
to pay for the taxi, P.
>> Yeah. Are you at street?
>> You said it your own mouth and it's been cleaned.
>> Okay. So, you're at street station. Yeah.
>> Pay for my taxi £550. Now,
>> I am around the corner from M Street, right?
>> Okay. When you get to Okay. Show me when
you're at M Street then. Show me and
I'll order it and I'll give you the registration number.
>> I' I've already spoke to my friend. I've
got a lift organized to meet you and I'm
going to come like a thief in the night,
Peter, and you won't expect me coming.
>> Now you're just talking [ __ ]
>> I don't have to [ __ ] block,
>> bro. Now he's just talking [ __ ] again.
Well, that doesn't make sense.
>> My heart and it's going ahead regardless
of what you guys think. Right
>> now, you're saying that you got a
>> He doesn't make sense, bro. Get yourself
to M Street and then let me know if
you're there and all these little
[ __ ] spastics. I'm being realistic
now. I will be coming down to get the
car sorted right in the next couple of
days or two, right? I will come when you
don't expect it, Peter.
>> So, you're not coming now?
>> Cuz that's what I do.
>> Just go and you will man up.
>> So, now
he's lesson from prime.
>> Be realistic, Timmy.
>> Are you going to pay for the taxi today
or not? Let me
>> Yes. If you go to If you go to Marshall
Yeah. If you go to Mar Street, right? >> Yeah.
>> I'm not sorry, mate. Yeah, I I thank you
Smokey that you offered to pay and I
appreciate that and I really do laz.
Right. But I don't want you to pay.
Peter said he's got all this money that
he's got and I will pay and I will pay.
>> He said he said he will pay. I said I'll
pay something. You're going for free.
>> You said you're going to pay for the taxi.
>> Yeah. Go to street and I'll pay for the
taxi in a minute. Right. I'll come on
your hangouts and you will need to pay
for the taxi, Peter. Yes or no?
>> Yes. Yes. Yes. Are you going to pay for
the tax? 100%. It's £188. I'll pay for
your street. He's going to GET A TAXI.
GIVE IT A raise
over and over and over again. Go street.
He's going to get you a taxi.
>> The [ __ ] excuses you're coming up
with. Hurry up and do it.
>> Is a [ __ ] madness, isn't it?
>> Yeah. They make it so diff they make it impossible.
making it impossible.
>> That's the That's the problem. Bangers
has called it straight out there. It's
like he You will pay, I will pay, anyone
will pay. He could pay him [ __ ] self. It's like
>> You really think Listen, you really
think this guy's going to be sitting in
a car for 2 and 1 half hours, bro? Come on.
>> But it just doesn't matter if you want
to call if you're calling that [ __ ] out, just go. >> Yeah.
>> [ __ ] It's It's not difficult.
>> Isn't he at New Street? Is he's at New
Street in it? So why isn't he just
dropped dropped the train from New
Street? Exa. Exactly. Get a [ __ ]
Uber. [ __ ] it. If it cost 70 quid there,
[ __ ] it. Let's go.
>> [ __ ] hell, man. Right. We'll see if
he goes to and and I I'll order it and
I'll give him the registration number
and all he has to do is give my name.
I'll give him the last free [ __ ]
Muhamad. Come on there in a [ __ ] Toyota prize.
>> It's about 15. Yeah, it's about
>> jump in the [ __ ] and go.
>> It's about 15 20 pound. Yeah. For a train. Yeah.
>> There you go. Now he's saying the next
couple of days. I don't know why he does
this, you know.
>> I knew as soon as he said that he was
say he's he's not coming. >> Nah,
>> it's never coming.
>> Never ever ever.
>> And I'm not even being funny. Birmingham
ain't even that far, you know, to be
honest with you. It's not even that far.
>> Well, Birmingham from you is what, like
two and a half, three hours.
>> On a train, if he gets a fast train,
it's about an hour and 20 minutes on a
fast train. Oh,
>> yeah. Even I'll meet him at the station
if he wants.
I don't know the new
>> only the midnight
it's it's not like it's Liverpool or
[ __ ] Scotland. You know what I mean?
>> Where do you live now? You live in your
M house, don't you?
>> Yeah, but I'll get I'll beat you at the
station in it. It's not a problem.
>> Where are you in Essics?
>> Basically. Yeah, but I can get the
Elizabeth line straight to you know what
I'm saying? It's not hard.
>> I'm not out in the sticks. Does that
make sense? I'm not out in the sticks, bro. Like
>> you're in this where you're earning
mistakes enough to be fair.
>> But to to be honest with you, yeah, he
was and he he was even trying to say
that from from him to me it's 4 and a
half hours. No, it ain't. It's not even
4 and a half hours to Newcastle on a train, bro.
>> I don't know. Where's where's the
closest train station? Do you?
>> Um it's like So you get the bus, it's
about 10 minutes on the bus, but then
the train goes straight basically to
where he is cuz it's Elizabeth line. Do
you get it?
>> You uh you're east, aren't you? >> Yeah.
>> Yeah. So, you just get off at Liverpool
Street and get the um line to Houston.
It's It's simple, bro. >> Simple.
>> Don't forget it's London, you know, once
you're in uh London.
>> He said he said he was coming to 55 when
he saw to your man's house and like Rome.
>> Yeah. He doesn't even need to do that.
I'll meet him if he's in London, isn't
it? Like [ __ ] You know what I mean? But yeah. >> Yeah.
>> Now, you were when you were in Albert
Square, you were more like north sort of
London, weren't you?
No, it's east.
>> Northeast, really? Is it?
>> No, Stratford is east. Stratford is east London.
>> You should know this, man. You've been
You've been along with
>> Yeah, but it's more it's more northeast,
I think, to be fair, than like proper
like east, in it.
>> I don't know. All I know is it's east,
bro. It's always been east. I mean, it's
it's by bow. It's by [ __ ] you know by
it's by boat. You know, you know where
you know where B is?
>> Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
>> Yeah. So
he's [ __ ] knows.
>> [ __ ] knows to be honest though. Not that
it makes any much of a difference. No [ __ ]
>> No, he's just making excuses. Yeah, he's
>> It is I know it's Yeah, it is East
London. Yeah, Fire Stick it is. It
doesn't matter, bro. It doesn't matter
anyways. It's It's near enough to [ __ ]
>> So where where Okay. Okay. Do you know
where Okay. What part of London is
Brixton in? You know I
>> I've spent like since I've been here for
about 15 years. I spent about 10 years
in London like for work. So I've been here.
>> Well, do you know do you know what is it
then? What part of London is Brixton then then?
>> Brixton is more like central is it?
>> Ah South. >> Yeah.
>> South London. Yeah. It's not it's not
central. It's south.
>> Where? It's not proper south of the
river. Is it Brandon?
>> I think so. Yeah. Is this South London?
It's a little bit near central. Huh?
>> Oh, it's a bit south of Lambbeath, is it?
>> CL. Yeah. Yeah,
>> something like that. All their phones
will be I've been I've been all over
London, man. Is there places you ain't
been in London? You've been everywhere now.
>> No, not much to be for. We used to go a
lot of like central London for work. So, >> yeah.
>> But then it's the same. It's like it's
not like we're really [ __ ] hanging
around in these places. We're just going
dropping [ __ ] off and bouncing. So
>> yeah. Have I been to the bookies? No, bro.
I swear to God, Smokey B. These people
think I gamble every day. I swear to God
I don't. Bro,
>> it's just because everybody gamles every
day. So they just want you to gamble
every day. So do you sense? So you know me.
>> No, not today. No, not today. I gambled
in was the bookies with that 20 pound a
few days ago. Bro, I don't gamble every day, lad.
>> But then
>> it's more like every few weeks, huh?
>> People want you to do your bollocks in
because they understand your situation.
It's like you might have money, but you
you don't have like money money if you
know what I mean.
>> But how much is money to you?
>> Like proper like money money.
>> Yeah. But how I don't know how much you
get, right? Let's be honest. Nobody
knows how much you get.
How much do you think I have?
>> I think you might potentially get like
two grand a month.
>> No, I don't even get I don't get two
grand a month. But I'm saying how much
do you think I have now?
>> Yeah. Well,
>> I don't get two grand a month.
>> Listen. Okay. So, I think that you
potentially get like say two grand a
month. You might have to give your mass
some money. You might have some bills to
pay. You might end up with about 1,500
quid a month. But then you might spend
[ __ ] between500 and a,000 pound a
month like on just [ __ ] living like
everybody does. You can
>> I don't get two Yeah, I don't get two
grand. I don't get two grand a month.
>> In six months you might see be able to
save between like I don't know what's
realistic to be
>> I have two grand but I have two I have I
have two grand but I don't get two grand
a month. Does that make sense?
>> Well, I mean there you go. If what in
six months you've managed to save 2K?
Okay, fair enough.
>> No, not it wouldn't take No, no, no. Not
six months. If it never took me six
months to save two grand, bro.
>> Or well, I don't know. Then what the
[ __ ] I don't know what you're
>> No, it's just like, bro, like you you
carry money over like say say you get a
payment. Yeah. Whatever it is, you you
you just carry some money over. You know
when you carry bits over and then get me?
>> That's the same for anybody who does anything.
>> Yeah, that's what I'm saying. Yeah. No,
not six. No, not six months, bro.
>> Yeah, but I'm just saying It's like well
in 6 months if you've managed to save a
couple of grand and you have a few grand
in the bank then it is what it is and
it's like it's not like a lot you don't have a
>> you're not you don't have a lot of
money. It's like people who have money
understand and people who don't have money like >> tax
you for like
>> Yeah. Are you at more street? Yeah. >> Finished
>> bloody cheap now. >> Right.
>> Right. Are you at more street? Yeah.
>> You where you order me the taxi and
you're paying for it. So I make sure she
>> Are you at more street? Yeah.
>> Getting it if Smokey's paid for it. Right.
>> Are you at M Street?
>> Paying for it cuz you were skinn. I want
to see your bank account.
>> Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Are you at M Street?
>> So order the taxi. Right.
>> Yeah. Are you at M Street? Yeah.
>> Rose, right?
>> No. Show where you are. I'll show you at
more street and I'll order and I'll order it. >> Rose
>> and I'll order it.
>> I've just told you to order it.
>> No. Show me you're at street station and
I'll order it.
>> Rose waiting. No, bro. Show me you're at street station.
>> What you're saying now?
>> No, no, no, no. I said prove to me
you're at street station and I'll order
you a taxi.
>> Rose is around the corner. I'm having a
pod before I get the taxi.
>> No, no, no, no, no. When you're there,
show me. When you're there, show me and
I'll order it. He's not He's still at
New Street. He's still at He's still at
>> No, no, no. I'm not telling you what I
am. So, you can phone the pub, right?
>> Phone the pub. I don't phone pubs. I
don't do that.
>> That's what Laur does. I don't do that.
Show me you're at street and I'll order it anywhere.
>> PJ Tim told you he's at the the Marley
Rose or the Barley Rose. Order it there.
>> No, I said to him I'll order him a
>> What's the difference?
>> Because he's not where we saying he is.
You idiot. Why would he put the barley
Rose? Why would he?
>> Why would he put his camera on? Why
>> People will ring the pub and get him thrown out.
>> How are they going to know what pub is if he's
going to know what pub is? Okay, then.
He said where he is.
>> Listen, just tell him to show me where
he is with the camera. I'll order it now.
>> He just said he's in the bar rules. What
are you waiting on?
>> Okay. Okay. Okay. Okay. We'll wait until
he comes outside then. Yeah.
>> What do you mean? Order the taxi and
then when it's
>> He's not where he's saying he is.
>> That's what I'm saying. >> Tell
his bluff. DJ's [ __ ] skinny and got
500 quid on taxis.
>> 500 again. Bro, you don't know how much
money I have. You don't know nothing
about me. This is what I'm saying. This
is what you call, bro. This is what you
call speculation. Speculating. Yeah.
Show me you're at the where you are and
I'll order it now. Simple.
What is he doing? Drinking in a pub.
>> Who's chatting [ __ ]
>> He's chatting [ __ ] Why is he even in a
pub drinking? He said he's going to go
to a train station. Show him and I will
order it. Birmingham Street station.
Done. I'll give you the registration
number. You say you're me and that's it. He's
Timmy. Timmy is never going to come to
me to be honest.
>> He didn't eat, bro. He's drink. Anyways,
back on to what I was saying, but but
yeah. No, it doesn't take [ __ ] months
and months to show to save two grand though.
>> But it doesn't whatever. Yeah.
>> Well, yeah, exactly. It doesn't take
much money to like it doesn't take long
time to save any type of money to be honest.
>> It could just be boring sometimes, is it?
>> Just this course is boring. It's like,
do you think like just working and
saving money is like any type of
entertainment? Of course, it's nuts. It
>> doesn't matter how much money you get as
well. It's still It's still boring,
isn't it? It is boring.
>> That's what I'm saying. It's like we I
spend [ __ ] seven, eight months of the
year just working and saving money. So,
>> yeah, you must Yeah, but you must Yeah,
but you must have went out drinking now.
>> Well, yeah, of course. It's like do
stupid stuff or have barbecues or have
people around to the house and you do stuff.
>> Oh, but you would just spend less in it.
But you just spend less in it. Yeah.
>> But it's like Yeah. But ultimately,
you're saving money like the whole time. >> Yeah.
>> It doesn't matter. You end up at the end
of the year and you've got [ __ ] save
20 grand or whatever, but you just going
to spend it on something for the house or whatever.
>> Maybe a four or something, isn't it?
>> Yeah. It's just It's not exactly
exciting. It's [ __ ] It's nothing, you know?
>> Do you think Do you think two do you
reckon losing two grand is a lot?
>> No. To be honest, it's not
>> Well, it is.
>> It's not It's not nice. It's not nice to
lose, are it? Well, it is to be honest,
>> but it's nice to lose.
>> I've lost I lost two grand the first two
weeks of the month or something
>> and then lost two grand the first the
second two weeks. So, and the MS was beyond raging.
>> Pissed. Yeah, she Well, the MS was be beyond pissed.
>> Yeah, but now what I'm saying is you was
raging as well, was it?
>> Well, yeah, I was pissed as well. But
then I'm like a gambler. So to me it's
>> Did you ever smash up the bookies like
years ago when you used to lose?
>> No. To be honest, I'm the sort of person
that like if I go there I went to the casino
>> and I lose like 2k. Then I went and lost like 2.3
>> and I'm like and I think to myself like
within two weeks I'm like [ __ ] four
and a halfk down
>> and it could literally tilt you right
over the edge. But then at the same
time, I'm just like, what's the point? You know,
>> it's my fault essenti. It's my fault essentially. So,
>> can't be mad about it.
>> I know I know I know someone that
smashed the bookies up, they got they
went to court and that had to pay a fine.
>> Yeah. But then you see that's just like
stupid, you know?
>> Yeah. But you don't think at the time
you're angry in it, but obviously if
they're mad, then they're not going to, you know,
>> Yeah. But if you're any type of sensible
person, it's like, you know, I mean, if
you do something like that, then you
just [ __ ] yourself over like harder.
I've smashed bookies up, but I ain't
been like caught.
>> Yeah, but why why would you want to lose
like a grand and then like do something
stupid like that then [ __ ]
>> and then you have to pay a fine on top of it.
>> Yeah. Then pay a fine on top and then
get [ __ ] criminally. It's like that's
the most ridiculous [ __ ] going. So
>> yeah, why does it matter if I get less
than two grand a month? Why why does
that matter? Why are you so Why are you
so interested, bro?
>> Money. Whoever has any money doesn't
matter. You've got it. Literally doesn't
matter. Nobody It's not like anybody on
here is hanging out with anybody else. It's
>> you know you know another thing. Yeah.
That what these people in this community
don't understand yet. They don't seem to
understand yet that the more money you
get, the more you adjust, the more you
spend. They I don't think they understand it.
>> It it doesn't matter. It's like it's
different. Do you know what I mean? It's
like when I had friends and we would go
to the casino and it's like I would take
a certain amount of money to the casino.
They would take a certain amount of
money to the casino. You were like best
friends. So if I took [ __ ] 4K to the
casino and I took 100 quid,
>> they might feel a little bit like, "Oh,
I need to up my game because he's taking that money."
>> It's like, yeah, it's nobody on here
owes anybody any anything. >> Yeah.
>> It's like what does it matter? You could
take 50p. Timmy could take 50 grand, but
it literally doesn't matter.
>> That's called being poor. Okay, bro.
>> You know what I mean?
>> See you later, lad. >> Yeah,
>> literally it literally does not matter. It's just
>> you any money you get, you would any
money you get, you just adjust.
>> That's that's another thing that people don't get.
>> Think that's why people adjust. You know
what I mean? Look, look at Monty. He's
[ __ ] skinned. His Mrs. is a crackhead.
>> But do you know what? To be fair,
there's no reason for him to be skinned.
He gets like bro he actually gets enough
to not be skint but [ __ ]
>> but somebody like Monty gets his money
and he gets all of his money and he's a
[ __ ] He's so stupid to like
>> she's a simp.
>> Yeah, exactly. Natalie smart. She's not
like stupid. You know what I'm saying?
Like she comes from [ __ ] Lisa who's a
grifter as well. They're not like
stupid. They just rinse all of his
money. Give me all your money. Blah blah
blah. Here we go. the whites flying for
a couple of weeks.
>> Would you say you're a mill? Would you
say Would you say you're a millionaire?
>> Who me? >> Yeah.
>> No. No.
>> Do you think one day you might be?
Maybe. Is it? >> Hopefully.
That's the goal. I mean,
>> like one of them like one of them like
one of them big YouTubers, isn't it?
>> No. No. Not like not anything like that.
I'm very much more like bricks and
mortar. You know what I mean? I've got a
business. They've got a secondary
>> I'm sure he heard you heard about that
in it when I said I wanted to smash the
bookies with a can of coke. I think I'm
pretty sure he heard, bro.
>> Yeah, but if you want to do some [ __ ]
like that, it's just stupid in it.
>> I did. Yeah, but that's what I felt like
doing in it. I felt like doing it in it.
>> You've got to think what's best for
yourself and somebody like to be honest.
Somebody like you who to be honest has
you've got like [ __ ] nothing to worry
about. You can afford to do a little bit
of like fraud or whatever like you do.
You know what I'm saying? I don't do fraud, lad.
>> No, you know, but you know what I'm
saying? Whenever you were No.
>> What do you mean fraud? I don't I don't
do I don't do fraud, bro.
>> Well, well, your [ __ ] sister and
whatever might have done a little bit of
fraud in the past and you might have
done a bit of fraud with your sublet and
stuff like this.
>> Yeah, but that's Yeah, but you you say
it's fraud, but think about it.
Theoretic theor theoretically that's a
loophole. I mean, you would have done
the same thing as well.
>> That that's that's what I'm saying. It's
theoretically a loophole. you might have
went got away with it or it's very much
like hard to I don't know press the
>> when you can't get you can't get nicked
for it like that's the thing.
>> Well, that's what I'm saying. You know
what I mean?
>> I mean would you Okay. Would you Okay.
Well, would you do it?
>> Not in my position now, but in your
position potentially it's different than it.
>> Yeah. Yeah. Obviously. Yeah.
>> There you go. So, it's what I'm saying.
>> Yeah. Okay. So, what would you Okay. So,
what would you do then? Cuz say you got
left like a five, sixbedroom house here.
What what would you do with it then?
Like another house than what you're living in.
>> Well, to be honest, how you did it was
probably the best way to do it. So,
>> yeah. There you go.
>> Well, that's what I'm saying. But that's
what I'm saying. But then what did you
do with the money? You [ __ ] it off.
>> Not really. I lived a life with it, bro.
>> Of course I did.
>> Yeah. What What [ __ ] it off?
>> I should have I should have saved more.
Yeah, I should have saved more. I could
have done better with it, but I was
living life, bro.
>> So, how much? You much You had three
grand a month.
>> Uh-huh. But I used to win money, though.
Don't No, no, but don't forget I used to
win a month time 12 is 36 * 2. So, you
had essentially 108 grand.
>> Yeah. But you're obviously going to go
out and live life, bro. Is it? You can't
you can't see it like that, is it?
>> So, yeah. What? I mean, come on. You got
to be [ __ ] sensible. It's like if you
think that's your one and only potential
shot to do that even
>> I mean what I mean what did you what did
you expect me what did you expect me to do
>> 72 grand well I mean be a bit more
[ __ ] sensible but it's hard
>> yeah but do you think yeah but when
you're when you're single and you're
living you live in London bro of course
you're going to cut out and live life
>> but then I would rather bro you could
die tomorrow think about it
>> yeah but you're someone that's who's
never had to manage money as well so
it's like it's it's different you know
>> but you you know you know what I'm
saying though I should have saved like
theoretically if I could go back I'd
save maybe honestly £300 a month, £400 a
month. I should have been saving.
>> You had three grand a month say for 12
months for 3 years.
>> No, it was it was three years. Three,
four years. Yeah.
>> Yeah. For three years. So you hadund you
like about approximately 108 grand. >> Uhhuh.
>> So you had £100,000
>> which would have been like, you know,
you could have bought yourself like an
apartment paid out in London somewhere.
>> Yeah. But then you wouldn't be you
wouldn't have been living life at this.
You know what I'm saying? So
>> yeah, but doesn't matter. But no, you
would have been living life.
>> Did I gamble all that? Did I gamble all
that money? One second.
>> Doesn't matter.
>> Did I gamble all of it? Well, obviously
I didn't gamble all of it. Did I?
>> Well, of course.
>> Come on, bro.
>> Yeah, it just went on things. I should
have been I should have. Yeah,
>> but yeah, but that's what I'm saying.
It's like if you have that type of
opportunity, it's like being self-aware
enough to be able to like maximize it.
It's like you people like you, Timmy, a
lot of people like, you know what I mean?
>> Monty's had opportunities. You've all
just you struggle to like be able to
maximize the opportunity. It's just what it is.
>> What What opportunities has he had?
>> A few opportunities like
>> Yeah. But what I'm trying to say to you,
what I'm trying to say to you is it's
very easy to look back on it now. Do you
get what I mean? Like,
>> but that's what I'm saying. That's
self-development, isn't it?
>> Yeah, obviously. Like,
>> of course it is.
>> You're in your prime, bro. What are you
going to do? Just sit and and save and do nothing.
>> Yeah, but that's just mean
self-development. You just look back in
your life and go, "Oh, okay. That was
[ __ ] I [ __ ] that up. I could have
done this. I could have done that." Then
next time you go come across any sort of
situation like that, you go, "Okay, I'm
going to do this completely different."
Where on here it's just [ __ ] rinse
and repeat. Rinse and repeat every single time. >> Really?
>> And that's the same [ __ ] with like
whenever you have Tim on here calling
you out and stuff like this. And Tim is
like, you know what I mean? Like people
like him, he's just
>> Bro, we're not talking about 100 grand
for a flat in London, bro. You're not.
You missed what we was the point we was
getting at. They misheardd us, bro. They took out.
>> You can spend 100 grand and get a flat
in London. Depends where you are. If
you're in North London or something like this,
>> or some direction, you can definitely
get like a little [ __ ] apartment in London.
>> If PJ wanted everybody's rentree rent
free, you could. >> Yeah.
Doesn't matter anyways, bro. You said
you get more. You said that you get way
more than three grand a month. hear me?
>> Yeah, of course.