Where the [ __ ] are these [ __ ]
He was supposed to be at that [ __ ]
station 20 [ __ ] minutes ago.
Put the link up.
What a rude fellow.
right? Let him show where he is and I'm
going to order this Uber. Yeah. Seriously. [ __ ]
Right. I've got it. I've got a split
screen now. Yeah. Come on.
If he goes on camera, I'm ordering this
Uber, bro. I've got it split screen.
And no, I didn't lose all that money,
bro. I was living life with that money
and I wouldn't take anything back to be
honest with you.
You can't put a price on life experiences, laddy.
[ __ ] knows. I'm ordering this Uber, bro.
If he shows he's at the thing here, Mar
Street Station, I'm ordering it. I've
got Uber split screen, lad. Right,
let's have a look. Timmy,
this is a [ __ ] with these people. Fire
stick. It just goes round and round in
circles. That's why I don't be on here, bro.
This [ __ ] was mentioning me yesterday,
ain't it? So, yeah.
[ __ ] sake, bro.
Another one trying to porn bomb, I reckon.
>> Trying to porn bomb. You need to grow up, lad.
Seriously. Seriously need to grow up,
you [ __ ] [ __ ]
>> Still trying to porn bomb. [ __ ]
[ __ ] community lad.
made a video. Yeah.
Wait, tell him. Yeah. And wait for me, bro.
Tell him to show where he is and stay on
the live stream. I'm going to order this Uber. One sec. One second.
One sec, bro. I'm listening to the I'm
listening to I'm listening to this
video, bro. One sec.
No, he's just playing stupid games, bro.
He's playing play He's playing stupid games.
He's playing stupid games again, bro.
This is just He's just playing stupid
games, bro. He's a [ __ ] [ __ ]
right? Come on my come on my live. Go to
Mar Street and I'm ordering it. Simple as that.
180. It is. Come on.
Come on, bro.
It's all because Timmy's done his balls
in, bro. I'm coming off this community
after today, lad.
I'm coming off this [ __ ] again after
today, bro. After I call this guy's bluff.
[ __ ] so disabled, lad. Okay, here we go.
>> Right. You at street? Yeah.
>> Oh, you at M Street? Yeah. I'm going to
order this Uber. I'm going to order this
Uber. Why are you in a I'm going to
order this Uber. Show you at M Street.
I'm going to order this
>> and then say pay for a tax that you can't afford.
>> Listen, go to more street. Yeah, I've
got it up right here now. Come onate you
for being a liar.
>> Okay. Okay. More street railway station.
Okay. One second.
Right. So, put your money where you
[ __ ] Right. Listen. Go to more
street. I've got it up right here. I've
got it up right here. Go to the train
station. Stay live and walk to the train
It's £184. I'll get you the £198 one if
it's faster. 2 minutes. It's 2 minutes,
right? It's 2 minutes. Right. Go there
and I guarantee you I'm going to get
this. I'm going to get this 2-minute
one, bro. Yeah. And he's not going to
get in it. Tell him to walk. Tell him to
go to M Street and put his camera on.
I'm going to order this Uber right now. £198. Yeah,
simple. Why is he [ __ ] drinking in a pub? Come on.
Come on. Yeah. 3 to 12 minutes. We don't
want that one. We want the 2-minute one.
Come on, Jimmy. Come on. £198.
I'm splitting the screen. I'm splitting Come on.
Come on, Timmy. I've got it here.
Easy win for the slug. It's not an easy
win for him because the link's up and
I'm about to order this Uber that's 2
minutes away from to more street station
to this address.
He's [ __ ] his pants. Look, he's gone
off. Link again.
Why do you think he's hiding in pubs?
Why is he hiding in pubs, bro? What the
[ __ ] It's not no easy win for him. He's lost.
There you go.
198 95. It's 2 minutes away.
Right. How far is he from street? How
far is he from street? Does anyone know
how far he is from street?
H. Does anyone know how far this guy is
from M Street?
He needs to come on here and talk cuz
I'm going to order this Uber, bro. Yeah. Come on.
You live in Wolf Hampton? I didn't know
you was a Yam Yam.
I don't know, bro. All they need to do
is go to M Street or if he tells me he's
like a minute or two minutes away from
there, I'll just order it. Simple.
He ain't getting in no cab. He's not
getting in no [ __ ] He's not getting
in no car, bro. Trust me. Yeah. Come on.
Come on. What you waiting for?
They don't call it a disabled community
for no reason. lad.
Right. Come on. What is he waiting for?
The link's there.
I've got it here, bro. Come on.
M Street Railway Station 55. Give fuel close.
Order it to the pub, bro. Tell him to
come back on here now.
Tell him to come back on here now.
One second. Tell him to come back on here now.
And I'll just order it wherever, bro.
Just tell him to come back on here now
and stay and stay like stay on the
camera in it. So then I can tell him
where the where the Uber is. I don't
want to hear no excuses. Okay,
>> I'm still waiting for this taxi Peter
outside the street.
>> Timmy, how far you from street around the corner?
>> Right. How far you from street tax the rose? Simple.
>> How far are you from street?
>> No, no, no, no. Rose, it's easy. Weber
spoons. By rose, Birmingham. You can put
it on a new one.
>> Weber spoons off. Right.
>> No, stay live. One second.
>> Yeah. One second. One second.
>> Question. It's very simple. Right.
>> Barley. What's it called? What's it
>> Why can't you order the
>> What is it called? I'm trying to order
you this Uber. What's it called?
>> Well, it's called the Barley Rose.
>> The Barley The Barley Rose.
>> Yes. The Barley Rose.
>> Barley Rose Birmingham. Hold on.
The Barley Rose Birmingham.
>> Yeah. To your mom.
>> I can't find it, lad. I want to be back.
>> I can't I can't I can't find it. I'm
typing it up here now. Barley Barley Rose.
>> Yes, cuz I will go live when the taxi
comes to prove that you
>> I can't find it. The right one. And it's
got to be paid by one second. Find out.
>> Oh, the bribery rose. Okay. One sec.
Stay live. One sec.
>> Okay. I'll be back in a minute cuz I got
>> No, no, no, no, no. I'm ordering you
this. I'm ordering you this thing. I'll
be back. Oh, here it is. Here it is.
>> We'll talk about it now.
>> I'm ordering you this. I'm ordering it.
One second. Don't leave. One second.
There we go. Right.
The Barney Rose. Right. I'm ordering it now. Yeah.
I'm ordering it now to me.
Yeah. I'm ordering it now. Yeah. One
second. Let me screen record this, bro.
I'm ordering this now. One second.
Yeah. Okay. I've ordered it, right? I've
ordered it, Timmy. It's going to be
there in 3 minutes. Make sure you go
outside. Yeah. The registration number is LXY.
And just say and just say my name. Yeah.
Cuz obviously the Uber's in my name.
Yeah. I've just ordered it to me. It's
going to be there in 4 minutes.
Yeah. The the the the three the last
digits of the registration number is LXY. Come on.
Come on to me.
Come on. 4 minutes to finish that pint.
You wanted people to order it. It's been ordered.
Come on. I've ordered it to that to the pub.
You know the registration number? Yep. Right. 3 minutes.
And obviously when he's there, when the
guy doesn't come,
then obviously um I'll I'll just get the money back.
Come on. Way outside to me.
Come on. Don't be a [ __ ] house. You know
the registration number. You just need
to say your name is PJ.
I can track where you are on the journey as well.
There we go. Right. 2 minutes.
2 minutes. Yeah, it's been booked.
The the last three digits of the
registration number is LXY.
And all he has to do is give my name.
But we'll be a waste of a kebab, bro,
because this guy's not this guy is not coming in.
This guy's not coming.
Are you Are you coming? Are you going to
Where is he? He's not joining now.
>> Has it been ordered? So I can wear
>> It's been ordered. Yeah, it's been
ordered. Where are you? You're still in the pub.
>> Party, bro.
>> You're still Yeah, it's been ordered.
You're still at the pub.
>> You're still at the pub. Come outside.
Get in the car. Get in the car. It's a
minute away. Get in the car. Come on.
Where is he?
>> It's He's outside.
>> Let's have a look.
>> It's going to be a minute away. >> Yeah.
>> Right. It's 1 minute away. I don't want
to hear any excuses. >> Yeah.
>> Thanks, bud.
>> Let's have a look. Peter, is he here? >> Yeah.
>> It's one minute away. It's one minute
away. It's one minute away.
>> I'm out.
>> It's a LXY registration. Hey,
>> it's mate. It's 1 minute away. It's
coming. It's coming. It's coming.
>> I want to be back here by
>> It's coming. It's 1 minute away.
>> Why is he left? Now he's left. Okay, one
second. I'm tracking him now.
It should be It should be there now.
All right. It should be there now. LXY,
that's the registration. It should be
there now, mate.
Yeah, it should be there now, lad. All
you got to do is go in and give my name. Simple.
Yeah, you need to go and give my name.
Just say that your name is PJ.
Come on. The driver's name is Muhammad.
Yeah, you know the registration number. Come on.
Come on, lad.
No, you have to pay first.
You have to pay first, lad.
No, the only guess. No, you pay first.
You have to pay. I'm doing it. I'm doing
it via the app. You pay first. But
obviously, if he doesn't come in, then
if he doesn't go in it, then they're
just going to refund my money.
They just refund the money.
Yeah, they just refund the money
obviously if he doesn't get in.
Right. He's there. So,
yeah, he's there.
He's definitely there, lad.
There is a there is a chance because I'm
going to get the money back because he's
not he's not he's not going to come.
He's not going to go. So when he doesn't
go, I'll get the money back. Of course,
there's a chance because they're going
to refund me. It basically re one minute
for a refund, you know.
Come on, lad.
No, I paid
I've already paid £198.
But when he bottles it, obviously I'll
just just cancel in it.
No. No. Where is he? Where is Timmy?
Where is the Uber driver's name is
Muhammad. Where is he?
But where has he gone? Come on.
Is he getting in it or not? Muhammad's
waiting. And they're probably going to
take a fee off now. They're probably
going to take a free off. A fee off.
They're probably going to take a [ __ ] fee off.
Like a fee because obviously he's been waiting, right?
Where the [ __ ] is this [ __ ] He's got six minutes
>> here. Uber don't take the money off you
until you until the journey's over.
>> No, no, it doesn't work like that. Now,
>> what are you telling lies for?
>> No, they they've already took the money.
No, no, no, no, no. They take the money,
you [ __ ] They take the money.
>> I got an Uber from Burman.
>> Listen, mate. I've worked for Uber. I've
worked for Uber. Don't try and tell me how.
>> I've used Uber. I've used Uber a million
times. You got an Uber from Berlin. Say
your report. They take the money off of
you straight away.
>> They didn't take the money off me until I got
>> They take the money first. You don't
know nothing. You don't know nothing.
Anyone that's used Uber would know. They
take the money first. You're a [ __ ]
Everyone knows it. No one's like,
>> "I got an Uber from City Airport."
Uber. They take the money first. They
didn't take the money until I Bye-bye,
[ __ ] See, they're coming out with
lies again. See, this is what I'm
saying. You can't win with these people.
You can't win with these people, lad.
You can't win with them.
Fire stick. You can't win with them.
Anyways, I'm going to give him till 6:40
and then I'm cancel and then obviously
I'm canceling it. It's as simple as that.
He's got four minutes. Where is he?
LXY is the registration number.
Yeah, you can't remember these people, bro.
You can't remember them trying to say
that they don't take the money first.
Now you're trolling. So now you're actually trolling.
Now you're trolling people now. Oh, so you're trolling.
Yeah. I'm I'm giving him four minutes.
He's got four minutes. Yeah. taxi.
>> Yeah, it's outside. You got You got Why
are you going back inside? Why are you
back in the pub? Why are you back in the
pub? It's outside.
>> Where is the taxi?
>> It's outside.
>> You're full of [ __ ] aren't you?
>> No, I'm not full of [ __ ] Come on, big man.
>> Right now, the taxi.
>> Come on then, big man. It's LXY is the
registration number. Why are you back
inside? Come on.
>> I just bought him a point because you're dragging.
>> Oh, cuz you're not coming then. Cuz
you're full of [ __ ]
>> Cuz you're full of [ __ ]
>> Yeah. Yeah. And he's left. See, he's a
[ __ ] See? Where is it? Where is it?
When he's inside. What a [ __ ] It is.
This is why I don't understand. Yeah.
Why he does this? What's the point of
calling people out if you're going to do
this every time? I don't understand.
Lxy Muham Muhammad's waiting for you, you know.
This is what I mean. And then LJ saying
they take the money after. See, then
they just go to trolling. Then they
resort to trolling again.
Then they resort to [ __ ] trolling again.
You know, if he goes outside the pub, he
will see the Uber.
You know, he will see the [ __ ] Uber.
Yeah. Goes back in for a pint.
But I swear to God. Yeah,
he mentions people's [ __ ] name and he
won't meet anyone.
I told you the registration number, you know.
Uh, he is doing it without pay. Yeah,
exact. Well, yeah, exactly. Yeah, it
doesn't matter. Even in London, they
take the payment up front. Even in
London, they take the payment up front.
He's got two minutes, lad. No, I'll give
it two minutes.
His name is Muhammad. Yeah.
Why is he back? Why is he back inside the pub?
Huh? No, it doesn't matter what happens,
bro. It doesn't matter what happens. If
they don't believe me, they don't
believe me. Simple as that. At the end
of the day, he's back in the pub drinking.
So, that's it. He's not outside. He's
not in that Uber that I've ordered and
I'm about to get my money back. Yeah,
I'm tingling it in a minute.
I'm tingling this in a minute. Yeah, you
are a virgin. See you later.
See you later, lads.
There you go. He's
a [ __ ] house, bro. An absolute [ __ ] house.
I've still got my Uber picture cuz it's
on the account.
Well, I'm canceling it now anyways.
You're clearly not getting in it.
I've cancelled it.
>> I cancelled it, lad. >> Yeah.
>> Hello, Pete.
>> Why have you cancelled it?
>> Yeah, he's not. He's not here. Why is he
Why is he not in the cab?
>> Well, you actually ordered it.
>> I Yeah, I ordered it. I've just canled
it now cuz you wasn't getting in it.
Come on, Pete. You're telling Paul he's here. >> 100%.
>> You got like a screenshot or something?
>> Yeah. I don't I don't need to show proof.
>> Well, put it in the backstage so I can
just see it.
>> No, at the end of the day, he wasn't
outside. He should be outside waiting
for that Uber. Why Why did he go back
inside? If I'm lying then, okay, if I'm
lying, why why did he go back inside?
>> It doesn't matter about me, lad.
We just want to see the proof. >> Huh?
>> Just want to see the proof in the pudding.
>> No, but Lord J says I'm lying. So that's
it in it. You think if you think I'm
lying, you think I'm lying. That's it. Simple.
That's it, Dad.
So, yeah. Sorry, man. Someone come in the room.
I'm not screenshot cuz I don't need to
prove anything, lad.
I ordered it. Even when you people get
shown proof, you still talk [ __ ] Why am
I going to show proof, Grezy? One
second, Grezy. One second. One second.
Yeah. You want me to prove it? For what exactly?
Why do I need to prove it? For what reason?
So then, and then if you prove it, then what?
What? So like all of the other things.
Okay. But I've proved I've had sex, but
people still call me a virgin. I proved
I've got money, people still call me
skint. So, you're not really doing it
for me, lad. I mean, someone called me a
virgin earlier and he got 10 thumbs up. So, I mean,
I don't know, bro. I don't think people
It's It's a waste of time. People prove stuff.
>> Where's she taxi,
>> mate? You know, I just canled it. You
know, I just canled it. You know I just
>> No taxi.
>> You know I just canled it. Do you want
me to order it again? Do you want me to
>> Do you want me to order it again?
>> Beat you up.
>> Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Your skin tint.
>> Wait. Do you want me to order it again?
>> Do you want me to order it again?
>> Have a few beers.
>> Do you want me to order it again? Stay
live. Stay. Stay here. Stay here. Do you
want me to order it again?
>> [ __ ] 15 [ __ ]
>> Do you want me to order it again?
>> [ __ ] free drink.
>> I want to order it again. Can you stay?
Can you stay? Can you stay for four or
five minutes? See you.
>> Don't leave. Don't leave. I'm going to
order it. I'm going to order it. Wait.
I'm going to order it again.
>> I'm going to order it again.
>> I'm going to See, look. He won't stay.
Just tell him to stay and I will order
it and he'll be there in about 3 4 minutes >> again.
Yeah. Tell him to stay, bro. Why is he
coming off? Why is he Why is he coming
off? He waited until I said I cancelled
it, so he went outside.
Come on. Come on. Just stay and I will
order it again.
Mr. Bean, tell him to stay and I will
order it again and I'll screenshot it
this time just for you. Just for you.
I'll screenshot it this time just for you. Yeah.
Just for you, lad. Just for you. How
about that one? Yeah. So, tell him to
stay. Tell him to come and stay and
don't leave. Simple.
And you're going to see the car pull up.
You're going to see the car pull up.
You're going to see the car pull up. And
then he's not going to have no excuse.
You understand? Yeah. Simple, right?
The link's up. Are you going to join or what?
It doesn't matter, bro. I got the money
back. I got the money back.
Yeah, I've got the money back. And it
doesn't matter why they do it. Um,
Greasy, why they say that you're this?
They're still doing it. It doesn't
matter. It proves their bias. That was
my point. It doesn't matter why they're
doing it. Whether to make you mad or
whatever, it doesn't matter why they're
doing it. They're doing it.
>> Hello. Right. I'm going to order this. Yeah.
>> My taxi.
>> I'm waiting for taxi. Oh, we got a car.
>> You're waiting outside now. Yeah.
>> Your taxi.
>> Let's have a look.
>> You're waiting? Yeah. Okay. I'm ordering it again. >> Right.
>> Right there. We're asking if that's your
taxi. Let's have a look. Is that an
Uber? Let's have a look. >> Hello.
>> Timmy, you're making a fool of yourself.
I'm going to order this again. Yeah.
[ __ ] I mean, it's like a bird. She didn't know.
>> I'm I'm going to order this again. Yeah.
Are you going to stay outside?
>> Fella, you are
>> Oh, you mate. You went back inside. You
went back inside. You went back inside.
>> You went back inside.
>> You went back inside my [ __ ] way. And
you can't even simple weather.
>> Right. Can you wait outside? Are you Can
you wait for four minutes? Can you wait
for four minutes? I'm ordering this.
>> I'm ordering this.
>> I'm ordering this. Peter, I'll leave you opportunity.
>> Stay here. I'm ordering it. Don't stop
leaving. Don't leave. Don't leave. I'm
ordering it. Don't leave.
>> I'm ordering it. Don't leave. Stay. I'm
ordering it. Can you stay for 4 minutes?
>> Do you know what it was? I was playing a
game from you from day. I was playing a game.
>> Listen, I want to Can you wait for 4 minutes? >> [ __ ]
>> Can you wait for 4 minutes?
>> I have to come to Birmingham first.
>> [ __ ] bell. Can you wait for 4
minutes? See, he won't wait. He won't
wait. He won't wait. See, I'm I will
order it again. I will order it again. Bro,
But he's not He keeps coming off. He
Just say you're going to wait for 4
minutes. Stay with me. Stay with me. And that's it.
This is so autistic, bro.
But yeah, it doesn't matter why they do
it. Um whether it's to get you mad,
whether it's to not get you mad, they do
it. It's as simple as that, Greavvesy.
They do it and they're biased.
So it doesn't matter why they do it. It
it it it shows that there's no point
wasting your time with them.
You know what I'm saying? Like
simple simple, bro.
Simple as that, lad.
Yeah. So, it doesn't matter if it's to
make people mad or not. You're biased,
so no one's going to show anything to
you. But at the end of the day, if he
wants to if he wants to wait, if he
wants to wait, I will order it again.
Simple. I will order it again. Why Why
isn't he waiting at the same spot?
[ __ ] [ __ ] He's a [ __ ] spazzy.
a proper proper proper spaz.
Went back inside, ordered another drink,
and then went back outside when I
cancelled it. He's a [ __ ]
It's just an autistic community. That's
why they call it an autistic disabled community, lad.
And I don't get mad about anyone trying
to call me a virgin. So, you can't say,
lad, you can't say that I I get mad. I
don't get mad at them. I just say that
they're biased and they're idiots for
doing it. When have I gone mad saying,
"Fuck, someone's called me a [ __ ]
bird. You can't."
>> I don't get mad at them. I just state
how they're biased and how you can't win
with them. That's not getting mad.
That's speaking the truth. You know? Yeah.
Yeah. I don't get mad, bro.
I'm just stating what they're doing. You
know what I mean?
And now on, bro. When this guy mentions
my name, I'm just going to ignore him
now. Anyways, just like I ignore the
rest of the other people. Simple.
He ain't going anywhere, mate. He ain't going anywhere.
He's not going anywhere.
I'm not going anywhere.
No, I've already had the win. I've
already had the win, lad. I don't need
to show anything. I'm against showing
No, I'm not showing nothing.
Uh-uh. I'm not showing [ __ ] all. If he
stayed outside, he would have saw the
the registration number. And that's that.
That's what we're going to start doing
now. It's as simple as that.
I'm not showing nothing. Simple.
>> Right. Are you going to wait this time?
>> Where's the taxi, Peter?
>> Right. Where are you going to wait for
me yet? Are you going to wait for this
Uber? I'm serious about this. I'm going
to knock your nose up. So where?
>> Okay. You Wait. Wait. Don't leave. Don't
leave. Do not leave. I'm ordering it.
>> Excuses. Why?
>> I'm ordering it.
>> I'll own you again.
>> I'm ordering it. Yeah.
>> Like I always do. Why?
>> Cuz you can't afford the taxi.
>> Okay. Yeah. I can't it off anytime any
ordering it now. Yeah. Don't leave.
>> Don't leave.
>> Do not leave. Do not leave. Do not
leave. Are you going to stay? Yeah. Are
you staying? Just are you staying? Are
>> Are you staying?
>> No, that's not that's some woman. That is a baker.
>> Are you staying? Do you mind me?
>> Are you staying or not? Are you staying
for for three minutes? Notice. Yeah.
>> Are you ordering?
>> Are you a [ __ ]
>> Are you staying? Can I order this taxi
for so you can stay
up and get the taxi? You better stay.
>> Okay. I'm ordering it now. Yeah. Okay,
I'm ordering it now. There we go. [ __ ]
>> There we go. Yeah. Right.
One second, bro.
Do you want me to just order it, Grezy?
Do you just want me to just order it again?
Do you want me to just order it again?
Simple. Because he's not listening, bro.
Do you want me to just order it again,
bro? Cuz I'm I'll just order it again. Yeah. Yeah. Okay.
Right. I'm ordering it now. Yeah. Simple.
Right. It's been ordered.
There we go.
Right. Let's see if he comes back. Yeah. [ __ ] bro.
One second, bro.
The Bravari Rose weather spoons. Yeah.
Simple as that, bro. All right,
one second. Let me put the link back up. One second.
There we go. One sec.
Hold on, bro.
I don't want this guy using any excuses. Yeah. You know,
I think that needs to be bigger than the
actual live stream thing. Yeah,
it seems like you're far from this
point. Do you need someone? >> Yo,
>> you're seriously busting my balls here.
>> Right. Are you stay Can you stay for Can
you stay for three minutes?
>> Right. Stay on Stay on the live stream. Yeah.
>> Stay on the live stream. Yeah.
>> Now, I [ __ ] want to hurt you.
>> Right. Stay on the live stream. Stay in
the live stream. Yeah.
>> Cuz you cuz you know I will [ __ ] hurt you.
>> You're not going to hurt no one, mate.
You You You're back inside again. You're
back inside again. No, she's warm, mate.
>> You're back inside again.
>> Right. I'm leaving in a minute, Peter.
So, so sorry. I apologize.
>> Are you stay Oh, you stay here.
>> Right. Can you stay on now?
>> Can you stay on?
>> Okay. Can you stay on?
>> 5 minutes maximum. I'm going to Shirley
and you have to order it from there. Right.
>> Can you stay on?
>> You have been yet and yet again.
>> Okay. Are you Are you staying on? Yeah.
That's the skid monk.
>> Are you staying on? And he's left again.
See, it's just talking. He's just a
wobbler. He's just a wobbler.
A wobbler, bro. He's just a wobbler.
He's not meeting no one and he will
never meet anyone. Simple as that. He keeps leaving.
He keeps leaving, bro.
He's an He's an idiot, bro.
Yeah, because he's not going anywhere,
bro. He's not going anywhere. That's why.
That's why, lad.
I know. It's embarrassing, bro. So, it's
a proper disabled community, isn't it?
There we go. One sec.
There we go, lad.
You wanted a screenshot? Yeah.
Right. One second. Connecting you to a driver.
Finding drivers nearby. One second.
Give it a sec.
It's loading. It's loading. It's loading, bro.
There we go. Pick up in 5 minutes. Right. XXV.
Don't need no excuses. Put the
screenshot up now. Yeah. XX.
One second, lad. Got it right here.
Just 5 minutes away.
Don't need any excuses, bro.
There we go.
No excuses. No excuses.
XXV want to hear no excuses. It's right
there, bro. I'll send it to you on I'll
send it to you, bro, on uh
There you go. I'll send it to you on uh Instagram, bro.
There we go. I sent it to you, bro.
You don't have the money. There you go.
You've been sent it on Instagram, Grezy.
I don't hear no excuses now.
There you go, lad. I've sent it to you on Instagram.
He's 4 minutes away.
4 minutes away, lad.
33 minutes away. Come on to me.
One minute away. He's one minute away
now. No excuses,
Timmy. No excuses. Come on.
He's one minute away. Come on. No excuses.
Did it cost me £200? Come on, Timmy.
Come on. Come on. Come on.
Come on, lad.
Right. He's 0.2 two miles away, which is
a minute. Come on to me.
His name is Vasel. There you go. Come on.
£196. It's cost me. You can't.
He's arriving now. Come on to me.
Come on to me. What are you waiting for?
Where is it? I'm tracking the guy right now, bro.
Guys, got a few minutes to get there,
lad. Or I'm canceling this.
Come on to me.
He's right outside, lad. He's got no excuse.
He's got no excuse, bro.
>> Right. The driver's dead to me. I'm
drinking it. I'm willing to wait.
>> No, no, no, no, no, no, no. He's there
now. He's there now. Come on, you little
[ __ ] He's there now. He's outside now. Come on.
>> Come on, you little [ __ ] Come on, you
>> Come on, you little [ __ ] To everyone that
>> Come on, you little He's outside. He's
arrived. Go outside. Go outside.
>> He's outside. He is outside.
>> He is outside. Go outside.
Mate, he's got outside. Everyone see
>> Tim. He's ordered you a taxi. It's outside.
>> He's outside. Come on.
>> It's outside. Tim,
>> he's outside.
>> It's outside. STOP THE [ __ ] COME OUTSIDE.
>> It's outside. Slug.
>> Go outside.
>> Slug. It's outside.
>> I'm giving him three I'm giving him a
couple of minutes, bro. He's outside the
pub. Go outside.
[ __ ] hell. I can't believe I put the
screenshot up as well, by the way. I'm
putting the screenshot up, by the way,
so you can see.
>> Yeah. Okay, I will. I'll put on my community post.
>> And he's not going outside. Slug, delete
the app. You're finished on here. You
let this clown bully. >> Yeah.
Come on. He's got two minutes. And
there's no reason why he can't come in.
There's no reason why. Come on. All you
got to do is go outside. Come on.
What is he waiting for?
Come on. Now he can never talk [ __ ]
again. He can never call Monty man out
ever again. Now he's had a 200 pound
taxi paid for him. He's had a 200 pound
taxi paid for him. Yeah. Simple, right?
Come on. He's waiting for you, Timmy.
Come on, Timmy. He's waiting. He's
waiting. Come on. Come on.
He can never call Monty man out again.
Please don't let this guy talk about
fighting anymore, bro. Please. He's had
a 200 pound [ __ ] cab paid for him,
man. He's not coming out.
Just Just Timmy, you can never ever ever
call anyone out again, bro. Come on.
Come on, Timmy. Before I unconfirm this trip, come on.
He's waiting for you. Come on. Waiting.
I'm going to give him another minute.
These people, lad. Come on.
Come on, mate. He's literally outside.
Well, I'm canceling it now.
Here we go.
That's cost me6 out of my own money for
a [ __ ] cuz I've had to cancel it. I
gave the guy6 for his time. I didn't
have to, but just give him six pound.
Just give the just give the poor fucker6.
There you go.
There we [ __ ] go.
You bro, you [ __ ] [ __ ]
Stop calling people out, you [ __ ] [ __ ] lad.
Yeah, I gave him6 tip. Poor [ __ ] Poor [ __ ] lad.
Yeah, he'll join back in a minute, mate.
He knew where he was. He was outside for
like 6 minutes, lad.
He was outside for 6 minutes.
Yeah, he was out He was outside for 6
minutes, bro. He can never ever ever
call anyone out again, bro.
He can never call anyone out again.
Ever, bro. He can't. He literally he he
refused to jump in a paid taxi. He can't
ever call anyone out ever again, bro.
One second, bro.
Yep. I'm doing this on a community post. Yeah.
on a community post on it now.
So he mentions and then even when people
and I told him he can meet London Taylor
as well. I'm not scared of him either.
If he wants to come if he wants to come
with him as well cuz we know he likes to
try to get himself involved. He can also
bring him as well because he's going to
get involved in it. So that's it. Look,
there you go. You got all the proof now.
So there you go.
Stop [ __ ] calling people out, you
[ __ ] [ __ ] telling people that
they're [ __ ] skin. You don't know how
much [ __ ] money people have, you
[ __ ] clown. There you go. Look, it's
on the community post. [ __ ] [ __ ] that proper.
He's a [ __ ] bro. A [ __ ]
Imagine you didn't get the money back.
He's a [ __ ] [ __ ] lad.
Did you look at my community post on my
main channel, Grezy? It's all there.
And he's calling people out and then
someone's off. See, see, I said this to
Terry multiple times. Yeah. I said this
to Terry multiple times. If you gave me
that offer, I would have jumped in the
Uber. I would have jumped in the cab. I
would have jumped in the Uber.
I would have jumped in the cab. I would
have jumped in the Uber.
If he comes back, I'm going to I'll just
order it again. If he comes back, I'll
It's as simple as that. I'll order it
again. If he comes back, I'll just keep
ordering it. As simple as that.
Then you'll be [ __ ] isn't it? [ __ ] [ __ ] Yeah. So, yeah.
She's a [ __ ] idiot, isn't it?
[ __ ] idiot, bro.
No, I didn't give the other one a tip to be honest.
He just embarrasses himself in it. He He
just embarrasses himself in it. He does,
bro. Is it? Yeah.
[ __ ] [ __ ] bro.
He's a [ __ ] Yeah.
Yeah. They're not going to deny it
because they don't like him. That's the
reason why they're not going to deny it,
Grezy, cuz they hate Timmy. But if they
didn't hate Timmy, then they would have, lad.
Do you get it?
Then obviously, you know, then they
couldn't, you know, then they would deny
it. They would deny it.
That guy has done 1540 trips.
1540 trips he's done. Wow.
That's pretty impressive, isn't it, Greasy?
So, he comes on YouTube mentioning
people's names. He's been doing this all
day. He gets people to order him a taxi
and then he doesn't even step in step in
the taxi. How long would have it took? 2
hours. What's the day today? Monday. I
reckon he could have got here in about 2 hours.
I reckon he could have got here in about
2 hours. It's Monday today, is it? So,
the traffic wouldn't have been that bad.
The [ __ ] He could have got here in
about 2 hours, I reckon. Greasy.
Monday. Is it
mate? The taxi was ordered to where I
ordered it to.
You understand, lad? Yeah. So,
we would have just directed him to where
it was. I can prove I ordered it from
there as well. I can show where I
ordered it, lad.
I can actually show exactly where I've
ordered it as well.
Yeah. One sec.
This is good. Like this, bro.
Where do you see where your orders are, lad? Yeah.
Just Timmy needs to stop this [ __ ] lad. Activity
six pound. Yeah. Yeah. There we go, lad.
25 Bets Hill, Birmingham, West Midlands.
There you go.
So, he was actually prepared to drive
all the way here, Greezy. [ __ ] hell. Madness.
So, he's wasted people's time. He's
wasted people's time. And then maybe the
taxi driver could have got involved with
Grezy. The taxi driver could have got
involved as well.
So that's enough evidence now to surely
take back what he's saying about people
not having money, right? Um Greasy.
So that's how much money we spent today.
like over 200 pound that come from our
um pocket even though we got the two uh
well 200 pound back. So now he can stop
projecting he skip this on people as
well, can't he?
He said that he wanted people to show
20. Well, you got shown more than 10
times 20 today and you bottled it at the
same time. So it's a double it's a
double win, isn't it?
Yeah. So it's a double uh it's a double
win then, isn't it? Yeah.
Is Kitty going to Monty's? Really?
Is Kitty really going Monty's or no? I'm
on it right now, but I know where she's going.
Timmy's been embarrassed today. He calls people skin.
People shown they've got money by ordering that.
Am I lying, Greasy? Tell me I'm lying.
I'm not lying, am I? Nah.
So, you said that someone's skin.
You said that someone's skin,
I need to talk to my mom. One sec,
mom. Did you see the video with the cat?
That's enough Tik Tok for today.
And it started going mad.
Yeah, he like the cat likes Tik Tok.
That's enough Tik Tok for today. Bless you.
By is half asleep.
Bless her. Bless her alive.
That's enough Tik Tok for today. Yep. 196
But you see why I bring up LT though is
in it Greavesy. You know why I bring up
LT in it? Because if he comes to London,
what will happen is say Timmy goes to
London. Yeah. Let's just say he got a
train to London, right? And I met him.
What do you think the first thing is
going to happen? LT is going to be on
here saying, "Oh, you meet these other
people." You know what's going to
happen, bro? Whether it's a day later,
two days later, because people are
always watching. So I think, okay, well,
both of you, if you came down to London,
I would have met him with anyone. I
don't give a [ __ ] who it is. I don't care, bro.
Cuz you know exactly what's going to
happen. You know exactly what's going to
happen. Is it [ __ ] [ __ ]
He's a [ __ ] bro.
calling people skint that's got more
money than him saying he's going to meet people.
But now when he mentions my name now
when when he talks about meeting people
now do you know what I'm going to do?
I'm just going to laugh.
Can we all laugh at it now when he says
he's going to meet someone again?
Griezy. Can we just laugh at him?
Can we just laugh? Can we just laugh
when he calls people out now?
Is she actually going to monies?
That's enough Tik Tok for today.
It went bad, didn't it? The cat. That's
enough Tik Tok for today. Yes.
If he ordered me a taxi, I would have
jumped in it. And I don't even like
motorways, bro. I don't even like motorways.
Think about it. It's jumping in a car.
If the guy can't jump in a car that's
paid for, how is he meeting anyone?
Gregy, how is he ever going to meet
anyone? If you can't jump in a car
that's paid for, then
so why? Okay. So cuz I because I because
I gave you some entertainment today. Um Greavvesy,
why did why was Nons saying Chev's attractive?
Come on. After all, I did give you some
content, poor [ __ ]
I did give you some content. Listen,
you you scratch my back, Greasy.
I I'll scratch yours.
You scratch my back. I scratch yours.
So now that's it from Timmy now. He'll
never come back, will he, Grievy? He
won't be calling people out again, will
he? He won't be talking about people
again, will he?
He won't be calling people out, will he? You know,
at least we prove Mont was lying. I wasn't lying.
The screenshots. The screenshot. The
taxi was there.
Oh, so now they're going to try and use
the excuse that it's not the place to
where it should have been.
Oh, Jesus [ __ ] Christ, bro. Yeah,
they can't do that, bro. Really can't.
Cuz if he went outside and it wasn't
there, then he would have found it,
wouldn't he? Grezy,
we were all waiting for him to jump in
the taxi. Grezy, we were waiting like
the guy in the shop.
[ __ ] hell, bro.
Yeah, he's just like nons. He's just
like his boyfriend, isn't he? A lot of similarities.
They've got a lot of similarities.
No, it won't be. It won't be again, bro.
Because if anyone entertains him Yeah.
If anyone had any if anyone ever had if anyone Yeah,
bro. If anyone has got a brain in this
community, they won't argue with him again.
All he had to do was jump in the cab for
about 2 hours. It's a Monday, bro. The
traffic would have been that bad.
It wouldn't have been that bad.
£200 is nothing to me, bro. I said I
would do a round trip.
Yeah. You understand?
Yeah. So why didn't he get in? Bro, it's
only two. I'm I'm sure it would have
been no longer than 2 hours at this time
of night on a Monday. I don't think it
would have been.
What do you think? I'd say about 2
hours. Maybe 2 hours and 10. It wouldn't
have been long.
2 hours and 26 minutes it's saying.
So I reckon they could have got there a
bit quicker though.
It's a Monday, isn't it? So
doesn't matter how long it would be to
be fair. All he had to do was jump in.
He got it paid for, so
he can't talk [ __ ] anymore. He's had a
200 pound tax he paid for. He wouldn't
jump in. So that's it. He's a [ __ ] That's it.
And now he'll go quiet now. I don't
think he'll come back on it ever again
now, will he? Griezy. Nope.
He won't come back on now, will he?
Ever again? I don't think now.
No, I think he's done for.
No, I already ate. I had Chinese,
you know. I already had Chinese.
You know, I had Chinese lads. So,
No, he hasn't. No.
Did you actually think he was going to
jump in the taxi, Grezy? Seriously, you
really think him of all people is going
to is going to sit is going to is going
to sat is going to sit in a taxi for two hours?
If he was really going to do something
like that, he would have jumped the
train. Come on, bro. It's not It's not
[ __ ] It's not rocket science, you know?
I'm going to do a video to him as well.
Nah, of course he wouldn't. What? He's
going to sit in a taxi. Nah, no way.
Yeah, but he would have not got in it. I
don't think he would have got in it.
He wouldn't have got in it.
He wouldn't have got in it, lad.
He might have, but he wouldn't have got in it.
I reckon he would have had more chance
getting in it drunk than sober, I reckon.
So, he's been proved on two things
today. That he is the one that skimmed
and he is the one that will never meet anyone.
You said that people are skint lad.
You [ __ ] [ __ ] Yeah.
So I don't understand why he comes on
YouTube doing this.
Anyone that argues with him now,
they're, like I said, they're stupid.
Anyone that argues with him now, they're stupid.
If you can't even jump in a car, right?
Yeah. I tipped the guy six. He said,
"Oh, do you want to tip him or no?" I
just said, "Yeah, because poor fucker."
Greasy. He was waiting around like a
[ __ ] for 6 minutes. Poor [ __ ]
And I know I'd like to be [ __ ]
tipped, you know, if I'm [ __ ] waiting
for some [ __ ] They've had to drive as
well, like 5 minutes. Poor [ __ ] You know,
The Uber driver doesn't know it's
YouTube, does he, Grezy?
He doesn't know it's YouTube, does he?
He doesn't know it's YouTube, in it,
so he drops Timmy off. Yeah. And then
there's a fight. Oh [ __ ] Yeah.
Who's my mama now? Greavvesy
question is he's my mama.
She's my mama. It
There's There's no Uber driver. Well,
there was an Uber driver because it's on
my community post.
Well, there is an Uber driver, mate,
because it's on my community post. All the screenshots.
So, yes, there is. That's the good thing
with having this fold phone. You multitask.
There [ __ ] well is. Yeah.
Well, there is because it's on my community post. >> Yeah.
>> And remember he was trying to say, "Oh,
if I had a car, I'd drive there." I done
him one even better. I paid a 200 pound
Uber and he couldn't even step in it.
So, if he can't even step in an Uber,
mate, it's already on my community post
on my main channel. Everyone's seen it.
If he can't even step in an Uber Greavvesy
that's paid for, I don't think he's
going to be driving to no London somehow.
I don't think he's going to be driving
to no London, is he?
He's showing her face now. Where is she?
Don't go Mon now.
Oh, [ __ ] hell, bro.
yeah. Look, it's been recorded. If I had
a car today. R
If I had If I had If I had a car today,
you had a car paid for you.
I would have come today. [ __ ] off.
[ __ ] off, man. Yep.
You you can see it on my community post.
Yeah, that's what he does cuz he's never
going to meet anyone. What he does is he
does his balls in starts calling people
skin when he skin himself
says that he's going to fight people and
then he doesn't.
He's a [ __ ] Look how you should have
known that with with the whole Monty
thing. You know that when the whole
Monty and Timmy thing was going on, bro,
that took about a month for them to
actually meet. They kept going back and
forth and back and forth and back and
forth and back and forth.
It went on, bro, for how long did that
go on for that Monty and Timmy thing?
And they were doing anything in their
power to not meet. Yet they lived in the same place.
They lived in the same city.
You know, mad, bro. [ __ ] madness.
Why can't I like dance anymore?
I love that, bro. I love that.
Come on. Peter Belly's worked hard to
give you content. You po [ __ ] Yep. Yeah.
Do you remember Timmy? I'm going to
knock him out. You're not going to knock
no one out. You [ __ ] [ __ ] house. Shut up, man. Shut up.
I got a headache now.
So, anything he says now, well, I won't
be entertaining, but anything he says
now, anything he says now, all you need
to say is, "Mate, you got a 200 taxi
ordered for you and you didn't even step
in it. [ __ ] off." Absolutely [ __ ] off.
Something that Terry's never done for
me, yet when he's come on here and spoke
the most [ __ ] [ __ ] off, man. [ __ ] off.
He went in a pub with a full pint. Greavvesy. Mad.
He's going to come out with an excuse, isn't he?
He's going to come out with an excuse.
But I have 20 to my name. I lost my last 20 apparently.
Yeah, I lost my last 20 apparently. H. Yeah.
Yeah. Literally. But it's not just him.
It's nons legs as well. You show more
money than them. They speak [ __ ] You
show you've had sex. They still call you
virgin. You know, he's not the only one,
bro. You can't win with any of them.
It's a bit like that with most of the
people in this community. Yeah.
Yep, I would have paid for a return as well.
You never know how much money people
have when you don't know when you don't
know who you're talking about. That's
also a lesson to stop talking about
people that you don't know. Isn't that
right, Greavesy? Stop talking about
people that you don't know. You know,
stop talking about people that you don't
know. That's a good lesson to come from
this as well.
You're making videos. You've been on all
day saying that people don't have this
and people don't have that and people
don't have this and people don't have that.
Yeah. People can't afford what was it?
an arch from Big Mac. An arch burger. I
almost lost that like £10, bro.
Yeah, he said I can't afford an arch.
What the [ __ ] is he going on about, bro?
Just a [ __ ]
Tom Wood said it's like playing a um
chess with a pigeon. Even if you beat
the pigeon, it will strut around and act
like it's one and shhat all over the
chess and [ __ ] all over the chess board.
It's like playing chess with a pigeon.
I love that little quote.
It's pretty accurate though, isn't it? Yeah.
So, he's been shown 200 pound today,
Greasy. So that means he has to show 400, right?
That means he has to show 400, isn't it?
So taxi 200. Yeah. So he's been shown
two. He's been shown £200 basically,
hasn't he? So he also has to show us £400
cuz you remember he said about playing
the money game, right?
You remember Griezy? He come on earlier
showing 70 and said that people didn't have money.
You know what I'm saying, bro?
Yeah. Okay. So, then he has to show £400
as well. He needs to show £400 as well.
Yeah. So, he has Okay. So, then he has
to show £400 then. Okay. So, forget the
pass, right? Okay. So, forget the past
like years ago. So, I've shown 200
pound. So, he has to show£400 now. Yeah.
So, he has to show £400 now. it. Yeah.
Yeah. So, he has to show £400
cuz he said I was skinn.
So, he has to show£400.
So, I proved today that he's a [ __ ]
house and I proved that he was also
talking about himself.
Nah. No, I'm lazy, bro. No, I'm lazy.
I didn't mind paying the four or500. I'm
just lazy, you know.
Why am I going to do that? Why am I
going to Why am I going to get a cab on
a Monday to then stay in a hotel on a
Monday to come back?
No, it's not about starting the money
game again. He's been shown 200 today.
He's been shown 200 today theoretically,
but he called people skin. He said that
people don't have 20.
Okay, [ __ ] that then. Okay, he said that
people don't have to He said that people
have lost their last 20 pound. Did you
not watch his video earlier? He said
that people lost their last 20 pound. Now
I showed 210 today.
Yeah, but he said I lost my last 20. So
yeah, he proved that he's talking about himself again. Yeah.
And I'm done with these people now.
Anyways, lads, I'm going to do one last
video to this clown and that's it.
And you can pretend that you're going to
meet people and pretend you didn't see
this. Like, no. Shut up. Shut the [ __ ]
up. Yeah. Simple. That's that 101 excuses,
you know, just like his boyfriend. Not
legs. Both self projectors. [ __ ] Yeah, man.
I need a drink, lad.
Like a Coke drink. Oh, that's what I
mean by I drink like a Coke. [ __ ] hell.
Oh, a headache, bro.
Yeah, I've already got it back. I've
I just won't drink a Coke today, bro. I
can't be asked to be fair.
Yeah, it makes your mouth dry.
But he come on today and he said that I was skimmed.
Yeah. But he said that I was skimmed. He
said I didn't have 20.
He said that I didn't have 20.
He said that people are skinned and they
don't have 20 and I showed more money
than him today.
Again, stop talking about yourself.
Something like something like your
something what your nods boyfriend does
like to talk about people that you don't know Yeah, man. One second.
I got Laura J trying to follow me on
Instagram. So obvious. >> Yep.
One second, brother.
It's like playing chess with a pigeon. >> Yep. Oh,
I fancy playing some roulette, lads. Oh,
what the [ __ ] man? I'm not going to,
man. But yeah, I won't I'm not going to
play it. Yeah.
I'm okay. I'm okay. I'm okay. I might
have I'm okay.
He's a [ __ ] No wonder.
No wonder he sticks up for launch legs.
He's another launch legs.
He's another nonsleg. Steven Howard.
He's another nonslex.
You'll you'll wait.
Yes. Until it's been made. Yep. Listen
to him. PJ is skin. Call his bluff and
go to where he wants. He won't get the
taxi. Uhhuh. See,
self projection gets you nowhere in life, lad. my head.
Yep. It's not going to blow over cuz I'm
doing a video on M Grezy. It's not going
to blow over.
It's not going to blow over, lad. Cuz
I'm doing a video.
Okay with you, boss.
Grievy. Is that okay with you, boss, if
I do a little video?
Do you want my opinion, Greasy?
They're all [ __ ]
What's your opinion?
Your skin. Your skin. Your skin.
they're all [ __ ]
You like little doggies. Greed. You like
baby French fencies. Baby French
bulldogs. They're cute, aren't they?
Yeah, they're cute, isn't it?
You're not having a takeaway tomorrow,
are you? Greasy.
What is Timmy another nonsleg? Steven
Howard seems so.
It seems he's another nonsleg, doesn't it? Yeah,
I think he's another launch legs lan.
He's another launch legs.
Yeah, Timmy's another launch legs.
[ __ ] couple of quid. You ain't got a
couple of quid. And even does he have a
couple of quid? You're both [ __ ] skin.
[ __ ] little virgins.
Little virgins in it.
You don't care about trying to fit in,
do you, Greavvesy?
You've never really I've noticed that
about you. You've You was never really
one to fit in, was you?
I'm going to try and I'm going to try
and spend £3 tomorrow on food and a drink.
I'll see how far that gets me, Greavvesy.
Let's see how far that gets me.
£3. What could you get for £3?
What the [ __ ] could you get for £3? I'll
think of something.
I'm going to start this challenge.
Not for £3 pound. I don't think you could. Yeah.
Wings. Oh yeah, you can. This place
sells 17 wings for £5.
That's quite cheap, isn't it?
Yeah, but I'll need to buy a drink as well.
I lost two days dinner because of
Greavves. Uh because of Timmy Greavvesy.
Two days I lost two days dinner because of him.
Six pound. I lost two days dinner.
I know he's got autism.
It's like his boyfriend Nons.
He was sucking his dick earlier. He was
like, "Oh, well, why do you think Nons
has a few quid?" Uh, easy. Because he
doesn't have a few quid. He's [ __ ] skint.
Bit like you, Timmy. Bit like you, lad.
Right. I think it's roulette time. Steven Howard.
Yeah, I reckon it's roulette time, lad.
Yeah, it's roulette time, lad.
Is it [ __ ]
Never. I'm going to do a football bet on Saturday.
I'll do a football bet on Saturday.
We doing a football bet Saturday,
Stephen. How would you
dodge has gotten worse on the football?
Oh, look at this dog.
Oh, here we go.
Here we go.
Here we go. Greasy. Oh gosh.
Oh gosh. I did that little saying here.
There's the link. Come on.
I come up with it, didn't I, Grezy?
>> Oh, you little [ __ ] house.
>> Porker. I mean, not porker because we
all know Dusty's [ __ ] [ __ ] Dusty.
No one's done anywhere. Pete has been
done for years. Your best mates, right? Your best.
>> Why didn't you come in a taxi?
>> Marshall's pip. So, I know it's you,
Steven Harshall's pip. Right. So, you've
never left your house. These [ __ ]
>> Why didn't you come in the taxi?
>> Right. Let's get to the point, right?
>> Why didn't you order my taxi, Peter? Now,
>> I ordered your taxi.
>> Get Smokey Be to order it. Right. I'll be back.
>> See, this is what he does. This is what
>> Pointless, bro. It's pointless.
This is what he does. Greasy.
I'm getting roulette urges. Greavvesy,
bless me if I'm getting roulette urges.
No, my [ __ ] bro. My [ __ ]
No, my [ __ ] lad.
Yeah, the odds are really crap. I'm
thinking we need to do a both teams to
score and a team to win.
[ __ ] I'm thinking we need to do both
teams to score and a team to win.
Yeah, that's what we need to do. We need
to do both teams to score and and the
actual team to win.
That's what I'm going with anyways.
That's what I'll go with.
Give it a little while. Grezy, I would
like you. Give it a little while.
Yeah, I would.
Give a little while. Remember
Greavvesy, them [ __ ] were laughing at
us, mocking us. Grezy, them [ __ ] were
laughing at you.
And when I said to that account, "It
wasn't you, it was us." Then he changed
it. Them [ __ ] were laughing at us.
It was trolling me, Quezy. That account
was trolling me.
You know exactly what I'm talking about.
Ain't it? Laughing at you, mocking you. Yeah.
>> We're laughing at you, mocking you.
So why don't you meet me taxi? [ __ ]
dusty is a [ __ ] lowlight. You and me
talking now you internet [ __ ] [ __ ]
olds who sit their bed seats making out
the gangsters knocking people who can I
mean Ding's a bit of a prick but at
least he can [ __ ] afford.
>> Why didn't you get in a taxi mocking
Ding who didn't get in the taxi?
>> So [ __ ] off you little bastard. Right.
Let's get to the point. We'll talk men.
Right. Why didn't you order my taxi?
>> Why didn't you get in the taxi? You
didn't order my taxi, brother. You did
not order my taxi.
>> A [ __ ] sake, bro. I give up.
>> I give up, bro. I give up. I completely
give up, lad. Sorry. I've had to kick
him out. I give up.
I give up. Greasy, lad. Now be saying I
haven't ordered the taxi.
I give up, bro.
You can't win, lad. You can't win.
She's fit. Grievesy,
what does that remind you of? She's fit.
Yeah. She's so fit. Oh my god.
You're a little copycat,
bro. She doesn't even make my dick hard.
My dick don't even go hard.
Is my Is my dick supposed to go hard at
an average looking person?
>> Jimmy, why didn't you come?
>> So, why won't you let Oh, you let me
back in. So, Peter, right, order my taxi
now. I'll get smoky cuz I will come down
tonight. I'm winning and that's not a
threat. That's a promise. Not like
>> I already ordered your taxi.
>> Pokemon sleeping assore [ __ ] pip flats. Right.
>> [ __ ] He plays Pokemon. Right. We'll talk.
>> I already ordered your taxi.
>> I'll get Smokey to pay for the taxi.
>> Right. I'm in Shirley now. I'll even
give the address. >> Timmy.
>> No, I already ordered your taxi. How
>> serious? I'm going to hurt you.
>> You're going to hurt me? I don't think
realize your best mate Dusty realizes
how serious this is cuz you're going to
hurt me. I go with your [ __ ] pyo who
I'm the [ __ ] doll.
>> I will meet you when you don't expect it, lad.
>> Oh yeah, yeah, yeah. You're another Jo
then. You're another Jo.
>> Peter, you power to pay for the taxi. If
you want if you want to fight, guys,
smokey be I'm serious. Order it. I'll
get the train back the next day. I'm going to
>> I already ordered your taxi.
You can't you can't win with him, lad.
It's like playing chess with a pigeon, Mr. B.
You can't It's like playing chess with a pigeon.
Even if you beat the pigeon,
it will strut around and [ __ ] all over
the board and act like it's one.
Greavesy. It's like playing chess with a pigeon. Yep.
Well, Monty man wasn't watching today,
was he? Griezy.
So, when I Grezy, so when I do videos on
Tibby, does Monty see it? Does
We does Monty's here.
Are you telling P keys, Mr. B? You ask
me. No, I'm not telling P keys.
No, I'm not telling P keys, lad. Jeez fit.
Okay, Grezy. Well, I I might get myself
a Canada goose coat.
What's your opinion on that? I'm I'm
going to I'm going to get myself a
Canada goose coat.
How do you feel about that? Greasy.
That's enough Tik Tok for today.
You going mad. The little cat was going
Doesn't even give me a boner. Sh.
Don't see it. Definitely. I don't see
what all the hust and fuss was about, lads. Sorry.
Sorry to keep repeating this. This just
looks like someone you'd
you'd see um you see on the street.
Don't see what the hust and fuss was about. Nothing special at all.
Definitely not anything to question
people's sexuality about if a certain
person's watching Grezy.
Definitely definitely not.
Definitely. Definitely not. No.
[ __ ] weirdo, bro.
Oh, my screen's gone now.
Sorry about that, lad. My [ __ ] screen went
greasy. Phone is looking a bit dodge.
It's looking a bit dodge, lad.
So, you're kicking me out the hangouts again. Okay.
>> Why didn't you come in the taxi?
>> And I'm giving you address now. The pump house, right?
>> Why didn't you come in a taxi?
>> You don't get it. I am winning for this
tonight, Pete. I know you're [ __ ]
dusty talking that I don't go with these
playground people. All
right, we'll talk. Shut your mouth and
hear me out. Right,
>> Jimmy? Why don't you come in a taxi?
Taxi. I'll be your 55 address within the
next 3 hours.
>> Oh, really?
>> That's not [ __ ] sake. He needs to fill it in.
>> Okay, come on then.
>> Right. Like his little gangster [ __ ]
harsh pit. Right.
>> Why didn't you come in the taxi?
>> He's going to get up.
>> Why didn't you come in a taxi? So if you
want to see some blood and guts, you
want to get attacked Smokey. Game on. Pump house.
Oh [ __ ] hell, bro. He's a [ __ ] house in here.
the [ __ ] outside.
Is this meat going to happen or what?
Grezy, is this [ __ ] meat going to happen?
Is this meet up going to happen or what?
I need to go and get some drink, bro.
I want to get some drink.
So, what about tomorrow? Is something
going to happen, Graves? Huh?
I fancy some popcorn.
Okay with you, [ __ ]
Is that all right with you, [ __ ]
All right with you, [ __ ]
So why did Timmy say I was skin? Um,
Timmy. So, why?
Yeah, I love that. You can if you want,
but I won't be there.
Yeah, you can if you like, but I won't be there.
Yeah, is a lovely little saying. Yeah,
we're going to go and we can go and we
can go and see USA Izzy if you want. You
can if you like, but I won't be there.
Well, I won't be there.
>> Are you coming to London?
>> I think that we hardly. I don't think
you understand. I'll be like banger.
I'll come when you don't expect it.
>> Uh blah blah blah blah blah blah blah. Bye-bye now.
He's called me skint.
He called me skint.
So Steven Howard, the most you're
putting on the football now is what? 20 pound, right? Oh,
I need to nip you to the shop, Breezy.
So, you're just going to wait until I
come back, right?
That's okay. I'll just wait until you come back.
You'll You wait? Yes. Until you come back.
You You wait.
Yes. until you come back.
This [ __ ] has cost me [ __ ] money today.
Six [ __ ] pound. Could have bought
some wings with that. Greasy.
I don't know. I fancy something, bro.
But I don't like something sweet,
Greasy. You know when you fancy
something quite sweet
and you don't know what.
It's [ __ ] very annoying, bro.
You get me?
You get me, Grezy?
Yeah. I said to my mate, I'm going to go
out next week with him for a drink.
Well, this week, but I won't be there.
He'll show up, Grezy. You can if you
like, but I won't be there.
can if you like.
>> I won't be there.
>> He'll be waiting until I come.
Right. I'll be back in a moment.
>> Just going to get some snacks.