Sorry, I'm back.
Thought about that.
I'm not that Come on. Ah,
yeah. I went to get some popcorn and poke. Mhm.
I think I'm probably done after today, lad.
I lost brain cells.
This community makes you lose brain cells.
The spastics in it.
Proper recharge, lad.
YouTube should pay me, bro. Even if it's
like £500 a month.
>> Yeah, they should pay me, lad.
I think that's the only way I'd stay on
here if I was getting paid to.
If I was getting paid to, I was on
today, bro, cuz of Timmy. I wanted to
show everyone that he's a [ __ ] Billy bullshitter.
You know what I mean? Dusty [ __ ]
Well, I'm coming up in a bit. Yeah. A [ __ ] no [ __ ] virgin.
Look at these versions of this [ __ ] community. Mhm. Okay. Don't.
Yeah, I got some popcorn and some tic tac.
Okay with you, boss.
I spent5, bro. [ __ ] it on.
All right. This woman wasn't opening my messages. Greasy on Instagram
and as soon as I sent her a picture, she opened it.
So what's he being a little ignory?
What's he being a little ignorer?
was she being a little ignor for a grave day. Yeah.
>> Yeah. So, we'll do a 10 pound football
bet on Saturday. Yeah.
Okay with you, boss.
seeing a messages but she's not responding.
Oh, Smokey B paid for it and not me. Impossible.
Impossible, lad. I put the screenshots
up with my card. That's impossible.
Like I said, it goes back to my original
point of the day. You can't ever win
with these people.
You can't win with these people.
He said that Smoky B transferred me the money.
You can't remember these people, Dad.
Wait, was he actually saying that? Are
you chatting [ __ ]
No, bro. You got to be chatting [ __ ] He
hasn't really He didn't really say that, did he?
nearly unstable. To which I replied,
says the one ignoring like a [ __ ] on Instagram.
I said says the one ignoring like a [ __ ] on ID. >> [ __ ]
>> Well, he actually said that
he smoking me transferred me the money. Yeah,
just you're never going to win with Timmy, lad.
Let me see.
So even when you show that you've got money,
they come out with another excuse.
Let me see.
I'm listening to now.
Why is my audio [ __ ] Hold up, bro.
What's this comment? Absolute legend.
Tim M are running scared as usual. He
never ordered a cab. He's a uh he's a liar.
Yeah, I don't know how you I don't know
how you can say that I didn't when I've
literally showed screenshots of it, but
okay. One second.
Uh it wasn't at 11:00 p.m. It was
actually at 7:00 p.m.
Yeah. Stop making excuses, lad. He
didn't get in the cab. Stop making excuses.
So, he's actually trying to say that
Smokey B sent me money. Smokey B doesn't
know me. He doesn't even have my number.
Excuses upon excuses upon excuses.
That's all you get with this excuse with
this disabled community. Excuses upon
excuses upon excuses. Yeah.
He would have almost been here by now.
He would have almost been here.
Yeah. I'm not your mate firstly. So, how
about you leave it out, mate? Cuz I'm
not your mate and I'll never be your mate. So
yeah, you can't win with these people,
lad. It's like I was saying earlier, you
can't win with them, bro. Yeah, mad.
So now he's saying that he sent money.
It's just excuses.
Like I was saying to you before, it's
always going to be excuses with these people. Yeah.
Yeah. It doesn't matter if I'm a fighter
or not. Your boyfriend shut it. He asked
me to order a taxi. I ordered a taxi. He
didn't show up. [ __ ] house.
He's a [ __ ] house, bro.
[ __ ] house, is he?
Proper little [ __ ] house. I fancy
playing some live roulette fire stick.
I'm not going to do it, though. But I do
fancy it, bro. Obviously,
I'm not going to do it, but yeah, I got
100. Nah, bro.
No, I'm not doing it, bro.
Not even 100. Not even 50. No.
No. I'm not doing it, bro. Yeah.
Why is he saying that? Because he's talking [ __ ]
You know why he's saying that, bro? Why
are you asking me questions that you
already know the answer to?
Because he's trying to get out of the
fact that he's a [ __ ] house.
Why are you asking questions when you
already know the the answer, lad?
You know why he's saying that? You know
why are you doing that?
Um, I'm not playing roulette, lad.
Simply that. Nah, I'm all right, bro.
I'm all right, lad.
We know he's lying, lad. We already know
he's lying. He's a [ __ ] house.
Like I said to you, you will not win
with these people. Yeah.
So more money than them. They talk [ __ ]
[ __ ] a woman. They talk [ __ ]
They talk so much on the hell.
They all do this, bro. It's not only him.
I mean, someone called me a virgin
earlier and it got it got 11 thumbs up.
So, that should tell you all you need to
know about this disabled community.
That's all you need to um know about
this disabled community, lad.
But you don't like smoking. You don't
like Smokey be um Steve Howard
like I'm going to save money for 3 years
when I'm getting three grand a month.
No, I'd rather live life like I was doing, lad.
I'd rather live life like I was doing.
I'm not going to save money for 3 years,
am I? What's the [ __ ] point of that?
No. The [ __ ] bro?
And what position are people in, lad?
You know, like you want people to do
their balls and because they know my
position. What's my position? You don't
know how much money I've got.
What's people's position?
Let's hear it from the horse's mouth.
You see what I'm trying to say? The
people on this community,
they love talking about people that they don't know.
You understand what I'm saying? They
love talking about people that they don't know.
Like Timmy, you know, they like talking
about people they don't know. Let me
see. Timmy's live.
Hosties on Timmy's.
Oh, Monty man's on. Monty man's on.
Is that a real Monty man on Timmy's? Yeah.
Yeah. Isn't it?
And now it's just going around in
circles now with him and Monty.
Now it's just going around in circles.
Yeah, it's just going around in circles. Squeezy.
It's just going around in circles, lad.
Yeah, it's going around in circles.
Yeah, I see it.
You came in earlier, didn't you? And you
said, "Am I telling porkies, Mr. B?"
Nah, be I don't tell porkies, bro.
this woman on Instagram said
I mentally unstable Fire Stick when
she's the one ignoring on Instagram like a [ __ ]
Is she right? Get the hint and [ __ ] off.
I said you [ __ ] off, you ugly slag.
[ __ ] talk to me like that, you [ __ ]
I was sending her pictures of like Peter
Griffin and that, bro.
You [ __ ] off, you stupid ugly slag.
You know what I'm saying? Oh, just some
random fire stick. Just some random on Instagram, lad.
I don't sing birds. I was insulting her, you [ __ ]
Yeah, I thought you thought I don't and
you thought right. I don't sing birds.
No, I was insulting her.
You [ __ ] off, you stupid ugly slag.
Let me tell her to get something else as
well on a voice note. I can't text it
cuz you're going to get my Instagram banned.
My mom got her Instagram banned cuz I
went on it starting some madness with
some [ __ ] in it.
You [ __ ] stupid [ __ ]
You know when you're not in the mood
anyways, Fire Stick. Yeah, there's this
community and then you have someone talking [ __ ] So yeah. Yeah.
No, I don't simp women on Instagram. I'm
not like your boyfriend.
Not your boyfriend, RJ. No, I don't
simp. I'm not liking lunch. Yeah,
these are the kind of people that make
you hate women. Fire stick.
Imagine looking like a squirrel and
having an ego like that. Allow it, bro.
having an attitude like that, thinking
you're the [ __ ] Imagine, bro.
I was [ __ ] saying, "Why does this
happen? Why does this happening?" And I
called him out
for being an ignor. No one was
interested in you. I didn't once asked
you out. I didn't once compliment you. I
wasn't interested in you, you stupid [ __ ]
Lower your ego down. You look like a [ __ ] scribble. Anyways,
um, no it isn't.
No, it isn't.
Obviously it isn't.
I didn't compliment you once or try to
be nice to you once.
And you're saying you're not interested
when no one's interested in you. Lower
the ego down, please. Come on now. lower
the ego down. Do you know? Do you know
what's so funny is you don't get people
like Do you know the thing? You don't
get people at Cuz I don't like people
ignoring. It's annoying. It could be a
man. It could be a woman. It could be a
disabled woman. I don't like people
ignoring me. It's annoying
cuz it's annoying. Even if it's a man, I
don't like it. It's annoying. There you
go. I answered your question. Do you
know the funny thing is Fire Stick? Do
you know women in Scandinavian countries
don't act like this? You know, like the
West is [ __ ] and that like they're all
stuck up in like America and that, you
know, have you seen these people, bro,
in like Sweden, they don't act like
this, you know?
They're more feminine. You understand?
They're not like fours out of 10
thinking that they're better than you,
even when you're not hitting on them.
Like, they're actually, you know, you
know, bro. Yeah.
You know, people I'm not the only one
that said it, you know. Yeah. England is
the worst place.
They bring your energy down. I've
noticed that as well. Someone said it on Thingy.
Um someone said it on um Ed Matthews um
stream. And I get what he means. They
do. They bring your energy down. Like
the women in this country. Yeah. They
actually do bring your energy down.
I've noticed that as well.
They really are.
That is that is spot on. I don't know. I
know he's falling.
Imagine that, bro. Anyways,
so Monty was watching all along.
No, no one wants you.
No one wants you, lad.
No one wants you.
London is not.
Yeah, but the people are [ __ ]
Yeah, but the people in London are
[ __ ] The best place in the world is Thailand.
Hey, you know why I don't even go out
much anymore? Fire stick. You know, the
drinking here is so [ __ ] Like the whole
drinking culture and that
um the drinking culture and all that.
Yeah. Like you know the actual drinking
scene here is so [ __ ]
It's actually like proper [ __ ] Like the
drinking culture and that. Do you get
what I mean?
like the clubing, the um
the the the clubbing scene and stuff,
bro. Do you get me? That's why I don't
really go out much, bro. That um
That's why I don't really go out, lad.
It's like I was telling you when we was
talking for six hours the other day, lad.
[ __ ] stupid [ __ ] >> Yeah.
You still there, man?
There's a meme. there of Peter Parker
when he's walking around New York City
with a quote, "This is how you feel when
you give up with dating. La peaceful and
it's like Peter Parker like walking
Greavves. Have you seen the meme when
you finally give up with women and stuff
and you see Peter Parker just like
walking having a nice stroll?"
Yeah. Yeah, bro.
Have you se You've seen it, Grezy.
What? You've seen it, Grezy.
You've seen it in it.
Yeah. It's It's a lovely little meme,
isn't it? Where did you see it?
Where did you see it, lad?
Oh gosh. Where Where did you see it?
Ah, but you've definitely seen it though. Yeah.
No, it's not it's not Christian is he
that's being like that. Christian Izzy
would never be like that to Peter Belly.
Is that right, Grezy?
He'd never be like that to Peter Belly. Yeah,
I agree with you. I'm going to send you
a screenshot on um Instagram.
Okay with you, boss. Yeah.
And you wonder why I could never be a s.
white knight. I even sent it to you.
Well, I sent it to you now.
This is what makes me laugh when people
I sent you the screenshot that on
Instagram. This is why it baffles me
when you have all of these men
defending these women. It baffles me.
It baffles me to [ __ ] Ry. It really baffles me.
I'm very baffled. Oh gosh.
Triple H used to love me doing them little voices,
you know. Like we used to
like we used to Isabella.
I don't know. He used to love them little voices.
I've got a feeling Monty and Timmy's
going to be going back and forth tomorrow.
There's only one way Timmy can can make a comeback
by going on to by going on Monty's door in it.
That's the only way in it, Grezy. If you
went on Monty's door,
that's what I would do if I took a big L
now. Yeah, that's that's probably
something that I would do. Isn't that right, Greavves?
You can if you like, but I won't be there.
I sent you something called Instagram, Grezy.
No, he hasn't. He hasn't turned up more
than me. Uh-uh.
He's not turned up more than me, lad.
Jimmy has definitely not turned up more than me.
Timmy has not turned up more than me.
I've been everywhere in this country
cuz you don't.
You can if you like,
but I won't be there.
Oh, Greasy, she's fit.
Greasy, she's hot. She's hot. Yeah.
You see what I mean?
What a lovely fight.
And you see why G can't defend them.
How can anyone defend people like that
that are blaming [ __ ]
Um, I said to her like, "Why is a dating
scene so hard?"
And then she's like, "Do you normally
message people like this?" I said, "No."
And I said, "Why?" And then they started
ignoring. So I never come on to her. I
didn't compliment her. And yeah, she
just started ignoring and I sent her
Chewbecka. Chew Becca the be the um Y
and bear. And then she went on the
message straight away. She was just
being an ignoring [ __ ]
Wasn't complimenting her. Weren't trying
to meet her, nothing. That's how you
know they're narcissistic.
That's how you know, Greasy, that
they're very narcissistic.
No one [ __ ] begged you. No one even
complimented you, you stupid little [ __ ] The [ __ ]
Don't get ahead of yourself. And this is
why Groovy I don't understand why men
defend women. Do you see my point? Do
you see my point, lad?
If they're not going to defend men, then
don't defend women. Simple. We're both adults,
Greasy. We're both adults. Look, you've
got proof of them being [ __ ]
stupid [ __ ] [ __ ] So, do you think
it's out of line when I'm baffled why
you've got these people defending them?
It's common sense. It's common sense.
You know what I'm saying? Like, it's common sense
how they can defend people like that.
That's the kind of people that they're defending. Yeah.
No one's interested in you. I didn't ask
them out. I didn't compliment them.
They wished I [ __ ] did, but I [ __ ] never.
By saying, "Why you being an ignoring
cunt?" [ __ ] no one would beg you,
mate. If I was going to beg someone, it
[ __ ] wouldn't be bloody well you, would it,
you stupid [ __ ]
But do you understand what I mean,
Grezy? Grievy, listen to me. Why are
they defending women when women are [ __ ]
Do you understand, Grezy? Why are they
defending women when women are [ __ ]
What's the goal here? Do you think
they're going to sleep with you or
weird as [ __ ] why they would defend
people that are worse than men?
Women are worse than men.
Women are worse than [ __ ] men and
then you have these people [ __ ] defending them.
Imagine that, Grezy.
How does that even make sense? Squeezy.
What did you think of the conversation,
Greasy? They were [ __ ] it. They
didn't write back to me because they
know I'm right.
They know I'm [ __ ] right.
They know I'm [ __ ] right. Ain't it, Grezy?
I come across people that are like that
on Reddit as well, Greavvesy. Like
you'll share them like your approaching
videos, right? And they'll be like, "Oh,
I'm not clicking it. Can you explain And
I'm like, "No, if you can't be bothered
to watch the video, that's on you. I'm
not explaining it to you. How are you
supposed to explain approaching videos?"
No, a voice call never happened. I tried
calling them and they didn't pick up.
As you can see, started at 31, ended at
31 past. They didn't answer.
No, they didn't answer.
They didn't answer, lad. I didn't talk
to them on the phone. I called them to
see how fast it would take for them to
go on the message.
And then you got men that are defending
these kind of scumbags,
right? You got men that are defending
these kind of scum. How does how is that
even possible, bro? you know, defending women.
You know, you have the likes of non legs, right?
Don't legs and other people defending
them when they're blatant [ __ ]
Makes you wonder, don't it, lad?
What do you think? We Yeah.
And I knew there's no way they they had
there's no way they can take a day off
of Instagram. These westernized women
grievy, they can't take an hour off of Instagram.
Instagram's their life. Tik Tok's their
life. When you're going to these bars
and clubs, you'll see that they're not
even enjoying themselves. They've got
their head glued. They've got their head
glued to the to their phone, lad.
They've got their head glued to their
phone. So, um you know, they can't take
a day off of social media, can they Grezy?
That's enough Tik Tok for today.
That's literally how they'd act.
Yeah, I had this woman on Instagram
being a [ __ ] I had to tell her about
herself, lad. I said, "You look like a
[ __ ] squirrel and you're get and
you're trying to get rude to me."
Calling people mentally unstable when
you're the stupid [ __ ] ignoring you
[ __ ] westernized pig.
You [ __ ] westernized [ __ ]
At least my eyes, Greavesy. My eyes look
normal. You see my eyes? They're just
normal. There's no Westinity in my eyes. Look,
must be a Tik Tok thing. But there's no
Westinity in my eyes, lad. Yeah.
You can see the Westinity in their eyes. Yeah.
Look at my eyes.
I'll show you my eyes. Yeah. Look,
there's no westernity in my eyes. Look,
they're just normal brown eyes. Just
like they were supposed to be in the
80s. Just like they were supposed to be
in like the 1980s and [ __ ] You know
what I'm saying? Bro, look. No
westernity in my eyes.
See? No dirty western eyes look in my eyes.
You can see the Westinity in their eyes.
Yeah. The eyes never lie, lad. The eyes never lie.
We see. The eyes never lie, lad.
The eyes never lie.
So, you're telling me I can't find a woman?
So, I can't find a woman that that that
doesn't have that in their eyes.
I can't find a woman in their 20s that
don't have that in their in their eye.
Nope. You have to go for 40 year olds.
You can see the western energy in their eyes.
Yeah, the eyes never lie, Greavvesy. The
eyes never lie.
So, why are my eyes look like that then?
Why isn't my eyes westernized?
Why isn't my eyes like I don't have that
look in my eye?
It's like an MPC kind of look.
It's hard to explain it. It's like um
It's hard to explain it. If you know,
you know that
nasty recognized look.
But Grezy, she's fit. She's fit.
What do you think to that? She's fit.
What's your opinion on that? Oh gosh.
Oh gosh. Brizzy. Oh gosh.
So, no, but honestly, honest. Is he
really trying to say Smokeoky B sent me the money?
Yeah. You'll never win with these people, lad. Never.
Never win with him. Will you
Monty man was commenting on Timmy's live? Weezy,
that's funny, is it? We yeah.
So, is that what needs to happen to nons? Yeah,
she was proper proper blown out of proportion. Grezy,
I'm looking again. My dick ain't going hard.
Nah, nothing to question anyone's sexuality about.
Ant-Man said everybody wanted her. I
[ __ ] never wanted her.
But then again, I'm not a little copycat.
Everybody wanted her.
Not [ __ ] me, mate. Never.
Never. Ever. Ever. Ever. I used to I
used to watch the X Factor as a kid, Grezy. Um,
back before Simon Cow became really old.
And I never wanted her.
Not me, lad.
Never ever ever did I ever want her. But
was never my celebrity crush ever, bro.
Sure you could go into London and find better.
What about you, Henry?
Did you use the fancy shell car?
Did you use the fancy? I never [ __ ] fancy.
Maybe Henry did, but I never.
Yeah, people used to say Henry, if you
didn't find her attractive, you're gay,
but to be honest, nonregs wasn't Well,
he still is a virgin. But he was a
raging virgin back then. So, you got to
understand like hormones and stuff grievy.
You know, when someone has got a
erectile dysfunction problem and
obviously they're a virgin like he was
and is, um, you know, it's even worse, you know. Yeah,
there some little virgin in a [ __ ]
bedit owned by the council about to talk
about people's sexuality
because they want to be different and
not copy the crowd. Huh? [ __ ] copycats.
No, what I want what I want to do is I
want to I want to be a police officer,
right? And go and nickny,
dirty, copycat little virgin.
Oh, Simon Wilson's post a new video.
I'll be watching that. Um
um and also um
also played a [ __ ] guitar
and they're very very serious charges. Greasy.
Very very serious charges
and playing a [ __ ] guitar.
You know you're looking at 10 years in prison, mate.
If if you found guilty being a dirty,
stinky, copycat virgin
and playing a [ __ ] guitar. Yeah. Would
you would you laugh at the arrest, Grezy?
Would you laugh at the arrest
if you saw it on video? It's a serious
serious crime, mate. Serious serious crime.
Yeah, serious crime, lad.
Alvis Prey was [ __ ] [ __ ]
I don't know why people used to like
him. He's a [ __ ] load of [ __ ] Load
of [ __ ] he
n he was [ __ ] bro.
Do you remember?
No. [ __ ] mate. Elvis.
Did you like Elvis? Crazy.
Women get a bad rap.
Women that cheat need to be hung across
a bridge. It's disgusting. What do you
think, Dusty? Women Women that cheat are [ __ ] vile. Yeah,
they're [ __ ] gross. They need to be
hung across the bridge.
I think if someone cheated on me, I
think I would just rob them. Grezy, I
would just [ __ ] rob them.
I'd get him back nasty. I'd do it dirty.
Trust me, I would do it. I I I would I
would do it dirty. Greasy,
do you like that talk? Greasy.
I like to do it dirty. Yeah.
So, you're telling me I ordered a taxi today,
Grezy, for Timmy, on the same website.
You can watch Little Harry Potter on
Harry Potter as a child
and baby Spider-Man. Is that what you're
trying to tell me?
So I can watch baby Spider-Man on the same website.
Nah, you're taking a piss in it.
Monty's watching in the background. He
knew all about the taxi thing it
Monty knew all about the taxi thing it Yeah.
I brought Monty man on this community in
it. I brought Monty man on here. Imagine
how his life would have turned out if he
didn't come on here. Yeah.
No, I've actually been to prison. It's
not that bad.
I've actually been to prison.
Yeah, I've been to prison, mate.
It's not that bad, you know. Prison.
I've been to prison in it, Grezy.
Yeah, I've been to prison.
Yeah, prison. Prison's all right.
Do you like Mariah Carey, Greavvesy?
Mariah Carey. Greavvesy. I think you do. Huh?
How comes Grezy?
Nons used to talk about [ __ ]
Don't want to feel left out.
You don't want to feel left out.
It's the fear of being left out. It's a
big thing, Dusty.
And you know when someone's caught
copying another person,
you know, it can be quite dangerous
when you're c copying another person.
It's quite dangerous, bro. and you're
caught copying another person,
especially autistic people, you know,
[ __ ] She's [ __ ] hot, crazy. She's
N in all fairness, Greasy, she's average.
Like completely being unbiased. Just completely average.
Average with a [ __ ] body.
Soon to be Robert the Bear. Greavesy.
soon to be Rupet the Bear lad. Oh. Oh gosh.
What a lovely site.
I have the best says on this community,
Dusty. What a lovely site. Mad.
No, I could play £100 on roulette, but
that will pay for my little date with me
and Christian. Izzy, isn't that right, Reevesy?£100
will cover the little date, won't it? Yep.
That will pay for the little date, won't it? Oh.
Oh, look at that dog. That dog so cute. Oh.
Who was in shot? Who's that?
Well, I can have a baby. Dusty.
Dusty. I can have a baby. Can I?
Oh, do you remember Afghan? Does anyone
Oh, I do remember Afghan dandusty.
You remember Afghanam?
He is one weird looking [ __ ] He is.
Yeah, he's he's weird man.
Do you remember Afghan dang?
The ugly the ugliest [ __ ]
I can think of is that [ __ ]
is that [ __ ] Money Mike. Bro,
what would you do if you look like Money
Mike Greavesy? Would you kill yourself?
What would you do if you look like him, Dusty?
He's Timmy's friend. The albino looking [ __ ]
If I look like that, bro, I would
actually kill myself.
If you look like him, Dusty, would you
kill yourself or would you just would
you just try to make the best out of your situation?
I think I'd kill myself, bro.
There's some people, yeah, there's just
like no hope for them.
The way they look here, some people, the
way they look like Timmy, there's just
like no hope for them.
It's over. It's actually over, lad.
Even if you're average, bro. Average is
good enough. You can, you know, you can
build your body and [ __ ] But if you're
ugly, bro, what about if you was What if
you was ginger, but you wasn't ugly?
Say you was ginger,
but you wasn't ugly. What would you do?
Would you Would you still dye your hair?
Would you just dye your hair or would
you not would you not bother dyeing your hair?
What would you do
that Ali Lar ginger in it? Um Greavesy
Ali Lars Ginger,
but he doesn't look bad. So, I mean,
you could kind of work with it if you
look like that in it. You could kind of
own it in it, but
I wouldn't want to be ginger.
And having a ginger beard doesn't count
as being ginger. You need to have ginger
hair as well.
Gingers are rare.
But no, I mean,
would you care if you was ginger greasy?
Would you care or not?
Mariah Care's got big boobies. Greasy. You remember
he's got big boobies.
Yeah, not care. Yeah. But do you reckon
a lot of women would reject you for just
being ginger? I reckon so.
I reckon so. Yeah.
Well, you don't really see many gingers
about in it, but I reckon some would.
Yeah. I reckon some would just reject
you for being ginger.
Do you think, Greasy? Yeah,
I reckon they would, bro. I think they
would. Some of them would. Yeah.
Can someone reject you for being ginger, bro? Yeah. Yep.
Yeah, some gingers do, but still
I tan good in the summer. Greavesy. I
tan really good. When I was doing Uber,
I got like a really nice tan.
I got a really nice tan.
But I have to I think I'm going to have
to ban that UK asylum lad. He says that
I'm a troll when I'm not a troll.
I've never ever trolled anyone.
Order an Uber. I ordered an Uber.
Never trolled anyone. I've never trolled
anyone. I'm just a little wind up.
Yeah. What's your opinion on the G
dating game, Grezy? Poor [ __ ]
Oh, bless you if you think it's a waste of time. Bless.
I feel like Peter Parker.
When you Oh, did you see the Teletubby
one as well?
When you finally given up on dating.
Did you see it?
I like these little memes. Grezy.
Oh, I was watching some something a
Spongebob meme um yesterday, Grezy, and
the customer was like um they were
closed and it's like, I'll just have a
burger, please. And Squidward was like,
"No, you won't."
Squidward was like, "No, you won't." And
then they made And then they made it
open 24 hours. The Crusty Crab. Crazy.
I'll just have one burger, please. No,
you will not.
We are closed.
Oh, Squidward's a lovely little character.
I like um
Mermaid Man and Barnacle Boy.
Oh, Crash is next to me.
He always sleeps next to me. Look,
he's always here.
He's an original crash. Crashes. So, yeah. Um,
I'll just get a burger, please, no.
No, you won't.
Yep. It's my little friend.
This Teddy doesn't talk back to me. This
Teddy doesn't ask me for money. It beats
having a woman. Dusty.
Crash doesn't talk back.
Crash is loyal.
Crush is a loyal um little toy.
He doesn't cheat or anything like that. Yep.
Yep. He's a lovely little He's a lovely little toy.
Who's your favorite character in
Spongebob? Um, Greavvesy.
I like Sandy Cheeks. Yeah. Nope.
I don't know. I like um
do you remember the one where um
Squidward tried to I can actually
remember episodes cuz I've watched it so
many times. Do you remember when
Squidward Yeah. tried to get away from
them and and they found and they found him
and they found him in the Squid home
when he tried to get away from them. He
wanted like a break and then they found him.
I remember the one where they were
parents and Patrick was watching the TV. I remember
when Gary got lost.
Gary, come home.
Quite a sad song to be honest. Um,
I actually remember some episodes off by
heart. I always used to watch Spongebob, man. Yeah,
Grevy, me and you need to go to New York together.
We can see Spongebob. We can see
Spider-Man. That's where it all comes from. Grey um
um Greavves did. Um yeah. Yeah. Greasy,
we should go to New York and see all of
the stuff that come from there,
which is literally like everything.
Would you be up for that, Grezy?
Me and you go together. We do a little vlog.
Everything comes from there.
Yep. We can go see Spider-Man, Mary Jane, Chucky,
Chucky, everything comes from there. Spongebob, everything.
Gravy, everything. A lot of it comes from there.
Trust me, it does. Chucky comes from
there as well.
Everything comes from there.
Everything, everything, everything.
I like Spider-Man and Mary Jane.
They were so cute.
What's your favorite, Dusty? Superman,
Spider-Man, or Batman?
Mine's Spider-Man, then Superman.
Every kid loves Spider-Man.
Spider-Man's a hero. I like Batman and Joker.
I like Batman and Joker, you know.
I do like Batman and Joker. I've never
watched it, but I just like the characters. Greasy.
I like Joker. He's a lovely character.
I think they do Lego Batman actually.
Why not? Let me have a little look.
Might start a collection up again.
Let me have a look. Look at Amazon.
Let me have a little Oh, yeah. £42.
is that Batman?
It sure is Batman. And there's Joker as well.
Yeah, that's definitely It's£42. Greasy. What?
Yeah, they do Lego Batman.
I'll I'll wait. Greasy.
Yeah, they do a lot of Batman Lego, bro.
But if I buy it, I need to start building it.
Well, no. With Batman, you just buy one
in it because it's just Batman and
Joker. You don't need any.
No, it's already been reduced.
Maybe I'll play some roulette.
No, I'm not playing that.
Tempting, but nah.
Nah, I'm not playing it, bro.
It's [ __ ] Why is it so? No.
Maybe I can try and win £50 to pay for
the Lego Grezy. Nah,
that'd be funny, isn't it? They buy by Joker, it'll you'll wait.
Yes. Until it's been made.
The bookies is closed
and I can't go live on this phone.
You can't go live on this phone, lad.
Oh, Timmy's live.
When it goes on 11 greaves and I don't
have no money on it, it makes me cry. I actually cry.
No, actually I do cry when it goes on
number 11. I cry, bro, if I don't have
money on it.
Yeah, Timmy's live now.
Don't gamble, folks. You end up with an iPhone free.
I'm not gay. I'm not gay. Oh, really?
What I'm going to do is I'm going to wait. Greasy,
you you you wait.
Yes. Until these people get a life.
I'll wait until they get alive.
How's that sound, Grezy?
You'll you'll wait. Yes. Until they get alive. Yeah.
So, do you reckon Christian is going to
give me vitamins then
when she meets me?
Do you reckon she's going to give me lovely vitamins?
No, he didn't win the money game, lad.
I won the money game when I found when I
showed 5.7 grand. Nice try, though.
Nice try, though, lad.
Yeah, nice try though.
So yeah, Timmy and Monty can fight all
they want tomorrow. They can go back and
forth tomorrow. They can if they like,
but I won't be there.
But I won't be there. Yeah,
my brain I'll come off for maybe a
couple of days minimum. Grezy, my brain
cells need to come back. I lost my brain
cells at the minute, Grezy.
That's what happens um when you come on
this community. You lose brain cells
after a while. I need to get them back.
So, you're just going to have to bear
with me, Greavvesy.
I reckon if I come on here every day for
a month, I'd actually get brain cancer, bro.
I actually think I'd have brain cancer.
Like, I mean, every day for a month. No.
Yeah. I think I'd have brain cancer, bro.
I think I'd have a [ __ ] seizure or some [ __ ]
It's a disabled community.
Unworthy commented saying that this is madness.
Oh, Charlie's a miserable old [ __ ] but
we love him. Griezy,
he's a miserable [ __ ] but we love him.
So Greavesy, if him and Monty man starts
arguing, are they going to meet or go
around in circles?
Are they going to meet or is it going to
go around in circles? Huh?
No, no, no, no, no. I'll just just wait. You wait.
Yes. Till they get alive.
Till they get alive, lad.
until they get alive.
Oh gosh, Queezy.
I didn't want to feel left out.
Didn't want to feel left out.
Right. All right. So, I try £100 on this roulette.
Press press one if I should. Press two
if I shouldn't.
We need a vote. Right.
What do you think? We
think I should try 100 pounds. No
done with my [ __ ] car, bro.
Oh, what my All
right, we'll try this £100. Yeah. Right.
Yeah. Let's give it a while in it. M.
Hate Bliss, bro. I hate this.
Right. Let's try and find a roulette table, bro.
want to play.
One second, bro.
Okay. Give it a little while. [ __ ] it.
do 250 pound spins. Yeah. Let's do like 30.
Can you hear me? Yeah.
It's got noise going on.
Oh, at least it was 30, not 11.
Okay. 19 pound spins.
All right. 11, bro. Come on.
Stay away from zero section. Whatever you do,
but keep going. You [ __ ] [ __ ]
20 [ __ ] N, bro.
29 [ __ ] bro.
Got to build a balance.
Some of these are like money back numbers.
Stay away from zero section. 27 [ __ ] Money back.
No, it's money back. [ __ ] bro.
I'm just going to do two I'm just going
to do two big big spins. Two big ones.
Try and be a little bit positive, man. Come on.
Stop 11. Yes.
Come on, baby.
Come on. 11.
Come on, 11.
Come on. One more time, baby.
Yeah, I've got it to 150. I got it to 200.
I got to 200. One more. One more. One
[ __ ] 30 [ __ ] four.
3 [ __ ] four, bro. Yeah,
I'm just taking a 50 profit, lad.
Yeah, I'm at 15 151 £151.
[ __ ] stupid [ __ ] [ __ ] 34, bro.
3 [ __ ] four again.
Well, I'll stop spinning now, bro. 3 [ __ ] four.
Why couldn't have it just been 17, bro?
[ __ ] this [ __ ] [ __ ] bro. It's
annoying, bro. I got 151 in the balance,
No, I won't going to take 100 profit,
bro. I'll just take 50 profit. [ __ ] it.
In it. Guess I can just buy the Lego.
That is so annoying, bro. Why? Why 34?
Why, bro? Why 3 [ __ ] four?
You know how much I had on 17, bro? I
don't like a 50 spin.
Why, bro? Why?
You never win life changing money. You
can't even get two in a row. I hit 11.
It got me to 200.
You'll never win life changing money.
Never. You'll never ever win life changing money.
You'll never ever ever ever win life changing money.
Cuz what it will do is it will just [ __ ]
you. Well, 50 pound will pay for my
bets, isn't it?
It will never It will never ever ever.
It will always [ __ ] you. That's why you
can never win life-changing money, bro.
Dirty dirty [ __ ]
Dirty dirty dirty bastard.
It hit 11, got me to [ __ ] 200.
And then look, yeah, I'll just take the
profit. I'll just take the 50 profit. Simple, it
pays for like the cinema and [ __ ]
No, I wouldn't have took 200,
but if I missed again, I would have took
the 50. So
that's not good, bro.
Yeah, I'll try again maybe in a week.
I'll try again in like a week or something.
[ __ ] lovely 11. That was
why it just hit again. Why? Why? Why? 34. Why?
Why 34? Why? Why? Why? Why? Why?
Right. We'll try again in um maybe I'll
try roulette again in like a week or something.
Yeah. See, you might not see 50 pound as
anything, but that's like the cinema on
a football bet to me, bro. So, just take
the 50 or if you want to buy the Lego
if you want to buy the Lego and you know
what I'm saying. So,
every [ __ ] time it [ __ ] me royally,
bro. Every time it [ __ ] me royally.
That's why you'll never win. You can't
even get a couple in a row, bro. You
can't even get a couple of wins in a row.
That's why you'll never win. You can't
get a couple of wins in a row. hits 11.
I didn't He didn't even need to hit 11
again. 2 5 17 20.
It didn't even need to hit again like a
big amount number.
But nah, no chance. It's [ __ ] you
every [ __ ] time.
Oh, well, at least we got 50, bro. At
least we got 50 quid in it. So we either
buy the Batman Lego or what it pays for
the cinema and [ __ ]
Yeah. I won't going to take a 100, bro.
Cuz I don't do it like that. What I do
is I repeat. Yeah.
I will repeat it.
I repeat it, bro. And if it loses, then
I'll just take less because that's the
way you got to do it sometimes.
It could have hit two, it could hit
eight, it could hit 11, 17, 20, it could
have hit any number out of half the board. So,
yeah, we'll try again. And um
yeah, I'll get a big win one day, bro. Trust me.
[ __ ] 11, man. Yeah,
probably get that money tomorrow.
I [ __ ] around today. [ __ ] I had to
give that [ __ ] £8. £8,
you know what I mean? 8 pound [ __ ]
Did you hear me when I said it hit 11?
Grezy, did you hear me
when I said it hit 11?
What do we get?
What should we spend it on?
I used to just gamble online and if I
win, yeah, I just get an escort. I don't
really do escorts anymore.
I mean, we can get a lot of pick and mix
and popcorn with 50 gzy.
We can buy a lot of stuff at the cinema with that.
Will it pay for a football bet Anderson
more greasy? I think so.
Yeah. 50. I think so. Greasy. No.
Yeah, I reckon. I think it would. No.
So, we're going to I can't even do the
football bol thingy cuz my lad books
account is closed.
Yeah. [ __ ] sake.
Yeah. I normally spend about 30 35
if I get a lot. Yeah.
Yeah, I normally spend 30 35. Yeah, same.
Or should we try and push it and win more? Nah.
Nah, bro. Maybe in a week.
I can't believe I didn't hit another
number. Steven Howard, what the [ __ ]
Oh my god, bro.
I can't believe I didn't hit another
number. What the [ __ ]
34. You dirty [ __ ]
It is a dirty number, isn't it?
Oh, look what was after that 34.
You know what was after that 34?
You know what was after that 34, lad?
2 33 17 24 36 18 Yeah, right.
Yeah, [ __ ] right. Was it?
No, it [ __ ] was not. How, bro?
What is 34?
Oh, no. The worst is 25 cuz it's in
between 17 and two, isn't it?
No, that's worse, bro.
[ __ ] sake, bro.
Well, at least we we proved today that
Timmy's full of [ __ ] ain't it? Yeah.
You reckon it's going to ever happen,
Grezy, where I win a life changing
amount of money online?
Is it ever going to happen? Um, crazy day.
Listen to me, Stephen Howard. I was
going to put 150 on the football. Listen. Yeah.
I was going to put 150 on the football,
but it was offering me £340 back.
It was offering me £350 back, so it
wasn't worth it.
It wasn't worth doing, lad. I want
like400 pound back if I'm putting
[ __ ] 150s and [ __ ] in. You know what I mean?
You know what I mean, bro?
I thought I was going to get a little
streak going there, Steven Howard.
I thought I was going to get a little streak going.
Nah, Grievy, it would have been too
easy, wouldn't it? It would have been
too easy, wouldn't it?
Yeah, it would have been too easy.
If the if that film weren't coming out
in the cinema, I would have just bought the Lego.
Yeah, it would have been too easy, wouldn't it?
Oh, yeah. Last year, even Yeah. 6 months
ago, bro, I put 20 I put 120 and I got
380 back. 387 back. Now it's [ __ ]
You know what you want to try doing? You
want to try getting a both teams to
score in the first half.
Then we're talking money, bro. You know,
then we're talking money,
man. That 17 was going to be That 17
would have been mega.
Couldn't believe it went on 11.
[ __ ] sake, man. Why could it have just
been 11 again?
Been too easy, ain't it?
Would have been too easy.
No, I just put 100 pound and I got it to
200. I took 150.
I missed like um a 50 something pound
spin. [ __ ] bro. It went on 30
[ __ ] four. Dirty [ __ ] number. Dirty
[ __ ] number. I had 90 numbers.
I just took the 50, bro. I don't want to
risk losing it. [ __ ] it.
I'll go back to it maybe, bro. In like a
week or something, can it?
I'll go back in maybe two weeks or
something. We're going to do a football
bet Saturday anyways.
>> Yeah, exactly, bro. And I got £50 on top
of it in it. So, it'll pay for my
[ __ ] football that
it'll pay for um cinema on football in it.
So that spin could have bought the Lego.
That spin I lost Greavvesy could have
bought the Lego.
>> Yeah, but you're not going to think of that, bro.
When you've got 80 90 numbers covered
and you can have a nice spin, you're
going to spin again, aren't you? You're
not going to You're not going to [ __ ]
You know, you're not going to think, are you?
>> Yeah. Uh, to think of it, that would
have got me a£10 football bet and it
would have paid for the Lego.
[ __ ] 34 is a dirty [ __ ] number,
Dusty. It's a such a dirty [ __ ] number
cuz it don't I hit 11, but it don't need
to be 11. All it has to be is 17, 20,
14, two. Just keep going, building the
money up, you know? [ __ ] bastards.
Do you want my opinion, Grezy?
They're all [ __ ]
Oh, there's some football tomorrow to be fair.
There's some football tomorrow.
But we're not doing it tomorrow. There
is actually some football tomorrow.
There's some footy tomorrow, ain't
there? There is. Yeah.
But I'm only going to bet when Slow and
Enfield play at home.
I'm waiting for the I'm I'm I'm waiting
for the right lineup. Grievy. So some
would say Greavvesy. So some would say
Griezy. I'm picking my moment.
Yeah, Greavesy. Some would say
that I'm picking my moment.
I reckon I can get this in, bro. Once
they play home, I reckon.
Just sat there picking my moment
like a good little fellow.
Just picking my moment. Yeah.
So, when do I tell this Izzy that I want
to have a baby, Greavesy? I take it not
let I take it not yet. Right. I said to
her, "What do you think her babies would
look like?" He said, "For [ __ ] sake, probably you.
You have strong features. Lovely.
Yeah, I can, Dusty.
No, I can have a kid. I can have kids.
Of course I can have kids.
Yeah, I can.
But why? I'd be a fit father, Dusty.
Seriously, Steven Howard, are you ever
going to put 150 on a football bat?
Are you actually going to put 150 on a football bet?
I'm just going to do a [ __ ] really
good football bet, bro.
So, I wouldn't put more than 20 pound on it.
I don't think I'd put more than 20 pound
on it now, bro.
Saying that though, if there there's two
there these two teams there, if you put
600 on it, you get 1,700 back. Yeah,
I actually would, you know,
I actually would you know
600 pound on two teams.
[ __ ] that bro.
You get like 17,800 back but it's not worth it.
So I don't think it's worth it. I reckon. Yeah.
I would do that if they if they gave if
they gave like if they gave 2,700 back
then maybe I'd consider it.
But 17,800 doesn't seem to be that much.
You know what I mean?
You know what I'm saying?
It don't seem to be that much.
But imagine you could win like £50 a day.
You'd be laughing if you could win £50 a
day. Yeah. Imagine that grieves you. You
could win £50 a day.
Quite a lot. It
say you could win £50 a day for spending
like 2 minutes on something. Yeah.
Both teams to score. No draw. could do,
but even that is getting [ __ ] You would
need to put like 5060 pound on it. Two
teams. No, what I'm going to do is I'm
going to do both teams to score and the
team to win. The specific team to win.
No, I think with that, bro, you do two
teams. You do you do you do two teams
slow and Enfield playing at home. I
reckon you got it.
I reckon you got it.
I reckon you'll win.
3 [ __ ] four, man. That's stupid. I
hate that number.
I [ __ ] hate that number.
I think that's got to be the worst
number in six, isn't it?
That number in six has got to be the worst. [ __ ] No.
No. Like some co I'm not general coy cat.
That cunt's a boner kill.
She's a boner kill.
She's a [ __ ] boner kill, lad.
Makes my dicks off.
She's my [ __ ] dicks off, lad.
What do you think of that, Greasy?
And do you know why that is, Grezy?
Do you know why that is, Grezy?
Do you know why that is? Because I'm not
a little copycat.
I'm not a little copycat.
I need to change my bed in a bit, bro.
Yeah, with that £100 I could have spent
it on [ __ ]
I could have spent it
on this Lego.
If I buy it today, it will come tomorrow.
[ __ ] hell, bro. [ __ ] me.
No, it just needs change and it's dirty.
I'm still not going to go out until
March. Bro, I said to my friend I'm
going to go out next week with him, but nah.
When am I going to go out again? I think
I'm just going to wait until St. Patrick's Day.
Should I just wait until St. Patrick's Day? Dusty.
I don't like drinking that much, bro.
St. Patrick's Day, I reckon. Bro,
I think it's better just to go out once
a month or maybe twice a month.
No, I can't get in O'Neals. Like, I'm
banned. Oh, I just played roulette by
the way. Fire.
[ __ ] turn 100 to 200. I just took the
150 50 up and it
mate I done 150 spin. It went on [ __ ]
[ __ ] It went on [ __ ] 34. Dirty [ __ ]
I hit 11. That's my number. Then it went
on 30. It went on 34.
Bastard. [ __ ] [ __ ] [ __ ] bastard.
No, I think I'll go out like St.
Patrick's Day. I think, bro,
I know a few places I could go.
That's like the only event I think I
would go out. I think I'd only go out
and you St. Patrick's Day, lad.
Yeah, I won't play now for like two
weeks, bro. [ __ ] it. In it. The 50 will
pay for the cinema and [ __ ]
[ __ ] it, bro. I just spend that £50 in
the cinema Thursday.
Yeah. [ __ ] it in it. Yeah, I'll go back
to in a couple weeks. So,
I need to do a football bet on Saturday.
I'm just going to do a 10 pound football bet Saturday.
Yeah, that's the only event I think I'd
go out. You know, New Year's Eve
overrated Pat. Boxing Day. Overrated. Yeah. Bank holiday.
Pat. Yeah. I think St. Patrick's Day.
Yeah. I'm going to do an I'm going to do
an all accum I might do one tomorrow
instead. I don't think any of the I
don't think the National League's playing Saturday.
Yeah, bro. Yeah, I can't go to that
O'Neals ever again. I'm banned. Bed bun bun bun. Banned.
I'm banned, bro. [ __ ] It Oh, [ __ ]
Yeah, I know it's live, lad. I've been
there about a million times.
That's the only O'Neal that is live.
Waxies is good. I used to go to O'Neals
on Thursday. I used to get all them
American [ __ ] dusty.
I used to cuz I used to get I used to
have this obsession with like [ __ ]
these American [ __ ] and that, bro.
And I knew by going there Thursdays I'd
[ __ ] find them.
I'd find them. Rezy, you know what I'm saying?
I knew, lad. I knew.
But that place gets addicting, dusty.
You go once, you want to go again. It's
addicting. It's an addicting place.
That only was his addictive. Yeah.
Yeah. Not only was it addicting, bro,
I used to walk in with like 50 notes
that I won from the casino. The bouncers
used to be like, "Oh, you got all this money?"
They used to be like, "You got all this money, huh?
It was fun, bro.
Remember the army [ __ ] They ain't been
going for a while, Grezy.
They ain't been coming. They ain't been
coming for a while, have they?
I don't know, but they ain't been coming
for a while. Crazy.
That is funny as [ __ ] bro.
They were really stupid to ban me though
cuz I used to put I used to like
I used to spend a lot of money in that place.
Yeah, I used to spend a lot of money in
that place, bro.
I used to spend a lot of money in that place, bro. [ __ ] hell.
Why don't you go to the O'Neals, Dusty? Yeah.
Oh man, I need to figure I need to get a
haircut again soon, bro. [ __ ]
I still got my little roof at the bare pants.
Would you like to see them?
Yeah, I've got Robert to bear pants. Actually,
I've actually got them.
There you are. [ __ ]
They are right here.
Robert the Bear.
Yep. I'll tell you what I'll wear. I'll
tell you what I'll wear going out,
Grezy. If you want,
I'll wear this if you want. One second. One sec. it.
I'll [ __ ] do it.
I'll [ __ ] do it, Greasy. Don't [ __ ] with me.
I've also got shoes to go with it as
well. Don't [ __ ] with me, Grezy. Yep. Oh,
should I wear that when I go out next week?
Should I wear that? We
put the bear Yeah.
And a green light.
You're so silly.
My underpants smell. Greasy.
My underpants smell. Greasy. What's your
opinion on that?
My underpants smell. Yeah,
I need to wash them. Oh gosh.
Can anyone say it like me?
Can anyone say it like me? Greasy. Oh gosh. H. Oh, [ __ ]
[ __ ] hell, man.
I might get this Lego Greavesy. I'm not sure.
I'm not too sure.
I might just put £150 on a roulette spin
and do a video on it. UK asylum. Just do
£150 on one spin. Nah.
Imagine that. No. [ __ ] that, bro. [ __ ] that.
Well, I've done it before. I've done 300
bounce spins. Nah, [ __ ] that, bro.
No, cuz it's links. Uh, sorry, Lego.
Links. Uh, the Lego, bro.
Yeah. No, bro. Not not no.
You know, the maddest thing is if you
done 150 pound spin, any of them 80
numbers would be [ __ ] lush.
They would be lush. But nah,
I can't remember the Well, I done I done
100 pound spins actually last month.
When you do roulette, Dusty, and your
number hits, do you double the bet?
Do you double the bet?
I don't but if it loses sometimes I used
to do that. Oh gosh.
Is it Is the National League playing
Saturday or what?
Are they playing Saturday or not?
Do you remember Griezy? Stay the hell
away from us. Nope.
I'm never staying away. Nope. Never.
This This woman on Reddit said, "Stay
the hell away from us, Grezy." No. Okay. So,
I've played it before. It's just
impossible to bonus. I just played some roulette.
50 up. I'll go back to it in like 10 days.
See if we can make some money on it.
I've played it before. Yeah, it's just
impossible to bonus.
Yeah, they're not playing Saturday then, are they?
Yeah, they're not playing tomorrow then, are they?
I hate Saturdays, you know. I like I
feel the vibe on Saturday and that, but
I just don't like going out. I don't
like drinking on Saturdays, you know. I just don't
I just don't like drinking on Saturdays.
I take a Friday over Saturday. I just
don't like Saturdays. Let me see anyways
the lineup for tomorrow properly. Um,
so what I'll do Yeah. Okay. So okay,
I might do Enfield to win both teams to score.
Do to win both teams to score and
slow to win both teams to score. Yeah,
maybe I'll do something. No.
Yeah. Yeah, I would. Yeah.
And that's a big return if that comes in, bro. that.
Oh, I could just put 150 on a double.
Both teams to score
and that do one returns a good
wrist on it, bro.
Oh, look on the Oh, look on look on it,
bro. Look on it, bro. Look on it.
The do one's definitely they're
definitely both scoring, bro.
But that's not worth it cuz I got it to
100 on roulette. So,
no, I don't think it's worth it. Made stone.
Let me see what the odds are on it. The
odds are quite good on this one.
150 returns 436.
That's a good return from 150, isn't it?
Or 600 returns. 1744.
Maybe we put 600 on it. No,
no, but seriously, 150. So if you put one
Yeah, 15. Yeah, it's [ __ ] To be fair,
you can win way more than that on
roulette with 150.
With 150, you could easily get to 400.
We need to Okay, let me let me see.
Right. Both teams to score.
Both teams score. Both score. Oh,
do I want to do a correct score?
Give it a wall.
Do you want to do like a correct score?
Right. Nil nil
and nil nil. What's the chances? Right. So
Maidstone versus Anfield nil nil. End
over Hornurch nil nil. It's 131 to1.
I reckon that's all right.
Never know till you try.
Isn't that right, Dusty?
No, that's a chance. It isn't. What's
the chances, Dusty?£10 returns 1320.
It could happen though.
It could happen.
What do you think, Dusty?
I reckon it could.
Okay. So, the only way to do it, Stephen
Howard, is both teams to score and the
specific team to win.
That's the only way, lad.
The only way is pick two, three teams to
win and both teams to score that.
I think that's the only way.
Yeah, but even for both for both teams
to score is [ __ ] odds. Yeah, but a four
both teams to score is [ __ ] odds.
Yeah, but that's [ __ ] odds, lad.
No, but that's [ __ ] odds. I got five
both teams to score and I only got 220.
I got five both teams to score and I
only got 220. That's [ __ ] disgusting.
I got I won 200 pound for that. That's [ __ ]
That is [ __ ] bro.
You need to do a result both teams to
score, lad. Literally. Yeah.
Yeah. You need to do assault routine to score. Yeah.
Slow and Anfield Town when they're playing home.
When they're playing home. Yeah.
Yeah. Five teams to win. But what's the chances, bro?
Yeah, you're right. I won £75 before off
of a pound.
75 pound off of a pound before
and it was a sixfold
when I was 19. I didn't have a clue
about football. I just picked [ __ ] six teams.
Yeah, you need to pick you need to do
both teams to score with the specific
team to win.
With the specific with the specific team to win
with the spe with the specific team to
win in it
slow and end maybe like a freefold
Nah, I'm not a copycat, lad. Am I
grievy? No, I'm not a copycat.
If I was going to copy, I would be
telling you that I think Cheryl Cole is attractive.
I'd be telling you Cole's attractive.
Now, I don't copy, lad. There's no
copying on this channel.
Isn't that right, Grezy?
Oh, I might copy um LJ's bet. Squeezey.
What's your opinion on that?
Anything to say about that or Oh. Yeah. So, yeah. So,
right. Is this guy being a s grezy my
friend? Yeah. I showed him what that
woman was saying. He said, "Don't say
that again." I said, "They are [ __ ]
It's best just to not kick off at them."
I said, "But they are [ __ ] isn't it?"
He said, "I think some can be, but men
can be [ __ ] too. It's not really a specific gender."
Yeah, but more women are [ __ ] than men.
And I don't like no one. I'm I'm not
even biased, bro. I'm not even being
biased. But I mean, think about it.
Women are more [ __ ] than men.
Like, if you really if you really if you
really wanted to gener if you really
wanted to be real, Yeah.
I'd say they're more [ __ ] than than men.
But do men get defended? But here's the
thing, Greavves. Okay. Okay. Okay. So,
so, so both are as bad as each other,
but isn't it? Do men ever get defended?
So, what are you going to what you going
to think on Saturday, Greavesy, when I
do a tenfold over 1.5 goal?
Is that going to look specific or is
that going to look sorry, suspicious or what?
So, is my friend sing then? Um, Grezy,
you will never message a man on
Instagram and then start being a cult.
You would never You never get No, no,
no, no, no. It is It is women. It is
women. Trust me. How you can say it's
not a specific gender when women are
worse than men is beyond me. Women are
worse than men. Women are way worse than
men. The [ __ ] they do to play the games
they play. They are worse than men.
What's your opinion, Stephen Hour? No,
they are worse than men. Definitely
They are. And you'll know that because
you don't run into these problems with men
like you do women. So, no, it is. No,
women women are [ __ ]
Trust me, it's not a big thing, bro.
No, women are worse.
When I was working doing that Uber, when
I was dealing with rude people, it was mainly women.
It was actually mainly women. When I was
doing that Uber job, it happened about three times.
No, it was it's women, bro. It's
definitely definitely women. I think I
had one guy try to be a [ __ ]
But no, no, no. It was It was definitely definitely women.
What do you think? What do you think,
Steven Howard? Who do you think's worse,
men or women?
From my experience, it's definitely
women that are worse than men.
It's definitely definitely definitely
women that are worse than men in my
opinion. My in my experiences
I'm not a s.
I'm not a s. Steven Howard.
Women are disgusting. I'm not a s.
I'm not no [ __ ] s.
Why do you think I get so much [ __ ] from
people, bro? I speak my mind.
Never s in my life.
Never s in my life, lad.
So, has Timmy been has Timmy been defeated today? Uh,
uh, Greasy, has he been has he been defeated
after being defeated?
after being defeated.
After being defeated.
So what? You're saying he's been defeated?
I got nine thumbs up on that community
post and this is what they do to
nonslegs. I see now. I see what they do
now. I see what they do. So if I go for
Timmy every day, people will like me in it, Greavvesy.
Just like the way Nons goes for me. Ah,
I see. I see. Yeah,
that's how it works, isn't it, Greasy?
Oh, that's how it works, isn't it, Greasy?
Oh, I see. I see.
If women said to me yesterday, "Fuck
you, you cocknney cunt."
I'm not [ __ ] Cockney.
I'm not Cockney.
I'm not Cockney, Dusty. No.
I'm not cocky, lad.
No, I'm not [ __ ] Cockney.
Yeah. So, I see I see how it works now.
So, Timmy's the most hated
and I think I'm second. Yeah.
Yeah, that's what that's what it is. But
I have more people obsessed with me. No.
Well, no, I don't think so. No, no, no.
I don't think Timmy's hated more than me
just by people's obsession with me and
stuff. No, I think No, no, no. I don't think so.
I don't know. It's hard to say, lad. [ __ ]
Timmy's a proper [ __ ] bro.
Hey, bro. He didn't come in the the He
didn't go in the car, bro.
>> I know. I was watching everything. I
watched the whole lot. He's down on it.
He's [ __ ] He's He's just [ __ ]
>> What's What's What's your opinion?
Honestly, I I think women are worse than
men. I don't know what you think.
>> I don't know about that, but Timmy was
[ __ ] That's a joke. He was like He
had the car right outside, isn't it? >> Yeah.
>> He never went out.
Yeah, cuz he left [ __ ] Did you notice?
>> Did you notice when when you was saying
to him, "He's outside. He's outside.
He's outside." Yeah. He wouldn't let you talk.
>> He kept going back in, in it. He kept
>> Yeah. And he kept shouting over you like
talking bare [ __ ]
>> Yeah. He's never meeting anyone, bro.
You know what? I wasn't on YouTube yet.
Uh, sorry, not yesterday. The day
before. Yeah. I just watched like his
gambling videos in it cuz I thought,
"Oh, it's interesting." You know, like
some of the stuff.
>> They're crap. They're crapto. They're
only 20 piece steak. They're boring. No,
like when he was talking about gambling
like the blog like when he's talking
about industry I find I find it like I
find it um interesting in it. So I'm
listening and I'm listening to it and
this cunt's mentioning my name like what
and he done it over and over again. I
thought no [ __ ] this bro do you know
what I mean?
>> Yeah I heard that. That's when you got
the annoying bro. No it was annoying.
And it was and it was the way he was doing it. >> Yeah.
>> What he likes to do, bro, is he likes to
draw people out and start. And I heard
him he's arguing with Monty man again,
bro. It's just they just go around in circles.
>> He's a [ __ ] [ __ ]
>> They do go around in circles, don't it? >> Yeah.
>> So, why is this girl ignoring Oh, yeah.
PJ, why is this girl ignoring you? Yeah.
Why is she doing that?
>> I don't know. It was just someone on
Instagram, some random. I blocked them
anyways. It was some random in it.
>> Yeah, it sounds like you chat to her and
then she just went quiet.
>> No, I won't like get I weren't trying to
get into her and that.
>> No way, bro. I would say if I did, [ __ ] her anyways.
>> But no, I think I think women are I
think women are worse than men in like
the way like [ __ ] behavior. I do
believe that, bro. As [ __ ] as men are,
I believe they're worse. >> Yeah. Did
>> that you know that taxi earlier on? Yeah. Yeah.
>> Did Did Smokey Did Smokey have anything
to do with it? He didn't. Did he?
>> Well, obviously not, bro.
>> Do you think I'm going to Do you think
I'm going to give him my bank details?
He doesn't even know me, bro. He doesn't
even have my number.
>> Yeah. No, apparently he done a transfer.
I knew you wouldn't any I know it's [ __ ]
>> No, he's bullshitting, bro. Why? This
what I'm saying. He makes You can't win
with them, bro. This is what I'm saying to you.
>> Yeah, I agree with you. Why do you think
Tim was screaming the
>> It's not Kieran. It sounds like Kieran.
It's not Kieran. This guy isn't Kieran,
bro. He sounds like him, but it's not.
>> Who's Kieran?
>> This Oh, it's some other guy that sounds
like you. The one I was sending you by
the other day.
>> The reason Timmy kept shouting over you
earlier on is because you were saying
the car's outside. The car's outside. He
had nothing you can answer to that.
That's why he just kept talking over you.
>> It does sound like it.
>> You actually sound like Kieran though.
>> Yeah. I don't even know who that is.
He comes on a cut. It used to be called
Rocky Ride Rage.
>> I've had I joined, you know, I joined
one of Ellie's panels about 2 years ago
and people was commenting in the chat.
So people was commenting in the chat
saying this is PJ's mate who used to
talk to PJ and about 10 people were
saying it and I never even knew you were
I never even spoke to you then.
>> Yeah. No, it's rocking ride. Yeah, you
just sound Yeah, you just sound the
same, bro. But you're not I know you're
not him, but Yeah.
[ __ ] sake, man. I've had all different
names on here. I had one name on there
as Raymond. Then I had uh Hugh and now I got Fire.
>> So what's your actual What's your What's
your actual first name?
>> No comment.
>> Fair enough.
>> I knew I knew I knew it. I knew it
weren't Hugh. I knew it weren't Hugh.
>> Yeah. Yeah. Obviously not. That's a
disgusting name. I don't like telling
nothing on the air cuz you know these
weirdos are lot.
>> Yeah. Obviously. Yeah. Obviously.
Obviously. Obviously. Obviously.
>> I can't believe PJ. I can't believe you
started gambling, bro. I thought you
weren't going to do it, bro.
You know what, bro? It was a stressful
day in it. It was It was a stressful
day, is it?
>> Why don't you just [ __ ]
>> What? So, you deposited a one, I got
deposited. I I deposited 100. Yeah. I
got it to two. I hit 11. Yeah. On like
my last spin, so I got up to two in it.
A 50 spin. It went on 34. The dirty
[ __ ] [ __ ] bro. I just in it.
>> I just
Wait, Dusty. Dusty, do you remember that
about two years ago, isn't it? When I
was out my nut, I got arrested. You
know, you know, listen, I don't even
need to tell you. Yeah, you know the
numbers I cover. You know my exact bets
in it. You know exactly how they are.
>> 11. Yeah, it went on 34, bro. Even 17 was good.
>> It doesn't even need to be. It could be
17, 20. Like if it kept hitting in a
row. Imagine that hit four times in a
>> So tell me what happened. Yeah. You
deposited a one or did you do 100 spins straight away?
No, I done like 30 and then
what's the highest you got up to? 200.
>> Yeah, the highest I just rebet and then
just took the 150. [ __ ] it in it.
>> Yeah, but that's [ __ ] that's still
good though. That took willpower to do
that. Most people would never be able to
do that. Cuz I know cuz you know it gets
you it gets you in a bad mood in it.
That's the thing that I lost 50. Yeah.
I'd carry on spinning and if you're
doing 50 spins, there's only three more.
>> Yeah. Yeah. But [ __ ] that in it, bro.
Let's just go back to it
>> in a bit. Bro, like all I had to, bro,
Imagine I hit 17 though. That would have
been a good hit, isn't it? Yeah.
>> Could you Did you uh could you [ __ ]
Can you like cancel the withdrawal on
your thing on your app and carry on?
>> Yeah, but yeah, but I'm not going to
cancel it, bro. Don't worry.
>> Oh, please don't please don't do that. I
promise you you're losing if you do that.
>> You You know it, bro. Look, you see what
I'm saying, though? It gave me 11 to get
me hooked chair. I rebet and it missed.
I had 19 numbers coming. 19 numbers,
bro. Yeah, that's a lot.
>> How many went on? 34, bro. 3 [ __ ] four.
>> I hate that number.
>> 17 was good, bro.
>> 17's next door, isn't it?
>> Yeah, that was good.
>> What does it go? It's like six. Uh, what
is it? 34 uh 6
>> 27 27 25 is it? >> Yeah.
>> The worst is 25 cuz that's in between,
bro. That's That's in between 17. That's
in between 70 17 and 20. That's the
worst, bro. That's the worst.
>> What is
>> [ __ ] 25?
>> Yeah. Well, do you like that number?
That's a disgusting number.
>> No, bro. Do you know what though? I used
to I went through a period like two
years ago. I started betting on 25 and
it kept coming in. So,
>> why? It's [ __ ] horrible number.
>> Cuz some woman told me I'd be her 25th
before, so I kept betting on the 25 and
it kept coming in.
I swear. Is that right? Gley,
>> you're winding up.
>> No, I swear to God. I swear to God. And
I kept betting on it in it cuz the
number always used to [ __ ] me over. So I
thought, "Fuck this. I'm going to start
betting on it."
>> Well, it started coming in.
>> It started coming in, bro. On my
birthday, I hit 25 on my birthday. I had
like eight pound on it in the bookies,
you know, like the the bar. I swear I
had eight pound on it. Come in. That's
>> £8. left 288, ain't it? >> Yeah.
>> Or but
>> it was on my birthday though, is it? I
won on my birthday.
>> Did you walk away? >> Yeah.
>> Did you walk?
>> I couldn't go I couldn't go out I
couldn't go out drinking cuz I went out
the night before Saturday. My birthday
was on a Sunday in it. So I was too [ __ ]
>> Yeah, I was too [ __ ] in it.
>> When you walked out the bookies, did you
keep looking back and you wanted to turn around? >> Nah.
>> How much did you collect?
I think 300 I put in.
>> Yeah, that's decent.
>> All right, but the you you don't bet on
sports, you said, is it? No, you said
you don't bet on it.
>> Not not really. No, I just normally play roulette.
>> Yeah. When do you re When do you reckon
you play it again? I think you're going
to play again soon.
>> No, [ __ ] that. You're going to play it
again soon, is it? No.
>> No, I ain't. I actually ain't. >> Yeah.
But to win life changing money, bro, you
need to streak. But what's the chances
you'll streak? It's rare, isn't it? >> Yeah.
>> Sorry, I'm just looking on my iPad at
Timmy's last video. His face makes me
laugh so many times as well, Pete. What
iPad have you got? >> What?
>> What iPad have you got?
>> I ain't got a [ __ ] clue.
>> Is it expensive?
>> No, about 600 quid about 4 years ago.
>> Nice, bro.
The phone the phone I got is a S23. It's
not special. I bought it out of CEX. It
was quite dear. They overpriced in there. >> Yeah.
>> That was a couple years ago. Like 400 and something.
>> Have you seen that money mic?
>> Yeah. I don't know him, but I've
>> seen He's [ __ ] ugly, isn't it?
>> He's uh Yeah, he's Timmy's mate, isn't it?
>> Yeah. What would you do if you look like that? Oh,
>> would you kill yourself?
>> I'm not even I'm not even being oral.
Yeah, but if you look like that, yeah, I
don't even mean it's oral. Yeah, you're
[ __ ] Yeah. Like, what woman's going
to want to go near that?
>> That short, fat, midlife, piss head.
>> Um, I would think I' I'd actually
consider it. Yeah. Would you?
>> I'd probably go bald and try to grow a
beard. Just make the most best of my
situation. Is it? If you if you look
like him, would you really want to kill yourself?
>> Yeah, probably.
>> Yeah, that would be Pete, wouldn't it?
>> It's all right. You don't even need to
be good-looking. You could be average
and still like got the body.
>> When Timmy was live a little while ago,
Red Star was in his chat. Yeah. And
Timmy was like, "Oh, Red Star, you
[ __ ] legend. I love you." >> Yeah.
>> Yeah. They're [ __ ] batty man, bro.
Batty man, is it? Would you would you
kill yourself if you was just ginger but not ugly? >> No.
>> Well, you just you just you just go you
just you wouldn't mind that.
>> No, I don't like ginger but I wouldn't
kill myself just over that. If I look
like like Money Mike or someone similar
to that and then Yeah. want to kill
myself. Would you want to kill me?
>> What about Timmy?
>> Oh, [ __ ] Yeah. No, Timmy ain't Timmy.
Timmy ain't getting no woman. I'm
laughing. Yeah, because I've seen I'm
laughing because so many times I've been
watching your streams over the years and
when his face comes up with the glasses
and the hat and that you always start laughing it. >> Yeah.
>> What if you look like What if you look
like Monty Man?
>> What do you mean? Well, bold.
>> No, like look like him.
>> If I was bold, I would just wear a hat
all the time. Would you What would you
do if you look like Timmy? Would you
really want to kill yourself? >> Yeah.
Wait, someone said that that even Lord
Even if I look like Lord Jay, I would
like it. Even if it's disgusting.
>> Like he's bald. He's got Bro, that is disgusting.
>> He's well fat as well, isn't it? >> Yeah.
>> Someone someone said earlier on in
Timmy's chat that you're selling your
bed or something. I know it's [ __ ]
I just want to tell you.
>> Apparently, I heard of it. I know what
they're on about is when you said you
was going to strip your bed off, then
someone's twisted it around to you're
stripping your bed to sell it.
>> [ __ ] idiots, isn't it?
>> They always do stuff like that, isn't it?
>> Yeah, they're retards in it.
>> If you got skin, would you ever sell
your bed? [ __ ] that.
>> Um, never.
No, I would never sell my bed, lads. No,
I don't believe in sending any of your
things to be honest.
No, I don't even selling [ __ ]
>> Really, bro? I don't like selling stuff,
bro. Unless you've got like a double.
Like, say you had like Rolex watches
yet. You had B and you sold one like 20
years ago and you still had some, you
know, they'll be worth money in 20
years, you know? >> Yeah.
>> [ __ ] No, I wouldn't, bro.
>> When are you buying more Lego sets? I
ain't got I haven't got I don't know you
have the patience to do them.
>> I don't I haven't done it.
I thought I see I see you completed one
of them in it.
>> No, I got I got I got so far almost. But
there's I got another one, bro. It cost me 120.
>> Have you done it yet?
>> No, I haven't even touched it. I just I
just like the figures.
>> I see the other day you had like a white
[ __ ] Vader, isn't it?
>> Yeah, bro.
>> I'm a massive massive Star Wars fan.
When it comes to Star Wars,
>> I love Star Wars. I love Star Wars, bro.
As a kid,
>> I I always have,
>> bro. But it used to come on every
Sunday. Do you remember? Like years ago,
it used to come on every Sunday. Do you remember?
>> No, I can't say I do.
>> Yeah. Well, it used to come on. I used
to like the [ __ ] um Do you remember
Darth Darth Maul? That was like my
favorite fight, bro.
>> When I when I was killed.
>> Yeah. Liam Le gets killed. Quon Jin.
That was my favorite one. That That's um
Phantom of the Menace 1999 that come out.
>> But I have to say it, bro. I have to say
100% my favorite is Spider-Man, bro. I
think it has to be in it.
>> Yeah. But in my eyes, Spider-Man is
[ __ ] Toby Magguire. Like Spider-Man
1, 2, and 3, like 2004 onwards.
>> All the newer Spider-Man's are [ __ ]
Like there's one of them. There's one
Spider-Man, and he's [ __ ] black.
>> There's no cuz nothing is like how it
used to be. It will never be how it used
to be. That's anything. Games, movies.
>> The original Spider-Man's a sick film. I
watched it a while ago.
>> Yeah, there was one in 2002, 2004, 2007.
Yeah, I watched all three of I watched
all three of them a little while ago. I
watched the first one.
>> I was thinking of I was thinking of
watching them all again, bro.
>> Yeah, I watched the first one. It was on
the telly was on ITD, I remember. And
then I went online and watched the other two.
>> The second the second
>> one of is the second one is the Green
Goblin one. The third one's with
Sandman, isn't it?
>> No, third one is when he has a black
turns into a black suit, is it?
>> Yeah, that's the third one. Yeah, that's
the third one. Yeah, the Yeah, with the
black Spider-Man. Yeah,
>> I watched the new Superman last year.
Was it last year? The one that come in the cinema?
>> Last seen.
>> It was last year, was it? Yeah, I think.
Yeah, I watched it. It was all right. You know,
I need to go cinema on Thursday to watch
this new Scream.
>> Is it out? Yeah,
>> it's on uh Thursday. >> Yeah.
>> I love horror films in the cinema. I go
every time there's one, bro.
>> What? Horror films? Yeah, I love him, bro.
>> Yeah, I do like the cinema,
>> but there's not always something there's
not always something to watch. You get me?
>> I went about two weeks ago and I watched
that new Jason Stathithm film and it was
All these films are the same, bro. It's
about a girl and she they want to kidnap
her. Every one of them is about like the
same. This one was [ __ ]
>> You don't know Chucky though, is it?
>> Yeah, I've seen all of them. I loved
them when I was a kid.
>> They're good in it. Yeah. Yeah,
>> I used to I like the first one, you
know, the 1980 one.
>> Yeah, that's banging. Bride and Chucky's
good as well.
>> Think about it, bro. Back in the day,
they have better games, better movies, better porn.
>> Yeah, life nowadays [ __ ] in it.
>> It's all that Tik Tok [ __ ] and that.
Have you seen the memes?
>> Do you have Tik Tok? I don't have it.
>> No, there was there was there was a meme
yet of this cat on the phone. It said,
"That's enough Tik Tok for today." And
then the cat started getting mad. It
started raing. Did you see it?
>> No. No. But you've seen you've seen
stuff like that, I guess.
>> Hey, what's that Discord? I've never had
that. That looks real confusing.
>> Oh, it's just some it's it's like Do you
remember Skype? It's a bit like what
Skype used to be. Do you remember Skype?
>> Yeah. Everyone I always hear everyone
say on here, PJ, you're on Discord and
you always say, "No, I ain't." Why do
they always say that you are when you if you ain't?
>> Don't know. They're idiots, lad.
>> Have you got an account? >> No.
>> No. No. Right.
>> You remember Skype, though? Do you remember Skype?
>> Yeah. Cool to do. Skype was decent. It's
not It's not You don't hear about it
anymore though, is it?
>> Yeah. It's gone quiet. There was another
>> back in 2012. It was used to be the
thing. People just used to use it in it. >> Yeah.
>> There's there's another one as well. It
was like WhatsApp. It was called Viber.
>> Yeah, I heard of that.
>> It was [ __ ] >> Yeah.
>> Did you have a Blackberry?
>> Yep. BBM, bro.
>> Yeah. Yeah, Blackberry Bold and that is it.
>> Yeah, that was Blackberry Curve. That
was another one, isn't it?
>> Yeah, I think I think I had the Curve or
the Bold. I can't remember.
>> The Bold is better.
>> And everyone in school had each other on
BBM and like, "Oh, those were the good days, bro."
>> Yeah, BBM was good.
>> BBM was [ __ ] And people just used to
add each other like people used to like,
"Yeah, it was the days, bro."
O do you remember? Do you remember them?
You might not remember this. Yeah. But
do you remember them penguin dippers?
You know, penguin chocolate. Yeah. You
know, with the penguin on it.
>> Yeah, of course I do.
>> Years ago, years ago, they used to do
this dip thing and I'm talking [ __ ]
about 15, 16, 17 years ago. They stopped
doing them. Oh my god, they were nice,
bro. They were [ __ ] nice.
>> And they stopped doing them.
Do you like Lunchables? Huh?
>> What's that? Lunchables. They have like
biscuits and ham and [ __ ] Or there's
another one called like attacker snacks
and it has like a tortilla wrap in it.
>> No. When you when you go Greg's Yeah.
What's your favorite thing?
>> Uh normally get a shortage roll and a chicken bake.
>> Um a bacon and cheese wrap, bro. That's my favorite.
>> Oh, they're so nice. Aren't they? Bacon
and cheese turnover.
>> But when they when they come up when
they first come out, you know, when they
first come out. Oh my god, bro. They're nice.
>> Do you prefer it? Do you prefer it when
you go Gregs and the food's warm or
cold? I hate it when it's cold.
>> Obviously warm, bro. Yeah, it's better.
>> What kind of cook is that? You silly goose.
>> No, no, no, no. You know, you know the
bacon and cheese wraps, bro. So, every
time I go to Gregs, maybe one in 10
times it's warm cuz they're not like
sausage rolls. They're not popular like
sausage rolls. So, they're not always
making them. You get me? So, if you just
get a sausage roll, then they're they're
warm eight times out of 10, I'd say. You
know what I mean? But cheese.
>> Sausage rolls take ages to cool down in it.
>> I don't really like them that much. I
don't mind them. I don't just dislike
them. I like the steak bake and the
bacon and cheese wrap.
>> Yeah, that's nice. Oh, you love cheese
strings, isn't it?
>> I used to. Yeah, bro. When I was Yeah,
>> they're nice, don't they?
>> I used to have a pack lunch with like,
you know, Tik Tok the orange and lime. I
used to have winders
>> winders. Yeah.
>> Like when the the thing you peel off
them, if you look at it, it's like a
story, isn't it? You read along it. >> Yeah.
>> Oh, I used to love them. I used to peel
I didn't used to eat a bit at a time. I
used to peel the whole thing off then
put the whole thing in my mouth as well. Nice.
>> Yeah, man.
Yeah. I've got I've got Tic Tacs here.
Right here now, bro.
>> What? You got Tic Tacs? What flavor?
Orange and lime.
>> Yeah, bro.
You remember Hubba Bubba?
>> Yeah, that was on a roll as well, wasn't
it? I used to like the cola one.
What did you What did you eat today?
got me left. Oh gosh.
UK asylum. Oh gosh.
>> Don't know what happened there, lad.
>> [ __ ] no. What was you saying? Do I remember? What?
>> Do you remember um PS1? Like there was a
certain game, but Crash Bandicut on the PS1.
>> I was just going to say Crash Bandicoot
PS1 was the [ __ ] that the game was
>> I've got Crash Bandicut right here, lad.
I used to play I used to play Tony
skateboarded as well.
>> Used to play what? All bro, do you
remember? No. No. Do you know the de
when they used to put [ __ ] toys in
the in in the cinema? Not the cinema, the cereal. >> Yeah.
>> You remember when they used to do like
do you know the Invincibles and they
used to put the toys in the [ __ ]
>> Bro, those were the days, man.
>> You remember um in I don't know if you
had it near you in your local McDonald's
when you was a kid. Did you have the
thing and you put like a penny in it and
it goes round and round and round?
>> Yep. Yep. The light store one had it.
>> It was also a play area. They used to
have a player area in it.
>> Look on Look on eBay. Yeah. Some of the
used Lego sets. Yeah. From years ago.
They're worth a lot of money. >> Really?
>> Some of them are rare as [ __ ] Yeah.
>> Do you remember the period though in
McDonald's when they done the dogs?
>> I don't know. They probably have done so
much, haven't they? Did you collect everyone?
>> No, the toy though. They used to do toy
dogs. No. No. They used to do like You
know, you know when you used to get a
toy in a Happy Meal? >> Yeah.
>> Yeah. They used to do actual like toy
dogs and it was the fun to collect.
>> Did you collect every one? You had the last few.
>> I think maybe two. Yeah, bro. Cuz what?
Every week in it. >> Yeah.
>> You get me?
>> Some McDonald's would have the same toys for ages.
>> Yeah. And then you
>> I don't know how much one is now. I
bought one for years. I bet they're
about five now, >> probably.
>> What's your What did you eat? What did
you eat today? Oh, we did the Indian.
>> Oh, yeah. What'd you get? Uh,
>> pillow rice.
>> Nice, man. The madress is nice, bro. Was it lamb?
>> No, chicken. Lamb lamb madress is really
nice as well, ain't it?
>> I normally just get the lamb, bro.
>> I get chicken. Sometimes I get I don't
really get the chicken to be I have had
it obviously. I have. Have you ever had
>> You should get like a lamb t You know,
you know how they do lamb? They do they
do lamb chicken ticker and lamb ticker.
You should try the lamb ticker one as well.
>> Yeah, I've had chicken tikka masala.
I've not had the lamb one. Is it any good? >> Yeah.
>> Well, that's not very hot though, is it?
You like hot stuff, don't you?
>> No, I have a madress sometimes. No,
sometimes I do have a mad. It depends, isn't it?
>> It just depends what I feel like in it.
Like more when it's not as cold, I'll
get a madress in it. Do you get me? Like
depends. Yeah. Go on.
>> Do you get Bombay potato sagaloo?
Whatever it's called. No, but they give
it sometimes for free.
>> You love onion bis? >> No,
>> I don't like them.
>> So, how much how much was the Indian?
>> Uh, let me get the thing.
>> 22 quid.
>> It was nice. Yeah.
>> Yeah, it was all right.
No, I like chicken ticker. I always get
that chicken tick on the side, is it?
But I try to avoid at night when I get a
curry now. I just try I just get the
curry and the rice. I tried to just get
the curry and the rice cuz um obviously
if you have tickle all the time and that
you get fat and that ain't it? I tried
to cut down on [ __ ] ain't it?
>> Yeah. Someone said Timmy's call
someone's Timmy's calling you out live.
>> Let me see. Well, he's not live. He's
just come off live.
>> He's a retarder.
>> He got the [ __ ] got SIM card in his
phone. He has to keep going in pubs and
connecting to Wi-Fi.
>> To be fair, my phone's blocked. I have
to do that as well. >> Why?
Oh, I didn't pay my phone bill. My phone
long story, bro. But yeah.
>> Can't you just put Can't you just chuck
that Can't you just chuck that SIM card
away and put a page you go in it?
>> No, cuz they blocked the phone. The phone's blocked.
>> Oh [ __ ] I didn't think they could do
that anymore. I thought that was old school.
>> No, they can. I never thought they could
that they can and they do it in stages
as well. They do it in stages. Like
they'll stop a certain part then and
then after the third time they'll just
completely block it.
>> Yeah, they do that now, lad. They do
that now. Yeah. Some people just manage
to put a pair as you go sim in and it
works. But I thought that was old school
>> I think it's a new thing, bro. I think
it's a new Maybe it's with certain phones maybe.
>> Yeah. How much is the bill if you want
to pay it? I bet it's loads in it.
>> Yeah. And they wouldn't put the services
back if you the longer you go about
paying it, even if you paid it, it's not
like they they put it. So what happens
when you don't pay it? Yeah. For over a
certain period of time, they will put it
on um they will what's it? They will uh
>> Yeah. They'll take the money from you.
>> They will they will put it they will put
it they'll they'll transfer it to a debt
company like collector. Sorry. So then
but even if you pay it they they might
not put the services on. Do you get me?
What do you get what I'm saying?
>> Yeah. Then they won't even unbox the
phone either. That just be
>> That's what I mean. Yeah. That's what
I'm saying, bro. Cuz I had it before. I
said I can pay it. But they said, "Oh,
even if you pay, it's not guaranteed." I
said, "Well, I'm not going to Why am I
going to pay it then?"
>> What they say then?
>> They just said nothing. The whole thing
just didn't make sense. But obviously
like the thing is, bro, yeah. When I go
out in London central where there's
Wi-Fi everywhere, you you understand?
It's like it's Wi-Fi is everywhere, bro.
You get me?
>> Someone said, "Uh, PJ, have you had more
wins and losses?" I doubt it. All most
gamblers are down.
>> Probably even, bro. Or down a bit. Yeah.
>> Look at Timmy. He's live again. He's a
[ __ ] ugly [ __ ] bro.
>> If he's If he's not going to step If
he's not going to step in the taxi, he's
not going to be meeting anyone. Think about
>> Have you Have you got your other phone there?
>> I don't have another phone, bro.
>> Oh, I thought you had two. I was going
to say turn him up. I want to hear what he's saying.
>> No, no, no, no. He's just What? But
everyone's going at Timmy. Yeah. But
have you noticed when I go for Timmy,
people people stop going for me. That's
how much he's hated. It's It's similar
to nonslegs. It makes sense, isn't it?
>> Yeah, it does. And earlier on, when you
blatantly prove that you booked that
taxi, Yeah. everyone was on your side in this community.
>> Yeah. But if I prove something against
nonslegs, they tap [ __ ] in it. That's
what I'm saying. It goes by who's liked
and than that and who's hat cuz everyone
hates Timmy. But I would say people are
still more obsessed with me than Timmy.
I re I think so, bro.
>> Timmy. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Definitely.
Look at the amount. You get much more
videos than that made about you than
what Timmy does. They're more obsessed with you.
>> I've got channels dedicated specifically to me. >> Yeah.
>> But you know what I'm saying? Like Yeah.
Which is worse. Which is worse, bro? In my opinion. >> Yeah.
>> Yeah. They're more obsessed with you.
>> Why do you think they do it? I think
they're gay in it.
>> Yeah. You always say this, isn't it?
>> I think they are gay. Definitely, lad. Yeah.
>> You like Red Star, for example, when he
wakes up. Yeah. Within the first within
the first five minutes of his eyes
opening, do you reckon he's checked your channel? 100%.
>> Yeah, he probably has, isn't it? And
what's so mad is they don't even get
paid for it. Imagine doing that for
years for free. What a batty, man. Bro,
>> wait. How long has he been doing this to you for?
>> Years, bro. Like three, four years.
>> [ __ ] hell. I didn't know that long. I
only found Red Star a few months ago,
>> man. These people here that you see that
do this have been doing it for years.
Years, bro. To to everyone. Yeah.
Nothing new on this community. What you
see on this community has been happening for years.
>> Riff Riff has done a lot of videos on
you and it was in your chat earlier. >> Really? >> Yeah.
>> One second.
>> Oh yeah.
But not one not one person's taking um
Timmy's side in it. No.
Why Why is Timmy hated so much on here?
>> Probably cuz he's a [ __ ] house. He done
all that earlier on. You got him a taxi. He didn't
>> All he had to do was get in that taxi in it.
>> All he had to do, bro. Yeah.
>> He was saying
>> I would have I would have I would have
paid for it back as well.
>> Would you? >> Yeah.
>> He was saying that you booked it for 11
p.m. But you said that you booked it for 7.
>> Yeah. He's talking [ __ ] bro. The cab
was out. You saw the screenshot. It was outside.
>> Oh no, it was outside.
And then Timmy was saying about half
hour ago on his live stream that, oh,
you've adopted it in his AI. That was
way too quick for you to [ __ ] sake, bro.
What the [ __ ] Is that what you were saying?
>> I'm not even allowed to do any of that.
>> You must have got a cancellation charge,
isn't it? It's like six quid, I think.
>> Yeah. He said, "Do I want to tip him or
not?" And I just said, "Yeah, just [ __ ]
it in it."
>> How much did you give him? Five or six
pound? Just leave it in it, bro. >> Yeah,
>> cuz I would be pissed off if someone Do
you get what I'm saying, bro?
>> Yeah, that's PJ. That's why he wouldn't
let you talk. That's why he kept
shouting over you when you were saying
go outside. Go outside. He was shouting
over to shouting over you. He wouldn't
let you speak.
>> But that that cab driver was really
going to drive all the way, is it? He
would have done. Yeah.
>> Yeah, of course he would. And oh,
another thing as well, PJ. Yeah, Lord J
and and a few others were saying they
take the money after. No, they
definitely don't. I know they take the
money first, bro.
>> Yeah. Yeah. See,
>> 100% fact. They take the money first.
>> If you order Do you reckon Do you reckon
if you ordered an Uber from here to
Scotland? Do you reckon one driver would
do it? One would. Yeah. It
>> Yeah. One. Yeah. One would. Yeah.
>> It be hard though. It'd be hard to find
one that would do. Do you know what I
would do, brother? Yeah. You know what I
do? Yeah. If I won Yeah. I swear to God.
If I won like 100 grand, this is another
thing I do. Yeah. I'd buy like a camper
van and just go all over Europe, bro.
>> Oh, yes. Yes. You know, I've always
wanted one. They're so expensive.
>> Do that, bro.
>> Have you seen how much they are? They're well.
>> They're dear, in it. They're there. I
know they're there.
>> People want 20 grand for an old shitty one.
>> [ __ ] hell, bro.
>> I'd get like a [ __ ] like a nice bed,
a nice telly. Yeah. Put your Xbox like
Xbox. Yeah. Get like a a hot tub. Like
I'd like a bro, I'd do it nice. Just go
all over Europe.
>> I'd live I'd live in one of them. 100% I would.
>> Would you Would you go all over Europe
and that? Yeah.
>> Yeah, I would. Yeah,
>> 100%. You wouldn't even need to pay for
hotels in it.
>> No, I'd do exactly the same as you. Just
get a banging telly, get the latest
console out. That'd be sick.
>> It'd be sick, bro. You'd save so much
money on hotels as well. So much money.
>> I'd literally go straight away as well when you
>> Yeah, 100%. Like would you be would you
be hesitant about leaving or would you just go?
>> I would just go.
>> But obviously I'd have to learn to drive
it. But that's the only thing. >> Yeah.
>> I don't have you have a driving license. >> Yeah.
>> You really? >> Yeah.
>> Nice. I don't. Bro,
>> have you never done your theory test?
>> No. How old was you when you got yours then?
>> Uh 2018 I done mine.
Oh, a few years ago then. >> Yeah.
LJ don't even have his driver's license, you know.
>> Don't he
something about I think some people
don't. Is it?
>> He was the one who said earlier on that
Uber charge you afterwards.
>> Yeah. He's a [ __ ] [ __ ] isn't it?
>> Even a even a normal taxi. Yeah. If you
went down to your local station now went
up to a taxi rank and said Birmingham,
mate, you'd have to pay up front.
>> Yeah, of course. But at least half. At
Yeah, he's talking [ __ ] He said he uses
Uber. Of course he's talking.
>> He said he uses Uber all the time and
they always charge afterwards. No way.
That's B. He never uses Uber.
>> He never uses Uber, bro.
>> He definitely don't.
>> He doesn't. But do you know what scares
me? Yeah. Say you actually did gamble
online. Yeah. And you actually won like
80 grand. Imagine trying to get it.
I always think that they do they'd lock
it off and do bare checks and that.
>> I think they would just close your account.
>> I actually think they would just close I
I reckon they would just close the whole
your whole account.
>> I do as well to be fair. >> They'd
hold the money for ages and talk bare [ __ ]
>> How much do you reckon they would do
that? Do you reckon they'd do it for
four grand or do you reckon they would
just pay the four grand? I think with
four grand they might pay it. Yeah, four
grand they'd pay it if he was ID
verified and all that [ __ ] but
>> I reckon something like 20 or 30. I
reckon they'd [ __ ] you over, bro.
>> Yeah, they'd stop it and do further
checks and stuff.
>> Casinos pay it in it. Like lamb one. Yeah. >> Yeah.
>> But they'd probably like make you go
through hoops and [ __ ] in it.
>> Yeah, probably if you have a massive win.
>> You know what I mean?
I remember that time I won four grand.
They put it in like these blue like
wallets, bro. Like£1,000 wallets.
>> Yeah, it I got the Do you know when the
new notes come out, bro? With a [ __ ]
whatever his name is on the on the note,
bro. I got the the new one.
>> Charles, Prince Charles. >> Yeah,
>> he's a king now. It
>> Yeah, bro. See, that's where you you
can't always get them£50 notes, but when
you go casino, you always get them, bro.
always got 50 pound lunch. Never
I prefer having 20s to 50s.
>> The only thing with 50 is is you know
the annoying thing about 50s is like say
you go into like a pub. Yeah. And you
have to carry all that change in.
>> Yeah. And some places as well they check
them check them for ages.
>> Yeah. In case they're faking it.
>> The old paper 50s they used to rub them
on a white bit of paper.
>> Yeah. JD JT JD like put felt tip on it in it.
>> Yeah. Like a pen thing. Yeah. money pin.
>> We need to go to one of them casinos and
just rob it, lad.
>> Get caught. You get caught straight away.
>> They've got They've got a million there.
I know they do, bro. Behind that counter, it
>> got better money, bro.
>> There's got to be like a million, bro.
There's got to be in it.
>> I think they have I think casinos have
to have enough to cover all the chips
and everything on the floor.
>> How much do you reckon? Like a million.
>> Yeah, it's got to be. I ain't got a clue
that much. But it's going to be a lot.
You really want to go casino, isn't it?
>> I want to rob it. I want to rob it. Like
[ __ ] We should rob it, bro.
>> Are you going to go casino tomorrow and play roulette?
>> No. Are you?
>> No. No. Don't do it.
>> Oh, should we rob Should we do Should we
rob it though? >> No.
I don't want to go to I don't want to go
in prison. He's long.
>> We could get away though, is it? No,
>> not these days. Back in the day, you
probably could. Like 30, 40 years ago,
you might had a chance. You might have
had a fighting chance in it. >> Yeah.
>> No, you can't, bro.
>> Well, so why you know that that video
what Tim put up the other day saying get
a gambling vlog? Yeah.
>> I didn't I didn't actually watch that
one. What does he Is that the one? Does
he randomly start talking about you?
>> Yeah, he randomly starts talking about
me, bro. Saying, "Oh, your skin, your
this and I was like, what the [ __ ] bro?
>> What the [ __ ] that got to do with
anything? I know. Yeah, because he just
he tries to draw people out. This is
what I mean. He tries to draw people out, bro.
>> Why? He's a weirdo, isn't it?
>> Proper, bro. Proper
>> Look at his face. It's funny, isn't it?
>> Yeah. [ __ ]
>> You know these people that go on Timmy's
and Lord Jia, they must be on it 24/7. Is it? >> Yeah.
As soon as Timmy goes live, you click on
it, they're there straight away in it.
>> Yeah. All the regulars.
>> Screenshot. Have you got any pictures of
Timmy? Put it as your profile picture. I
want to see him. He makes me laugh. His face.
>> Okay, I'll do it right now.
>> You had a picture of him before. It was [ __ ] funny.
>> I do like to go on detox. I like detox, bro.
>> What's that? Like when you just stopped
drinking for a while, like a month for
>> detox. I thought you meant like a
website called detox. >> Ah,
>> yeah. No, that's good. Yeah. No, I do
it. It makes you feel good mentally as well.
>> And then and you enjoy it more when you
do go out, isn't it?
>> Yeah. When you go out once a month,
that's all right. If you go once if you
go out once a week, it just gets [ __ ]
>> I think every two weeks is all right, isn't it?
>> Yeah. Two weeks is all right. Yeah.
>> But Timmy drinks every day, bro.
>> He's always pissed. He's always always
in the pub. Does he get pissed out of
his head every day?
>> I see.
>> He was telling the truth.
>> There you go. Look, there you go.
>> Put on big screen.
>> One sec.
>> It's funny, isn't it?
>> Oh, mate. It's the
>> I think you like to me.
>> I think he's [ __ ] off his head.
You you you do the gear in it.
>> No, not no more.
>> You have done it.
>> Yeah, loads of times. I don't do it
anymore. [ __ ] That ain't no good for you.
>> Yeah, I've only done it twice, me.
>> Look at the size of his glasses, bro.
>> He does it all the time, bro.
>> Yeah, cuz he never used to be on He
never used to be on the packets, did he?
But he's Every time I see him now, he
always looks sniffed out of his head.
>> When did you last do it then? Uh, New
Year's Eve, but I ain't had nothing since.
>> Oh, fair enough, bro.
It's like£60 per person, isn't it?
>> Uh, I don't know. I just got 16th, which
is like 1.75 g. I got 16 for a one. >> Yeah.
>> Yeah. I've only tried it. Tried it. You
know what? The first time I tried it, it
was actually with Timmy,
>> was it?
>> Yeah. If I went to Birmingham, I knew he
was doing it.
>> Everyone's different. People do like
40s, like point fours. You get three 40s
for 100, two for 70.
>> Just made me It just made me so horny, bro.
>> Yeah, it it does.
>> But do you know what's so mad is that
people do it like it's normal. More
people that go clubbing do it than don't
do it, bro. Like they do it like it's the norm. >> Yeah.
>> You know what I mean? I don't do it,
bro. [ __ ] that.
>> Someone's in the background.
He said, "Stop talking like
>> I mean someone in the background chat,
he said, "Stop talking like [ __ ] you
pair of pedo py cunts."
>> UK you UK are silent. Who's that?
>> [ __ ] no, bro.
>> Did you ever have a GameCube?
>> Yeah, they were sick. Mario Kart used to play.
>> Yeah. And Simpsons hit him running. That was sick.
>> Oh yes. You know, Simpsons was the one.
That was the one. Yeah.
>> Oh my god. I had that on the I had that
on PS2. I can hear the sounds now. I
could sit there and play that right now. I swear.
>> I love that.
>> It was just like a Simpsons GTA.
>> Don't you miss the days? Yeah. Like when
you could just put a disc in your PS2
and it would just play. No downloading,
no internet, no Xbox.
>> Yeah. Yeah.
>> Why did you Why did you get an Xbox this
time? I think there's [ __ ] I've always been PlayStation.
>> You know what? I've never I I used to be
PlayStation. I never used to be Xbox. I
bought it just to have it for like
YouTube and that. Not like to seriously gaming.
>> Yeah, you can use it for YouTube.
>> You got to admit there. And I I I like
PlayStation, bro. I prefer PlayStation.
Trust me, I had PS2, PS3. Trust me, I
prefer PlayStation. But you've got to
admit the Xbox controller is better,
bro. Come on. You got
>> It's more It's more comfortable in the
hand like like the much more much more
comfortable. The PS5 controller is not very comfortable.
>> You know, do you know what my favorite
PlayStation was? You know, the old PS3,
that shiny one, bro. Oh, that was sexy,
>> Yeah. Do you remember? Yeah. Do you
remember that one?
>> But do you know what happened? When I
had it for so long, it started getting
loud, bro. Like a hoover, bro. They they
they started getting loud, though. Like
when I'd be speaking to someone on a
mic, you could hear it.
>> I missed the PS2. The sounds when I hear
the videos on YouTube, they're so nostalgic.
>> What was your What was your What was
your favorite GTA again? >> Um
probably [ __ ] There was Grand Theft
Auto 3. That was good. Um, that starts
when you're he's like he's in an orange
jumpsuit on the bridge and the car's on fire.
>> My one was San Andreas, I think, bro.
>> Vice City was good. San Andreas was
sick. Is that Do you remember when you
ride around on the BMX? I used to love that.
>> Yeah, I started that in it.
>> Yeah, I like all of them. The new ones [ __ ]
>> You know what? Hey, do you not do you
not watch them videos them shorts where
it says what what happens if you do this
in this GTA and it gives example. Have
you seen them? You must have seen them.
>> Yeah. Yeah, I have seen them. Yeah,
there's [ __ ] crazy. They were
addicting, bro. Bro, they were addicting as well.
>> I still remember I still remember the
[ __ ] um cheat code for weapons for I
think it was by city. It was R1, R2, L1,
R2, left, down, right up, left down,
right up. How mad is that? I still
remember that 20 years on.
>> Yeah, I don't remember that.
>> I used to give you all all different
>> You never You never You never played
Runescape, did you?
>> No. What is that? That's [ __ ] weird
[ __ ] bro. You can't It's a game where
you can't even explain it. Like, does
that make sense? Like you would be I
can't explain it. It's like
>> it looks weird. Too weird. >> Yeah.
>> It's like you you can't explain it.
There's no point. You'd have to actually
be here and I and you'd have to actually
get the gist of it. Does that make sense?
>> Well, do you play that?
>> No, I used to play when I was a kid. I
used to be addicted, bro. I used to be
addicted. But I haven't played it for
years, but my friend still plays it. My
friend in Amsterdam, I've actually met
him. He still plays it. But I don't I
ain't played it for like 12 years, bro.
I've never played Minecraft either.
>> That used to be the [ __ ] back in the
day, Runescape. But the thing is with
it, bro, like the the thing is with it,
I haven't met many people that can
relate because they never played it.
Obviously, there are people that play
it, but not people that I come across.
Does that make sense?
>> Yeah. What's What is it though? Is it a
battle based game or what is it?
>> How do explain it, Dusty? It's like [ __ ] you
It's like you you start off Yeah. and
you have to train your ski. You can't
explain it, bro. It's you'd have to
watch like tutorials of it. You can't
explain it. It's You can't explain it, bro.
>> Yeah. Yeah. This looks Well, this looks well confusing.
>> You can't explain it, Dusty. It's a game
that can't be Yeah, that's what I'm
saying. You can't explain it. And I
remember like I still remember certain
stuff to this day now, bro.
>> Oh, yeah. I had a [ __ ] I had a Game
Boy. Yeah. It was Silver and I flipped
it up and it had tribal in. You remember them? >> No.
>> Silver Game Boy?
Oh, I remember the game, boys. You know,
I remember the game, bro. I remember
Scooby-Doo. Do you remember the
Scooby-Doo game on it? Oh my god. >> Yeah.
>> No, I don't remember that though, bro.
But I remember I swear to God. I swear
to God about two weeks ago, I watched
Scooby-Doo. Scooby like the first movie
from like 2002 or whatever it was. I
love all them old films.
>> I used to love Scooby now, bro. The new
ones are [ __ ] Have you seen the new
Scooby? Have you seen what he looks like?
>> No. No. I've seen a trailer though. It
looks bare [ __ ] Well, Dusty, you you
used to play Rune Escape. And it's not
even just that as well. There's Crest.
You do Crest. You kill other people for stuff like
>> You could watch Scooby-Doo. Well, would
you watch Scooby-Doo movie in it? It's sick.
>> Uh, I watched it. Yeah. Yeah. The years
the one years and years and years ago.
Yeah, I watched it, bro. I used to love Scooby-Doo.
>> The one I watched the other week. They
go to that spooky island. It's got Mr.
Bean in it.
>> So, Dusty, you remember like you
remember V uh you remember um Faric, you
remember Grand Exchange? Do you remember
hand cannon? You remember void? Do you
remember having to get void when you got
killed, bro? When you get when you used
to get killed for void, you used to have
to spend three days back on the boat
getting it. Tell me I don't know about
Runescape, bro. I used to play all the time.
>> What the [ __ ]
>> What the [ __ ] you talking about? I don't
know what any of that means.
>> You You don't get it. This is what I'm
saying. You don't get it, bro. Cuz it's Runescape.
>> Oh, you're on about that Runescape thing.
>> Yeah, that's what I'm saying. Yeah,
there was a You got killed. You have to
go back to pest control.
>> I don't know this stuff, Dusty. Although
net is not I know everything, bro. Huh?
Rock crabs change. You know what I'm
saying? Yeah, I know everything, bro.
But it's a good and it's a name. It's a
game. It's a game. It's one of them
games um Fire Stick where you where it's
you can't complete it. Does that make sense?
>> Yeah. It just goes on and on.
>> It just goes on and on and on and on and on. So,
>> did you did you get proper addicted to it?
>> Yeah. I used to love it, bro. The quest
and everything. I used to love that
game, bro. killing people for Twilight,
bro. I used to love it.
>> Yeah. What? What did you play on? I
thought it was like a PC game.
>> PC. I used to play it on a computer. >> Yeah.
>> And then I moved to the private servers,
Dusty. I moved to the private servers.
You remember the private servers?
Private server is just like a sort like
a gimmick of it. It's like it's not
proper Runescape, but they try. They
make their own. There's no sense.
>> Nintendo SP. I think that's the [ __ ]
Game Boy. Yeah. Well, you used to play a
private server. Yeah, I used to play the
private servers, but do you remember do
you remember uh Feminic Trials? Do you
remember that? Uh do you remember that
quest, Dusty? Feminic Trials.
>> Yeah, it's on phone now, but it's not as
good on the phone, bro. You you'll get
killed that way. You need a PC or a
laptop. You'll get killed on the phone, bro.
>> Was you Trials, Dusty?
>> Was you good at it or was you crap?
>> No, I was good, bro.
>> Was your ask me any question like about
No, bro. Days of Treasure, Monkey Madness.
>> I a played it for 10 15 years, bro. 10
>> Why did you stop playing it?
>> They [ __ ] it up. They kept like doing
system update uh updates to the game and
they just [ __ ] it. And then they
brought back old school Runescape, but I
just never went back to it after that.
>> It died after like 2011. It become [ __ ]
>> They just [ __ ] it up with the updates.
They made it look like something completely different.
Does that make sense?
>> Yeah. Did you have a takeaway today, PG?
>> Yeah, I had a Chinese.
>> Did you get salt and pepper chicken?
>> No, I just got a curry, bro.
>> What? Chicken?
>> No. Beef
>> is any good? >> Yeah.
>> Nowhere near Nowhere near as good as the
Indian one. Are they?
>> No, it is quite nice to be honest, bro.
The ones I like about the Chinese is
they do beef. Indians don't do beef and
beef is quite like succulent. You know
what I mean? They don't do beef.
>> Well, it wasn't all chewy and horrible.
>> No, no, no, no, no, no. It's succulent,
bro. Always is when you get from the Chinese.
>> What rice did you get?
>> This plain r plain rice. Boiled rice. >> Yeah.
>> You know what I'm saying, bro? But yeah.
Um, yeah, I used to love San Andreas, bro.
>> Yeah, it was a sick game.
>> I used to like the WWE games. You
probably don't. You probably didn't, I guess. But
>> no, I used to love watching wrestling
when I was younger. Did you watch wrestling?
>> Yeah, bro. I went I went to see it two times.
>> I remember being really young and
[ __ ] staying up to watch like
Wrestlemania and that when he's on like
3 like 3 in the morning that it was
fools, but you had to pay more for the
You had to pay more. You had to pay
more. I used to have to beg my mother to
buy pay extra.
>> Well, you know, you know, it's funny you
used to say that. Yeah. You know when
you know when ver you know years ago
like 15 years ago Virgin Yeah. like you
know how much they used to charge for
the internet and the whole TV and
everything. Obviously for WWE you had to
pay a bit more. You're talking 18 to20
bro. Now you're you're paying over a
bill for you're paying you're paying
like at least 90 quid now.
>> You're paying mad money now bro. Mad money now.
>> Yeah. I used to like comedy central. I
used to like watching Two and a Half Men
>> on Comedy Central. I don't know if you
ever watched it, but I used to like watching it.
>> I've seen that. I've seen that Tom and half million.
>> So, but yeah, it just got really expensive, bro.
>> Who you with? Sky.
>> But they must not make much money
anymore, bro. They must make not much
money on the TVs because people are just
watching [ __ ] online, is it? So, I don't
think they're making money.
>> Um, I'm with Virgin, bro. Yeah, Virgin's good. Yeah,
>> their Wi-Fi is quite pretty decent, isn't it?
>> Yeah, it's good, bro. I had it back in
the old house. It was good. >> Yeah.
>> Yeah. Virgin's good, bro. Yeah. Um, and
you know, the thing is with Virgin, like
the area that I lived, Yeah. they never
ever done fiber optic, but they did with
the Virgin because Virgin uses a
different cable in it. You get me? >> Yeah.
>> You know, like Pluset and BT, they all
run off the same like it's like a
landline. So, if one doesn't offer it,
the other one doesn't offer it. But
Virgin Media somehow could. I don't know why.
>> Yeah. Get past a bullband, isn't it?
>> Have you ever been with BT?
>> Uh, no I ain't. The worst one I've been
with was Talk. That was [ __ ] [ __ ]
>> Oh, I remember Talk. [ __ ] hell. They
used to They used to charge like3 pound
something a month for the They used to
try Do you remember the adverts that
used to come on?
>> Yeah. Seven quid or something like it.
>> Yeah. And then there was Plus as well.
>> Yeah. No. Talk [ __ ] And they sent me out
>> years ago. years ago, you used to have
to wait months for broadband to be
installed. You used to have to wait absolutely months.
>> I can't remember. Was it ages?
>> Yeah, it was ages. Cuz I remember like
my mom never used to like she didn't
really have money to keep up with like
the payment. So, we'd go to another one
and bro, sometimes you'd have to wait
like 3 months and there was nothing you could do.
>> You have to use like a dongle like a
like a USB dongle, but sometimes it
would run out and you'd have to top it up.
>> Yeah, I remember they [ __ ] on they
>> because you can't Yeah, we had to in
>> I had one of them. I had one of them
from free. I used to put 20 pound on it.
>> Yeah. Yeah. That's the one I had. That's
all I had.
>> Yeah. Stick with a card in it in it. >> Mhm.
>> Yeah. Absolute [ __ ] I used to pay about
20 pound for the weekend. >> Yeah.
>> Why didn't you Why didn't you get
broadband? Was you waiting for it or something?
>> Uh yeah. I don't know. I can't remember.
It was years ago.
>> Like back in 2012. And it Yeah. You're
talking them times, bro. I bet you are.
>> Yeah. About 2010 11. I'm trying to think
what other games was good on the
PlayStation, bro. I liked Midnight. Oh,
bro. Do you remember you remember
PlayStation Home? That was sick, isn't it?
>> Yeah, PlayStation Home was Did you never
play [ __ ] uh any Tony Hawk
skateboarding games? They was all good. >> No,
>> I like them. Did you play FIFA?
>> Yeah, I used to [ __ ] smash
controllers when I lost. I used to hate
losing on that [ __ ] [ __ ]
>> Yeah, I'm still like that now. Do you uh
Do you remember FE Did you have a PSP?
Yeah, I had a PSP with the game
>> the best FIFA game was FIFA Street.
>> Yeah, I had it on PSP.
>> Yeah, I had it on PS2.
>> Did you have a PSP? I had a white one.
>> Yeah, I had one. Yeah. Yeah.
>> You get films as well, isn't it?
>> Uh-huh. They stopped doing them though. It
>> Yeah, I used to love that.
>> But you know PS, you know the PS3 when
it first come out? How much was it? I
swear it was like £700.
>> I don't know. I always Google stuff like that.
>> And it was and that was a lot of money.
He won't store a lot of money now, but
back then especially was a lot. But
£700, bro. That was Don't forget money
was worth more back in the day.
>> Google now on your phone how much was
PS3 when it come out. See what it says.
>> Yeah. Well, I'm sure it was about £700.
I'm sure it was.
>> But I could never I could never afford
it, bro. What I What I done Yeah, was I
collected like consoles. I sold all of
my consoles and just got a PS3 and I
just had it for like 3 years.
>> Yeah. How much you saying? 700. I don't
think it was that much, was it?
>> One second. Oh, look now. Um,
one second, bro. £425,
was it? I'm sure it was more than that.
Maybe. But even still, even even still, like
>> that was that was a lot of money, bro,
back in the day.
>> Yeah. Does it say when it come out? Um
200 Yeah. Uh March 21st, 2007.
>> [ __ ] hell. That's mad, is it?
>> Yeah. I remember when I remember when it
first come out as well. I remember when
I I used to like the look of the Xbox.
Oh, bro. I used to Oh, bro. I tell you
the best best games, bro. Lego Star Wars
on the Xbox 360. I love
>> Oh my god. So did I. I used to play Lego
Star Wars on the Lego Star Wars on the
360. And I used to play Mortal Kombat as
well. Mortal Kombat versus DC. So you
could be like Liu Kang versus Batman.
>> I remember, bro. Yeah. You know the Star
Wars video game, there was one after
that called The Complete Saga, but it
never come out on normal Xbox or
PlayStation. Um it was like 360 and and
I never had one cuz I couldn't afford it
and took away ages cuz they didn't do it. Huh. >> Yeah.
>> That Lego Star Wars game on 360. They
used to if you double tapped a do a flip in it.
>> Yeah. You you knowing it, bro. Bro, do
you remember that Do you remember the
video game? Yeah. when you used to fight
the enemies and it used to do that big
jump but you could never do it like
Darth Maul do remember but you could
never do the same jump as them I tried
and I couldn't
>> so frustrating leaping
>> they were leaping and that in it yeah
>> I used to love Lego Star Wars bro
>> what other Star Wars games was there
there was more than Lego Star Wars
>> there was one there was one I had before
bro and it wasn't Lego I forget and it
was like five in the back
>> the one I used to play on PS2 was it was
called Jang Django Fett or something Um, you
>> No, there was another There was another
Star Wars game I used to play. What was
it called now? One second. Star Wars
game. It wasn't Lego. One second.
I used to love I had all the lightsabers
and everything, bro.
>> Yeah, I did when I was a kid.
>> What was your favorite color? I like the
purple one and the red.
>> Purple one. That's Windows, isn't it?
>> It was called Oh, yeah. Episode Star
Wars episode 3 Revenge of the Sith. >> Yeah,
>> that's what they had.
>> Yeah, those were the get those were the days, bro.
>> They're going donkey's years then, isn't
it? Star Wars Donkeys years.
>> Life's so [ __ ] and boring now.
>> Yeah, it is.
>> Someone wants to join. Hold on. this.
>> Yo, what's up?
What's up, Bob? >> Hey.
Yeah, I just came to porn bomb you and
stuff. No, I'm just joking, dude.
>> Where you from, man?
>> I'm from America.
>> Yeah, I gathered. But like, where else? >> Ohio.
>> What? Cincinnati, huh?
>> Yeah. Yep.
>> I knew. Who's this? You know. >> Yeah.
>> So, how how the [ __ ] did you how did you find me?
>> I look up random streams to join. >> Oh,
I think I think I think you'll love this community.
>> He sounds like he'll fit right in.
>> Are you sure?
>> He sounds like he'll fit right in this
community, doesn't he?
>> Yeah. You'll fit in here, right? Lovely, bro. Yeah.
>> [ __ ] awesome, man.
>> Yeah, man. >> Cool. >> Huh?
>> Sure, I guess.
>> Fella, what's your name? I bet it's
Chad. I guarantee his name's Chad. Chad,
man. Hey, Chad. Chad from Ohio, man.
>> No, not Chad.
What's it begin with?
>> I don't know if I've ever met a guy
called Chad in Ohio.
I can tell by
>> I know I know one guy called Chad. He
lives in Canada.
>> Yeah, that's Canada.
>> I can tell by your voice. Yeah. That you
drink Monster and watch WWE. Don't tell
me you don't.
>> No, I'm drinking Monster right now.
>> No, I don't watch WWE.
>> How How old are you, man? >> 43.
>> Oh, nice, man.
>> 43. [ __ ] hell. Yeah.
>> How did you find this channel?
>> He said he said he just watch it. He
just looks up streams and that
>> I look up random streams. Yeah. >> Yeah.
>> Fire stick. Do you watch this guy on
YouTube called Simon Wilson? He does
some good content.
>> No, I've never heard of him. >> Really?
>> You have?
>> Have you ever heard of him, Chad?
>> I don't. No. It sounds familiar though, huh? >> Yeah.
>> I don't know who you're talking about,
but it sounds familiar, but I can't picture it,
>> dude. Hey, hey, uh, zombies, dude, do
you know who the Sidemen are?
>> The sidemen. >> Yeah.
>> Yeah. Just call him Chad.
>> You know who they are?
>> Okay. Have you ever heard of a guy called Baby? >> Yeah.
>> No, I never heard of him.
I come from that community and they're
English like you.
>> Oh yeah. Whereabouts?
>> I come from the Bibby.
>> I don't know. They're just from England
or something. I don't know. [ __ ] What's
it called? What's your Debbie? >> Bibby.
>> I've never heard of it. Have you PJ? >> Bibby.
>> Yeah. He's the English. Do you know Do
you know Do you know who Donald Trump is?
>> Yeah, dude.
I love Donald Trump. So, you better
watch out, dude.
>> I heard people in the south loved Donald
Trump. I heard this in America. Yeah.
All the people from the southern states love him.
>> Yeah, dude. I love Donald [ __ ] Trump.
They're Hell yeah.
>> I didn't know who he was until the other
day. I didn't even know who he was.
>> I'm MAGA.
I'm MAGA. I don't know. I heard your
guys's prince was arrested for Epstein stuff, though.
>> Yeah, he was. Oh man. Chad.
Yeah, we're going to call you Chad.
>> I say I said straight away I said I bet
he watches WWE and he drinks Monster and
he was drinking Monster. I knew it.
>> Oh, I used to drink, you know, the green
Monster like 10 years ago. But bro, they
don't work for keeping you awake. They
don't They never worked, bro.
>> I can drink I could drink four cans of
that and then go straight to sleep. I
guarantee I can.
>> Yeah. Now, the best monster that was
crazy I've ever had was it was like this
German monster. It said imported from
Germany and it was um um
Oh, whatever they do to like the beer.
It was fermented. Yeah.
>> And it said fermented monster from
Germany and they had to cancel it cuz it was like
messing people up.
>> Have you ever been Have you ever Have
you ever been to New York?
I I drove through there and it was a
[ __ ] It's horrible. It's [ __ ]
>> You know that's where you know you know
that's where Spider-Man comes from, right?
>> Yeah, that shit's [ __ ] I mean, New
York is is full of retards, dude. I I
drove through there and anybody I talk
to like they sound [ __ ] They got
this weird accent and they're [ __ ] dude.
>> Are you Have you been to uh California?
No, but that's full of retards, too. Yeah,
>> that's what's your what's your opinion
on American women, Chad?
>> Stuck up.
>> Well, half of them are [ __ ] ass ugly
and the other half are [ __ ] hot as
>> So, it's either ass ugly or hot.
>> They're stuck. They're stuck up though, zombies.
>> I don't know. Man, I they're either
[ __ ] like you get blonde [ __ ] holy
[ __ ] baddies or it's just like
purplehaired monster [ __ ]
>> What What do you think of What do you
think of the women from uh from Georgia?
Like specifically Georgia?
>> Oh, I don't know. Well, I'm Some of them
are hot. It's the same anywhere you go.
They're either hot or not.
>> I had Hey, Chad. I had one give me a
[ __ ] in the alleyway. That's kind of gross, huh?
>> Hey, hey, Chad. Chad, do you think like
American women Yeah. Do you think they
stuck up and treat like treat men like
and get away with anything they want to do?
>> Yeah, it's just most women for you really. But
>> yeah, I was just going to ask that,
Dusty. But you know a lot of the women
here. Hey Chad, you know a lot of the
women here. Yeah. You can see the
westernity in their eyes. >> Yeah.
>> Do you know what I mean? Like they have
this like dead look in their eyes.
That's what I You can see the minity in
their eyes. No, but seriously, you
laugh. Yeah, you laugh by a stick. But
you know exactly what I'm talking about.
Is it when you look at their eyes in it?
You can see
>> too much. European women can look
better, but I don't really know cuz
>> I don't see a lot of European women and stuff.
>> Chad. Chad. Chad, have you been smoking
weed? You sound hot.
>> No, you can call me Aaron if you want.
said to Chad.
>> Chad's better. Chad's better.
>> Yeah, Chad's better.
>> Yeah, Chad is better, bro.
>> Yeah, bro.
>> You're Chad. You're not [ __ ] zombie.
You're not Aaron. You're Chad. Chad
drinking monster, man.
>> Yeah, bro. >> Yes. >> [ __ ]
>> You're definitely
stoned, isn't he? >> Yeah.
>> O, Chad, have you ever been to Canada?
>> No. It sounds horrible, though. [ __ ] him.
>> You know what? Yeah. It it seems the you
know the thing is with that country,
bro, it just looks it just seems so
cold. It looks cold, bro.
>> So so cold and depressing.
>> Yeah. Well, it's
>> I don't know. It's not even that just
everybody there cuz they'll say like
Americans or hillbillies and then Brett.
It's like no, that's what they seem like they're projecting.
>> You know, the thing is by a sticker, you
know, when you go central London, you
never really meet a lot of Canadians.
You'll meet Americans and [ __ ] You'll
meet, but you don't really come across
many Canadians, you know?
>> Yeah. PJ PJ I ask Chad what he thinks on
the dating game in America.
>> What do you think of the dating game in
America? What do you think of the the
way it is?
>> Oh, I don't really date, but it sucks. Anyways,
>> why do you why do you not why do you not
why do you not date if you had like
women you had like women like just
ignore you and that?
>> It just feels weird, man. Like at
>> bum chick can be fun for a little bit,
but then it just it's embarrassing. It's
like It could be like hanging out with your
>> parents or something, dude. Like it
>> Well, you feel like when you're hanging
around with a with a bird, with a woman,
you feel like you're hanging around with
your parents. That's weird, man.
>> Well, are you are you gay?
>> No, at first like at first it might be
hot. Like, oh yeah, this hot dumb [ __ ]
But then after a while you're like, oh
no, [ __ ] this.
>> So, you'll sit there and you'll think,
oh, you're a hot [ __ ] And then next it
reminds you of your family. That's what
you would have said, isn't it?
Well, it's like being embarrassed. Like
if you were hanging out with your
family, that was being embarrassing. If
your family was embarrassing.
>> Well, you know what's scary about
America, Chad? It's so big, is it? Fire
stick. It's so big, bro. It looks scary.
So massive, it
>> bro. It looks and and and and a lot of
the states here, you have to drive
everywhere, bro. It's scary, isn't it?
>> It's It's definitely big and [ __ ] That
for sure. But I'm so I guess you just
get used to it. I'm guessing. But I
don't know how I don't know, bro. I
where I live.
>> How could they get How could they get
used to a country that that big, bro? I
don't feel I could in it.
>> H it just feels open and good and it it
you can get used. Do you know what I
mean though? But do you know what I
mean? Fire stick.
>> I couldn't get used to a country that
big that's just way too big. It's ridiculous.
>> But the thing though, but the thing is
sticking out. It's not like, you know,
like New York, here you can get trains
and stuff and whatever, bro. So you
wouldn't seem as bad. But I mean, like,
say you was in Georgia or like somewhere
like Georgia or Tennessee, bro. [ __ ]
It's weird, isn't it? >> Yeah.
>> Cuz I go to Tennessee every now and then.
>> And um
>> Yeah. And it's definitely like a if I go
to my if I go to the local town, like if
I want to go to Walmart, it's an hour
drive for me to go to Walmart.
>> But like an hour drive for you, you
could like probably,
>> you know, drive halfway across your
country or something. I mean, I don't
know. Yeah. If we if we if we get a
train if we get a train, bro, just how
[ __ ] up it is. Yeah. If we get a train
fire sticker like 5 hours away, we're in
Scotland. In California, if they're
drive in California and Texas, if
they're driving four or five hours,
they're still in the same state, bro.
>> I was just gonna say that
>> they're still in the same state, bro.
It's mad, is it?
>> Like you just said, if me and you, if me
and you left like Houston now, we'd be
in Scotland in 5 hours. Literally, like,
you're 100% right. He'd like you, Chad,
tell him, Chad, man, tell him, man.
>> But here's the thing, though. But here's
the thing. Here's the thing. So, like,
what is the biggest state? It's either
Texas or California, is it?
Well, it's Alaska, but that's not really
any where anybody goes because that's like above.
>> What's the second? What's the second
Texas, isn't it? It's Texas.
>> It's like Yeah. Texas. California is
really long. So, if you was to drive
like the length of California, it's
literally like driving four states.
>> Yeah. Literally. Fire sticker. You're
So, say you're in Los Angeles.
>> It's huge. Like California is almost
like it own [ __ ] country big time. If
you're listening in Los Angeles, if
you're the money that is there,
>> listen, if you're in Los Angeles and you
drive the whole country, dude,
>> tons of [ __ ] money.
>> No, no, no. Listen. If you drive,
listen. If you're in Los Angeles, right,
and you drive 4 hours, you're in San
Diego in the same state. You're just in
a different city.
>> You know what I mean, bro?
>> Yeah, that's [ __ ] long, is it? You
know what? I'd be scared to go like
[ __ ] Detroit, bro. You get shot in
it. They'll just shoot you in it.
>> Yeah, definitely.
>> You got to get a gun and shoot back here
in America. But I mean, you got to know
how to do that.
>> Why do you know who Do you know who's
from? Do you know who's from Detroit?
>> No, I don't. I've never been there, but
I'd probably get trouble cuz I'd [ __ ]
take out I'd want to [ __ ] people. I
don't I don't know. That's just bro.
>> Wait, Chad, what's the time where you
>> No, no, but you know the thing Fire
Stick, the good thing about the thing in
America, bro, they've got all different
kinds of popcorn and that salted in a
packet. Like they they've got so many
varieties. Like we only have You don't
have anything compared to
>> We just have We have like car We have
caramel salted. That's it.
>> Yeah. And we have butter, but it's all
microwave. Like I'd love to have butter
in like a in a packet or in a cinema.
They don't do it, bro. You get me? Yeah.
Chad, what's the time where you are?
>> It's 7 around 700 p.m. at 6.
>> You're six. You're six hours behind.
You're 6 hours behind us, isn't it? >> Yeah.
>> Cuz I've got friends in the UK.
Actually, in America, everybody I meet,
dude, they're [ __ ] [ __ ] and all
pedtoy or nonsas or whatever,
>> dude. Bad.
>> You know when you you know when you've
been like Cypress and that Yeah. Yeah.
>> You know, like when you've been to Cypus
and other countries, I bet the only
thing you don't like here was getting
used to the food and that in it.
>> Oh, yeah. I get I get scared.
>> When I went to Amsterdam, bro, you
couldn't I couldn't find a curry house
to save my life, bro.
>> Yeah. I just drink bold water normally.
>> Oh, I went to a
>> there's a curry place in my town and I
went there and I've never ate that in my
life and it in the middle of the night I
woke up with diarrhea. Like, what the [ __ ]
You had diarrhea.
>> You're crazy. You're crazy, man.
>> Wait, how bad Chad, how bad was the
diarrhea? Did you have stomach pains?
>> No, it was about medium, but it still happened.
>> It was about medium. I probably had worse.
>> I watch Chad, you know, I watch, Chad, I
watch a lot of, you know, like these uh
body cams of police in America where
they stop people like police knew they hide them.
>> I'm sub to all of them. I'm sub to all
of them. Are you? Yeah.
>> I see people I watched one the other
day. The geyser gets pulled over on the
highway. The literally the minute the
cop goes over to the car, he just shoots
him in the head with a shotgun and drives off.
>> Bad. Yeah, it's bad. It's bad.
>> Oh, yeah. Chad, did you What did you
say? Everyone you've been speaking to on
YouTube, a lot of them are weirdos and
ped and pedophiles.
>> Dude, everybody in America may as well
be a [ __ ] pedophile as far as I give
a [ __ ] dude. Seriously.
Chad, if I Chad, Chad, if I went if I
went to where you live, Yeah. would you
class that as me going abroad or that?
>> I don't know.
>> Like, would you would you would you say
it's going abroad or not?
>> I mean, it'd be a little different, but
it wouldn't be that bad.
>> Like, they try to make sound scarier
than it is. It's not that bad. But I mean,
>> you know, Chad, Chad, answer the
question. If he if he flew from from
London, UK to where you are
>> abroad, but I mean, America is different
cuz we are Americans. It depends on
where you went.
>> I mean, Fire Stick, would you class that as abroad? >> Yeah,
it definitely is, isn't it? Yeah.
>> Well, you could go to uh China or
something, you know, like
>> what would you Hey, fire sticker.
Listen, bro. Yeah. Say you say you was
say you had like money like loads and
loads and loads of money and you was
going to go America. Would you go for a
week or would you just go for like 3
months and just [ __ ] around everywhere?
>> I'd go for 3 months.
>> Just go every like most not all the
states but like most like you get me in
it like most of main places in it.
>> If you if you went if you went for a
week and then you wanted to visit places
you only you're only going to get to the
next state. And and the thing is, bro,
the thing is Yeah. Do you know the thing
is um Fire Sticker like the thing um
you'd be so [ __ ] with when you got
back though, like jet lag and tie. You'd be [ __ ]
>> Yeah. Yeah, you would. Yeah, you would.
>> You could go like two weeks in the East
Coast. Yeah. Do all the East Coast. Then
the next time you go do like the mid and
then do the West, you could do something like that.
>> Chad. Chad, have you got a massive fear
of flying, Chad?
>> Yeah. Yeah. No, I under certain
circumstances like I if I fly I want a
parachute. Like I have to I would have
but as long as I got a parachute I'd be
like I don't give a [ __ ]
>> Yeah. Have you been on Have you been on
a plane? Have you been on a plane before?
>> No, actually no. I've never been on a
plane but I've been on a helicopter for
like 15 minutes and then
um when I got off the next person that
got on the helicopter they died. They
they they died, dude.
>> [ __ ] hell.
>> So I was like,
>> you know how [ __ ] up this is? Fire
stick. Yeah. Like five stick. Do you
know how [ __ ] up this is? Yeah. From
New York to California on a plane is us
to Egypt. Yeah. It is bad, bro.
>> That's ridiculous, bro. >> Yeah.
>> But think about Egypt. Yeah. Egypt 5
hours away. New New York to California
on a plane is 5 hours. Imagine that. 5 hours, bro.
>> What? So, Chad, if you was on a plane
with a parachute, it' put your mind at rest. Yeah.
>> A little bit. Cuz I do know if like the
plane spiraled in the heavy genie force
like you're [ __ ] anyways. Like you
>> fireick fire stick. You just like your
feet on the ground, isn't it? >> Yeah.
>> You like your feet on the ground.
Or at least on a boat you could like you
got life boats or some [ __ ]
>> Bro, my dad big enough.
>> Dude, I heard some stories where these
people were on a train.
>> My dad My dad died at 55. He never went
on a plane, bro. Some people don't.
>> Well, Chad,
>> I want to fly a plane. If I could fly
the plane myself, I'd be all good to go.
Chad, when uh Chad, are you going to
play the new GTA when it comes out? Yes or no?
>> Yeah, it says it's supposed to come out
what, in 9 months or something?
>> It says it's coming out in November. Is it now?
>> 6 months. Yeah,
dude. I I could even barely play the
last GTA. Like,
>> what do you What do you do? What do you
do if you're falling in love with
someone, you can't get over them and
they ghosted you?
>> I'd [ __ ] murder them. Oh, sorry. Never mind.
No, seriously. What do you do?
>> If I can't have them, no one else will.
>> No, seriously. Yeah, that's what I used
to think, but that's Chad.
>> Yeah, I don't think that's the right way
to think. Sorry.
>> Chad. Chad, what what curry did you get
when you when it when it gives you food
poisoning? What did you have? Did you
have a chicken masala?
>> Yeah, that's what it was. What the
stupid garlic bread [ __ ]
>> Yeah. Hey, have you ever Have you ever tasted alligator?
>> I don't know.
>> Yeah, he's stone, bro. >> Yeah.
>> Oh, do you know what brand I like here?
It's Fire Stick, man. Lacrosse. But it's
so expensive, isn't it? >> What?
>> Lacros, bro. Lacost.
>> Yeah. I like I like just plain lacros
with just a little logo.
Expensive though, ain't it? It's expensive though.
>> Yeah, it's world deer. Is it? You know
what country it comes from?
>> No, I don't. >> France.
>> Does it? >> Mhm.
>> Is O Chad in America? Yeah. Is it
expensive for Stone Island jumpers?
>> Stone Island jumpers? I don't know what
the [ __ ] that is,
>> but you're stone it. What the
>> He's so stone, man. >> Yeah,
>> he's eating Cheetos. I can hear him.
>> Fire stick. Would you go to Hey, Fire
Stick, would you go to Wisconsin?
>> No. [ __ ] that. >> Why?
>> There's nothing appeals there to me.
>> You know where it is, isn't it?
>> Yeah, of course. But I just wouldn't go there.
>> What about Mryland?
>> No. Would you?
>> No. That's where Michael Jackson had
like the affair and that
>> uh was it was called [ __ ] Neverland,
isn't it? Not not Maryland. Neverland.
>> Would you have gone there?
You You used to listen to You used to
listen to Elvis Presley, in it.
What the [ __ ]
He's a He's a N isn't it?
>> Yeah, proper.
>> That's what N's like.
>> Chad. Chad, do you listen to Michael Jackson,
Annie? It's okay.
>> Oh, this guy's on [ __ ] something, isn't it?
>> Yeah, he's on. He's out of his knot.
>> You You used to like Michael Jackson, is it?
>> No. No,
>> I think he was right. I thought I
thought I think he was all right, bro. I
I didn't mind, bro.
>> Well, you know who used to be thick sick
fire stick? Aon, bro. He used to be
sick, bro. I used
>> back in 2009. Back in 2009, did it, bro? Yeah. Yeah. >> Yeah.
>> Him and Snoop Dogg and Eminem, bro. That
was those were the days, bro. That's
when that was like the peak of music,
you know. 2008, 2009. You want to smack
that? Smack that all on the floor. Smack that.
>> They don't they don't a paj Punjabi
version as well. Did you ever listen to it? >> No.
>> Yeah, they don't a Punjabi version, bro.
>> Wait, ask Chad if he knows about Runescape.
>> You know about Runescape?
>> Runescape? Like the game?
>> Yeah, bro.
>> I've heard of it. I've never played it.
I thought about playing it cuz they said
it still existed and I'm like, dude,
that'd be weird to play an old ass game or something.
>> I I've never played. It sounds kind of
cool, I guess. Like, cuz it's old.
>> Oh, Chad, do you know Chad Chad, do you
know who Eminem is?
>> Yeah, the dude sucks. [ __ ] him, man.
>> He's just like Chad,
>> oh my god,
>> he just said like they act like they
know. They don't [ __ ] know.
>> Hey, Chad, like me and PJ. Yeah. When we
when we've got like rubbish, we say
we're going to take the rubbish out and
put it in the bin. Do you say trash?
>> I'm going to take out the trash, man.
>> Yeah, that's how you say it.
>> I'm going to take out the trash. You
remember they used to call Eminem Taylor
Park trash. Remember? You ever watch?
>> Yeah, of course. >> Everybody
put your mother hands up and follow me.
>> So, what you're what you're saying, Fire
Stick, is people from America or
foreigners ass. Is that what you're saying? >> Yeah.
>> Hold on. Let me take out my rubbish. >> Yeah.
>> I can't do that. Sorry.
>> They're bonus. That's weird, isn't it?
>> Yeah. Seriously, Chad, do you say like
trash and fries and candy?
>> I have to take out the trash.
>> Yeah, dude. No, we do say trash or garbage.
>> You sound like You sound like you've
perked up a bit now, isn't it? And they
call crisps. They're called crisp chips.
>> Yeah. That's so annoying, isn't it?
>> Yeah. Yeah. Now when they say that I
think of a portion of chips in it
by fire stick, do you know about uh
Oxford Oxford Uni?
>> Yeah, of course.
>> I met a couple of guys in Liverpool
Street that went there, but bro, they
were too stuck up and snobby. They were
unbearable, bro. Like you can't even you
can't get I can't be around them people.
Even the way they talk and that just
makes you want to punch them in the head.
>> Well, you've you've come across people
that's gone to that unit. I haven't. I
haven't, but I've seen them on videos
and they're just snobby horrible [ __ ]
>> They think they're too They think
they're smarter than they are in it.
>> Yeah. And they try and make you feel like [ __ ]
>> Yeah. You know, ain't it, bro? You know.
Yeah. Yeah. Liverpool Street, this guy
um he went they try and make you feel
low and uncomfortable. That's why I hate them. >> Yeah.
>> Knobby [ __ ] bro. Snobby [ __ ] Just
cuz they got rich parents, isn't it?
>> How old is Chad?
>> How old are you, Chad?
I thought I told you. I said 43.
>> Oh, we are 43.
>> Are you single?
>> What? What? What? What month was you born?
>> In July.
>> Oh, nice, man. I was born October. So, I
assume you're cancer. >> Yeah.
>> Your can your cancer star sign? Yeah. >> Yeah.
>> July is a good month, bro. It's hot, isn't it? >> Yeah.
What did you when when was that you had
food poisoning from the Indian restaurant?
>> Oh, a couple weeks ago. Like I cuz I was
like I couldn't figure out I wanted to
try something new. I'm like I want to
try something new. I'm tired of all this
stuff I'm eating and I thought
Fire Stick. Have you ever had strep throat? >> Yeah.
>> It's like swallowing knives. It's like
that's that's bad.
>> Like swallowing razor blades. I've never
had it. It's meant to be really painful.
It was paid. I had it once about eight
years ago, bro. All I could eat was a
chili concardi, bro.
>> And it took me It took me like 40
minutes. Took me like 40 minutes to eat it.
>> I heard it a couple times. It was funny.
I went to the doctor and the doctor
looked at my throat and he instantly was
like, "Oh, yeah. You're [ __ ] up."
>> Well, Chad, who do who do you live with?
>> Oh, I live by myself. So, if I come to
America, could I stay with you?
>> I don't know. I've thought about it. I'm
like half tempted to let people stay
here, but then I realize I'm like, "Oh,
man. Probably probably shouldn't."
>> I promise you. I I'll get I'll get the plane over.
>> Wait, Chad. Chad, you love steaks, isn't
it? You like love a steak.
>> Well, yeah. I got some steaks. I got
Yeah, Chad's a good guy, man.
>> Yes, Chad. I'll show you your steak.
It's little, but I got a steak.
>> Yeah, look how stoned you look. Look,
>> you're stoned, bro. Where's your Where's your beard?
>> Oh, I trim it off with these Crayola
scissors. This is how I shave. I just
sit here and I go like this. I'm like
>> bless you then if you go like that.
>> Chad Chad show some Chad show some steaks please. >> Okay.
>> My phone's done. But I can I can
probably go in and show the stakes.
>> Yeah. Then do a fridge tour. Fridge car. Dude
with the other
fire stick. Yeah. Would you you'd shag
Natalie in it? >> No.
>> Well, at all.
>> No, I wouldn't I wouldn't personally,
but didn't you said you rejected her or
something before Monty was with her?
>> Yeah, she tried meeting me like when I
was 22, like years ago, and I said like,
"No, bro." Cuz I thought that age was
weird and I don't really like her. Look, >> [ __ ]
>> I'm not going to lie, bro. If I had like
50 Guinnesses and she just randomly
offered me a [ __ ] that's probably
all I'd get. I'd probably without her. Yeah.
>> Chad, why? Chad, why does it take you so
long to get to the fridge? [ __ ] how big is
>> Why would you Why would you Why would
you get with Why would you get with her?
>> It's not my type. >> No.
>> How Chad? Why did it take you so long to
get there? How long How big is your apartment?
>> Big store.
>> You got bare [ __ ] You got bare. You got loads.
>> I want to come and see you, Chad.
>> Chad, have you got any soda?
>> Uh, right. That's it. right here. >> Yeah.
>> I want to come and see I want to come
and see you, Chad.
>> Where's the stakes?
>> Oh, in here in the freezer there.
>> Nice, Chad.
sirloin. Yeah, sirloin steak. Yeah, that's nice.
>> Yeah, lovely. Sun.
>> But maybe maybe I can come. Hey, Chad.
Maybe I can come. Chad, maybe I can come
and you can cook for me. >> Yeah,
>> Chad. What do you think?
>> He will come, Chad. Trust me, he will come.
>> I will come. And I smoke ribs, too.
>> I like to smoke ribs.
>> I PJ, I bet you can't cook ribs in it.
I've never tried to be fair.
>> No, neither have I.
>> What ri What ribs do you like? I like
the Chinese the spare barbecue ones.
They're lush, bro. Oh,
>> how much did you pay for them, Chad?
$14. 14 bucks.
>> It was bar free.
>> O, you know, oi Chad, you know Homer Simpson. Yeah. >> Yeah.
>> I never see him ever when I go out. Why?
Why is that?
You go out,
>> Chad. I never ever see Homer Simpson
when I go out. Is that weird?
>> What do you mean, bro?
>> Like, you know Homer Simpson?
>> Yeah, of course I do. But why would you
What do you mean see him? What? Like,
what do you mean by see him?
>> Like, I never see him on the street.
>> You ain't going to, are you? He's not
real. What do you mean?
>> Well, I see him on TV, but I see him on
TV, isn't it?
>> It's a cartoon.
No, I see I see the Simpsons on TV, but
I never see them in real life. Wave,
>> Chad. Chad, why did you say like most
people Why did you say most people that
are streaming in America are like pedos? Pedoph,
dude. It's like everybody's in on the
Epstein [ __ ] dude.
Everybody, they might be afraid or
they're in owner. Like
>> someone said in the chat that he knows
someone said in the chat that Chad knows Rick Berry.
>> I've heard of that.
>> Yeah. O you know what my favorite
fridges are saying that. Yeah. Fire
Stick and Dusty. I like them Double Dawn
American ones. You know them ones. I've never
>> Yeah, one.
>> That's the AIDS infected gay [ __ ]
Who? Rick Barry.
>> Yeah, dude. What the [ __ ]
>> Do you actually Do you actually know him? >> No,
that's the AIDS infected [ __ ] Dude,
what the [ __ ]
>> Yeah, he's got AIDS. Is he? Oh, PJ. Is
he actually got AIDS?
>> I don't know, bro. >> Yeah,
>> I've never I don't I've seen him on
there. Apparently, he's Apparently, he's
a pedophile. Gay and a gay pedo. Yeah,
dude. What the [ __ ]
What the hell is that?
Chad Chad, have you been out today?
>> Yeah, I had to get my battery replaced and >> [ __ ]
>> I bet Chad, I bet I bet you drive a full
truck in it.
>> I I'm need to get a truck. I wanted a
truck, but they're like hard to get cuz
everybody wants a [ __ ] truck. And I
had a truck and I'm like, I don't want I
don't like it. And it ran perfect. So I
sold it. I'm like, [ __ ] this truck. >> Yeah.
>> I drive.
>> Bless bless you in life, Chad. Bless you in life.
>> I want a truck.
>> [ __ ] truck.
>> What? Wait, Chad. What console have you
got? Are you Xbox or PlayStation?
>> No, I had to get rid of them a while
ago. I'm so I'm PC.
Do you play zombies?
>> Yes, I'm bullied.
>> What What What religion are you?
>> Okay. I'm a Christian.
>> Oh, I'm Muslim.
>> [ __ ] Ramadan. No, I'm just saying.
>> The [ __ ] are you, [ __ ]
>> No, I'm Muslim.
>> No, I apologize. Sorry. No,
>> that's all right, man.
He's Well, you're racist.
fight. Hey, hey, fight. I'm actually a Muslim. Yeah.
>> No, you're not.
>> I am, bro.
>> No, you're not. That's why you're laughing.
>> How How am I laughing?
>> Well, if you was your Muslim. Yeah. I've
never I've never seen All the years I've
known you, I've never seen you go mosque.
>> Yeah. I don't go mosque, but I pray in
like the house.
>> What have you got a prayer mat? >> No.
>> I just use a towel in it. >> Yeah.
>> Okay. So when they're fast and someone
said you could eat breakfast and then dinner.
>> I like bacon sandwiches.
>> That's like Okay. All right. Let me get started.
>> No. When they're fasting, when they're
fasting, they can't eat until I think
it's sunset or some [ __ ] like that.
>> You know, when I used to cook here in
front of the tenants when I used to rent
the house. Yeah. I used to cook pork
chops. You should have saw that. Their
face would look disgusted. They hate
pork in it.
>> Yeah. But there's nothing that wrong
with P, bro. Like the way I see it,
yeah, obviously I know the story behind
it. What it is with them is they try to
say that like pigs eat [ __ ] and stuff,
but like bro, at the end of the day, if
you're eating an animal, you're eating a
[ __ ] animal, bro. And it like say
pigs eat [ __ ] Look, look at him. Look
smoking up fat joint.
>> No, dude. I have
like the secret to why they can't eat it.
>> Have you ever had a fire stick? Have you
ever had like pork?
>> There's a secret.
>> Yeah, of course I have. The reason
Muslims, you know, when you cook them
slowly, like when you Bro, they're nice,
isn't it? They're nice.
>> Yeah. The The reason Muslims don't eat
pork is cuz they say the pigs don't have
sweat glands and they roll around in
their own [ __ ] and that. >> Yeah.
>> Yeah. Well, that's part of it. But no,
>> what do you think?
What do you think of What do you think,
Nola? But do you know the thing I don't
agree with Muslim is the circumcision is
child abuse. Unless there's a medical
reason, bro, why are you chopping skin
off your [ __ ] child's dick?
>> Yeah. It's terrible. Well, that's the
thing I don't agree with.
>> Do that, too. I don't know. A lot of
Americans do that.
>> No, obviously, you know, like girl, you
know, baby girls, yeah, you know, when
people have like a baby girl that they
get their ears pierced like from But
that's different, bro. That's There's a
difference between getting your [ __ ]
ear pierced, bro, and getting [ __ ]
skin took off your your dick. You get me?
>> Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
>> Well, that's basically what they do in
America with the chemicals and everything where
>> they do it in America. They do it.
Jewish people do it as well. Fire stick.
You know, Jewish people, there's a lot
of Jewish people in America. I'm sure
they circumcise as well. >> Yeah.
>> And so they get
>> child abuse.
>> Like a plastic bottle
is made of hormones.
>> To be fair, to be fair, fire stick.
Yeah. I I I do agree with the hygiene
reason, bro. Because like say you know
that sometimes when you don't shower for
a day or day and a half, sometimes you
get lazy, bro. Your dick your dick
starts smelling the cheese, isn't it?
>> Um no, I don't I've never had that
personally. I wash before it gets to
that stage. Yeah, but yeah, but I wash I
wash I shower every day. But I'm saying
Yeah. Like say you don't shower for like
a day and a half or whatever. Like you
you know what I mean?
>> Bro, if you're you said the other day
that your dick burns. Yeah. Now you're
saying you get cheese dick. Yeah, bro.
You need to get tested, bro.
>> Yeah, I've already been tested, isn't it?
>> No, you ain't, bro. That's why you're laughing.
>> I've been tested, bro. I did. I'm not
scared of needle. I've been tested, bro.
>> Yeah, but did you have a full STD blood?
They take your blood? Yeah. What do you
think? I've got AIDS. No.
You know what I'm saying?
>> Do they have like medicine for AIDS and stuff?
>> Uh to manage it. Yeah. There's no cure though.
>> Yeah. Just to manage it.
>> I swear that Charlie in in Two and a
Half Men got aids in it. I hate Tabby.
>> I'm not sure.
>> Yeah, he did. I know. He Yeah, he did.
>> Look how much smoke. Chad, what are you smoking?
Oh, you smoking a smoking a [ __ ] sig.
I thought you were smoking a joint.
>> Smoking a pig.
>> Are you getting Are you getting a
takeaway tomorrow? Fire stick or you
just want to cook?
>> I don't know. I might just cook
tomorrow. I might make a chili. You made
me want chili now.
>> Oh, more like a chili conne. >> Yeah.
I might get one as well with jalap.
Yeah, I might get one, bro. They're
nice. I love me.
>> Put jalapino and loads of hot chili
powder in it. Yeah. You know, bro.
>> Chad. Chad, do you ever make chili?
>> Yeah, I made some the other day. It was really
>> Let's meet on Saturday. Fire stick.
>> Chad, how um how hot do you have your
How hot do you have your chili, Chad?
>> U I I only like it like medium or or
mild. I like a little hot, just not a lot. Like
It's just like more mild. Yeah. But a
little bit of heat, but not a lot. I
don't know. Like the peppers. Like I
don't mind if it's got a lot of cayenne
and but it's like a certain amount. Like
you're balancing it and like you want it
there and you don't want it over hot. I
don't know why. >> Yeah.
>> I don't mind hot chili when I have it as
long as it's not too bad. But no
kind of still got space.
>> What's What's the What's the nearest
state from you? >> Tennessee.
>> Ah, that's why you have you have you
ever been to Alaska? I've got a No, not
Alaska. Sorry. Um Oklahoma. No,
>> I think I've been to Iowa.
Oklahoma. Yeah, I got I got a friend
that lives in um
I got a friend that lives in um Oklahoma.
>> You've been to Texas, isn't it?
>> No, I've never been to Texas.
Dude, what are you doing tomorrow, Chad?
>> Oh, [ __ ] What am I doing?
Oh [ __ ] I guess being [ __ ] [ __ ] >> Huh?
>> Damn. I don't know. [ __ ]
>> I am going to bed. Yeah, man.