Oh, still going on about me. You [ __ ] obsessed weirdos.
Peter belly on the mind. Peter belly on
[ __ ] hell. Give it a rest, man. Come
out the closet already.
Come out the closet already.
[ __ ] chronicle scenes.
Chronicle chronicle scenes at this
point, you lad.
[ __ ] every 20 comments was about me.
Leave me alone. I don't swing that way.
You gay bastard. Talking about men on
YouTube all day.
Yet you don't have a woman yourself.
You've never been on a date yourself.
Cuz most of the people in this
community, let's face it, are [ __ ] virgins
trying to criticize people. But they're
in a worse position than you. I love it,
bro. I love it.
They're in a worse position than you in
life with everything that they talk
about. And then they try to talk about
you. Yeah. Only on this disabled
community. That's 1 2 3 4 5 6 7 8 9 10.
Yeah, that's almost 20 comments solid
straight about Peter Belly. Come out the
closet already. Do the world of good.
Yep. They'll do the world of good coming
out the closet, lad.
You definitely need to come out the
closet. It's [ __ ] gay, bro. They're
they're proper proper gay on here.
Jealousy. But then I just remember, bro,
like I don't they don't annoy me
anyways. It's just jealousy mixed with a
bit of gayness. I went on Lord J's bro.
I just come out the shower. Yeah.
[ __ ] I went a law J. 20 comments are
about me in a row. They're gay, bro.
They're just They're just gay in it.
They're just They're just gay and
jealous, isn't it, lad? Oh, you cooking
nice, man. I'm going to get a curry in a bit.
Yeah, they're gay, bro. They're gay and
jealous, bro. 100%, lad. Someone's
telling me how they've just been to the
hospital and they're because someone so
that their woman's given birth and then
they're on YouTube talking about me.
They're [ __ ] gay, bro. They are
actual gay. Like, that's not even me
being triggered. They are actually gay.
And they're talking about me with women
and stuff, bro. I've had more women than
everyone on this community.
Like you're you're in a worse you're in
a worse position than anyone that you're
trying to talk about.
That's what that's what I'm saying. Like
the people on here are in a worse
position. No women, worst looks, no
money. They're worse than you.
They are literally worse than you, bro.
These gay people.
They are proper proper obsessed.
No. No. But they are proper proper
obsessed. You can never have me coming
on here talking about men every day.
Anyways, moving on.
Yeah, they are gay, Joker. Yeah, we know
they're gay. Proper gay.
Yeah, bro. I did do it, but then I deleted it.
Yeah, I'm going to do it now. Actually,
I'm going to do it again, lad. One
second. I'll come back live. I actually
did do one and I deleted it.
One second. Yeah. Two sets, lad.
Sorry about that, lad. Yeah, I was going
to do a video, but I can't be bothered.
But yeah, they're just they're just obsessed, lad.
Every comment was about me. Yeah,
they're definitely definitely gay. And
then they say that we and they say that
we react to them.
Oh, do you want to know what I commented
on on Timmy's channel, Cory?
Um, someone said on Tim's channel, Tim
mate, I've told you he's a filthy creep.
You have to nail him one right hand
straight down the pipe. He's a creep. I
showed a female friend. She was
gobsmacked. Said he's dangerous, should
not be around the women. I said, "Ew, a
s." Um, then he um ignored my comment.
And then I wrote back to him saying,
"Women aren't innocent, lad. They are
just as bad as men, if not worse. Simps
and white knights like you defending
them is crazy to me." Laughing emoji.
What a simp white knight.
[ __ ] simp. White nights. So many so
many white knights, bro. Embarrassing.
They generally think that
they generally think that that these
women are going to sleep with them if
they defend them. They're delusional, lady.
They're delusional. They actually they
think that defending women is going to
make women like them.
And it never has and it never will.
It's so [ __ ] pathetic, bro.
And it's like, think about it, bro. Look
at Launch Legs. He defends women. He's
He's still a [ __ ] virgin with a
disabled girl that can't consent to sex.
I've been with my women. Joseph Ferrar
is chronically single, even though he
pretends he's got a misses. He doesn't
have no MS, lad. He spent the past hour
typing about me on YouTube. He's
obsessed. Think about it. Like, sing don't work.
Women don't like simps. Why do they do it?
Maybe I'll do a video about this, bro,
and start a a podcast like we were
saying. I want to I want to understand I
actually generally want to understand
why they do it. Glory. I'd love to know,
bro. I don't so I don't have to wonder anymore.
Look at Nlegs. He's a [ __ ] virgin.
Never been with any normal woman ever.
Women don't like him. Um he Alton Alton
Rose he simps over Alton Rose and if
Alton Rose had to pick between me and
the Virgin she'd pick me and I said that
she's an ugly fat [ __ ] but she'd pick
me over him
and someone else and you know and other
people as well. You know what I'm
saying? Like they don't like simps
defending them. It's gay as [ __ ] It's
beta male behavior.
Get it in your thick [ __ ] brain.
Kill it in your [ __ ] brain sand.
They're not going to let you hit it.
They're not going to [ __ ] you.
You get me? Yeah.
Defending women, bro.
Got to be a disease. It's got to be autism.
Defending women, but women don't like them.
Yeah, maybe someone will explain to me
one day that baby cakes.
Tell Jose if to come on camera. Tell
Joseph Warren show he's misses.
He ain't got a misses. He's just a
lonely closeted gay.
Another one that hates the fact that they're gay.
[ __ ] gay lords on it, lad.
It's a disabled community, Cory. That's
what the community is. It's a disabled community.
Oh, you don't know the community. You don't know.
Oh, well, it's a disabled community basically.
I just don't understand why they white.
I don't understand why they do it.
And they all seem to be virgins that do
it. Like nonss and other people. I I
just don't know why they do it.
I don't know why why they do it, lad.
Yeah. It's a disabled community.
Cory, I paid for uh Timmy's Uber the
other day and he wouldn't get in the
taxi. Did you see it? He wouldn't get in
it. He literally wouldn't get in the taxi.
Of course he does. Everyone knows what
white lighting is.
What do you think about these white knights,
Mr. Bean? I don't know why they do it.
>> Yeah, but they're never going to get
laid. Women are never going to get with them.
They want to get laid, but they don't
get laid. They try to defend women, but
women don't like them. Same with Nonlegs.
How many times has he defended women and
he's still a virgin?
And no one's and no one's gravitated
towards him, man.
Think about it. The kid's a virgin. The
And he's [ __ ] he defends women, but
women don't like him.
Do I think he's a virgin? No, I don't.
I don't really think he's a virgin. Nah, not really.
I don't think he is. No,
cuz I know he is.
I don't think he is. I know he is. Yeah.
Yeah. They're proper they're proper gay
on this community though, bro.
They're proper gay on this community, bro.
Nope. Well, yeah, I am going out
tomorrow. I'm going to the cinema.
Yeah, I'm going to the cinema tomorrow.
Yeah, I was about to say no. I'm
thinking on Yeah, I am. Oh yeah. Yeah.
Maybe 30 odd pound.
Yeah, 30 odd pound. I like
I like showy. Um,
I don't have I don't have tango ice
blast. I've not had that in years.
I'm going to go for the spindle soon. Greavves.
Oh, I've just got a notification from
Fruit Mad World Grezy.
for a roulette video.
>> He's g Timmy's gambling again.
Well, watching this guy just hurts my
brain. Uh, Mr. B, do you remember when
he said that's a nice bit of money on
the table when he's playing the roulette
on the machine? He said not the best not
the best number on the table.
He's a [ __ ] [ __ ] right there.
No, no. I will be going out in a minute
though. I need to get some food, bro.
Oh, look. He done a video of a big arch.
Timmy done a big arch video. Grieves.
I'm going to get a nice curry.
Oh, Timmy's gambling.
Timmy's gambling. Cory.
So, what you're saying is is Timmy as
Timmy posted a video, Greavves, you're
on the same website you can watch
Spider-Man on, or is it a different website?
Oh, look, Lego's just made a new video.
Well, that's quite dangerous, isn't it, Grezy?
That they're allowed that that website
can on on this YouTube people can meet for fights.
This YouTube people can meet for fights.
And you can watch Spongebob on the same website.
I remember grievously Chicago summers.
Tico Summers. He called Chicago Summers.
Yeah, that little white knight didn't um
that white knight didn't come back, did
he? Well, I'm going to do a panel today,
Greavvesy. I'm going to do a little
video after I eat and say I want to have
this discussion about white knighting.
and stuff. I want I want Let's have a discussion.
I'm going to put it as as the title.
See if uh people come in and joined. I
want to get to the bottom of this.
Yeah, I want to get to the bottom of this.
able to answer it.
All did you did you get the notification
from Monty that he went live?
Did you get a notification
that he went live?
I've got the bell on. I'm subscribed to
Monty and Timmy. Yeah.
Did you like my video on the dating
game, Pip Smoker?
Yeah, I would have been up £50 if they
didn't scam me out of this money.
I got scammed out of this [ __ ] money, bro.
I got two thumbs up on my little dating
video. That's nice. Yeah.
Ricky Millington commented, "Yes, Timmy.
Have a gambling session. Prop call with
PJ. Go live. That would be a right laugh.
How about you [ __ ] off, you [ __ ]
No, I'm not meeting no one, bro. I'm not
drinking or nothing. I'm not doing any
of that [ __ ]
I'm just going to be like greasy now.
Stay home and do nothing. Yeah.
got banned from typing on Instagram for
[ __ ] seven eyes. Yes, forever.
I think I should delete YouTube forever.
That's why I don't really like talking
about dating to be honest with you.
Really like doing the videos and that's
why I'm not really on Reddit much
because the whole white knight and [ __ ]
and the biasness annoys me. So, anything
that you post about it, you're just
going to get white knights. That's why I
tried to avoid getting into like any
kind of discussion.
And when I go on Reddit now, I don't ask for advice.
I kind of just dictate. I don't ask for advice. Um,
and I don't complain either because if
you complain then you're going to get white knights
and people defend women and stuff. So if you complain,
if you complain and stuff, that's what happens.
If you complain or ask for advice
and that's when it goes around in
circles, isn't it greasy? Yeah.
Do you reckon do you reckon if I was gay
Chicago summers people would be making
excuses for men like they do women or nah?
If I was saying like oh I'm struggling
with men. And you reckon people would blame me?
>> What do you reckon?
Greasy. Do I ask questions that I
already know the answer to? Nah.
Hopefully this person meets. We could
have babies and stuff.
Labor could have babies. Greezy.
I can have babies quite like Greezy.
Why can't I have babies?
Why? What would happen if I did?
thought I could.
So what you're saying Gre is they'd get removed.
Would they just get removed from the
hospital straight away?
Would they just get removed straight
from the hospital? We see
Oh, Timmy's done a video on me. Grezy
Oh, he's so [ __ ] autistic. This Timmy,
what's the chance of Timmy coming to
meet me today? Graves.
Oh yeah, he's projecting. This is how
you know it was projecting with him when
he was saying that, "Oh, I can't even
afford an Arch burger." What the [ __ ]
I've never had an Archber burger in my
life. That's how you know it was projection.
He's saying he's trying to win money to
pay for the tickets.
What the [ __ ]
This is the same [ __ ] with this guy, bro. Same [ __ ]
No, I don't really like McDonald's, but
I only get the nuggets.
I don't find I don't really like the
burgers and stuff, bro.
So, what do you reckon, Grezy? If he
wins £2,000, do you reckon he's going to
do you reckon he's going to book the
train ticket or do you think he's going
to come out with another excuse?
What do you think?
Yeah, he's calling himself a virgin.
Timmy is a virgin.
Yeah, Timmy's calling himself a virgin, lad.
He's calling himself a virgin.
He says he has to get a train ticket
next week. He's skint. He can't even
afford a train ticket.
He said if he doesn't win, he's going to
get the train ticket next week.
He's [ __ ] skinty.
He's skinn than the virgin. Well,
they're both virgins, but you know what
I'm talking about. Crazy.
Oh, for God's sake, man.
So, do you reckon he's coming today
then? Um, greasy.
>> You reckon he's coming today?
Yeah, Timmy might be coming today if he
wins another 30. Green Hill, you excited?
>> Yeah. He said if he wins another uh30,
he's going to get the train tickets.
Are you looking forward to that?
My mom asked me, "What is a white knight?"
I said people that defend women for the
sake of defending women.
So Greezy, why did Lunch used to watch
the X Factor?
Why did he used to Why did he used to
watch the X Factor?
You sort TX factor.
I'm not a troll. Greavesy.
How am I a troll? That's what UK asylum
said that I'm a troll.
Why? How am I trolling?
How I troll, man. Never
never trolled in my life, lad.
Let's pack it in.
I'm not trolling. I actually did get
scammed out of money, bro. I actually
did win and they refused to pay out.
And they actually refused to pay out.
No, I actually did get scammed out of money.
Yep. I lost £100. until I got it to 150.
They wouldn't give me it.
Yep. Them [ __ ] were laughing at us, mocking us,
laughing at you, mocking you,
mocking you. Weezy
Weezy says I'm a troll.
Monsters used to watch the X. Copycat. D do
I'm not a trolly lad.
Oh, this poo this poo account is a
proper white night, lad.
It can never be women's fault.
What a white night. You know what he
wrote? He said, "Papa Pete finds every
excuse in the world to avoid
accountability." No, that's what women
do and you do to women. He's too young.
He's too old. He's Muslim. He's not
Muslim. He has a beard. He hasn't got a
beard. It's women's fault. It's S's
fault. It's still Yep. Definitely it is
women's faults. Uh and it is the West
fault. Yep. Which is why many people
leave. There's statistics to prove that
it's Instagram fault. No. man to it's
your fault. Pika peach. Too much the
reason why I've run away from him. Yeah,
that's a white knight right there, lad.
Proper proper white lighting. No, it
definitely definitely is women's fault,
which is why we gave up to get away from it.
Of course, it's women's fault. They're
stuck up [ __ ]
The [ __ ] How are you even going to try
and deny that in 2026?
That dude's probably a virgin.
No, you would. These people will not
hold account women accountable for anything
even when it's proven.
I [ __ ] hate women, bro, with a passion.
I know I've had more women than these
white knights and simps.
I've had more women than both of than
all of them combined, lad.
I just hate them because of what they're
like. I'm allowed to have an opinion. I
can say what I want, bro. Do you get me?
So yeah, no one can ask for advice. No one can.
Why is there so many white knights
saying they defending women
even when you prove like women have led
you on and been [ __ ] Why? I don't know
why they still defend them. They must
think it's going to it's going to get
them laid or something, bro.
I think they think by defending women
they're going to get laid or something. Who knows?
Anyways, uh has Thingy re-uploaded?
That's what I think, bro. They think
they're going to get laid.
What do you think of the double standards? China.
What's your opinion, lad?
You don't need to live with a woman.
You don't need to live with a woman, lad.
And I don't give a [ __ ] if people don't
take who uh
I don't already I don't already know.
You don't need to live with a woman.
Just like you don't need to be in a
relationship to know what they're like.
You don't need to do either of them
things. You don't need to live with a
woman. I've met enough women and I know
exactly what they're like. I don't need
to live with the [ __ ]
This is just another excuse.
You don't need to live with a woman to
know what they're like. They're [ __ ]
They're [ __ ] Simple as that. You
don't need to live with them to know
what they're like. I hate talking about
this, bro. This is depressing.
Um, this is just pointless back and
forth depressing. Depression [ __ ] I
don't even like talking about this
dating [ __ ] bro. It's depressing.
I don't like talking about this [ __ ]
JNA, bro. When I go on when I go on
Reddit now, I don't even ask for advice.
I don't complain. I don't do nothing.
Why would I, bro?
Why would I? Why would anyone ask for advice?
You're never going to get fair advice.
You're never going to get a fair answer
unless you was gay or something. You're
never going to get a fair answer.
That's why I don't think there's re there's there's
there's any point anyone asking for advice.
Oh yeah, it's way better than this
place. Yeah, but I don't like the the
people make excuses for women. JNA, like
when women [ __ ] me over and led me on
and stuff, they make excuses for them on
Reddit. I noticed that. I don't know if
you noticed that with the with the with the subreddit.
But they make excuses for women when
they do shitty things.
They won't hold them accountable for
anything. That's why I stopped asking
them for advice and stuff.
It's like when you show women f No, I
mean I've private messaged people.
Message people, lad.
Oh, Mr. Bean. What happened to Vary?
Do you remember Vary? Mr. B.
No, I private message people. I'm I
private message people, lad.
And they just make excuses for them. Very Mr. By
mocking you Grezy.
They're laugh they're laughing at me. Mocking me. Would
you say they're biased on their JNA and
make excuses for women? They definitely
do. They won't hold women accountable for anything.
That's why I never asked for advice.
That's why I don't do anything because
they just defend them.
I mean, what did you think of my dating video? Um,
JNA mean it got two thumbs up.
I assume you watched it. I know it's
quite long, but
uh but obviously this is the wrong place to
to post that really because Yeah.
They do defend women and try to put the
blame onto you.
That's why I gave up JNA.
It makes sense, isn't it?
I might get a McDonald's greasy. I might
get a big arts burger.
I might get a big arch.
What? And you're completely fine with
that, Grezy. Me getting a big arch.
Maybe I Well, I like Cheryl Cole. I'm
going to watch the X Factor.
I'm going to watch the X Factor and be
like non legs.
Nah, bro. I'm not having McDonald's,
bro. [ __ ] that.
There's no point. It just comes cold.
There's a meme on Instagram. Yeah. It
says you're trying to sleep but you
can't stop thinking why you didn't cash
out when you had the chance
and it's doing dinky whipsy dipsy.
Have you seen it? Oh gosh,
Grezy. Oh gosh.
Is that cute? Grezy. Oh gosh. Meow.
Meow. Yeah, it is the copycat community.
I'm not your friend. UK asylum
calling me a troll and [ __ ]
What's your opinion on on my dating video? JNA,
you didn't you didn't tell me.
UK assign him. Bro, you I actually did
get scammed yesterday. They didn't give
me that 150. It was £151 they owed me
and they didn't give me it.
I put £100 on my own money. I got to
£151. I tried to take it. They reverse
the withdrawal. How am I trolling? You
say that I'm a troll. How?
That actually did happen.
No, it actually did happen, bro.
So why are you saying that I'm a troll lad?
No, JNA. JNA JNA. I've um
JNA. Um I've I I put the video on my main.
Yeah, you need to watch it, JNA. I've
done it on my main channel. Watch it and
come back. I'll just wait for the
review. I'll just sit I'll just wait.
You'll You'll wait.
Yes, until you've watched the 23 minute video.
I'll just wait.
Don't know where to be. But no, UK
asylum. I don't troll ad. No way.
I'll wait until you've watched it. I'll
be like this. Look. I'm waiting.
I'm waiting on you.
It's not funny. Graves,
watch my video now or I'll come to your
house and beat you with a stick.
Well, at least [ __ ]
at least uh
replied back and we was talking. Maybe
I'll be able to get this baby now. Is it Grievy?
Not a prime candidate for baby Peter.
There's been some women that just
weren't a prime candidate for baby Peter. Greasy.
Not everyone's suitable to carry baby Peter. Easy.
Keep watching, lad. Keep watching.
Keep watching, JNA. Keep watching, lad.
Do you want my opinion, Zippy?
Uh uh. Uh-huh.
They're all [ __ ]
What a [ __ ] day I've had. UK asylum
before I went to sleep yesterday. Yeah.
I was like, "What a [ __ ] day I've had."
It's the [ __ ] truth though, isn't it?
What a [ __ ] day I had. They're [ __ ] [ __ ]
Imagine that though. Killing yourself
over roulette UK asylum. Over a little
bull on the wheel.
Over a little ball on the wheel. Imagine that.
that dying over roulette.
Well, she didn't ghost me in the end,
did she, Greg? She didn't ghost in the
end, did she?
Yeah. You don't gamble, do you? UK
asylum, you're a good little fellow.
Yeah, you're a you're a uh you're a good fellow.
You're a good fellow,
isn't he? Greasy. UK Asylum's a good little fellow.
Yeah, I got mad over Christian. He said,
"Oh, what's with all these messages?" I
said, "I thought you ran away. I thought you ghosted."
But I thought my little Christian is he
wouldn't do that to me.
Is that right, Grezy?
You wouldn't do that to Pabelli.
Leave me all by myself. Well, I'll never
all be I'll never be by myself cuz I've
got Crash Grezy. The worst comes to
worse, I've got Crash Bandicut by my side.
He's my little mate.
Yep. I used to have King, but he got
took back, so I don't have King anymore.
Uh, what you need to do is if you can
get this if you can get one of these
women, you need to trap them with a baby
grievy. That's what you need to do. It's
like sort of like it's a form of enttrapment,
you see. And obviously, they're not
going to have an abortion. A lot of them
will just keep the baby, you see. So the
same way they tried to trap men, you
need to sort of trap them from early on. You see,
that's how you kind of get someone to
stay with you.
Even if they're from international, even
if you have a hookup with someone from international,
if they go back to where they live, they
obviously have a baby and then that's
fine, you know. Oh gosh.
Yeah, basically. Yeah, baby. Yeah,
you're quite cute. We
ice cream man's outside. It must be hot
No, I would just cheat.
UK sign. I'll just cheat.
No, I would just I would just be a cheater.
You know her name, is it? Her name's
Christian Izzy Greavvesy.
That's my mama.
Do you actually know her real first name? Greavvesy.
Yeah, there's a reason why I renamed it.
So you didn't find out the name. Cuz you
might found you might have found out the name
and then gave her to these clowns. Poor [ __ ] Ain't it?
I wonder where JNA is. He's taking quite
a long time.
Greasy, do you reckon you could find her
now if you wanted to?
Nah. No way in it.
There's no way, isn't it, Grezy? There's
no way you could.
Do you Do you reckon you could?
Do you reckon you've got enough now?
Nah, you couldn't, could you?
The poor [ __ ]
How do you know I renamed it though,
Grezy? You knew I renamed it, didn't
you? You knew that wasn't the name from the get-go.
But all all seriousness though, like in
all seriousness, the dating game is bad,
bro. Like all jokes aside, it is [ __ ]
Like it's not even funny, bro.
I hate everything about it. The women,
the dating, the simps. I hate everything
about it. That's why you That's why you
um That's why you send me white knights
in it, Grezy. Yeah.
I hate everything about it.
No, no, no, no, no. Dipsy dipsy.
I want my little curry now. I'm a bit pecked.
What did you think of the video,
Captain? I'm going to get Laney to buy
me a takeaway today. Don't forget, I did
get scammed out of money.
I'm gonna get Laney, too. I'm going to
try and get Laney too.
No, that's not Christian. Is he
Um, what do you think about the eyes
or that woman that I showed you?
Would I [ __ ] Mr. B? She's [ __ ] stinking, son.
She's [ __ ] stinking, son. Any
opinion on her eyes? Greasy.
I like Mary Jane from Spider-Man. She
had lovely eyes. No, no Westinity in it
at all before Tik Tok, before Instagram,
before Facebook. [ __ ] lovely Mary Jane.
Mary Jane. It's It's cute.
I kind of got if I find some women on
Instagram, I find it kind of nice if the
if the woman has a kid or two kids,
greasy, because obviously it means that
they've got experience in being a
mother. So, they could be a mommy to
you. And if they had your baby,
maybe one kid. I think it's really I
don't know. I think that's kind of hot,
you know, if someone has one kid. Not sure
cuz obviously they could be a mother to
you as well and you know your if you had
a baby and stuff. I don't know.
I find it quite cute to be honest.
Yeah, keep watching JNA. Keep watching
the video, lad.
Keep watching the video. This is exactly
what I'm talking about.
In the video, I was discussing that even
if you took it slow and you spoke to
them for longer, they'll still [ __ ] you over.
No, it's not her. Um,
it's not her, dust. Um,
it's not her. Um, Greasy, bro. That's
That's not my mama. Yuck. Yuck.
That's That's not my mama. That's my
mama. Greavvesy. See, when I got put
into care, when I got abandoned, they
were trying to tell me, they were trying
to [ __ ] with my head, trying to say,
"This person was your mama. Sig was your
mama." And I was like, "No." And that
account that said to you, "Poor fucker."
It even said Sig was never your mama.
Sig not Peter Belly's mama.
That's why he come and said he said not
Peter Belly's mama.
I think Christy and Izzy could be my name. Mama,
I keep going on the little pictures that
she sent me of herself. Grezy,
she could be my mama, can't she? Crazy.
I want somebody to tell me that I'm the best. Grezy,
I want somebody to hug me and kiss me
and tell me I'm the best in the world.
What do you think of that, Grezy?
I want to be told I'm the [ __ ] best.
Yeah, Laney can buy me a takeaway today
after I did get [ __ ] scammed.
You order me a takeaway, then I'll be
then then I feel better. Breezy.
Yeah, I woke up. My eyes my eyes were
half open and then Christian Izzy
messaged me. I was like, "Oh, yay,
Grezy. I got a little few couple voice notes."
That's always nice, isn't it?
I thought I got abandoned again. That's not good.
When I wrote when I wrote things on
Reddit, Grezy. Some woman said, "What
the [ __ ] did I just read?" I was talking
about nutrients and stuff.
She was like, "What the [ __ ] did I just read?"
He says, She says, "No, that's not
normal for a grown man to get withdrawal
symptoms from boobs and stuff.
What the [ __ ] did I just read? Yep.
Right. This woman has posted up a video,
a photo of herself. It's got 103
comments. I'm going to write a comment.
You can you can see the westernity
in a tea
in your eyes.
It doesn't matter JNA lad. It doesn't
matter how long you speak to them for.
Well, she replied today. She did reply
today, JNA. But she still might not meet
me. Who knows? She might do, she might not.
That's what I'm saying. You You
might as well try to meet them
as soon as possible because they're
going to [ __ ] you over anyways. So,
you're damned if you do, you're damned
if you don't.
You're damned if you do, you're damned
if you don't. But people on Reddit JNA
say that you'll meet someone,
but you never do. They'll tell you for
years and years that you'll meet
someone, you don't know what's around the corner,
all this kind of stuff. But nothing
happens and nothing changes.
Why do you need to speak to someone for
a couple of weeks? You don't need to
speak to someone for a couple weeks. If
you've approached someone on the Thursday,
you could meet them by the next
Thursday. Why not?
Why is there these little rules for men?
For what reason?
No one says anything when a woman tries
to meet someone straight away.
I've had a woman say to me before, "Oh,
uh, yeah, do you still want to meet
Tuesday night?" And that was her first
message. So, if a woman could try to
meet you straight away, then
yeah, you can try and meet someone
within a week. Nah. Uh-uh.
I will try I I would try and meet
someone as soon as possible.
Um, the only way I wouldn't do that is
if I had multiple people I was talking to,
but that's the only way I wouldn't do
that. But no, I I got five numbers last
time I went out and I only got one response.
DN. So, I mean, it doesn't matter
really, does it anyways? They're still
going to [ __ ] you over. Even if you
speak to them for three or four weeks,
they're still going to flake.
So, if someone wants to meet you,
they'll meet you.
I wouldn't carry on speaking to someone for weeks.
I wouldn't carry on meeting I wouldn't
carry on speaking to someone for weeks
at all, lad.
Oh, have you got anxiety, Grezy?
So, yeah, I wouldn't I personally wouldn't JNA
unless there was a solid reason. If I
meet someone on Thursday, I want to meet
them by the next Thursday.
And if not, then
that's it in it.
But everyone has different strategies
and [ __ ] in it.
Cuz think about it, they have no problem
with you with a woman trying to meet you
straight away. JNA,
no, I'm not talking about dating apps.
I'm talking about approaching. I don't
use dating apps. I'm talking about women
I've actually approached. I don't need
to be speaking to a woman for weeks.
I don't use dating apps, lad.
I don't meet people from dating apps.
I'm talking about approaching. If I've
approached someone, I'm not speaking to
them for weeks. I don't have to speak to
them for weeks. Simple.
Well, it doesn't matter. Well, if they
don't meet me within a week, they're done.
Yeah. Well, if they don't meet me for if
they don't meet me, then that's it.
Right. But even like I've said again,
but even if you speak to them for weeks,
they're still going to flake. They're
still going to [ __ ] you over one way or
the other. So it's it's the same.
Whether you try to meet them straight
away, whether you try to meet them after
3 weeks, they're still going to [ __ ] you
over. They're not going to think, "Oh,
hold on. I've been speaking to this guy
for one month.
Maybe I should meet him. They're still
going to [ __ ] you over.
They're still going to mess you around.
Whether it's fast, whether it's slow,
whether it's in the middle. Does Does it matter?
Does it Does it really matter which one
you pick? Because they're still going to
[ __ ] you over. They don't care.
They're still going to mess you around.
So, that's it.
Like I said, no one has a problem when a
woman tries to meet you the same day. So
people shouldn't have problems.
Well, rather you than to me, lad. Rather
you than to me.
Rather you than me. I never take it
slow. If they're not meeting me within a
week, I'm done with them. Simple.
Rather you take that gamble, lad. You're
a brave man because I'm not doing it.
And there's there's not a and there's no
problem when a woman wants to meet you
straight away. So there shouldn't be a
problem with you trying to meet someone
within a week.
Double standards again.
So yeah, it doesn't matter. They're
still going to [ __ ] you over. They're
still going to mess you around.
Yeah, I know.
I don't care, bro. I don't care if they
do or they don't. I'm just saying I'm
not speaking to someone longer for
longer than a week.
I gave up on the dating thing anyways,
J. I gave up on it, lad.
I gave up on it, bro.
Long time ago, like I said in the video. Uh,
I gave up a long time ago, bro. So, yeah.
I hate women. I hate dating. I hate
white knights. I hate everything about it. Simple.
But each to their own, lad.
Each to their own.
And most of the time, you don't even get
a response when you get a number.
And another thing is like I I another
thing with the dating is that people
always try and make it seem like you're
doing something wrong when you're not.
Cuz you try their way, you try their
way, you still get the same thing.
So it's like no matter what you do,
they're always going to blame you. So
what what's the point of it?
There's no point of it, lad. So
most of the time they don't even respond back. So
yeah, I've given up dating forever, lad.
Well, if this person doesn't meet me,
then that's me done forever and ever and
ever, bro. And I mean it, lad. I mean it 100%.
It's never going to change. I don't know
why people on Reddit say it's going to change. JNA,
I'm surprised a lot of people on Reddit
are not telling people to go to Thailand.
If they if they knew about life, then
they'd surely know that the dating game
sucks in these westernized countries.
I'm surprised they don't tell people to
go to Thailand, to be fair. Yeah,
you got no chance as a man nowadays,
JNA. No chance.
No chance, bro. No chance.
Where do you live anyways? you know.
Yeah, but I'd rather go somewhere where
the women aren't [ __ ]
and you get less money.
That's why people go Thailand. Why do
you think Adman went to Thailand?
I just don't like westernized women. I
don't like the people here as well. I
just don't like the people here as well.
They're just [ __ ]
I actually do think that if I met a
woman, I would just ruin her life at
this point, lad.
I think if I ever did manage to meet
anyone, I would just ruin their life, bro.
I'm not lying, bro. Just for like revenge.
Yeah, it's getting like it there as
well, but it's not as bad as here, bro.
It's not as bad as here.
Yeah, my friend from Belgium said, "Yep,
I never yapp too much before meeting a
girl for the first time. Max 10 messages
or we call. If you don't agree between
those messages, then bye.
pretty much. Yeah.
But people on Reddit Ja, they give
people false hope.
Would you say, would you agree with that
about Reddit? They give people false hope.
No, I think that's solid, bro. I think
what he's saying is right.
Like I said, I would, like I said, I
wouldn't waste more than a week talking
to someone. I tried to meet them within
five messages. To be fair,
it doesn't matter anyways. It's them
that's the problem. So, we need to stop
thinking about what we could do better
or what we could do this cuz it's always
going to be the same no matter what we do
cuz it's them that or [ __ ] It's them
that's the problem. So, it doesn't
matter what you do, where you live, what
money you have, how you text, it's
always going to be the same cuz it's
them. It is them. So, that's it.
And there's been proof that it's them as well.
People can sit there and try and say,
"Oh, you blame women. You blame women."
But I've provided the evidence that gets
ignored. So, you can't win with these
people, bro. So, it's simple as that.
They want to carry on defending women,
thinking that they're innocent, thinking
that they're angels. They can do that,
bro. No skin off my nose. I gave up. So, you know,
I'd rather just chill and eat some nice
food. You know,
have some nice food.
Oh, [ __ ] [ __ ]
Oh, do you remember that Greavves in
Rainbow? Oh, [ __ ] [ __ ]
Do you remember when um Jeffrey said,
"Oh, [ __ ] Fuck." They forgot something in it.
I think they're all [ __ ]
But yeah, bro, I don't care. And I don't
There's no woman that's different. I
learned that a long time ago.
We'll see if Christian Izzy meets. We'll see.
But what I'd imagine is she'll probably
get back with her ex or something. Same
old story. We've heard it all before,
lad. We've been there before. We've
heard it all before. Isn't that right, Bezy?
I said to Antman like, "We need to stop
talking about it. It pisses me off, bro. You know,
you know when something so [ __ ] up,
you just don't want to talk about it. Greasy. 10 messages. Nah, bro.
I'm not in no queue, JNA. I'm not in no
queue, lad. Cuz I gave up.
I'm not in no queue
cuz I gave up the lad. So I'm not in any queue.
Isn't that right, [ __ ]
Is that all right with you, K?
All right, Mr. B. What happened to Vary?
What happened to Vary, lad?
Very snake, lad. Do you remember him in it?
Yeah, because you're Cuz you were being selfish.
You was being selfish. Very selfish.
Dy was being selfish.
I've just been scammed and she doesn't care. Greasy.
Well, I'm going to get myself some food.
Is that all right, Grezy?
Should I get a C or should I get a Vindeloo?
[ __ ] virgin. Huh?
Okay. I can either get a uh Madras
vinderoo or foul Rogan.
Should I get a foul and see if I can
have a foul?
Should I get that? See if I can take it.
Should I go for that instead of the vine? Yeah.
You don't need to know that.
But JNA, these women are [ __ ] I'm
going to get a foul. Yeah, I'm going to
get a foul. I need that after the
[ __ ] day I had, mate.
Yeah, some chicken tickle as well. Yeah.
Uh, where is the tickle?
There we go. Chicken ticker rice and curry.
Yeah, I got a lamb foul.
Let's see if I can take this. Right.
There we go. It's been ordered.
Let's see how how how much of a big
strong Turkish man I really am. Greavvesy. Okay, boss.
Is that okay with you, boss?
Is that okay with you, [ __ ]
Okay with you, [ __ ]
Yeah, I don't really have loads and
loads and loads of money left now cuz
I've been scammed.
It doesn't matter though, does it Greasy?
It doesn't matter that much, does it? No. Yeah.
[ __ ] it, lad.
Oh, [ __ ] bro.
You know what? I went I bought some
washing stuff. Greavves here.
Yesterday I bought some washing stuff
and I went to get some food and that cuz
obviously I was expecting this money
that was owed to me.
But obviously I didn't get it, did I? No,
>> you find it funny, Grezy. No,
it's not funny, bro.
150 is a lot of money, isn't it,
Grey? That could have that could have
paid for a nice little night out.
Haircut night out. Isn't that right, Grezy? 150.
Yeah, of course it would have.
Does anyone go on lights out anymore? Really?
I mean, anyone from this community. I
I stopped doing that ages ago, lad.
About a year and a half ago, I stopped going out.
My little legs are getting too old, Grezy.
I can't wait for this curry,
but I reckon it's going to [ __ ] kill
me. But don't worry, I'm a big strong
Turkish man. I've got plenty of cans and
coke. Cans of Coke.
No, you just teach English. If you're
going to go to If you're going to go
Thailand, you just teach English.
That's that's it. You don't need to do anything else.
Yeah, there [ __ ] in this country.
No, I'm not a copycat.
I'm not a copycat. You don't see me
calling people gay because they don't
find Sher Co attractive. Dr. Echo, that
was proper copying.
That was copying the crowd.
Yeah, that was just to fit in.
You want me to do a challenge of this
foul curry? You know what? I might do a
video on it. I might do like a video and
pull it up Grezy as like a challenge.
I want to.
Yeah, I think that would be a better
idea to be honest. Grezy.
Yeah, I reckon that would be a better idea.
Yeah, I reckon that would be better.
Just do a little video.
Virgin boy tried saying [ __ ] binderoo is mild.
I wouldn't say it's I wouldn't say it's mild.
You can if Oh, I got boiled rice instead
of pillow rice. I'm such a silly goose,
aren't I? Grevy. I'm such a silly goose. Oh, well.
What? And start saying about the virgin.
Hey, Dr. Echo, did you used to like Cheryl Carl?
I used to think she was [ __ ] ugly,
but I got called day for it by some
little virgin in a [ __ ] bed sit by
the [ __ ] council.
people who used to actually watch X
Factor and wanted her. Not me, lad. I've
just ordered a really spicy hot curry.
Like a really really hot curry. So,
we'll see how we do.
We'll see how we'll do. We'll see how we
do. That's what's happening. [ __ ] Yep.
Uh Timmy said, "Hey, did you see what
happened with Timmy?" Joseph Farah.
Oh, sorry. Joseph [ __ ] Farra. I
ordered him a taxi and he wouldn't come
in. He wouldn't step on in the taxi to
come to London.
He got me to order him a taxi. It was £196
and he didn't come in.
He said that he was I ordered the taxi and stuff.
So, I ordered the taxi and stuff, but he
didn't he didn't he didn't he didn't he
didn't didn't he didn't want to come.
And then he said he wants to win money
for the train ticket. What the [ __ ]
Winning money for a train ticket. Oh.
You know, the thing is Timmy would
actually be all right deep down if he
come off this [ __ ] for like 3 months.
You know that, Grey. If he actually come
off this community for 3 months and he
stopped this [ __ ] he'd actually be all
right. You know that.
You know that if he actually come off
this [ __ ] for about 3 months and you saw
him in public, bro, he he's actually all
right, you know? But like
he would be, but it's just this
community and [ __ ] is it, man?
He's a [ __ ] He's an idiot, man. He's
never meeting anyone.
Nah, you're a two-faced [ __ ] But I love
it anyways cuz when you talk about me,
it just proves that you're gay, lad.
That just proved that you're giving me attention.
So, you know. Yep.
You're not watching the X Factor on YouTube, Joe.
You're not watching the X Factor.
You used to like the X Factor, didn't you?
Did you hear about the casino that
[ __ ] me over, Joseph Ferrar?
It wasn't a joke. It was true. And
that's why, see, the thing is, listen to
me, you [ __ ] You and these
streamers, you slag off UK regulated
sites. You're slagging off these UK
regulated sites. Oh, don't give you
don't give them your money. This
wouldn't have happened on the UK
regulated site. Even if they asked for
proof of wealth or whatever, I knew I
would have got that money in the end.
See, people like you and secular slots
can slag off these UK regular regulated
sites. But no UK regular site would have
even tried that trick. they they
wouldn't even try it, bro. Let alone let
alone uh they would have got away with
it. It's as simple as that. So,
basically, I put £1100 in the casino and
I got it to £200. Um I respan it. I got
it to 150. I thought I'll just take the
50 profit, pays for a day out, whatever.
Let's go back to it in two weeks. So, I
reversed it. This is this is raw money.
No bonus money. There was no bonus
money. I don't I don't take bonus money.
The free spins they gave me before was
free spins they gave me. I don't accept
bonus money. Then they've then they've
reversed. Then they've reversed. It
wasn't bonus money. It was raw money. It
And I got the £100. Uh then they
reversed the £150. I'm thinking, uh, why
have you reversed the money? I'm
verified. I'm thinking they're going to
maybe ask me for documents.
Maybe they're going to ask me for
documents. And they said, oh, you you
need to wager. I said, "It's not bonus
money. It's my money." They said, "No,
yeah, we know it's not bonus money, but
that's what it says on the terms and
conditions." I said, "No, it [ __ ]
does not. No, it [ __ ] does not."
Uh, no it does not. And I went to see
the TNC's and it never said that and
they just weren't they just refused to
pay out. So, I was like, "Oh, okay. Let
me let me complete it."
So, this is why people use UK regulated
sites because even if people ask even if
they ask for source of uh even if they
ask for proof of income, they're going
to have to pay you regardless. They're
going to have to pay you.
So, yeah, they and they just weren't
giving it back. I tried. I tried and
they just weren't, you know. So, it's
it's a scam. They're scammers.
It's as simple as that, bro. If I lost
the money, then I would have been like,
"Oh, well, it's my own fault." After the
rage, after 3 hours, but it wasn't my
fault because they didn't let me take
the money that was mine. So, yeah.
So, they scammed me, bro. They they they
scam me. It's as simple as that. So, and
I was one off of a football bet
yesterday. I was one goal off a football bet.
All I needed was slow to score and I
would have got 266. So
personally now I wouldn't go in any site
that's not regulated by the UK.
Regulated sites, arcades or bookies.
That's it. Simple. I wouldn't even go
casino anymore. Like even if I could get
in, I'd say even then, nah.
What's your opinion on that, Joseph Ferrar?
Have you noticed as well when you have
used bonus money in the past how you
start winning? Joseph Ferrar, have you
noticed how you started how you will start winning?
Or if they give you free spins, have you
noticed you will start winning?
Ain't you noticed that before? They gave
me free They gave me 40. Listen to me.
They gave me 43 spins. Yeah, it wasn't
bonus money. 43 spins. So I went on the
slot. I got it to £4. I turned that £4
to57 on roulette again. Had to complete
the raing. And I'm thinking,
what the [ __ ] No, I can see your comments.
And I'm thinking that is rigged as [ __ ]
It is rigged as [ __ ] because when you
use when you when you use free spins,
you'll notice how you win. You'll notice
how you win £4 to £57 on roulette.
What's the chances of that? What is the
chances of that? Very rare, right? So,
it's all fixed. And even when you play
with your own money, they they said they
have to complete wagering
and they do these things cuz they can do
it and no one's going to stop them doing
it. So I'll just go back on the Ladbrook
site when it opens up in four weeks
if I want to gamble again. Simple as that.
They pay instant. So
Jesus [ __ ] Christ, bro.
See you later, lad.
You get kicked as Monty would say.
So yeah, Joe.
I don't know why these streamers say,
"Oh, don't go on regulated sites. Don't
Yeah. Or or even even even the bookie
sites online. I'm sure they'll pay you
even if you had to go through hoops and
stuff. This is the first time me
actually coming across this problem.
I've never had this problem though.
Ever. Ever. Ever. I've never had this
problem. I've had it where they've been
slow giving money.
There was bad reviews on some sites.
When I played Dog Spin before, there was
there was people saying that they never
got their money. They never got their
money. They never got their money. And I
thought, "Oh [ __ ] I'm in a bit of
trouble here. I'm waiting for £500."
They paid. So, every time they got a bad review,
uh, you'd get paid anyways. So, I don't
know if it's because people lost money
or whatever. So, I never had a problem
ever in my life until until yesterday.
They always paid no matter what site I used.
They might have asked for proof and
there's proof of that, but they've
always paid cuz I would have I would
have I would have I would have uh Yeah,
it's my sister's account. Yeah, I I
would have known. If I've had a problem
being paid out, I would have known.
So, I've never had a problem being paid
out except from a dodgy casino once.
I don't know about them.
I used Golden Better. They were fine.
But personally now after that, I would
never use a site that's not UK regulated.
I would never use a site now that's not UK regulated.
Well, I've already won money on it when
I won that football bet. 224 from 20.
They paid it instantly.
And even if they do ask for ID, they're
going to pay, aren't they? It's a bookie site. So
man that is bad. Really bad.
I don't I don't I done a double
yesterday. Joseph Ferrar I done I done a
both teams to score and win over to beat
Horns both teams to score. Slow and slow
to beat AFC Tott both teams to score and
[ __ ] slow didn't score one more
[ __ ] goal and it [ __ ] it all up.
That would have been a sick win from£10. Almost, bro.
No, because because my sister can verify it.
No, because my sister can verify it. So,
simple as that.
You're going to get your money, aren't
you? You're never going to get your So,
yeah, I wouldn't trust a a site that's
not UK regulated.
No, it was yes, this was yesterday.
So, now I'm not getting as much money as
I'm supposed to now, which is [ __ ]
You might not think 150 is a lot, but
when it's your money and you're not
getting it, 150, bro, you could go on a
nice night out, get some food, get a
haircut with that. It's money that's not theirs.
Just see it as that. And if you see it
as see as it's money that's not theirs
that they're not paying you, what the [ __ ] bro?
You could have done something with it,
bro. Like, what? Yeah. Oh, well.
And you say And you say stick to
bookies. What roulette is on the
bookies? [ __ ] a bar roulette.
What a bar [ __ ] roulette.
Yeah, [ __ ] shitty bar roulette maybe.
Yeah, [ __ ] sake. So, yeah, I would
never trust a site that's not UK regulated
or anyone that's not on Gamb basically.
But Golden Bet used to pay out.
Yeah, golden bet paid out, but
still it's not the point.
Lad Brook Lad Brooks pays instantly, Joe.
Lad Brooks pays instantly.
Yeah, it doesn't matter if I've got [ __ ] 1,4003,400.
That 150 is not their [ __ ] money, is it? So, yep.
Yep. It is
that football bet, man. What the [ __ ]
Can't get into any casinos, lads. You know this.
Unless I Well, I probably could to be honest, but yeah,
but then they tried to get out of paying
people as well. forever. Ever. Well,
yeah, I think so. Yeah.
Forever. Ever. Ever. Yeah.
Come on, food. I'm hungry.
I think I'm just going to be done with
the gambling, to be honest.
Come on food.
I am hungry.
I am hungry as [ __ ]
So, you've had no wins uh recently, Joseph Ferrar.
Nah, you done your balls in it. You done
your sacking, mate.
Oh, bless you then if you've had a few. wins.
Bless you then.
Well, when this curry get comes, I'm
going to do this challenge.
Let's see if this curry can beat me.
I'm being a bit of a copycat today, Joe.
I'm being a bit of a copycat. Like nods legs.
You remember Joe F? Ngs being a copycat.
I had a nice shower.
He's a copycat. >> Yes.
No, but Timmy's a projector. No,
seriously. He said the other day, "Oh,
I'm so skinn. I can't even afford a big
arch. Never had a big arch in my life. I
don't even like McDonald's much." And
look, he's done a video having a big arch.
So, he's he's projecting in it.
Yeah, that is that is projecting.
Right. Come on, food. Estimated
arrival 10 to 6. That's not possible cuz that's
in 6 minutes.
It's It's a foul.
It's hot. It's hotter than the Vindaloo.
Yeah. I've only had this once before.
So, I'll see if I can take it. Yeah. Sure am.
Sure am, Captain.
am, Captain [ __ ]
Sure am, Captain C.
I was scared as Christian is he ghosted
me, Joe, but she never, we spoke today
and stuff, which is good.
Hopefully we meet up and, you know, have
a baby and stuff in good time.
Is that right, Grezy?
Isn't that right? And if not, oh well,
I've got crash bandicut.
Simple as that.
There's this bastard curry. I'm [ __ ] hungry now.
Got some tickle on the side, too.
What's going on here then?
Come on, I'm hungry.
You can't even have a maj
is more for you, isn't it? Joseph Ka is
more for you. chicken ka.
You're not the only one in this
community that could only have a chicken kuma.
I'm not mentioning any names, but
there's more than one person
that could only have a chicken ka. Not
mentioning any names. Yeah. Come on.
Come on. We got loads of cans of Coke in
the fridge, Joe. So, if worse comes to
worse, I'll just, you know, drink a lot
of the Cokes, you know.
What have you preferred, Grezy? A big
arch with chips or a lovely curry with
rice and ticker? I know. I know which
one I'd prefer.
But I kind of figured the site was
dodgy, Joe, because they were doing
anything and everything not to close my account down.
Anything and everything not to close my account down.
which is a bit weird, isn't it? They
wouldn't let me put the puzzle limits on. Scaring [ __ ]
Oh, come on. It's still in progress. I
want to have this bastard curry greasy.
How could you still be working on it? God's sake.
I've just ordered a curry, lad.
I've ordered a I've ordered a lamb foul
instead of a vindaloo this time. So,
this one's hotter. So, we'll see how I
do. I'm going to record it.
Let's see how I do. Let's see if I can take it.
She was my biggest crush.
I know they're hotter than Vindaloo. She
was my biggest crush as an 11year-old
growing boy. Ah, you little copycat. I'm
going to comment.
Hey, you little copycat.
I just commented. You little copycat.
Are you a copycat? Fire stick.
All right. What are you saying, bro?
You're a little copycat.
Well, you don't So you don't
So you don't do stuff to fit in with the crowd?
You don't like to fit in with the crowd, lad? No.
Fair enough, bro.
You're a little copycat, lad. Where's
Chad? Where's Chad?
Fire stick. Where's Chad, lad?
Yeah, people that do that are losers, bro.
Yeah, people used to have celebrity uh
like crushes to fit in. Do you remember
them days? Fire stick
like back in the old like like the
school days and they used to copy each other.
Come on, man. I'm looking forward to this curry.
They used to fit in. Do you remember? Yeah.
>> Are you okay?
>> I don't think Laney's very well.
She's t She's tending to sleep quite a lot.
She's sleep quite sleeping a lot.
Nah, bro. I don't really like drinking that much.
If I drink, I go all out. You know,
there's no I don't have
I don't I go I go all out drinking, if
that makes sense.
No, she's just a bit like I think she's
in pain and stuff.
She's been sleeping all day.
Yeah, I told her to [ __ ] drop dead
yesterday, bro. I was pissed off. I got
scammed and she didn't give a [ __ ]
She didn't give a [ __ ]
Come on, food. I'm bloody starving.
Already found his mama.
Peter belly can't get attached fire
stick because he's already found his mama.
I'll never get over that account.
Greavvesy, he's already found he's mama.
Did I bring it on myself, Grezy? Did I
bring Did I bring them comments on myself?
That's what they were saying, is it?
No, there was an account that said that
that's like Peter Bennett, you can't get
attached anymore. you already found your
mama. I said to I said to her, "Why
didn't you why didn't my why didn't she
tell me that she was my mama and that?"
And they were, "Oh, she wanted to keep
it a secret."
And I said, "Yeah, but what about this
other woman?" She said that he said that
Sig was never your mama.
Sig not Peter Bell's mama.
Do you remember Grezy? Sig not Peter Pelly's mama.
I don't know why that made me laugh. And
it used to come on. And it used to come
on. Yeah. Fire stick and said, "Don't
let them [ __ ] women win. Don't let
them [ __ ] women win."
Yeah. It's funny as [ __ ] bro.
Where the [ __ ] Oh, no. There's another
saying, Grezy. Where the [ __ ] are these
Yeah, I see it, bro. Where the [ __ ] are
these [ __ ] Weepy. Where the [ __ ] are
That's another saying. Yeah.
And that account said I said, "How do
you know about the dates I've been on?"
And the account said, "Grees, do we know
all about Peter Belly's dates?
And and that account said to me, yeah,
that account said to me, that account
said to me, I just got chicken, ticker,
rice, and curry, bro. And the account
also said, yeah, there's a lot of uh
there's a lot of history for Peter Belly
in Elephant and Castle.
I had a one night stand in Elephant and
Castle in it. Um Fire Stick went on for
ages, bro. And then this this account
said there's a lot of history for Peter Belly.
in a castle.
No, I had I got I've got a lamb foul
curry with rice and I got chicken ticker
starter on the on the side, lad. Yeah.
When I put the picture when I put the
picture of the cat up, Grezy, they said
that looks like the virgin [ __ ]
Looks like the virgin [ __ ]
Looks like Where the [ __ ] is this food,
man? This is all It should be here.
Lamb dishes. Foul boiled rice. I don't
know why I got boiled. Boiled. Doesn't matter anyways.
Yeah, you got an Indian the other day in
it, Fire Stick. I wanted to copy
I wanted to kind of copy you.
Don't forget this is a copycat community.
I might put up Christian Izzy's picture.
Greavvesy, is that right?
Is that Is that all right? Is that all
right with you, boss?
No, I wouldn't do that, bro.
No, you're not seeing her, lad. Sorry.
Cuz people do reverse image and there's
a and there's a chance they would find her. So,
we can't do that, lad. Sorry. Too many
freaks on this community.
Come on. I'm starving,
Grezy. I'm absolutely starving.
Where the [ __ ] is this Curry, man?
Why did you see Monty's video? He's on
tag fire stick. Did you see his live
stream? He was showing his tag.
I wonder if I'll ever be put on tag. Nah,
they might try and do me for all of the
things I said. I had to go to the police
station a cut like two months ago, maybe
a month and a half, two months ago. But
they'll probably just NFA it.
But he said he got put on tag more for
the racism. Nah, I don't think so, bro.
It's got to be more to do with the
rights than the racism. I would have thought
maybe they might try to take me to
court, but I doubt it.
I doubt it, bro.
The amount of times I've been nicked and
they just let you get away with it. You
say mad stuff
so many times they just they just NFA
you after like 6 months.
But no, that tag would have definitely
been because of the riots, isn't it? Yeah.
[ __ ] doing community service though.
That is long, bro. Imagine that. Doing
community service. [ __ ] that.
At least with a fine. Yeah.
At least with a fine, you can sort of
just pay it. You know what I mean? Yeah.
Baby, come on. Come on.
I always get excited when the food arrives. Grezy,
what about you?
So, when I do the video, when I do the
video of the curry, LJ is not going to
see it in it, Breezy.
They're not all going to go on the
video, are they?
If I get defeated, I get defeated, bro.
But I'm pretty confident I can take this curry.
See you later, Virgin. you.
[ __ ] no, lad.
I just farted.
What do you think of my dating video?
Fire stick. I was pretty spot on in it, lad.
I was pretty spot on, wasn't I? pretty much
my friend wanted me to do one. I had
done one for a long time, so I thought, [ __ ] it.
Right. Where's his food? Come on.
It's got some They've got something new in KFC.
They got some new stuff in KFC. Grievy.
Cheesy melt. Cheesy melt burger.
What the hell is Bells?
I'll have to try that at some point.
Oh, there's so many simps though. In it,
Fire Stick, there's so many white
lights, lad. There's so many simps.
Yeah, I'll put the link up now, bro. One sec.
No. So, what you're saying is if I get
it, I'm a copycat.
So if I have it, I'm a copycat.
Still saying it's in progress. It can't be.
Can't be still in progress, bro.
I'm so hungry. It's going down to my
ass. My belly is rumbling, bro. Come on. You [ __ ]
Certain virgins weren't there, mate.
Certain virgins went there. I know two virgins,
LJ and Nlegs, weren't there.
wouldn't [ __ ] dare.
No, their anxiety and their taste buds
wouldn't allow it. Oh, bless.
>> All right, can I get How much did your
Indian come to? Uh 24.
>> Oh, that's weird. Mom was 23 the other day.
>> Yeah, I'm a copycat, bro. I copy you. It
>> always like a bit of chicken ticker on
the side, you know.
>> Yeah, it's nice. I know what you mean
about them copy people, though. Weirdos.
>> What do you mean?
>> I know what you mean. From years ago,
the people in school and that copying
people to try and be clever.
>> Yeah. What What do they do? Do you
remember all the Do you remember all the
trends on that?
>> Yeah, like pretending they're like the
same stuff on that.
>> Yeah, that was a thing back in the year
like football and that and celebrities in it.
>> I don't I can literally [ __ ] close my
eyes now and see especially one person
sitting there like pretending he really
likes football talking about football
and they don't know who's talking about.
>> Yeah, they used they used to pretend
that like celebrities were fitting it. >> Yeah,
>> they done it with bro. They used to go
on about that Rihanna all the time, bro.
Do you not remember?
>> Rihanna's quite sexy. Look.
>> Yeah, but like but they would What I'm
saying is they like they put them on
pedestals and that.
>> Yeah, I know. Put the [ __ ] on a pedestal,
>> you know. But then they used to say that
if you didn't like Beyonce, you was gay.
That I remember that. Is it? You remember that? >> Yeah.
>> Yeah. Years ago. Yeah. Yeah. They used
to copy each other in it.
>> I think Bianca's better than um Beyonce.
>> No. Would you think they actually did it
to fit in though? Yeah,
>> of course they did.
>> Yeah, bro. What you What are you eating today, man?
>> I don't know. I can't decide.
>> Have a uh Chinese, bro. Or some grilled
chicken? I had some grilled chicken the
other day, bro.
>> Yeah. What is it you had yesterday? I
never see what you had yesterday.
>> I had Brazilian, bro.
>> What was that like?
>> Lovely, bro. So they they carve it in
front of you. I went to the restaurant.
They like lamb gaming. Oh, ask Greasy. I
sent him like the videos. It was [ __ ] banging, bro.
>> I bet that was 50 quid, wasn't it? Just for you.
>> No, £24, bro. Cheap.
>> That's good.
>> And and and you can sit there and eat
all you want for 4 hours. I think you
can stay there for 4 hours. But
obviously I was stuffed after like 30
minutes, bro. I was stuffed, bro.
>> As he give you diamond diamond the only
meat they didn't have was turkey, but
who cares it? as he give you like upset
your stomach though and give you diarrhea.
>> No, not at all.
>> Oh, the order's on its way. Oh, I can't wait.
>> Oh, I'm going to record this curry, bro.
I want to see if I can take it. Do you
reckon I'll be able to take it?
>> I've tried it. It's unbearable.
>> It's unbearable,
bro. That was unbearable.
>> Try that next time. Try that. Try that
next time, bro. Try that next time. I've
not had that, but I've had a chicken
foul when I That was when I was in the
restaurant years ago and I had to swap
it. I said that she I said that [ __ ]
I was having a panic attack in the
toilet. My throat like swelling up.
>> No, no. I actually No, this is actually
my third time. No, no, no. I had it
during CO. No, no, I did. No, I actually
did have it during CO. >> Actually,
it was too hot. It was too hot for me
then, but then I tried it a few months
ago. It wasn't too hot for me. And
obviously now we're seeing it. It's
ridiculous. It's like it's mental how
hot it is. >> Yeah.
>> Honestly, I was in the toilet like
bending over being sick while I was
crying at the same time. I had like two
pack [ __ ] fell.
>> Yeah. I had two packies there like
speaking half English, half Indian
asking, "Do I want an ambulance?" All that [ __ ]
>> Well, it was that bad.
>> Yeah. Honestly,
>> that's how I was like that's how I was
like with a Carolina Reaper burger and I
was being sick, bro. I was I thought I
was going to die. I thought I was going >> Yeah,
>> I want to try that. Where is that from?
>> Slims chicken. Dave chicken. The Slims Chicken.
>> Yeah, I've had Slims Chicken. I've not
had that burger. Is it actually that hot?
>> Yeah, it's Yes, it is that hot, bro.
It's the world's the world's hottest
burger. It's the world's hottest burger.
>> In your opinion, is there no human who
can just sit there and just munch the
whole thing? I don't know how people do
it. I I I could, bro. I had like I think
I had about three bites.
>> That was nah.
>> How much was it?
>> I can't remember, bro. To be there's
one, you know, you know, uh square, you
know, you know, off Leicester Square.
You know, off China Chinatown, there's one. >> Yeah.
>> Yeah. There's one there. There's one in Liverpool Street.
>> We'll do Let's meet up and do Let's do
Let's meet up and do the challenge
together and we put it on YouTube.
>> Yeah. You know the [ __ ] you know um
you know as you leave Chinatown and uh
start heading towards like um solo. Yeah.
>> Have you been in that massive Lego shop
there? It's like [ __ ] huge.
>> No, I know what you're talking about though.
>> It's not You mean you mean opposite You
mean opposite Eminem World, isn't it?
>> Yeah, near I was just going to say it's
near Eminem World. And there's a casino
there as well.
>> Yeah. No, I know what it is, but I ain't
been inside it. It's always busy as
well. It's always taps. Yeah. Yeah. And
the queue's always coming outside, isn't it?
>> Yeah. No, I've not been there. I know
what it is, though.
>> Well, do you know that Weather Spoons in
in Leicester Square? It's good. You
know, the Weather Spoons.
>> I've never been to that one.
>> No, but you know, Have you seen it though? It
>> bro, you've been gambling today, is it? >> Nah. >> No.
>> Oh, nothing.
>> Nah, nothing.
>> Oh, yeah. Good.
>> No. What do you think of that slow let
me down yesterday? The [ __ ] man.
>> I thought I thought they might have just
nicked one right at the end.
>> That's what I thought. [ __ ] bastards.
>> What a waste. What a waste. You [ __ ]
>> What did you order from Uber Eats?
>> Um, no. I'm not going to say which one,
bro. Cuz you know what these people like
on it and it they try to like cancel
ring up it and say, "Oh, it's Peter."
And tell weird things.
>> Yeah. Yeah, I had I I used to use Just
Eat, but now I use a different one. >> Yeah.
>> What do you use? What do you use? You can say
>> I'm banned. I'm banned from Uber and
Just Eat from like keep getting bare refunds.
>> So, what do you use now then? >> Deliveroo. >> Yeah.
What was your favorite one? I used to
like Just Eat because I was used to it. Like,
>> have you ever seen that London Eats on YouTube?
>> Yep. I've had
>> and I've seen and I've seen um the other
one as well, London Hustle. Yeah.
>> Oh, I ain't seen him. I've had London
Esk deliver a couple of times.
>> Well, you've had him delivered to you.
>> Yeah, twice. >> Really? >> Yeah.
>> Yeah. He's from South. He's from South
as well. Yeah. Yeah. I know who he is,
bro. The guy that lives food.
>> But uh Yeah. There's one called London
Hustle and he's sim he's similar. It's
like a similar It's what I'm saying. You get me,
>> bro. I was chatting to London Eats the
second time he came here. He said to me
about that job. That's not his main job.
Yeah, that's just a side hustle he does. He said
>> he said that he said you cannot earn
enough money to for that to be a main
job. He said it's too hard. He said it's [ __ ] brutal.
>> I've done it. I've done it. So I know
done it, bro.
>> Yeah. During the summer last summer, I
was I done Uber, bro. And bro, the next
day you're [ __ ] Like your arms, your
eyes are hanging out your head. I worked
for like 10 hours and I couldn't do it.
>> Do it once. I couldn't do it every day.
I couldn't do I couldn't do it every
day. I was too [ __ ]
>> That's what he said to me. you can only
do like a 3 or 4 hour shift because
anything over there he said you're
aching and you feel like you just [ __ ] dying.
>> Yeah, it's a lot of energy. And I was
using and this was an ebike and an
electric bike and it doesn't matter cuz
you're still And you know what happened,
bro? Yeah. My hands were swollen, you
know, from like grabbing the bike
because I didn't wear gloves. Your my
>> But they went sore in it.
>> Yeah. For like two weeks, bro. And then
it went. But still.
>> Did he say it's worth doing it, though?
Um, not really. Basically, he said no,
don't do it. >> Yeah.
>> He said it's he said it's all right for
a side hustle. He said he said to me he
normally tries to get around 50 quid
then he goes home. But he said he said
he don't know how he said he don't know
how people do that as a main job. He
said because he just [ __ ] ruins.
>> Sometimes bro sometimes it's hard
because I remember I worked one Sunday.
I worked on a Sunday bro and it took me
about eight hours to make 50 quid. 8 hours, bro.
>> Yeah, [ __ ] that. That's [ __ ]
>> It depends. But obviously, but then but
then one day I made 90 in like 8 hours. 90.
>> Yeah. Yeah. 90 is all right. [ __ ]
>> It depends. It depends. But you want to
do But the thing is, every time I do it
on Saturday, bro, most of the times I do
it on Saturday, this is what happened.
They were doing something with like um
what's it called? You know, gay pride
and stuff, right? And and and what was
it called? Something to do with the
Palestine [ __ ] So they'd block, you
know, you know that road. there that um
uh Kala Square that goes up to West Minister.
>> Yeah, that's where people always protest.
>> Yeah. And then once they protest, they
block that and then that's 90% of all is
blocked because going through there goes
to mainland where mostly where I got the
orders. So if they block that road, you
can't work basically. Does that make sense?
>> You're [ __ ] You're [ __ ] in it.
>> You're basically [ __ ] Yeah. And it
used to happen most Saturdays.
>> What was all them weirdos protesting
about all that Palestine [ __ ]
>> Yeah. Yeah.
>> [ __ ] hell.
>> Do you remember? Do you remember what
the policeman said? I I tried. He said,
"Oh, you can't ride." I said, "I've got
delivery. I've got delivery." He said,
"Oh, can't you tell the customer to come
and get it?" I was like, "Well, no,
because the the customer is 10 minutes away."
>> Yeah. I said, "The customer is 10
minutes away." I just looked at him
thinking, "If your rider or driver
contacted you right now and said, "Meet
me 15 minutes away." Would you obviously
you'd say, "Fuck off, wouldn't you?"
>> Yeah. And I said, "Oh, I said, can I
walk with a bike?" They weren't having
it at all, bro.
>> Well, and he was on an order as well.
>> Yeah. On an order. They didn't care. It
was packed. But yeah, that's the only
way that's the only place you'll make
money doing that is central. I used to
just go to like the garage, rent the
bike, and then just go all over. That's
the only place you'll make money.
>> How much was it to rent the bike?
>> £13 a day. >> Yeah.
>> So, you made that in like two, three
orders, isn't it? >> Yeah.
>> But it was good though cuz you go all
around London. I've done it in the
summer. Yeah. You got to see like a lot
of like places. It was It was fun.
>> Yeah. Did you Is there Is it Was you Is
that when you was doing that? Is that
when you went over Tower Bridge on the
bike on the video? >> Yeah.
>> Yeah, I've seen that video.
>> Sick views in it, bro. Sick views. Oh.
>> Would you do it?
>> Not now. I've been diagnosed with TMAU.
>> No, you haven't, bro.
>> I have. One day I smell [ __ ] One day I
smell fish. Some people smell it, some
people can't. It's understood. And now
you're taking the piss, bro.
Yeah, I know.
>> What is it? He says,
>> "Have you Have you actually got Have you
got any condition? Have you actually got
any medical conditions?"
>> Uh, no. I ain't.
>> No, I don't either.
>> Not [ __ ] mad. I'm [ __ ] mad, but
physically I ain't I'm not
>> Everybody knows that you're a crazy [ __ ]
>> PJ PJ, what is it? He says, "I was
diagnosed with TMAU in 2005 by Sheffield University."
>> I don't even I didn't even watch him,
bro. I didn't even watch him.
>> He used to He used to give you shout outs sometimes.
>> Who's slow? Steven Howard. Who's slow?
>> Um Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. I know. But I've
never watched him like Greasy, so I I've
missed a lot of stuff, bro.
>> That's it. If I didn't know, I'd have
worked all my life. That's what he
always says, isn't it?
>> Yeah. Yeah. I remember that. I remember.
Do you remember when he was going mad
and he said, "I want you. You're getting
a [ __ ] lot. What you did to me?" Do
you remember? Remember?
>> Oh, yeah. That was so funny, wasn't it?
You think you're off the [ __ ] hook?
>> Yeah. What you done to me? Yeah.
>> Do you remember that Greg Z? And he
chucks. He's listening to
>> Yeah. People People used to say that he
was a troll.
>> Steven Howard Pip King. Yeah. He's slow.
I ain't slow, you [ __ ] You're called Pip King.
>> Hey, listen. Listen. Yeah. [ __ ] But
you know the thing is I don't
understand. Fire stick. People say that
I'm a troll.
>> Yeah. Someone was saying it earlier.
>> I'm not a troll, bro. Do you think I'm a troll?
>> I don't know. I don't know if you've got
troll accounts. I wouldn't know.
>> No, no, no, no. I've only got two accounts, bro.
>> To be fair, you stream a lot, so if you
was trolling, you would be streaming all the time.
>> Yeah, exactly. Grezy,
I'm not a troll at all. [ __ ] No.
>> See M
used to shout you out sometimes.
>> Yeah, man.
>> You going you going for a drink
Saturday? You going for a drink
>> No, I'm doing the same as you. I might
just go once a month. So, you appreciate
it's boring, isn't it? It's boring.
>> And once older, as you get to when you
get to out like when you're 23, 24, you
do twice a week or once a week or
whatever. But no, no.
>> Some someone earlier on said to you,
"Oh, why don't you have a few cobras
with your [ __ ] few cobras with your
curry?" That's a [ __ ] That's a Timmy move.
>> Nah, bro. I like to go on a nice detox
and then go all out, bro.
>> You know what you you know what you just
said earlier on about drinking cans of
beer or drink a can of Stella out the
can. It tastes [ __ ] vile.
>> Disgusting, bro. And it lingers. It
lingers. You just smell lingers, bro. On
the bus. They were drinking it in it. And it
>> even even like a non-alcohol drink. Even
Even a a bottle of Coke is better than a
can of Coke in my opinion. >> Yeah.
>> Yeah, it is. It is. Well, 100% it is.
>> Yeah. I don't know why. I just cans are horrible.
>> You're talking about the glass bottles
in it. Yeah.
>> Yeah. The glass bottles. Yeah.
>> The only good thing with No. No. But the
only good thing with a can coke the can
of Cokes is they don't go they don't go
off. Whereas the bottles do. Like in
like a plastic bottle they do, but the cans don't.
>> Yeah. In the plastic bottle they go
flat. Yeah. In the can.
>> Yeah. Flat. Yeah. That's what Yeah. You
love Red Bulls, isn't it?
>> Never had it in my life.
>> You must have tried it. >> Never.
>> Everyone's tried Red Bull.
>> I haven't, brother. I swear to God I
haven't. On my mom's life, I haven't.
>> Have you drunk Monster? You must have tried Monster.
>> I've drunk Monster, but I've not drunk
Red Bull. All you know what? When you go
to McDonald's yet, what's your favorite
milkshake if you get a milkshake? Mine's banana.
>> Oh my god. I was just going to say
banana. I don't like chocolate or
strawberry and vanilla's too.
>> Yeah, chocolate's too bitter.
Chocolate's too bitter, isn't it?
>> Yeah. Vanilla's boring. Strawberry [ __ ]
>> Five Guys milkshake. Do you know the
peanut butter milkshake? Five Guys. It's
so good. Oh my god.
>> Oh, I don't. You make me I really want
one of them right now.
>> They're nice, isn't it? They're nice and
thick and lovely.
>> Yeah, probably nice. Expensive, aren't they?
>> Yeah, they're 645.
>> Yeah, but what do you know I think with
things like that? Yeah, I can go and get
a milkshake I can go and get a milkshake
from the pack shop for a pound. Yeah,
but in my eyes 645 that's just free
spins on the roulette while I'd lose in 2 seconds.
>> How? Yeah, true.
>> What did you call it? A packing shop.
You're mad [ __ ] You are. You're a mad
>> So, when you go out drinking, are you
going to approach?
>> Uh, no. Probably not. I just get smashed straight away. >> Yeah.
>> Yeah. Funny, bro.
>> Where's Monty? Monty's been quiet.
>> Did you see his live streaming? He was
put on tag.
>> No. Did he live stream?
>> He went live earlier showing he's tagging it.
>> I knew he was going to do that.
>> Well, yeah. Hold on. I'll be back in a minute.
>> All right, Captain.
Right with you, [ __ ] I'm looking
forward for my to my dinner. Grezy,
what was he saying, bro? This guy on the
panel that people used to try to fit in at school. Copy him.
Copying, isn't it?
Yeah. Copying, isn't it? Uh,
they were laughing at you, mocking you.
mocking you. Oh,
I'm [ __ ] starving. I'm going to have
these bastard cornflakes.
Remember that one, Grezy?
Wakey wakey. Where are you bastards?
C. Time to get up,
aren't you? You flying master [ __ ] [ __ ]
off, Jeffrey. I'm going to [ __ ] kick
you in the bollocks. Up, down, up.
Smelly up, [ __ ] Yeah, you ain't been
[ __ ] I heard you lot last night
wanking in that [ __ ] bed. Funny, bro.
Oh, it's here. It's here. It's here.
Oh, we left it outside. Here we go, lads.
Right. I'm going to record this. Yeah.
I'll be back.