Sorry about that, bro. nothing bro
is that to restart we start the stream
is not coming to London same [ __ ] with him
yeah same [ __ ] with
2026 and Timmy's still being a [ __ ]
2026 and he's still a [ __ ] Absolute [ __ ]
launch legs got six thumbs up and he
called me a virgin. That's interesting.
That's actually quite funny to be
honest. That actually kind of made me laugh.
That's funny. I got called a virgin and
I got and it got six thumbs up on the
same channel that got that got banned for pornography. [ __ ] retards.
Yeah, but they they beat you at the
money game, haven't they? Yeah. Yeah.
Okay, bro. Yeah, cool sh, man.
So, this is what's going to happen with
Timmy now, bro. Every time he does his
balls in, he's going to start self projecting.
Huh? I got called a virgin and got six thumbs up.
That's funny, bro. Being called a virgin
even though I proved I've had sex.
Similar to the money game, isn't it?
Yeah, that sounds similar to the money
game, doesn't it?
Yeah, you will never win with these
jealous little losers on here. You'll
never ever ever ever win with them.
Never ever ever ever ever ever win with
them. If you try meeting them, if you
show more money them, if you prove
you've had sex, if you show you're
better looking than them, you never ever
win with them. these people
take a leaf out of my book.
But do you know what? They're so stupid
that it actually it does become like a dictim
trying to say that when I showed money
it never counted cuz it was ages ago.
It's funny as [ __ ] bro. It is to be
fair. It's actually funny. Ah,
isn't that so funny, bro? It doesn't
count because it was ages ago. So now
that if some if people take L's
ages ago, it doesn't count now. So now
they've made up a new rule, Dusty, that
if if if um if someone takes an L ages
ago, it doesn't count.
It doesn't count now all of a sudden.
So half the community took an L when I
beat them at the money game, but it
doesn't count because it was ages ago. Oh, right.
It's okay for them to show you money
from 10 years ago. Oh, okay.
That's a new that's a new bias rule. [ __ ] [ __ ] Absolute [ __ ] Yeah. So, yeah.
So, he's not coming to London.
But don't think that you're going to
start mentioning my name and I'm going
to get mad. Nonsense mentions my name
every day cuz he's an upset little virgin.
Um but you know
um that's not going to annoy me. Even if
he does videos, that's not going to
annoy me. It's just what Timmy was doing. Yeah.
Yo, this week. Oh. Oh, so now it's this
week then. Oh, so it's not today. Oh.
Oh, it's not today then. I mean, can't
you just get a train?
Can't you just get a train?
I mean, you can just get a train. It's
about an hour and 20 minutes.
I'll meet you wherever you want in
London. Well, what excuse do you have?
You say that you travel all over the
country for gambling. You go to Wales.
You go to Bristol and all of these
places. But why can't you travel an hour
and 20 minutes on the fast train to
London? London, Houston, as you call it. London, Houston.
He calls it London Houston.
>> London Houston. Do you remember that, Dusty?
>> Why do you get a train to London to Houston?
>> Peter. Peter, why won't you come to
Birmingham today? You're the one.
>> Because you said that you're Because the
plan was you was going to come to London.
>> No, no, no. Peter, I will be coming to London.
>> You said that you was coming to London.
Get a train to London
>> and the underground which takes 4 and
1/2 hours to get to your
>> What happened the last time Jimmy come
to my What happened the last time Jimmy
come to my door? He ran away.
>> Get a lift to your mom.
>> He let Tiger fight his battles and he
ran away and he ran away. He ran away
and I will go live at mommy's like
he ran away.
>> Explain to you poor mom. Why you trying
to think you're all hard on YouTube?
>> He ran away.
>> He ran away from me. It's I've got the
extra on my chat. You ran away from
>> Anyways, [ __ ] all of that. Just come to London today.
>> Prime in a minute. You come to London today.
>> You haven't hit no one, Peter.
>> Come to London today.
>> Come to London today. It's a shame you
stick around when the police turned up
cuz you would have been arrested.
>> Yeah. Yeah. Okay. Come to London today then.
>> So, so all right. So, let's talk about
this. You make out your hard. Why have
you J the hammer?
>> Right. No,
>> one second. You said one sec. One sec.
One second. One second. Uh, we can't
talk about the past. Uh, people on this channel.
>> No, no, no, no, no. You make your heart, PJ.
>> No, no. One second. Let me Let me kick
this bastic a second cuz he's not
letting me talk. Uh, we're not talking
about the past because it was ages ago
and it doesn't count. Just like when all
of you people got beat at the money
game, because it was one money and it
was ages ago, it doesn't count. So,
we're not talking about that. That doesn't count.
So, yeah, remember the past doesn't
count. things like ages ago don't count.
Like when you people got beat at a money
game and never counted because it was
ages ago. Okay. Well, that's ages ago,
so that doesn't count. So, we're playing
we'll play by your rules. There you go.
You get the link again.
There you go. The link again.
It doesn't count. It was ages ago.
Yeah. Yeah. No. The truth. Yeah. Yeah.
Yeah. The truth. Yeah. Yeah, yeah, yeah,
yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah. So,
you're not coming to London today. So,
you've started [ __ ] again on YouTube,
but you're not meeting anyone. [ __ ]
Absolute [ __ ] You won't even jump on
a train for an hour and 20 minutes.
Yeah, the past doesn't count. Yeah,
remember. Remember, because these people
got beat at the money game ages ago, it
never counted, did it? So, this doesn't
count. Nothing counts. There's no crime.
There's no nothing. If that's the way
you want to work it, that's the way you
want to say it. Yeah, that that's fine.
5.7 grand years ago never count so
nothing else count. We'll play you at
your game then. Yeah.
>> How about that?
>> So So why you at Lord J the Hammer now?
I don't know what you're talking about
[ __ ] He should have stayed around and
got you arrested.
>> I don't know what
>> and put inside for being a nons.
>> I don't know what you're talking about.
>> We know what I'm talking about. When
Lord Jay comes to yours and your mom
shattered that much because your I don't
know what you're on about son that she
had to press the panic alarm.
>> I don't know. I don't know what you're on about.
>> All on [ __ ] Vinnie videos. It's all
>> Get yourself a pick a mix. Get yourself
>> Stop making
what you're talking about.
>> Remember things ages ago don't count that you
>> things are ages ago don't count because
you are a fanny. Things that are ages
ago don't count your own [ __ ] mother.
>> Things not ages ago don't count.
>> [ __ ] embarrassment.
>> Things not ages ago don't count. Do you remember?
>> It was ages ago don't count. So that
makes it okay that you're a fatty.
>> Oh, but when I beat But when I beat you
people in the money game, you could use
the ages ago excuse. Oh. Oh. Oh. So it's
okay for you to use it as an excuse
about me going about the past. You're
>> when I showed thousands and you ran
away. That that doesn't count then, does it?
That could be ages ago.
>> I'll go back. I'll go to the bank in a
minute to show you more.
>> No, [ __ ] that. That's not fair.
You see the bias, Dusty? He's saying
that things that are ages ago count. But
then when they got beat at the money
game, oh, it's ages ago. It don't count.
You see? You see, they're contradicting
themselves now. You see, they're
contradicting themselves what they're
saying. When they got beat at the money
game, oh, it was ages ago. Oh, it was
ages ago, bro. But then when he's
talking about other stuff, he's talking
about years ago stuff, bro. Make up your
mind. Which one is it? Is it ages ago or
does ages ago count or does it not?
Someone in the chat tell me.
Does it does it count? Does things that
happened ages ago count or does it not?
I mean, it's one or the other. Seems to
count when it suits you, but other times
it doesn't. Like when you got beat at
the money game.
But then when you show four, five, six
year old videos of [ __ ] money that
you don't have now. Oh, I got beat at
the money game. I got beat in a money
game. I got beat in the money game. Oh,
so it doesn't count then. So it doesn't count.
Oh, so it doesn't count then. So it it
does count or it doesn't count
because when you've been told about you
losing the money game multiple times,
your the first excuse you go, "Oh, it
was ages ago. Oh, it was ages ago."
So when I if I go on Lord Jes later,
you're not going to be talking about
Prime. You're not going to be talking about um
anything. You're not going to be talking
about anything that was ages ago. No.
Okay, we'll see today then. Okay, we'll
see today. I don't want to hear any past
mentioned on L's today. I'm going to nip
and we'll see. Simple.
So it's when it suits yourselves
basically. Yeah. [ __ ] retards. Can't
remember these people in this disabled community.
Can't remember these people on this disabled community.
I am burning in the next hour. I might
be able to live month. What? See it?
Proper [ __ ] community in it.
Proper proper [ __ ] community in it.
>> Oh, you coming to London?
>> Deal. I've got to go meet Winchester
this Thursday in Sutton Coldfield.
Guarantee you he's bluff again. Right.
>> No. Come to London today. Chester. He's
not going to turn up Thursday. And
London owns me and all this. I don't
count this as PJ. I come to London today
coming to your mom's and humiliating you.
>> Yeah. Yeah. Come and do it.
>> Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Come and do it.
>> I'm not like whiff rats. I'm not like
okay then I know today on bangers come
today then bangers. Ginger [ __ ]
then even know what a fight is.
>> Okay. So come today then. You are you
are a lefty.
>> Okay. Well come today then.
>> Right wing. Right.
>> Yes. Let's get to the point. Right.
Let's get to the [ __ ] point. PJ.
Yeah. Let's get to the point. Right.
>> Right. Come to London today.
>> Let's answer my question. My Somebody
come to my mom's door. I would have used the hammer.
>> Come to You're trying to deflect now. Okay.
Your [ __ ] mother.
>> You're deflecting defending when you're
coming. Come to London today. When
>> come to London today. You mentioned my
name. You can't keep my name out of your
mouth. So come to London like you said
you was going to.
>> When he [ __ ] robbed your [ __ ]
>> Come to London like you said you was
going to. 500 quid.
going to. Stop deflecting. Stop bringing
up other people. You mentioned my name.
I messaged your family. So come to
London. Stop. I'm [ __ ] deflecting.
How hard [ __ ] pathetic Dusty who
doesn't even know what day of the
[ __ ] week it is. Doesn't even know
the meaning of the word nons. Right.
Let's let's do this people.
>> Okay. So, are you coming to London today or not?
>> You come to me cuz I want to see how
>> are you coming to London today? Yes or
no? I will be coming to you, Peter. But
>> are you coming today? Yes or no?
>> See how much of a man you are?
>> Okay. Are you coming? Yes or no?
>> I want you to prove to your loyal.
>> Are you coming today? Yes or no?
>> And dusty.
>> Yes or no? Are you coming to Birmingham
or do you want me to humiliate your
mom's? The choice.
>> Are you coming to London today or not? PJ,
>> see you later. Bye-bye. And there you
go. You get kicked. See, he just goes
round and round in circles trying to
bring other people up, trying to
deflect, and you just get kicked. Simple
as that. And you just get kicked. Uh,
you get kicked, lad.
And you just get kicked. Simple as that.
Lovely. I asked you the same thing about
[ __ ] god knows how many times
and you just ignored it. Talking about
LJ and all of this and all of that.
Another one that can start [ __ ] they can't finish. Dusty [ __ ] spastnic.
Now I have to go to Birmingham.
And now I have to go to Birmingham.
When you said that you was coming to
London, you said that I'm skin. I don't
have 20 pound. Okay. come to London then?
You said that you was going to come to
London and you said I'm skin. How can
you expect me to go to Birmingham when
you're calling me skin? You seem to know
everything about me. You said that I
don't have £20. Okay, I don't have £20,
bro. I'm skin. I've got nothing
according to you.
So why are you telling people to go to
[ __ ] Birmingham when you're telling
people that they're skin? Make up your mind, lad.
Be's getting some goodies. I'll be going
cinema on Thursday to watch the new Scream.
I'll be getting a lot of goodies. Yeah.
And some popcorn as well.
He said I'm skin and he's telling me to
go to Birmingham.
But he said that I'm skin. If I'm skinn,
why are you asking a skin person to go
to Birmingham? Make it make sense.
Yeah, it can be halfway all at once.
Milton Kees can be halfway all at once.
I'm not bothered. He said that he's
coming to London. End of. He said that
I'm skin and he said that he's coming to
London. End of.
Milton Kees can stay halfway. It can
stay halfway all at once. You don't need
to tell me where's halfway, lad. I've
been all over the country. Sure. I know
exactly where it is. Yeah.
Same [ __ ] with you little people. When
are you going to get off of YouTube and
get yourselves a life? Get a life for yourselves.
Get a little life for yourselves, lad.
Yeah, I'm good, bro. Just argue with this [ __ ]
Don't ask me why.
Right. One sec.
Oh, why do you keep kicking me out the
hangout? You big baby.
>> Cuz I asked you a question. You keep
avoiding it. Are you coming to London today?
>> I have said I will be at yours. You've
got two choices. Today, Thursday, or
I'll come to mommy's
>> today. Today. Come today.
>> No, no, no. So, you you're going to make
>> Yes. Yes. Yes. Yes. Yes. Come today.
Come today. money game and you've got
all no no you said that you're coming to London
>> card you said that you're coming to London
>> and I will beat you up
>> you said that you're coming to London
out you're the hardest man on YouTube
you're not coming to London then your
own [ __ ] mom yeah I haven't beaten
Peter but at least I've had a beat so
you're not coming to London today then like you
>> so you're not coming every fight
>> so you're not coming today no no
>> see you later bye-bye you get kicked lad
See, you get kicked. See, he's trying to
deflect again and change the subject. He
does this all the time. He said, "I've
got a choice. Today, tomorrow, or
Thursday? Today, please. Today works perfect." Yeah,
today works perfect.
Yeah, today's today works perfect.
Boozy. Yeah. Today, please. >> Yeah.
>> Yeah. Come today, please. I had a good
conversation with your sister last
night, which I've got the evidence I can put up. >> Yeah.
Cuz your sister said, "Please don't do
it to your mom."
>> Yeah. Yeah. DJ, stop. [ __ ]
>> You're the one that's You're addicted to
gambling. I'm not addicted to gambling.
That's you. to your sister. She hates
>> I'm not addicted. You're the one that
gambles every day. You skin mess. You
can't even You don't even have the money
to come to London.
>> That's how much she hates you.
>> Everything you say is projection. Virgin
you. Skint you.
>> You're a virgin. You're skint. You're a
gambling addict. You're the biggest
virgin going like your boyfriend.
>> You're You're a virgin like your
boyfriend nods legs. Like your skin
boyfriends legs. Ain't got no couple of
quids to your names. I know you don't
like that. I know you don't like it.
You're just like your virgin nle skint
boyfriend. You're both as [ __ ] Go and
show your benefits when you get some
money like him. Bro, bro, when you get
your benefits again, go and show don't
show your monthly benefit like nods
legs. Go and show your monthly skin
peanut money again.
>> You know me, Peter. It will happen.
>> Go on, bro. You think before
>> Well, come today then. Well, come today, Peter.
>> Come today, big man. You said that
you're coming today.
>> For your sister and
>> No, no, no.
No, no, no. Stop being a [ __ ] and come
today, big man. Big man, come today. You
said you was coming.
>> Mr. Big Man, come today. Come on.
>> And not get home tonight. It doesn't work.
>> See you later. You get kicked. Excuses
upon excuses upon excuses. Do you know
what someone needs to do with this [ __ ]
Yeah. They need to go around Birmingham
and just put up posters of him. That's
what one of you people need to do in
this community. Yeah. Just do the Just
do the old poster trick like what I done
to Nods Legs. That will teach the [ __ ]
You know what? If anyone knows where
this guy lives, just just put up
posters. That's what you need to do.
That will teach the [ __ ] [ __ ] That
will teach him Greavvesy. Yeah.
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. We're not
letting him in now until he shows that
he's coming to London. We're not letting
him in. We're not letting him in. We're
not letting him in until we until he
shows that he's coming. Right. He's he's
he's not coming in. He's not coming in the hangouts.
Right. Nope. You're kicked. See you later.
Yeah. Simple. You're kicked.
You're kicked, lad.
Yep. We'll wait.
We'll wait, lad. We'll wait.
We will wait, lad. We'll wait.
Yeah, we'll wait.
We'll wait. Greasy,
you you wait. Yes.
Yes, until he comes to London.
Yeah, until he comes to London. Oh gosh.
Do you like it when I say that Grezy? Oh gosh.
>> You don't come and meet me today, PJ? You finished?
>> So, you're coming to London? Yeah.
>> No, no, no. You're coming to Birmingham
when you finish. I don't give a [ __ ] about D.
>> See what I mean? See what I mean? See
what I mean? PJ, you know I will come to your
>> Greasy. Do you think Monty's watching this community?
Greasy, do you think Monty's watching
this? Why? Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Why
you doing a fake laugh, Peter? Why you
doing a fake laugh? Peter, do you know
if I get
>> would be at your door, Peter? You know
I'd be at your door and it will happen.
Peter, I don't give a [ __ ] about you.
>> You're not going anywhere.
>> You're not going anywhere. Peter, the
address is on [ __ ] BS. I've got it
with down the
down the drive, Peter.
>> You're not going anywhere. Shut up. I'm
not you're going to happen Peter say
Peter is you were finished. You ran away
from me. You Lord Jake owns you.
>> No one's ever run away from you. Byebye now.
>> See he's deflecting again. What he's
doing he's deflecting. He's trying to
get into a new argument Greavvesy so he
doesn't have to come.
>> You know and he's talking about stuff
that happened ages ago. Remember stuff
that happened ages ago don't count. Apparently
you got beaten at the money game. That
never counted cuz it was ages ago. So
that doesn't count. Simple. That doesn't
count then. That don't count. Yeah.
Oh, do you remember when Monty met Timmy Greavvesy?
Do you remember?
That was funny, isn't it? Both [ __ ]
bro. None of them could [ __ ] fight.
None of them can fight.
No. Do you want to go? Do you want to go
for a drink or do you want to do it dirty, Grezy?
I'm drinking a I'm drinking a Coke from McDonald's.
Do you want to go around? Do you want to
go for a drink or do you want to do it dirty, Grezy?
Or do you want to do it dirty? Huh?
>> Your sister says, "Are you on your way to London?"
>> Selfish monster putting your mom through the military.
>> Ugly. Have you seen you today?
>> Have you seen you you virgin? Peter and
you will see. Have you seen you? You virgin. >> Police.
>> Have you seen you? You virgin.
>> Yeah. Peter, I don't give a [ __ ] about you.
>> Timmy, you're a virgin. Just like nonsense.
>> Told your mom.
>> You're both You're both virgins.
>> Anyway, are you coming to London anyway?
>> Peter, you're going to be
>> Are you coming to London,
>> Peter? I'm trying to organize a lift. Do
you think I'm just going to come on a
train 4 and a half hours and then go
home again? No.
>> It's not 4 and a half hours, you [ __ ]
[ __ ] It's about It's not even 2
hours, you stupid idiot. and a half hours.
>> 4 and a half hours. He's making stuff
up. See, he's a [ __ ] [ __ ]
>> He's a [ __ ] 4 and a half hours. 4 and
1 half hours from Birmingham. Yeah, right.
>> 4 and 1/2 hours. He's making stuff up.
>> It doesn't even take 4 and 1 half hours
to go to Newcastle.
to go to [ __ ] Newcastle, mate.
>> On a train. It doesn't even take four
and a half hours to go to Newcastle on a train.
[ __ ] sp one four one four one four
one four one four one four one four one
four one four one four and a half hours
to go to Birmingham
>> the one
>> it's not even 4 hours to get to
Newcastle on the train you [ __ ]
>> blown the [ __ ] out of you and you were
scared to use the house
>> you [ __ ] re It's not even 4 hours on
the train to go Newcastle
>> you haven't given the tough talk
>> you are fuckingastic you are [ __ ] how
how far you from Birmingham trains see
look he left left see
4 and a half hours to go from Birmingham
to London yeah right Yeah, right.
Yeah. Yeah, right, bro.
Yeah, [ __ ] right.
>> Slug, stop bringing me up when you're
arguing with PJ. You have your own
problem with him. Stop bringing me up.
They're trying to [ __ ]
>> I'll [ __ ] I'll have I'll have I'll
have the both of you.
>> Yeah, I just heard
>> No, no. I'll have the [ __ ] both of you.
>> I just heard you say to Greasier.
Greasy, do you want to go for a drink or
do it dirty? Sounded like you're too
>> sound like two dirty. Just do it dirty.
>> Sound like two [ __ ]
bringing me to London this year.
>> Why is Slug bringing me up when he's
talking to you? He said he was coming to
London. Now he's backing out.
>> He said it's He said it's He said it's 4
and a half hours to come to London from Birmingham.
>> I I don't know. Is it?
>> No. It's like an hour and 20 minutes on the train.
>> Yeah. He's [ __ ] scared. It's not even
4 hours to go to Newcastle on a [ __ ] train.
>> I don't know. I don't trains everywhere.
I usually get flights or cars or whatever.
>> Well, yeah, it's it's an hour and 20
minutes. It's only the Midlands. It's
only the [ __ ] Midlands. He just makes
excuses every time.
>> He I heard him there and I say to you,
"Yeah, yeah. Do you want me to come
today Thursday or Friday?" And you said
come today anyway. No, no, no, no, no.
>> Yeah, everyone heard it.
>> Slug PJ owns you. It's a sad sad day
when PJ gets a win on here, but he's
done you there, slug.
>> So, are you coming? Are you coming? Are
you coming to London this? Oh, he left.
>> Yeah, he said today. Tomorrow, Thursday.
Do you remember Grezy? Today, tomorrow, Thursday.
He said that in it. today, tomorrow, Thursday.
That's what he said. Yeah,
I mean, I might need to go out and
collect again this week. Griezy, what do you think?
Going out and collecting, Grezy,
what do you think? Should I go out and collect?
Should I go and collect? Maybe this. No,
I don't think so. No.
Oh, do you know what I said, UK? I said
that women that cheat need to be hung
off a bridge.
Women that cheat on people need to be
hung from a bridge. That's [ __ ] disgusting.
That is absolutely vile. Yeah,
>> that's absolutely disgusting.
>> Do you want to play the money game, PJ?
As you'll see,
>> are you coming?
>> Are you coming to London today? >> Minted.
>> Yeah, he's not minted. He's skinn like you.
Yeah, he's skinn like you. It's so [ __ ]
>> No, no, no. Sex is skinn like you to me.
>> Anyway, bro, Peter can't afford a train to Birmingham.
>> Yeah, I can't afford a train. Yeah, I
know, bro. I'm going to have to give.
>> Yeah, I've got I've got one pound to my name.
>> Yeah. Yeah, I've got a pound to my name.
Didn't you know?
>> Are we going to play the money game? Cuz
we all know you haven't got 20 quid.
>> I played the money game and I beat you.
>> Quid, Peter. Show me.
>> I played the money game and I beat you
last February. I beat you.
>> Never beaten anyone. I've
>> Yeah, I'll play the money game when you
come to London. I'll play the money game
when you come to London. I don't cuz you
want to go if you want to play by the
pass Peter you have shown the least
money on here.
>> Well you're you're bringing up the pass
with L but you're bringing up the pass.
>> But you're bringing up the 15 grand but
you're bringing up the pass.
>> I've shown N grand. You
>> So why can't I? No, you haven't shown N grand.
>> No, you haven't shown N grand.
>> You lose.
>> No, you have not shown N. Peter, you're
and you know
>> you haven't shown N grand.
>> You can't even play the money game.
>> I think you had the money game. I beat
you at the money game.
>> Show off to your nons.
>> I beat you at the money game.
>> Your skits and you.
>> Yeah, I beat I already beat you at the
money game. You and your nunch
boyfriend. I beat you both at the money game.
>> I beat you both at the money game, >> [ __ ]
>> I beat you both at the money game.
>> Night with your mommy.
>> I I I I beat you both at the money game.
Do you remember Timmy? I beat you both
at the money game.
>> You can't.
>> So he's not coming to London every day.
He's a [ __ ] He's backed out again.
Peter, it's not about money.
>> This lefty has backed out again,
everyone. He's backed out again.
>> Hiding in a travel lodge, Peter.
>> He's backed out again.
>> Not gambling it.
>> He's He's backed out again. The gambling
the gambling addict. Virgin. The
virgin's backed out again. The virgin's
>> You're not So, you're not coming today then?
>> You're not about You were finished a
long time ago anyway when [ __ ] Tiger
put you in a mattress. Timmy, you ran
away. You ran away. When you come to
London, you ran up the road.
>> Then you you've been humiliated the
most. I'd rather be out by
>> But that's the pass. The pass doesn't count. >> Mattress.
>> But the pass doesn't count. You said
>> you can't believe you.
>> Yeah, but you But you said the pass doesn't count.
>> A filthy Pakistan mattress.
>> Have you pulled all your items?
>> Yeah, I bet that stank in it, PJ.
So, you've pulled your TV.
>> PJ, I'm going to upload the bit in a
minute where Tiger put you in a mattress. >> Okay.
>> You can't come and give it to me and I'm
going to upload the bit as well when
Lord Jay own the [ __ ] out of you and you
couldn't even but you said the past doesn't matter.
>> You can you can put the fight with me and Wast
I can Peter. At least I At least I'm not
a [ __ ] like you run on away from my
>> Didn't this guy just say that? Didn't
people say that the past doesn't matter?
>> You're [ __ ] PJ. You're not about it.
You're a [ __ ]
>> Okay. Well, come to London then.
>> Oh, no. No. You come to Birmingham. I will.
>> No. You said that you was going to come to London.
>> Trust me.
>> You said you was going to come to London.
>> Get excited and say all this, but I know
in my heart of hearts, Peter, it's going to
>> You said you was going to come to London.
>> Peter, I don't do demands by you. I will
catch you off guard when you go.
>> Here we go again. Here we go again. Here
we go again. You are dead.
>> Do you reckon if I go to Birmingham
today? Grey, do you reckon Monty will see it?
>> If I If I go to Birmingham today, do you
think Monty will see it or he'll be unaware?
>> You will see. You will see. And that's
not a threat. That's a [ __ ]
>> No, I won't see it. You said you was
going to come today.
>> Why aren't you going to Why aren't you
going to London today?
>> Because Oh, banger, come on. Why don't
you go to London today? You know
>> because I live in a different country
>> and I wasn't on YouTube last night
saying I was going to London today.
>> I live in the wheel well not you Tim but
you said it.
>> Banger banger bang.
>> It's not like PJ said I will come to
London. Tim you said you were going and
threaten him again
>> because I never wasn't on YouTube last
night saying I was going to PJ's house.
>> Come on here talking about fights when
you've when you run away from Tim. But
listen but now see you just wait. You
just said that he beat me. Now you're
saying that he ran away. Make up, bro.
You can't even make up your mind.
I don't Tim, listen. You said you were
going to banger. Real question. No
excuse. The train was delayed. Why did
you run away from from from I know the
reason why you run away from Jay and
Banger, but let's see your version.
>> Okay. Tell tells the reason.
>> No, no, no. Come on. When you run away,
so let's tell the reason.
>> I know the reason why you ran away from
B. Why are you standing up for a
21-year-old you said had CP in Discord?
>> No, no, no, no, no. Just, just answer
the question back. Tim, you were on
YouTube last night saying you're going
to London today. Now you're backing out
of it trying to get BJ to go to B.
You're not a burn. Just believe I'm absolutely finished.
>> So why did you run away from J?
>> He left. He left.
>> Yeah, he left because he knows that
he'll get [ __ ] owned. So bang, you
can go and do your silly little videos
about fight and that lot. A 21-year-old
guy from Yorkshire owns the [ __ ] [ __ ]
out of you.
>> Greasy. Oh, do you remember Security
Steve on account? Security Steve was a
legend, isn't it? Security Steve.
>> There used to be a YouTube account on
here called Security Steve. Do you
remember it, Grezy? Security Steve.
>> There used to be an account.
>> Anyway, but anyway, right. Anyway, right. Um,
so you coming to London? Yeah. Anyway, PJ,
>> there was an account we called security Steve.
>> Are we going to play the money game, PJ?
Are we going to play?
>> Yeah, you've already been beaten.
>> You haven't got any money. You ped in your TV.
>> You've already been beaten banger.
>> Tim, let me ask you a question. Wait,
let me ask you a question, Tim. All that
money was a couple of quid. Let me Tim,
let me ask you. Let me ask you this. Did
you Did you or did you not say last
night you were going to PJs? Angie,
you're not about it either. You're not
either. You did. And now today you're
not going. You're not about it.
>> You're not about it. You're a cryb.
>> You're coming on here and offering PJ
and then now you're batting out and
saying PJ's not about it. But PJ never
said he was going to Birmingham.
>> [ __ ] ridiculous slug.
Call me a SLUG NOW.
>> YEAH, SLUG. YEAH, he offered PJ. Tim
said last night he's going to PJ's today
and now he's not going. He's [ __ ] tragic.
>> The truth.
>> You're [ __ ] pathetic, slug.
>> So why? So you can call me a slug as
much as you want. Because you can't
answer my question, can you? Why didn't
you go and meet Jaden?
>> He left.
>> Why didn't you go and meet Jaden?
>> No, he's left again because he thinks
calling me a slug's going to get him out
of his battles cuz he's that [ __ ]
>> Yeah, but Timmy, you had an IVA.
>> Trying to impress his [ __ ] lefty mate.
>> Oh, that's a lovely little account.
That's a lovely little account, Greasy.
Look at a lovely little account.
>> Anyway, anyway, Peter, you've got till
Thursday maximum. So, let's go and play
the money game. Yeah, let's go and play the money.
>> You said that you're coming to London today.
>> Let's play the money game. Right. Let's
go and play the money game. Right.
>> You you you said
>> I shown you 70 quid last night. I can go
back to the bank and get Why can't you
show me 20 pounds
like last night again? Guarantee you.
What? What? Peter can't even show 20
quid. Pet Jeremy go. We need we need
security ste in a minute and I will
withdraw more money out. Peter, I will
go and draw some more. You don't have any money.
>> Yes, I don't have any money. Peter.
>> Okay, if that's the case, Peter, show
the camera. Peter, show the camera.
>> One second.
>> Show the camera.
>> Hold on.
>> Yeah, one second. Hold on. How do I Okay, two.
>> you can't throw that cuz you're that
[ __ ] skinned, Peter. You're that
>> you can't even show. Well, show 20 quid,
Peter. I've shown you 20 quid.
>> Oh my god, this guy is embarrassing.
>> No money. And it's [ __ ] 70.
>> You haven't even got 20 quid and Eene
doesn't get her [ __ ] dogs all fried.
You said she can't give you a load.
>> 70 pound.
>> Oh, Timmy. Timmy. Timmy. I've shown more
than that. Timmy, I showed you £1,300.
I've already shown I've already shown
more than him.
>> Yeah, but I showed I showed more in the
past and that's all that counts, Joe.
That's all that counts. That's all that
>> Unless the pass doesn't matter.
>> Yeah. 70 pound they used to. Yeah.
What the [ __ ]
>> Yeah. And I've shown more in the past.
>> Anyway, Peter.
>> Nope. Okay, Joe. Okay, Joe. Okay, Joe.
So then all of the L's that I've took
don't count then. Peter, I'm going to
all of the L's I've took doesn't count
then, is it?
>> Make up your mind. Make it make sense.
>> Oh, so the pass doesn't matter then. So
you're saying the pass don't matter then
prime don't matter l J don't matter if
that if that's okay then none of this
matters then does it 50 mega I mean
chicken mayo cuz he's
>> show us show us500
>> over PJ can't even afford a cheeseburger from McDonald's >> he's show us500
I'm coming to me
>> show us 500 got three days to man [ __ ]
Um, show us £500.
Oh, he left.
>> What the [ __ ] bro? You got beat at the
money game. I showed you £1,300 the last
time I last time I played you. Now it's
your turn to show 2,600.
Yeah. £2,600. It's your turn to show
I showed 1300. So that was uh that was last year. >> Yeah.
Yeah. You've all been beaten the money
game. Joe, you nons
Timmy. I beat you all at the money game.
I've beaten you all out the money game
and I'm still undefeated. Undefeated champion
when it comes to cash. I'm undefeated.
Like undertaker was undefeated at Wrestlemania
for 31 years. I'm undefeated.
Germany Germany Germany undefeated.
I'm the president of the money game. Not
the king. I'm the president.
I'm not I'm not the I'm not the king.
I'm the president of the money game.
Yeah, I'm the president.
Yeah, I'm the president. Me?
What do you think of that, Greavvesy?
The pre the president of the money game, huh?
I'm the president. Uh,
you show money and the other person's
supposed to double it. But every time
I've shown money in the past, no one's doubled it. So yeah.
So yeah. And then they made their own
little rules up and all of this and all of that. Yeah.
Yeah. They that's the that's what the
rules are supposed to be, but they make
up their own little rules cuz they're
biased. So even when you beat them, they
pretend that they beat you. They come
back showing less.
Nons ain't got no 13, 14 grand. Cuz if
you had 13, 14 grand, you would have
beat me over the summer. No problems asked.
No problems asked. No problems at all.
You would have easily come in and you
would have shown it, but you couldn't
cuz you don't have it. Just like Timmy.
It's as simple as that. And you know
it's the truth as well. You know it's the truth. So yeah,
I can easily [ __ ] double that £1,100.
But nah, not playing these games
anymore, mate. Nope, I don't gain
nothing. It's not like I get like £500
or £300 every time I show money to these
skin self-reflectors. You gain nothing.
You gain nothing. You gain nothing
at all. Nothing at all.
Just like when I'll be meeting this
person soon. I'm not putting it on
YouTube. Not showing what they look
like. Don't need to prove myself to any
of these people. Simple.
So then you're saying that the past does matter.
But when people say that they've shown
you money, you say that it was ages ago.
So you Which one is it? It does it
matter or does it not matter? Could only be one.
Eight thumbs up now.
Eight thumbs ups now to someone calling
me a virgin. That's very interesting.
Wow. Eight thumbs up to someone calling
someone that's proved they've had sex a
virgin. That's not very nice.
Seems a bit biased to me. Don't know
about any of you people, but seems a bit
biased to me.
Lovely. [ __ ] lovely. That's why no
one waste their time on you people.
That's why we don't waste our time.
I got a headache now. Greasy. The
autistic community is gave me a headache.
Now I need to take some painkillers.
Jesus Christ, my little head. Oh gosh.
Well, I need to My head's [ __ ] banging now.
You make up your own little rules.
You make up your own little rules and
you got beat up the money game. All of a
sudden, path doesn't matter now.
All of a sudden it doesn't matter
because you won the money.
Sorry, man. That's funny as hell.
Apparently now it doesn't all of that
stuff doesn't matter now. Sorry, lady.
Can you try and fix my bug, please? No,
>> it's completely [ __ ]
>> No, I anxious. It's not good.
>> Yeah, but mom, it's You [ __ ] the whole thing up.
Yeah, you did.
>> I wanted I want the new fold in July. Mom.
Mom. You better start saving, Mom.
>> You better start saving for the F.
>> Excuse me. Making myself a lovely cup of tea.
You better start saving your little one for that.
Is that funny?
You know, I froze you. I don't know
anything that you're saying.
All right, Mom.
All right, Laney.
I hope so.
So now all of a sudden in the past it
doesn't matter because you've won the money.
So now you've won the money now it doesn't count.
That's not right, is it? So if you want £100,000, right?
If you've won £100,000, right?
Does it not count because you won it?
They change the rules all the time,
these bloody people of this community,
and I've had enough of it.
I've had a [ __ ] enough.
Right, making myself a lovely cup of [ __ ] now.
A couple of [ __ ]
[ __ ] eight months off. Someone
calling me a virgin. How could I be a virgin?
How could I be a [ __ ] virgin? Eh,
Peter B of all people. mad.
And don't forget, if you win money and
you show money, you win. It doesn't
count. It's the past.
Even though these people do nothing but
bring up the past,
but it doesn't if you win money, if you
win money and you show money, it doesn't count.
News to me. I learned something new today. Oh, right.
So, that doesn't count because it was
one money and it was the past. Oh, interesting.
That is very interesting, isn't it?
Learn something new every day. All
right. Can you bring some of the
Yeah, I will. Sorry, Ma.
I do, Ma. I just didn't today. Huh?
Thank you, Ma. Okay.
Well, they're disabled, JA. What do you expect?
They they're [ __ ] disabled in this
community. Of course they're going to
listen to [ __ ] repeat him.
Of course they are. They're disabled.
They got no life.
Timmy's not coming today then. Another
another thing where he's backed out of.
Yeah. It's just I I Do you know what?
This community never fails to make you laugh.
I learned something new today, JNA. I I
I heard so I learned that if you show
money and you wonder money, it doesn't
count. And if it was ages ago, it doesn't count.
You learn something new every day, don't you?
So if these people in this community
take L's, it doesn't count because it's
it's the past. Oh,
you learn something new every day. I
learned a lesson today.
And if it's one money, it doesn't count.
So, say if you if you won £50,000 on the lottery.
Yeah. Oh. Oh, really? So, does that mean
if somebody humiliates you, that doesn't count then?
Oh, well, I I mean, I showed money for
about 15 to 18 months and no one doubled
it. I'm pretty sure that counts as
proving the people in this community to be skinn.
I mean I mean I'm pretty sure I'm pretty
sure it does count.
I'm pretty sure it does count when
you've shown people money for 15 to 18
months and not one person can join
Hangouts and show you anything. I'm sure
that counts. I'm sure it does.
Of course it counts. If it didn't count,
then me taking L's wouldn't count
because it's the past. It's as simple as
that. So, you make up your own little
agenda, your own little rules. That's
why no one waste their time.
It doesn't matter if it's gone. It
You got shown money and you ran away. It
doesn't change the L. The L doesn't
change. The L does not turn the L does
not change into a W.
It doesn't matter. You got shown money
and you ran away. It doesn't matter
where the money is. Invested, gone,
still there. It doesn't matter where it
is. You run away. You You can't take
back an L cuz it was ages ago. You can't
say that it's not an L. And this is how
you lose brain cells in this community.
This is how you actually start losing
brain cells. When the moment you start
arguing with these people, you just lose
brain cells. You're wasting your time.
You're literally wasting your time.
You're never with these jealous ugly
people. It's something I should have
learned a long and you are jealous. You
people are jealous. If you generally
weren't jealous, you wouldn't go on
about people every day. If you weren't
jealous, you wouldn't harp on about
people every day on YouTube if you
weren't [ __ ] jealous of something in
life. And that's facts. That is the
truth. That is facts. Yep.
Yeah. He was live. He was he come on my
So then launch legs that claimed that he
shown 13 grand. That doesn't count then does it.
Right. Right. Okay. Okay. Okay. So that
13 grand apparently what it was. That
doesn't count then does it? So that doesn't count.
Right. Oh, okay. Oh, so that that 13
grand doesn't count then, does it?
uh years ago. It was a video from years
ago. So that doesn't count then, does
it? So it doesn't count then. So does it
count or does it not count? Like you
you're confusing me. Which one is it? Is
it Does it count or does it not count?
Okay. So he hasn't beat anyone at the
money game then. Okay then.
So, but my question to you, and I you're
missing the point of what I'm trying to
make, is if people have shown you money
for 18 months and none of you people
could show anything, why would anyone
waste their time showing you money again?
Why would anyone show you money again
when you've already proven what you're
about? It's the same thing as being
shown with a woman. Why would anyone
come on here and show you with women
again and having sex again when you're
just going to call them a [ __ ] virgin?
Why would anyone waste their time if
someone's not shown anything in 15 to 18 months,
right? Why would anyone show money
again? Why would anyone show women
again? Why would anyone go and try to
meet anyone again?
You know, it's the point is not about
the money. It's to prove that these
people haven't got money.
And that's what them 15 months proved.
It doesn't matter how much money I've
got. One grand, two grand, 10 grand, a
million grand, million pounds. Sorry.
You know, it doesn't it doesn't matter.
I think a lot of these people in this
community need to grow the [ __ ] up.
You need to grow the [ __ ] up.
That's what I think a lot of these
people in this community need to do.
So yeah. So why are you ask why are you
still asking people to show you money?
Why are you still asking people to show
you women? Why are you still expecting
people to meet you for fights?
But you we know what you people do,
you know. I will never ever show money
unless someone gave me money for showing it like£300,
400 pound,£500 then I'll come back with
them I'll come back and beat these
people again you know
I will never ever ever show money again £510 never
ever ever ever ever
I will never show money ever again
whether I have it don't have it never again.
It's very childish. It's childish. It's
pathetic. It's disabled, you know. Yep.
So, Timmy's not meeting. Oh, no.
Right. I'll delete my video in a bit and
come off of here again.
Simple as that. Yeah.
We're not bragging about showing the
money either. The the point is we're not
bragging about showing the money. We're
bragging about what you people have done
when you got shown the money. That's
where the that's where the confusion is
coming. We're not bragging about money
that we no longer have. We're bragging
about you people being outed when you
got shown money and none of you could
have shown nothing. That's what That's
what we're show. That's what we're
talking about. That's what we're talking
about. We're talking about your
movements when you've been shown money
despite calling people skint yet you
couldn't show nothing. Projection.
That's what we're talking about. We're
not actually talking about, oh, this is
a lot of money. Oh, I've had this money.
We're talking about what you people have
done and you people don't change. So,
the same thing would have happened
again. That's something I think I needed
to clarify, I think. Yeah.
And that's it.
Nons hasn't shown money in a long long
long long long long long long time. Post
3, four grand. And then you got Timmy
sucking up his dick. The [ __ ] bro?
You ain't shown no serious money for a
very, very, very long time. Just the
same as you say to me that I haven't
shown money for a very, very long time.
Bias again, as always,
as it will always be.
I reckon you could go on a community,
bro. I reckon you could go on a on a
PlayStation community with a bunch of
kids and they'd have more brains than
these people. I reckon you could play
Call of Duty with a bunch of 12 year
olds. Yeah. Like, you could be on a
community full of kids and they'd have
more brains than these people. I
generally think you would, you know,
that's that's actually quite sad to say.
I don't know, bro. And I don't care.
I don't care if it was fake. I don't
care if it was real. You can't show it
now. You won't show it now.
Yeah, there's higher IQ with children on
a PlayStation community than than this community.
Yeah, we're not bragging about the money
or how much the money was. We was
bragging the fact that you didn't show
anything for 15 months. Why have all of
these people in this community that's
got all this money unable to show anything?
that is relevant and that will stay
relevant because that's part of your L.
You understand? You see, you can't start
saying the past don't matter when it's
when it shoots yourself and then then go
on to talk about the past.
My head's hurting me, bro. This
community hurts my head. It hurts my brain, bro.
It actually hurts my brain.
Yeah, it hurts my brain, bro. I got
someone JNA calling me a virgin and it
got eight thumbs up.
10 thumbs up. It's got 10 thumbs up.
Someone's calling me a virgin and it's
got 10 thumbs up. I mean, what more
evidence do you need that you're never
going to win with these people? You show a polo.
You show you in bed naked with women.
You have admitted women admitted to
sleeping with you and they still call
you a virgin.
You will never win with them. And that's
what you you need to you need to
understand as thing about this community
is you'll never ever ever win with these
jealous people. No matter what you show,
what you don't show, trust me, it's facts.
Facts. What I'm saying like is facts 100%.
You know that if they had a life, they
wouldn't come on YouTube talking about
people the way they do every day.
Freaky freaky fied community, bro.
I think you're missing. Does it matter?
Does it matter? Well,
they're biased, so it does matter. Yeah.
So, yeah, it does matter.
But yeah, you generally could go on a
community full of a bunch of 12y olds
and they've got more brains than these
people. Because I remember, bro, when I
was like 11, 12 and I used to be on
PlayStation before I met Monty, man.
[ __ ] years before. I'm sure these
people had more brains than these people.
I'm sure they had more brains than these people.
Pretty sure, bro.
sure they had more brains than these
people, bro. Pretty sure.
Yeah, they're just jealous, bro. You got
to understand with these people in this
community, it comes to jealousy with a
lot of these people. These people are
old. These people have got no life. They
got no family. It's a really weird
community. There's no point of it
either. No one puts up gambling videos
anymore. There's no point to this community either.
There's like no there's no actual point
to it. Do you understand? It's just
people that talk about people every day
that they don't know.
It's [ __ ] wild, bro. [ __ ] wild.
Doesn't make no sense.
You know what I mean? Anyways, I'm going to
I'm going to jump off now anyways, lad. Yeah. So,
I see you later, lad. See you later.
want to jump off now.