How we doing, man?
[ __ ] Yeah, I got the fridge done,
man. Good little investment. I wonder
how much you'll be saving.
Yeah. In a month just using that fridge.
[ __ ] [ __ ] ton, bro. Probably a [ __ ]
ton. Yeah, I'd say that was a good
investment, man. Well, I say, why didn't
I get one sooner?
Because I mean, you could get away with
it in January, February. You could just
leave stuff outside, but we're coming
summer now. So, good investment, man. Good
investment. But yeah, £100 does seem a
lot when you just bought a [ __ ] fridge. That was
£100. Yeah, there you
go. Good old
fridge coming your
way. Yeah, I've got a black
one. It's all good.
I spent £28 today. [ __ ]
hell. Bro, madness,
it won't have to get the [ __ ] shitty
[ __ ] small milks, would we? Hey, Zippy.
zippy. So we got 3
hours. Put it in there. I want to have
an Indian today. I'm
starving. Stop it, bro. [ __ ]
I spent £200 today. I just bought a
fridge cuz I can't get away with putting
stuff outside now cuz obviously it's warming up.
Fridge. I lost 100 gambling. So I lost
two I lost 200 pound down. 220 almost basically.
Yeah, it's all right. It you'll save a
lot of money with that
fridge. Stop keeping them [ __ ] corner
shops in [ __ ] business as
well. So yeah, stop keeping them bastards in
business. Yeah, you know all about skint
cuz you you skint
yourself. Yep, you would know cuz you
are skint. takes one to no one. Yeah,
bro. The reason I didn't buy a fridge
January, February is because I could get
away with it. I could get away with it
then, you know, because it was cold. It
was colder than putting stuff in the
fridge. But now, and it's like, yeah,
but I don't know why I didn't, to be
honest, cuz I'm sick of keeping them
[ __ ] corner shops in business. And
obviously where things don't [ __ ]
stay cold, you know? You have to keep
going and going. But now I can go to
like Tesco's, the biggest
Tesco's, and then like buy like cheaper.
And you'll save a lot of money with that
fridge. A lot of
money. You'll probably save that fridge
probably 100 pound a week easy.
Yeah. Chuck the other fridge out. It's [ __ ]
manky. It's disgusting, mate.
It better work properly. I assume it
will assume it will work
properly. Should be here in like a few days.
Uh can keep my little alcohol bottles in there as
well. Always something comes up, is it?
It's always something that comes up.
the way it is, isn't it,
guys? Oh, bye-bye.
So if I go out Thursday, Saturday
approaching cult, what is the least I
could spend two days together? I think
£100 isn't it? Yeah, I would. I'd say
that about 100
quid. I'd say about £100.
Yeah. I need to get an electric bike at
some point as well. It's going to cost quite a bit. Oh
boy. No, we're all good, man. We got all
the bills ready. We got the fridge
coming. It's all good,
really. It's all good,
man. 25th. So, it took a few
days. I'm getting hungry now. But I'll
wait. I will wait until the until the Indian opens. I'll
wait. I will wait patiently. [Music]
Oh, wait. Cole. Oh, wait.
You could put like small Ben & Jerry's
in it, can't you? Like the small Ben &
Jerry's. Yeah. Like you get cheaper ones
for like 50 quid, but I can't use a
um I can't use a secondhand [ __ ]
fridge. I can't use a secondhand fridge,
mate. That's [ __ ]
grim. That's [ __ ] grim.
Sure you'd agree on that as well. It's [ __ ] stinking,
mate. That is [ __ ] stinking. Stinking, son.
Stinking. I'm just going to get go for I
just ordered a fridge. I needed a fridge
to put stuff in.
Um yeah. Um lost 100 pound gambling and
I'm going to go for an
Indian. Yeah, I'm going to go for some
Indian at about 5 or something. So I've
got a few hours to wait. But
yeah, that should be good,
man. Fishing frenzy and
roulette. Friday, we'll go
cinema. Not we'll do Friday. We'll do Yeah.
cinema. No football bets, just cinema.
And yeah, Saturday, I don't know what
I'm going to do Saturday. I'm not
drinking. I'm not approaching.
So, I'll have to find something to do while I on [Music]
Saturday. Soon, man. Soon. I need to get
an ebike as well. I need to save up a
bit more money. I had to pull out 100
pound on a [ __ ] fridge cuz it's hot
now. And this fridge here is mankkey. So
I had to buy little
fridge. So yeah, I'll be going
uh some point,
bro. I'm bored of this country now, bro.
I'm bored of it. I will try again, but I
don't know when. Uh I'm bored of it,
lad. Uh you know, oh I've got a
boyfriend and all that [ __ ] It's
boring, bro. Very boring. So,
yeah. It's very
boring. There's a reason for it. I'm not
going to get into it. But
yeah, it's funny how you're asking me
about Thailand in it cuz you know this country is
dead. What I'm going to do is I'm going
to try to get this Indian. She says
she's going to meet me. The plan is try
to get this Indian woman to meet me. It
means be traveling there. If not, then
I'll probably pick th a week. Thursday,
Saturday. I'm going to send it Thursday,
Saturday. Then if I don't get nothing,
then I'm done for a month. But that's
not going to be for like two
weeks. That's what I'm saying. Just get
a bottle. Get a bottle of alcohol. Get
[ __ ] But the reason the thing is I'm
not doing it this week cuz I need to get
my haircut again. And I'm not wasting
money on my hair.
I'm not wasting money getting my hair done. So,
um, until like three weeks and then
obviously we'll do Thursday and we'll do
Saturday. We send send
send. We don't get nothing. Give up for
a month and do something like that. We
need to save money at the same time. You
know what I'm saying? It's not even that
we need to save money. It's just just
money is not worth it's not worth
spending loads and loads and loads of money.
Yeah. The thing you need to focus on is
exhausting all ways to make money and
leaving this country. That's what you
need to focus on. You need to focus on
basically ways to make money anyway you
can more and get out of this country.
That's that's basically what and that is
what I am focusing on because obviously
I'm not going to [ __ ] I'm not going
out this week. I didn't go out last
week. So, you know, I'm not doing this
[ __ ] every week. It's boring, bro. But I
do I did need to buy a fridge, though,
because I'll be saving like £100 a week
with that fridge. I don't have to keep
going to corner shops. I don't have to
keep buying Coke cuz because it's you
don't stay cold, you know? I can eat in,
know. No, I don't know what I'm
doing. No, I just wanted a bike to get
to places quicker.
Uh and then obviously just leave here in
it the way it is. No, I just wanted an
electric bike. Always like
bikes. So that's
it. And then obviously I can eat in with
the fridge as well cuz I can keep the
stuff refrigerated. That's going to save
me a [ __ ] ton of money as
well. Yeah, I lost £100 today. Man, it
didn't seem like much. Yeah, losing
£100. But when when you see it as like
he's already back when you see you just
bought a fridge for like 100 £107 with
the delivery and you've just lost £100.
It's kind of mad, is
it? But I won't be losing any more
money. This is the plan, bro. You just
do you got the fridge. I'm going to go
send them on Friday. I'll probably do a
football bet Saturday. Stick 20 pound on
the football. you could get me there
quicker. And that's that's all I'm
focusing on now,
bro. Yeah, I lost 100 pound, but I won't
be putting any more money in. That's my
100. Well, I do 20 pound every week with
the football, but that's
it. Do no more, bro. I just done that
cuz I posted my mom a card. I had to
post my mom card and the bookie was near the post
office. So, yeah, I just thought, let me try £100. Yeah.
But it never worked. So anyways, if I if
I lose £100 for this month just on them
machines, then [ __ ] call it lucky in
it. That fridge will save me a [ __ ] ton
of money. I can start cooking the pork chops as
well. Could start cooking the pork chops on
it. No, I just could I just don't want
to go back there, mate. I don't want to
go back there. Can't be bothered going
back there, bro. [ __ ] that.
Nah, can't be bothered, man. It's going
to cost me money getting there as well,
so I might as well just posted
it. Ooh, some more approaching
vids. Here we
go. But yeah, what do you think will
happen if I go out on um Saturday approaching Little
Fright? But I do need to go back there
at some point to get [ __ ] I got all
my clothes there. All my designer
clothes. So at some
point, what do you think will happen? Yeah.
Yeah. That's why you had to get on pit
before that, is it? Yeah,
man. Yeah, it's very mad. I I feel like,
bro, I wish I could just go out again.
Yeah. And just approach someone and it
be like the situation with that
American, like them offer me their
number, me hook up with them. But it
just never happened since like that. It
never happened like it did a few years
ago. I don't know how that happened,
bro, that time. Because it never it's
never happened since like that. I've had
other women, but not like [ __ ] not
like that, bro. Not you just go up to
someone on the street and them offer you
their number. That's a madness. Imagine
it always happen like that. That'd be
sick. You wouldn't even need to go to
Thailand. But it would always be the
same. But the thing is, but but the plan
is is obviously you go out once a week
because you go out drinking anyways. So
obviously before you go Thailand, you'll
go out once a week here, right? And then
you just try because you're going out
anyways. No, I've already been with her.
I [ __ ] her a few times.
She's That's a 19year-old. She went
funny. No, she started being funny,
man. No, she started being funny. Um yeah. [Music]
No. So no, I
can't. But yeah, it's hard. But like I
said, I've got this Indian woman that
said she'll meet me if I go to
her. I don't know, man. Because I kept
going on about this American and I kept
gambling. This was ages ago. And she
messaged me the other day, but then she
blocked me again. It was
weird. Last time she was here, she
sucked my dick. I remember that as
well. But I mean, she's too young for me
anyways. It's never going to work.
She's too young for me and we're
different stages in life and I would
never date her. It was more of just like
I go there, I [ __ ] her, she gets what
she wants, she gets
money, I get sex. Yeah. You know what
I'm saying? So, it's like it's not going to work,
bro. I want someone around see this
Indian, she's like 23, 24. It's
perfect. So, I No, I met her in a club.
So yeah, we'll try and get her, but that
means be traveling [ __ ] near
Birmingham like I keep saying. So
yeah. No, I had to know. No, no, no, no.
I banged her two times. No. How many
times I [ __ ] her? I [ __ ] her twice.
She sucked my dick once and then the lot
twice. But the last time she's like,
"Oh, I'm not doing anything with you
unless you stop gambling. And then she
stopped talking about this person in
America. She's like, "I'm not going to
do anything with you. I'm not going to
do anything with you until you change.
Like, honestly, I'm done." So, I said,
"Oh, what if I give you money?" I really
wanted a [ __ ] And she's like,
"Yeah." I said, "How much do you want?"
She said, "50." I had £50 on the side.
So, I just gave her £50 and she suck my
dick. But the other times, obviously,
she done it for free.
So, how do I meet her? um on the street.
I approached her on the
street. Madness. Like literally
approached her on the
street. Yeah. Um it was a Saturday. I
remember it as well. It was a
Saturday. Yeah, I know, bro. But money's
no object, bro. Who cares? I don't give
a [ __ ] bro. She was in my room, bro.
I'm [ __ ] horny. Yeah. If the [ __ ]
don't want to do something, I'll make
her do something by giving her money.
You know, that's that's
it. I could try getting in contact with her again,
but she she unblocked me and she messed
me. Then she blocked me
again. But then she blocked me again. It was proper
weird. I don't know. She said, "Oh, can
I come around?" And she just blocked me
again. It was weird,
lad. I don't
know. But I was a [ __ ] cuz I used to
lose money and I just used to ditch
people and I would just ditch people and
it weren't nice. So
yeah, that's what it is.
It in the [ __ ] wrong,
mate. Of course you will put out. Why
won't she put out? She's from England,
but she's just Indian. Indian
heritage. We'll see. Anyways, bro, time will
tell. It's not even an easy ride even if
she does say yeah because I've got to go
all the way
there. I think she will once she's had a
few drinks. I think she will.
She's not Indian. Like she's Indian but
not like what you're thinking. Like born
in India and
and whatnot. Know what I'm
saying? So yeah. One second.
Yeah. Nah, man. I'm not wasting my time
with [ __ ] on this community.
No, I'm not wasting my time with
[ __ ] in this community, bro. I'm
[ __ ] too old for
it. See, the time's going fast,
cult, you know. But that fridge thing
was a very good idea. I don't know why I
didn't think of it sooner. Well, like I said,
because the reason I didn't think of it
sooner is because it was cold outside.
So, I didn't there was no real need for it.
But now you can't put no milk outside
now, mate. It'll be [ __ ] off within a
hour. No, I won't be there. I said near
Birmingham. But it's not
Nah. Nah, mate. He's already been filled
in so many [ __ ] times. I don't know
why he still calls people out to be
fair. We get a nice curry today. Oh, a
nice [ __ ] curry.
But yeah, that American [ __ ] me over
last week as well. She was supposed to
meet me again. She [ __ ] me over. To be
fair, she wasn't really my type, but it
was something better than
nothing. You know what I'm saying? She
weren't ugly or fat. No, no, no.
Just can't explain it, bro. But
yeah, but they're all the same. They've
all got the same minds. You know what I'm saying?
Like that's just the way it is. It will
always be in this country.
So, but life could be worse, man.
So, I'm just waiting for this film in
the cinema roll on Friday. I can't wait to watch
it. I can't I cannot wait to [ __ ]
watch it, mate. I'll be there before you
[ __ ] know it. Believe that. What was
that? One second. Yeah.
Right, I'm gone. I'll be back later.