Sorry lad. Yeah.
Smash the [ __ ] bro. Dumb. Yeah,
I was going to reply to that Joe F.
Yeah, but I couldn't be bothered. UK
asylum, lad. I was going to respond, but
I couldn't be bothered.
He's like, listen to this, Joe. UK
asylum, right? Listen. Yeah, let me read
this out. This made me laugh, lad. Never
meeting anyone. Are we supposed to
forget yesterday? Are we l Where was
this energy yesterday? Yeah, you're
supposed to forget it. Of course. Just
like you forgot that you got beaten at
the money game multiple times. Just like
how you forgot that I've been with
multiple women and you let people call
me a virgin even though I proved I' had
sex. Just like I put up posters of
launch legs and had them scared to leave
his house for two weeks and you forgot
about that. Just like I've been up and
down the country and only you people
have shown up, including yourself. I
mean, I can list many me, many more
examples. I'm sure you'll live
forgetting about yesterday. I mean, you
seem to forget about the other things
very easily. Your biased [ __ ] So, I'm
sure you'll live. I'm sure you'll live.
I'm pretty sure I'm pretty sure I'm
pretty sure you'll live. Uh, you seem to
forget about the other L's that you and
your boyfriends have took. I'm sure
you'll live. Um, I'm sure he'll live.
He'll be okay, bro. No, no, no need to
call an ambulance. No need to No need to
do any of that stuff. I'm sure Joseph
Far will live.
He's managed to forget about loads of
other things in the past like being
beaten at the money game, nonslegs being
beaten when I've traveled up and down
the country. When I've stuck it on men
only for them to say, "Oh, they were at
work and laughing at you." I mean, bro,
you will live. Forgetting about
yesterday, you'll live. Now, now it's
your turn to meet LT.
Yeah, now it's your turn to meet LT. How
about that one? since you're bringing
the [ __ ] thing up. Now it's your
turn. Couldn't even reply to my comments
because you know I'm right. You forget
about yesterday just like you forgot
about all of the other things when
you've lost and you've made up the most ridiculous excuses
cuz you're a biased [ __ ] It's as simple
as that. You just forget it like that.
Is that even a question? Jesus Christ.
Just like when I stuck it on them two
men in front of the women, they were
laughing at me. You can't win. [ __ ]
hell. You forget about it just like you
forget that and the virgin thing. You
[ __ ] biased [ __ ] Why you backing out
now anyways? And no one's listen I
haven't asked Timmy to come here. He
started it and I said okay he started
it. Timmy has started all of this [ __ ]
I'm telling you hands down now. This fat
[ __ ] has started all of this [ __ ] Yeah.
He's saying how he's going to do this.
He's going to do that. Like I mean you
got your own beef with LT. Don't worry
about me and Timmy, bro.
Don't worry about me and Timmy. You
should be meeting [ __ ] London Taylor
like you both agreed. You don't need to
worry about my beef, bro. You don't need
to worry about anything. You don't need
to worry about forgetting anything.
And if Tim don't go, that's even better
for me. I don't particularly want to
knock out a [ __ ] that's showing off
for YouTube. Do you think that's any any
sk any skin off my nose? If this [ __ ]
don't come, I don't give a [ __ ] if he
comes or not. I don't care. We know he's
not going to come and I don't even give
a [ __ ] He's the one that started it
anyways to try to look good for YouTube.
Stupid [ __ ] clown. Yeah,
nothing but a jealous little self
projector. I couldn't give a [ __ ] if he
comes or he doesn't come. I couldn't care less.
You get me, bro?
Oh, this is [ __ ] again, man. the streams.
Sorry, lad. This makes you lose brain
cells hardcore, bro.
This community makes you lose brain cells rapid
when you start engaging with these
people. Well, how have you got four
thumbs up, bro? [ __ ] [ __ ]
Absolute clown, bro. Absolute clown.
Oh, it is working.
Yeah. How are we supposed to forget
about yesterday? Just like you forgotten
about all the other things L's that you
and your boyfriends took.
Just like you said you was going to meet
LT. You just forget about it like that.
What's what's what's hard? What's what's
what's the question, you know?
How is some biased [ __ ] comment on my
channel trying to say how are we to
forget about things? You forget about
everything and you twist [ __ ] all the time.
The [ __ ] bro. [ __ ] you to take
medication or something. Yeah.
I'm still unsub from Timmy, but I'm
still going on a channel channel manually
and then I'll stop going on the channel after Wednesday.
I think what is worse if he show you
know if he shows up then I'll I'll stay subbed.
But if he's done all of this for nothing
again then yeah just un which he has
done I'll just unsub. Simple. Yeah.
[ __ ] this is so [ __ ] bro. It's
bro. This Joe F. Yeah. All right, bro.
This guy come on my channel. Yeah. And
he said, "Never meeting anyone. We
supposed to forget yesterday, are we,
L?" I said, "Yeah, just like you forget
that I beat you at the money game. Just
like you forget that I own naunch legs
several times in real life and you still
make excuses. Just like how I've stuck
it on multiple multiple men only for you
to come out with, oh, they were at work
or oh, they were laughing at you." Yeah.
Yeah. Forget about it. Just like you
forgot about them things. And just like
you forgot about how you said that you
was going to be meeting London Taylor
and you haven't.
Yeah. Yeah. It's the truth though. Look
at look at my reply to him, bro. Look at
my reply to him. Yeah. Yeah, bro. But
look at my reply to him.
Look at my reply to him. He got wrecked.
He can't even respond back cuz he knows
it's the truth. He knows it's the truth.
You got beaten at the money game. You
pretend it never happened. You and your
boyfriend offered to meet you in
Nottingham. You ran away. Pretend it
never happened. Bro, you you literally
forgotten about every L that you've took.
You know, you [ __ ] you let somebody
call me a virgin even though I proved
I've had sex multiple [ __ ] times. But
when I call somebody a virgin that's got
a disabled girlfriend, you got such a
problem with it that you need to get
involved. You're a biased [ __ ] Don't
come on it. Don't come on my channel
with your biased self and start asking
questions, you [ __ ]
I'm not going to delete the comment. I
reply to it, bro. I reply to it. That's
it. I'm not I don't need to delete
comments. Comments don't scare me, bro.
I'm not like a certain little virgin
that has to delete comments. I don't
care how many thumbs up it gets. I don't
care how many thumbs up it doesn't get
cuz we know they're all biased on here.
You know, think about it. Yeah. Fire
stick. Every W I've took, they've made
an excuse every time, bro. They've made
an excuse every time with the bouncer,
with the two lads, with their nons legs,
with the money. They've always made
little excuses because of their own
little agenda. Am I lying? Tell me I'm
lying, bro. Tell me exactly how I'm lying.
Offer to me, LT, you've backed out. I
offered to go to Nottingham. You backed out.
No one wants Timmy to go. I don't give a
[ __ ] if he comes or he doesn't come. I
don't really care.
He's just trying to look good for
YouTube cuz he's a spaz. You get me? But yeah.
But yeah, I don't really care either
way. I'm going to stay on the channel or
I'm going to unsub to it. If he comes
and he actually really gives it a go and
he really does what he says he's going
to do, then yeah, I I can I'll stay sub
to him and then anyone he calls out now,
I think he's got a chance. Yeah. But if
not, then I'm done with him. I don't
even care. I don't want him to come
anyways. I don't really care, bro. Not particularly, but yeah,
look at my comments, bro. He got bodied,
bro. How can he He can't reply back to
me. All of them four thumbs up or Lord J Simps.
You can't even respond back to me, bro.
You know I'm right.
Let's not get into that, Mr. Ferrar.
Yeah, let's not get into that, lad.
Yeah, let's not get into that.
Nah. All right. Did you see what I
responded back to to Joseph Far? Am I lying?
You can agree, you can disagree,
whatever. Look at my respond back. Yeah.
Tell me I'm lying about what I wrote back.
And he's talking about people forgetting things.
People with selective memory forgetting
things. Really? Really? Someone with
selective memory is is telling me that
I'm about about forgetting things, bro. Really? Yeah, bro.
Should we get into it all over again? Do
you want me to do a video on you and get
into it all over again?
Do you want me to get into this all over
again with you?
Simple. And I will bring and I will now
bring up LT because you've agreed to meet him.
Yeah, I know. They look Look at this
guy. Yeah. Look at this guy. Yeah. He
said to me, "Bro, never meeting anyone.
We're Listen, I told you what I wrote
back. Never meeting anyone. We supposed
to forget yesterday, are we though?
Where was this energy yesterday? Joke.
Tim, don't go. It's pointless." I wrote,
"Just like when I agreed to meet you in
Nottingham, you backed out. Just like
when you've had my address before the LT
incident, you backed out. You did
nothing. Just like you agreed to meet LT
and now you're backing out. I've
actually met Timmy twice and beat him
once. Why would he come?" Unlike you,
you can't even talk on a panel. Move along, Joseph.
Y'all want to talk? Y'all want to talk
about forgetting things, Joseph? The
money game comes to mind and the women
I've slept with come to mind as well.
Never never got a reply back cuz he
knows I'm right, bro. He knows I'm
right. Respond back, bro. Let's see your
response back. Just like you forget when
I went to Nonlex's area and I made him
scared to leave the house for 2 weeks,
running to the police, and you made excuses.
Yeah. Just like how you allow people to
call me a virgin. I never hear about
Sig. I never hear about the 19-year-old,
but we hear about Nonlex's disabled
girlfriend every time I think about
calling him a virgin. Do you really want
to get into it? Cuz you're not going to
win. You're not going to win. Trust me,
you're not going to win, [ __ ] So, yes,
you will forget yesterday just like you
forgot everything else. Yeah, [ __ ] [ __ ]
Yeah, it's the truth, isn't it? It's the truth, bro.
Yeah, you [ __ ] little [ __ ]
Yeah, you said I've took an L from LT.
Okay, cool. Now it's your turn then.
It's your turn to meet him. It's your
turn to show me how it's done. It's your
turn to show me how you northerners do it.
You know, learn me how to fight. Show me
the way. If there's a will, there's a
way. And I want to see it.
Yeah, they all do it. A lot of them do
it, bro. A lot of them do it. A lot of
them do it, bro. A lot of them do it.
LT does it. I don't know why LT does it
cuz he's had his own problem with these
cowards. But hey ho, that's another
thing. There's a lot of people that do it, bro.
With the virginity thing, with the money
thing. There's a lot of people that do
it. And they've had their own problems
with this guy as well. It doesn't make
no sense. It's got to be jealousy, isn't
it, bro Leslie? It's got to be jealousy
with these people. It's definitely
jealousy with Timmy. He's shown his face
out there. These Lavie Mongs will not
show their faces.
These Lavine Mongs will not show their faces.
Five, not even 5% of them will. So,
we're talking about everyone, bro. We're
talking We're talking about the whole lot.
Someone sticks it on a man, they're at work.
Someone sticks on a on a pedestrian.
Oh, they laugh at you, bro. Come on now.
Just forget about yesterday and go and
meet London Taylor yourself. Yeah,
of course it's jealousy, bro. Sitting on
YouTube for years and years and years
stalking men. Of course it's jealousy,
bro. Of course it's jealousy with these
little weirdos, bro. The the day Yeah.
The day that these people come on here
and show that they're not the Mer, I'll
drop dead of a heart attack. It's as
simple as that, bro. It is as simple as
And they've been doing it for years as
well, bro. Years. Prior CO, all
throughout CO and after CO. Yeah. It's
got to be jealousy, bro. It's got to be.
Look at Timmy. He does his balls in.
Listen, look at me and look at Timmy and
he and and this is someone we know what
they we know what he looks like.
Yeah. We know what he looks like.
If if London Taylor beat me yesterday,
cool. Good. Now it's your turn. It's
your turn to meet London Taylor. Keep me
out of your [ __ ] Simple.
Yeah. And that's it. [ __ ] [ __ ]
I only come back on here today, bro, cuz
I lost that football bet and I'm around
now until Wednesday and that's it.
And you're telling Timmy to not go when
I've already met Timmy? How does that
make sense? [ __ ] When How can you say
to Timmy, "Don't go when you've
literally already met the guy?" That
doesn't even make sense, [ __ ] Yeah.
If Tim doesn't go, then Tim doesn't go.
I don't give a [ __ ]
You know, I really don't care. But I
would just advise everyone after today,
just don't ever um get into like any of
the drama and stuff. If you enjoy the
gambling videos, just watch the gambling
cuz that's what he does.
That is exactly what he does, bro.
Exactly what he does. Tries to draw
people out, trying to get people in a bad mood.
Gets everyone excited for something
that's never going to happen, i.e. a
fight. And then we're back to square one
again with this spaz.
You know what I mean?
That's it, lad. Yeah, she can stay in
Louis. I don't give a [ __ ]
I know who that is, bro.
I'm going to do a video to that Joe F,
bro. I swear to God if he doesn't reply,
I'm going to do a little video to that [ __ ]
Go and meet LT like you said. Simple as that. [ __ ] [ __ ] No. No.
Well, after Wednesday, bro, it's
finished. It's done, isn't it? Like, that's it.
It's done. It's done now, but I have to
stay now until Wednesday. I mean, it's
done, bro. I'm done. When Timmy shows
him off up on Wednesday, it's over. It's over.
They these people, you got to
understand, right? The
only way this is going to end with these
jealous ass people is when you when you
stop coming on this community, lad.
Yeah. When you stop coming on this community
or, you know, or like you stop engaging
with them. I'm personally coming off of
it because I just want a channel with
with with decent people. That's the only
way, bro. That's the only way.
But you just don't respond to them
because their jealousy is is always
going to go around in circles. Someone
like Timmy's done his balls in. He tries
to draw people out. You get into it. LT
gets into it. It goes around in circles
again. And that's what happens.
That's what happens. It's just going to
go round and round and round and round
and round and round in circles
and it's always just [ __ ] calling it.
Causing it, bro. It's always just Timmy
[ __ ] causing it,
you know? And that's it, bro.
You know what I mean?
It's toxic. That's all it is. It's
toxic. It's negative. It's boring as [ __ ]
That's why I don't go on LJ J's channel.
I don't go on LJ J's live stream because
it's just a bunch of old ugly men that
have failed at everything in life.
That failed at everything in life trying
to project their failures onto you.
Yeah, I know. I know. I know. I know.
It's the same thing, bro. It's been
going on for years. It's the same thing.
It's the same thing. It's incredibly boring. Right.
Why do you think he mentions my name,
Timmy, and no one else's?
No one like nons because he knows I'm
better than him, bro, in every way. So,
he's trying to put me in a bad mood. You
get it? Cuz he knows I'm better than the
spas in every way. I've had more women
than him and his boyfriend Nons legs.
I've got more money than both of them.
Why do you think he brings me up? Why do
you think he tries to rule me out?
Do you not understand what it is on this
place, bro? Do you not understand what it is? Yeah.
You got to understand, bro. It doesn't
take Elbert Einstein coming out from the
grave to tell you, bro. Yeah.
But you seem to forget how many how many
W's have I took on this community where
these people have tried forgetting about
it or they've tried or they've tried twisting it
cuz I've lost count, bro. I've actually lost count.
I've lost count with these biased
people. very very very lost count. You know,
I don't know what the funniest one was
to be honest. I think it was when they
were trying to say, "Oh, the bouncer
couldn't do anything because he was at work."
When bouncers fight people all the time.
I saw one in O'Neal's not so long ago, a
video where the bouncers was fighting people.
They would always come up with a little
excuse to try to twist it. That's what
they do. money, women, fights, what? It
doesn't matter what it is, bro.
That's what happens when you come on a
community that drags drags a society,
bro. Yeah, that's it, man. Yeah.
And that's it, bro.
See, when I've traveled to meet people
for fights and stuff, I always went by
myself. Arsenal mark bomb. Um, Terry,
[ __ ] loads of people, bro. I always
went by myself. Trevor Dawson,
that was another excuse as well. Another laughable excuse. Yeah.
No. No. No. No. No. No.
No. No. No. No. No. No. No.
And And Joe's like, "Tim, don't go."
Okay. Don't go.
It doesn't make a difference to my life
if you come or you don't come.
It makes literally no difference to my
life. I don't give a [ __ ]
But it's it is deep down rooted jealousy
on this community. And you'll see a lot
with these accounts as well.
You'll see a lot of it. And you know,
bro, you know they're just old dregs.
You know they are, bro, behind these
accounts. You know, they're life's
losers. They never These people can
never big themselves up and show
themselves, bro. Put it that way. They
can never big up themselves, talk [ __ ]
about other people, and show themselves
cuz they know, bro. They know. They
These people are depressed. These people
are skinn. These people are lonely as
[ __ ] on this community.
They prove it every time they're on it
all day. They prove it, lad. Yeah, man.
And then when people show themselves, we
can say it. What have they got to be
jealous of? Well, Timmy, for example,
look at Timmy and look at me.
You still going to say that, bro? You
get it? Yeah.
And he was right about the address as well.
Joseph Fars had two of my addresses
before this whole LT thing. Before this
Um, and yet continuously would write
comments but will never ever do anything to anyone
before LT, before all of that [ __ ]
So, you know, it's like what the [ __ ]
Cuz me personally, if I was obsessed
with someone on YouTube every day like
this clown, I would catch them if I knew
where they lived. Yeah. I would honestly
catch them. Okay. Yeah. Let's just say
that people don't come out their door,
right? Let's just say they want to use
the excuses, oh, uh, yeah, uh, we're
not, um, you know, we're not going to go
on your door cuz LT. So if they want to
roll with that excuse share, what I
would I would I would cut someone, bro.
Yeah. Just like if like before like
maybe like a year ago, two years ago, a
year and a half ago, if I knew like
where nons legs lived, I would catch
him, bro. I would catch the [ __ ] Even
if I had even if I had to camp outside.
So I mean there's not really no excuse
this [ __ ] can use really if you think about it. So,
I've lost brain cells already, bro. I can't lie, you know.
And that's it, bro.
Maybe he's wrote something on his
channel. No, nothing. Cuz you know I'm
right, Joseph Fra.
You know I'm right, man. Yeah,
stay live anyways. Might as well.
I'm done with this little weirdo place, weirdo sector.
You know, I'm I want, like I said, we're
starting a new channel. Me, Greasy,
Steven. I want to be off this place.
Laney doesn't even like me on YouTube.
It's [ __ ] All of it is [ __ ]
It's It's actually quite gay as well,
uh, to be honest with you. And yeah,
we're just going to live life with Laney
and [ __ ] basically. Yeah, that's what
we're going to do, bro.
Like Lena says, "Oh, I don't like you on YouTube.
I still come on YouTube." Cuz she's not
going to stop me going on YouTube. She
just doesn't like it. Right. So, it's
like, okay, and what can we go back and
say? Oh, I'm earning money on YouTube.
Oh, mom, I'm earning 34500 a month extra
on YouTube. I'm staying on. No, you're
arguing with spastics every day that
I've got no life. Let's be so real about
it. arguing with stupid jealous ass
people that ain't got no [ __ ] life
that can't tell me nothing. That's no
reason to stay, bro. That's no reason to
stay. You're not getting no money for
it. Yeah. Not getting no money for from
this place. You're not Most of the
people on here are retards. Even though
there are good people on here,
obviously, but most of the people are are retards.
What's What's to break the rule for,
bro? Come on.
What is to break the rule for retards?
There's no positives to it.
There is no positives to it.
We want to go on our own community talk
about football bets if we do football
bets or talk about this or try new food.
There's no benefits to this [ __ ]
place full of self-reflected jealous ass people.
Do you get it, bro? It is the truth.
Yeah, you should see I own Joe even
harder, lad. You should have saw my
response to Joe and his little biased
far thumbs up. [ __ ] little [ __ ]
Yeah, he he couldn't reply back to me
cuz he knows I'm right. He's a [ __ ] you know?
And that's it. He's a [ __ ] [ __ ] lad.
Proper little [ __ ] Yeah.
He's going to have an excuse for King on Wednesday.
If I got £400, £500 extra a month, I'd
stay on it, bro. Come on. Like an hour a day,
two hours a day, every other day,
maybe once a week.
name. No, I'd actually come on here
every Sunday. I reckon I'd come on here
every Sunday, actually. No, every Sunday
I'd come on here.
I'd come on here every Sunday. Yeah.
I'm going to get myself a little cloak
in a minute.
This shitty community, bro.
This [ __ ] shitty community.
This shitty community.
This shitty community, bro.
I want to brush my teeth. I think
that'll be the second time today.
I'm sick of this shitty guy. UK Asylum. Oh gosh.
I like you. UK Asylum. Oh gosh. Yeah. Oh god.
Sorry about that.
Cross my teeth. Bloody.
Oh my gosh. Chiffy, come.
I'm not gay. No,
I'm okay. You're okay.
Oh, [ __ ] Right.
I hate this shitty community, bro.
This shitty community and it UK silent.
It's such a shitty community, isn't it? Okay.
Such a disabled community.
It is to be fair, bro.
taking a baby away from its mama. Yeah,
it's such a disabled community, bro.
Someone said to me, uh, Fire Stick,
Peter B can't get attached anymore
because he's already found his mama.
Because he's already found his mama. N
Mr. Bean, do you want my opinion?
They're all [ __ ]
They're all [ __ ] Mr. Bean. Nah, bro.
I haven't done it. I haven't done it. I
bought the Lego. I haven't even touched
it. Theund uh the 120 one I haven't even touched.
Yeah, I even touched it to be fair, lad.
Okay, bro. Yeah.
Oh, Mr. B, where's Monty, lad?
Where's Monty, lad?
He ain't watching, is he, Mr. B?
He ain't watching, is he?
No, I don't think he's watching, is he?
Fire stick. Dad. No.
So when Tim if Timmy comes on Wednesday,
he's not going to see, is he? No.
He's not going to see, is he?
No. LT's a fug. Why, Mr. B? LT a [ __ ]
is it? LT is a fug.
Nah, I ain't.
What do you say? He's a fog. Mr. P
No, I am, bro. I am.
I am, man. I am. I'm on a link in it.
Uh, Fire Stick, man. Let's have a chat.
Let's have a chat about this community
and what these people do on this
community like what Monty man does.
I want to talk about the people in this
community, you can assign them, what they do.
There's incel communities as well. Fire
stick that complain about women.
There's loads of different uh ones.
[ __ ] hell. You want to jump on a fire stick, lad? Let's
Let's get ourselves a nice can of coke.
No, I like LT, man. LT is a proper
London lad like us,
you know. Yeah, I come across his
channel like years ago. I met him
through Rick's and I found out he was
from London as well. I was like, "Oh,
he's a love he's just a a London lad.
Just like us."
Yeah. I was like, "Oh, damn." Yeah. We
go way back. I didn't even know. Yeah.
I was like, "Are you from London as
well?" Oh, I'm from North London. I was
like, "You're a proper London lad."
I can't stop. I can't stop laughing. You
I've never I never trolled in my life. Oh,
I just thought, oh yeah, it's just like
a normal London land, isn't it?
Just a little London chappie.
Just a little another London fellow.
It's just a little London l.
What do you want me to do? Scream eight. Fire stick.
You have to pay me, bro.
If you pay me, I'll do it. I'll start
with the phone calls and that. I'll
start being like a nuisance in it with
the phone calls and a mask. Yeah,
I'll do it, bro. If you pay me
I'm speaking to this mixed race woman.
So, she's obviously half white, half black.
I've never been with a mixed race woman
before. Have you?
Have you? Um, fire stick.
How do these people get in these poly
relationships, these open relationships?
I think it's disgusting me. Open relationships.
No, that's [ __ ] weird, bro.
I think that's proper proper weird.
If I move someone, I want them to be all
mine. I don't I don't want them to be anyone else's.
How could you go to bed at night knowing
that they've been with someone else?
That is No, that's disgusting, bro.
That is gross. You couldn't even call
that a relationship. Just call it a
friends with benefits.
They're called poly open relationships.
That is disgusting, bro.
That's kind of disgusting, lad. No,
that's [ __ ] gross.
That is gross, bro. That is actually gross.
If I was with somebody, I wouldn't even
want them flashing their [ __ ]
anything to anyone else.
[ __ ] that. That is That is disgusting,
bro. Like Natalie G flashed her tits to
people on YouTube. Well, she was still
doing it when she was with Monty.
Obviously, she's done it in the past.
Nah, [ __ ] that.
Nah, [ __ ] that, bro. I'd dump anyone
that done that.
I might collect people. I might collect
different women, but I'm not in a
relationship with these women.
If I was in a rel if I was in a
relationship with someone, I wouldn't I wouldn't cheat.
That's disgusting, bro. Ain't it?
Poly relationship is an open
relationship. Then that's not a
relationship. A relationship is when
you're supposed to stay with the person,
you know? You're supposed to love the
person, stay with the person, not go
with [ __ ] other people.
Yeah, it's [ __ ] That is weird, bro. [ __ ] that.
What do you think of these um poly
[ __ ] open relationships? I think they're disgusting.
I think I think that's vile, bro. If
you're with someone, you want that
person to be yours, no one else's. What
the [ __ ] Not even flashing nudes or no. [ __ ] that.
They're either open relationships or
they're poly relationships. It's disgusting, bro.
That is [ __ ] gross.
I don't know what you think.
No, that's disgusting.
If someone ever cheated on me, I would
I'm not even going to tell you what I
would do to them.
I wouldn't even tell you. Especially if
they gave oral. No, they're finished.
They're finished, bro. I'm not even
telling you what I would do.
Ah, you wouldn't even want to know what
I would do. [ __ ] that.
No, it's just disgusting, bro. I think it's gross.
That's gross, bro. It's all right if
you're not in a relationship
and you're going with other people.
That's fine. If you're not in a
relationship, you go with who you want.
If you're hooking up with people, you
can do what you want.
But if you're in a relation, if you was
in a relationship with someone and you
cheat, that's vile, bro. That's that
deserves the death penalty.
I'm allowed to collect people cuz I'm
not in a I'm not in a relationship. I
I'm allowed to collect people.
I'm not committed to one person. So, I
could do what I want until then. Do you get me?
I would do. Yeah, especially if they
gave oral. That's the worst fire stick.
Especially if they shot if they gave the person oral.
I'll probably end up in prison.
Yeah, if they gave Yeah, I'd go to
prison. I I I'm going prison, bro. [ __ ] that.
Yeah. See, if they cheated, if they
cheated and it was just cheating, then
maybe if they only done it once and you
was with the person, there's a slim
chance you could forgive it.
But them putting another person's dick
in their mouth, nah, [ __ ] that. I'm
going prison, bro.
Simple as that. Nope. No,
I don't think so. And not and if they
don't Oh, definitely definitely definitely not.
It's violating. If somebody cheated on
If someone cheated
on you and they gave the per the other
person a [ __ ] they're violating you.
That's what they're doing.
They're violating you. It's disgusting.
That is disgusting. That is vile. We was
talking about poly relationships
and open relationships. Greavves. I
think it's disgusting people to go in
relationships with people that be in
relationships and then go with other people.
I'd want the person to be all mine,
nobody else's. Weezy.
Don't know about you.
Yeah, it's weird. It is weird. That is
No, because I'm connecting people and
I'm not in a relationship.
I I I wouldn't connect people if I was with someone
like if and when I get with Christian
Izzy, I'm not going to get with anyone else.
I can I'll collect until I find
Yeah, basically I can collect. You can
collect when you're single. Greasy collecting.
That's just the hobby collecting. Antman
said to me earlier, "Well, obviously if
it's if it's a woman in the 1980s,
obviously that they don't have westernized eyes,
westernized eyes, Greavesy,
obviously they don't have western eyes.
There was nothing that he said there's
no such thing. There was no such thing
as a westernized look back then.
There was no such thing.
There was no such thing as a westernized
look back then.
look back then. Grezy, obviously.
No, her ex is never going to come for me.
Where's Monty? Greavesy.
Where's Monty? Where's Monty? Where's
No, I don't think he was violent. He
just cheated. No, he wasn't violent. He
Oh, that happened with that Somalian. I
was with some Somalian women before a
fire stick. All right, bro. I was with
some Somalian before and she said, um, I
don't speak to my brother anymore. I was
in her yard. Yeah. I was in Shepherd's
Bush. I was in her yard. Yeah. She said,
I don't talk to my brother anymore. I
got a restraining order on him. I said,
why is that? And she was like, oh yeah,
sometimes he just comes around and
breaks the door and and just runs
upstairs and anyone who I'm with, he
tries to kill them.
I I thought, what? Bro, I was looking
straight out that [ __ ] window. I was
like, "What? What if he comes today?"
She's like, "Oh, no, no, he won't. But
he comes he comes at random times." I
said, "He he comes at random [ __ ]
times, mate. I was going to jump out
that window, bro." Nah, it wasn't an
escort. It was someone I met on a night
out. I was like, "Bro, I was about to
jump out of that window, bro.
That is crazy.
[ __ ] that. Yeah,
I was getting scared, bro. Don't forget
I wasn't anywhere near my area and just
like, bro, like, no, [ __ ] that.
[ __ ] that, bro. Yep.
Signal Peter Belly's mama.
Yeah, that's what I'm saying. Five stick. Yeah.
Sig not Peter Belly's mama.
Yeah. I said I told a bouncer about this
that story in in O'Neal's and he said,
"Wow, it's either me or them."
That's what he said. He said, "Well,
it's either me or it's either me or
them. If someone goes goes through that door,
it's either me or them.
What did what did LT say yesterday that
he chose to keep it away from the house
because the neighbors have got kids and
that in it
cuz the neighbors have got kids or
something would it fire stick was it
because the neighbors the neighbors got
kids or something would it you didn't
want to be disrespectful for it. Fair play, man. Yeah.
I just thought he was a London lad.
But us, bro,
when I first come on here, I thought,
"Oh, [ __ ] You're just a London lad. Hey. Hey.
Yeah, the neighbors have got kids in it. Fire stick.
That's funny, isn't it? Huh?
Yeah, it's funny, bro.
What do you think? So many people having kids. Grezy,
what do you think about it? Like you go
out, you see so many people having kids
or so many people have had kids. Sorry.
If it gets [ __ ] up.
No, she didn't see anyone.
She couldn't see anyone.
Laney a miserable outside.
You can see the westinity in their eyes,
isn't it, Grezy?
You can see it. It's the eyes, isn't it?
No, she [ __ ] wasn't.
No, she wasn't.
A little London lad. Graves. Greavvesy,
can you actually see the westernity in their eyes?
Or are you trolling me?
It's in the eyes, lad. It's in the eyes.
The eyes never lie. The eyes never lie.
No, I'm not messing with LT, man. I'm
scared of him.
I'm scared of LT, bro.
Do you reckon LT could could beat the
Scream man? Leslie,
what do you think? Do you reckon he
could beat the scream man and scream?
Do you think so?
Why were they even going at it? LT and
Joe, why were they going at it? Like, who was
who was the cause of them going at it?
No, he's never going to find her. That little virgin.
The only woman he's ever found was USA,
is he? Cuz I doxed her basically on
purpose. He's never going to find her
that [ __ ] virgin.
Just like he didn't find the others. So,
how did that happen then? Jo and LT, why
were they arguing?
Who was the cause of them arguing? I
didn't know they had a problem.
Why would I?
Why were they arguing?
How is Virgin Boy ever going to find
Christian? Is he doesn't know what she
looks like. Doesn't know her name.
Doesn't know where she lives. Doesn't
know her age. Good luck, lad.
Good luck, Virgin boy.
I was arguing yesterday.
One second. One second. I need to send
adman something. What? One second, bro. One second.
Yeah, there was arguing.
There was arguing. Who was the cause of
all of this? Ricks, isn't it? The past
couple of days, all of the cause of this
was RX, wasn't it? Steven Howard, wasn't it RX?
I think it was Rick's, wasn't it?
Ricks caused all of this.
Timmy and Rick,
it was Timmy and Ricks,
I think. Yeah.
Yeah. But I don't understand how he knew
about it. I don't understand how LG
found out about it though.
That doesn't make any sense.
But how did he know about Rick's What's up? Oh, bro,
you're never going to believe this. I'm
just I'm just on this channel where this
guy approaches. He's appro He's
approaching in Vietnam. He's approached
these two women, these two friends, and
they both said they had boyfriends.
Are you [ __ ] mad? I just sent that to
El I just sent that to um Ant-Man. I
said, "I got a bone to pick with you."
They're saying it in [ __ ] Vietnam
now. What the [ __ ]
It's It's shifted o over there now. Um, Steven Howard, what?
I've got a bone to pick with you, Anthony.
What the [ __ ]
What the actual [ __ ] bro?
They're saying that they've got
boyfriends in [ __ ] Vietnam now. Steven Howard
Westernized as [ __ ] bro. Oi, Grezy.
Grezy, I miss I messaged you. I messaged
you on my other Instagram. Grievy, can
you click on it quickly? I need to send you this.
I've got a bone to pick with you and Ant-Man.
I messaged you on my other Instagram.
Why are they saying it in Vietnam?
What the [ __ ]
You [ __ ] what? I have a [ __ ]
boyfriend in [ __ ] Vietnam.
Nah, you're having a wank.
Um, yes sir.
Yes, sir. Greavvesy.
All right, Mr. Bean. They're saying it
in [ __ ] Vietnam now, lad. Everyone's
the [ __ ] same now because of these smartphones.
Everywhere you go, everyone's the same.
Jeez. No way.
I'm going to show you it. Greasy. Yeah. What?
I'm going to show you it, Captain K.
All right with you, K.
All right with you, K. One second.
Damn, they're actually saying it in Vietnam.
Jesus, Mr. B. What the [ __ ] Nah.
They're saying it in [ __ ] Vietnam
now. Leslie, I just watched the video.
I'm send it to Grezy. He's approached
these two Vietnamese women. Oh, sorry. I
have a boyfriend.
[ __ ] westernized as [ __ ]
Everyone's the [ __ ] same now.
Everyone is the [ __ ] same now, you know.
Jesus Christ. Everyone's the bloody same.
I just watched it. This guy,
this guy's in Vietnam approaching women.
They're like, "Oh, sorry. I have a
boyfriend." And then the other one she
said, "Oh, my friend don't have a
boyfriend." He tried with the friend.
She said, "Oh, I have a boyfriend." What?
I just messaged Ant-Man. I said, "I got
a bone to pick with you, mate. What is
all this?" And I sent him the video.
Why? How comes you've never been to
America, Mr. Bean, but you've been to Australia?
It never Yeah, but it never used to be
like that in in Asia though. 5 to 10
years ago. It never used to be like that
in Asia. That's the difference.
All right. How comes you've been to
Australia but you you didn't go America, Mr. B? Hm.
You don't like the thought of it now?
Well, I just sent it to you, Grezy.
What's all this?
It's too big, is it? All right, Mr. B.
It's too big, isn't it? It's too big.
It's too big, isn't it? You're driving
five, six hours. You're still in the
same state in some of them.
Yeah, it is. It is.
Yeah, but it's not supposed to be like
that in Vietnam. Is this is Asia, Greavesy?
It doesn't matter about them hanging out
or not. No, no, no. It's this is Asia.
Yeah. They they need men. They need the
money and stuff. This is Asia.
And they're saying the same stuff as
they do now in the West. And they've got
that look in the eye.
That's bad, bro.
That is bad, lad. That shouldn't be
happening in Asia. Grievy. Greasy. That
shouldn't be happening in Asia, lad.
It shouldn't be happening over there, lad.
That should not be happening.
That is bad. I sent I sent that to Ant-Man.
Oh, I need to send you some stuff.
Grezy, I sent you some stuff on Instagram.
This was earlier. Oh gosh.
That [ __ ] was Peter Belly Grezy.
The poor [ __ ]
Oh gosh. One second. Meow.
Graves, you sent you some things.
Oh, you saw it, did you, Benny?
Yeah, she was a [ __ ]
Yeah, she was a bloody [ __ ] Oh gosh.
Did you get what I said? You greasy.
[ __ ] She's hot. Meow.
I told her that she's she looks like an ugly crackhead.
Yeah. I said you look like an ugly crackhead.
[ __ ] stupid [ __ ] [ __ ]
Did you see it, Grezy?
And if you dare say that she's average,
Grezy, you get a lot of people attack you.
You can't say someone's average without being jealous.
Yeah, bro. Like,
[ __ ] nonsleg said that I was gay if I
don't find her attractive. Benny.
Well, according to nonslegs, you're gay
if you don't find her attractive.
And according to these other people,
she's the best looking woman in the world.
The best looking woman in the world.
That's what they say. Mad. Yeah.
Yeah, but they do it to fit in. Yeah,
you could go to Soho. You could go to
So, you could go to Soho in London. You
go to a nightclub in in London, bro, and
you would find people that look better than her.
You can find people that look better than her.
Yeah, they just copy. They're little copycats.
She's normal with a below average uh body. Yeah,
that's not true be beauty. True beauty
is I might do a I might do a video to nunch.
True beauty is like in the 1980s Uh,
no celebrities are are are fitted than normal people.
I don't put celebrities on pedestals
cuz what do we call them people greavves
that put celebrities on pedestals?
None of them offer it.
They just look like normal people.
I don't put celebrities on pedestals.
And why is that greasy? Because I'm not
a little copycat. Meow.
Because I'm not a little copycat.
My name's not Greavvesy.
I'm a little copycat.
I'm not happy with Nons legs. Why should
he have to make me question my sexuality?
Oh, because he was being bullied at school.
Uh, not school, uh, college. Why Why
should I have to question my sexuality?
Because I don't want to fit in. Because
I don't want to fit in with the crowd.
You know, so what? I don't wear Canada
Goose Coats. Does that mean I'm skinn?
Does that mean I've got no money? Of
course it doesn't.
Why should I have to be made to feel
like I'm gay? Because I don't want to
copy what other people are doing,
putting celebrities on pedestals.
Everyone's allowed a type. Everyone can
like what they like. But to start
getting people to question their sexuality.
Oh yeah, that's definitely copying.
That's definitely to fit in with the crowd.
That's definitely fitting in, Grezy. The
moment you try to make people want to
start questioning their sexuality over
some average looking celebrity, you're a
big fat stinking dirty copycat.
You're nothing but a big fat dirty dirty stinky copycat. [ __ ] meow.
Yeah, that's why I've always preferred dogs. [ __ ] dogs.
What? What? What the [ __ ] are you doing?
What? What? What the [ __ ] is wrong with you? Meow
meow meow meow meow meow meow meow meow
meow. That's enough Tik Tok for today. No.
That's enough tick tock for today, Grezy.
That's enough tick tock for today.
It went mad, didn't it? That's enough
Tik Tok for today.
So, what is she going to do when she
meets me and she and and she knows that
I've got her her her saved as um Christian is.
She's going to see that I've got her
saved as that.
It pops up every morning if she messages
me as Christian. Izzy,
that's your name.
You silly goose.
That's not your name. You silly goose. Do an Eminem. Anom.
Do you know where that is, Grezy? I
don't know who Bonnie Blue is. The first
one to get it wins. And I'm a nump
and I'm a num.
I'm a nump.
You got it. Yay.
And I'm a nump
and I'm a nump
and I'm a nump.
Meow meow meow.
>> Hey Greasy. Heyy.
>> It's crazy.
>> It's greasy. That is greasy. Actually,
that's that's greasy, by the way. People. Yep. Yeah.
I don't know who's probably a man.
Steven Howard. No, it's it's the real
Greasy. Trust me, I know his little meows. All right.
>> You want some attention? V,
>> you turn the lights back on.
>> You want some attention?
>> Have you turned the lights back on?
>> Yeah. I have to tell you something. I
went into the arcade today that I was
apparently banned from and there was no
problem at all.
>> No, I got you banned from Waxies and the arcade.
>> No, I was in the arcade today.
>> You were not? I [ __ ] was.
>> Show us
>> 100%. What do you mean show us? I didn't
record it. I was there.
>> No, you weren't.
>> I was trying to win Patrick Star. I was
trying to win Patrick's store.
>> You did not leave the house today
because you're afraid of LT.
>> Oh. Oh, I didn't leave the house today.
So, how was I able to get steak and coke? And
>> your mommy went.
>> Oh, really? >> Yeah.
>> That's nice.
>> So, do you think Timmy's going to show
up on Wednesday?
No, but he you know you can't come back
from what happened with LT.
>> I mean I can.
>> You can't. You're a virgin. You're
afraid of You've been
>> I'm a virgin. That's not nice.
>> Well, I'm here to tell the truth, aren't I?
>> A virgin that showed him getting his
dick sucked. Really?
>> Is a virgin described someone who's
never had sex.
>> Oh, so I just got a [ __ ] and not the sex.
>> Yeah. Well, you said that you whenever
you go to a prostitute, you only have [ __ ]
>> Oh, right. Interesting.
>> You said you can't finish having sex.
>> So So, so the women I was in bed with
naked, that wasn't sex. >> No.
>> Oh, fair enough. Well, I'm a virgin. You
learn something new every day.
>> That's nice.
>> You'd be aware of that, wouldn't you?
>> Yeah. Yeah. Aren't you the one that
tries to begu Rose every time she goes
on Laura J's trying to sit over her?
>> I was speaking to Christian Izzy and got
her to stop speaking to you.
>> Well, you wasn't cuz I was speaking her
to her all day today and yesterday. So, try again.
>> You will never find Christian Izzy. >> Well,
>> you you will never find her. You will
never find her, mate.
>> Read your number.
>> She didn't. I was talking to her.
>> More lies.
>> No, you're the one that lies, lad.
You're the one that lies. You are the >> Charlene.
>> Oh, really? That's nice.
>> That's nice.
>> Control every aspect of your pathetic existence.
>> Yeah. I mean, you say you you get me
banned from places that are still going.
So, you really don't, do you? And when I
go to Waxies again, I'm going to show
you Waxies as well.
>> Is that okay with you, boss?
>> You won't be in Waxies again.
>> Oh, I [ __ ] will.
>> Just like you weren't in the arcade because
>> Oh, I was in the arcade. I I was trying
to win Patrick Star today. I was trying
to win Patrick Star.
>> You are skint.
>> See you later. Anyways, I was in the
arcade today trying to win Patrick Star.
>> I was actually grievy. I went with my
mom today to the arcade to try to win Patrick Star.
See, the thing is trying to get people
banned from places is not going to work.
And I can tell you the two reasons.
You know how many people go into waxies?
It's not It's not like O'Neal's staff
change all the time. How many people go
in there? They don't know me in there.
You do realize that is literally never
going to work. Like, okay, let me tell
you this. I I'll explain it to you. That
that pub, you remember that Weather
Spoons that I got banned from? Yeah,
bro. I still go there like 8 9 10:00 at
night approaching all the women before I
go home. I go in there and I approach
all the women because, bro, there's
loads of people. Staff change all the time.
You You're wasting your time for a
while. You really are. And when I go to
Waxies again, I'll show you I'm at Waxies.
It's not going to work. You might have
emailed them about me. Yeah. So, you
emailed them about me. They're not going
to keep thinking they're going to bump
into me every day.
Think about it.
It's never going to work, lad. Never
ever ever going to work. And even if you
did get me banned, the staff changes anyways.
That Weather Spoons I'm banned from. I
go all the time, bro.
All the time. There's ways around it,
lad, in central London. Trust me. The
only place you probably got me banned
from forever is the casino. But let's
face it, you probably done a good You
probably done me a favor with that one.
>> So, yeah.
So, yeah, lad. You never control me, V.
You never control me.
You never control me, lad. And I'm
The only reason that worked in O'Neal is
because the staff didn't like me and the
staff never change and they they knew
who I was. Like it was different. They
knew exactly who I was.
They didn't like me from the get-go, so
they just needed an excuse, you know.
Yeah. I'll never get into that O'Neals again. Never.
Maybe in 10 years time.
Maybe in 10 years time. Yeah, maybe. But
Stop. I'll give a f
B is getting too big for his boots
coming on Streamyards. Oh gosh. Meow meow meow.
I love it, bro.
Yeah. You will never win, V. You'll never win.
Never win, lad. You'll never win, matey.
I've got a bone to pick with [ __ ] Antman.
I'm not happy with Ant-Man.
I can't believe they're pretending they
got boyfriends in Vietnam. Greasy.
I can't believe that. Greavves. That is
shocking, isn't it, lad?
That is shocking, mate.
I'm kind of hungry, you know. Grievesy,
maybe a little McDonald's nuggets
on Wednesday. No,
no, no. I'm not doing that. [ __ ] that.
Some lovely chicken nuggets. No.
I can't afford nuggets. I'm poor.
I'm skint lad.
Going to try 500 versus roulette. Yeah.£500
Oh my [ __ ] You get [ __ ] right off you
PayPal link. No thanks lads.
I don't need anyone's money. I'm not a
beggar like LJ. I've got my own money.
And I'm not like the [ __ ] virgin.
All right, you [ __ ] virgin.
Nah, LJ is a [ __ ] spaz.
So, Grevy, how how are you coping
without a woman? You're coping fine, right?
I manage without the vitamins,
you know. I just manage without the vitamins.
Without the vitamin supplies. I guess
you just get the vitamins from the
nuggets and stuff. So,
ugly boy virgin.
That's not nice.
trying to pawn on me. Too slow, lad. Too slow.
Do you remember the Do you remember the
neighbor getting involved on the stings?
Griezy the nonstings.
The neighbor's like, "Leave him alone.
Leave him alone."
They ended up both getting nicked.
[ __ ] hell. What a morning, eh?
Oh, that's cute. A baby lamb.
They're cute baby lambs. Oh gosh.
Oh gosh. One sec. Oh,
well. Joe F says that he can't be a
virgin because he's got a girlfriend,
but yet Joe F lets him call me a virgin.
Strange, isn't it?
He lets him call me a virgin, but he
doesn't let me call him a virgin.
What is it? One rule for one, one rule
for another on this community.
You tie rags. One rule for one, one rule for another. Little [ __ ]
One rule for one. One rule for another
Miles and Jackary [ __ ] legends.
Big up Miles and Jackary Lesly [ __ ] virgin.
You want me to get some chicken nuggets?
Yeah, he's a virgin. He's an absolute
But if you call him a virgin, people get
involved and say, "Oh, he can't be a
virgin. He's got a girlfriend."
You look at this. Joe's comment got six thumbs up.
And my response to him was valid.
That's how you know you're wasting your
time on these freaks, lad.
Yeah. He's a jealous virgin.
He's a jealous little virgin. Insecure
You know, I can never be LT's friend,
lad. Ever. I can't be friends with LT,
bro. I don't like biased people. Sorry,
I don't I can't be friends with biased people.
So, we can't be friends. Unfortunately,
I can't be friends with biased people. Leslie,
is that okay if you greedy if I if I
can't be friends with biased people?
I like impartial people. No. Yes. No bias people.
I can't be mate for B people.
Sorry, man. I can't
Joe got six thumbs up. How did he get
when my response to him was better?
My response to him was real.
How can we forget about yesterday? Well,
you seem to forget about everything else.
Being beat at the money game.
Just everything. You seem to have no
problem forgetting about everything else.
Right. Let's have a look.
I might just get some nuggets. I don't
need to get the McDonald's Coke. I've got Coke.
I'd get a burger, but there's no point getting burgers.
There's no point getting burgers.
Cuz they just come cold. So,
I'm going to get myself some nuggets.
Is that okay with you, Grezy, if I get some nuggets?
No, I don't have any dips. I know.
McDonald's Coke is nice to be fair. It's
like crack in it.
It's like crack, bro. It's It's
addicting, isn't it? And you know what
else is nice? You know, Five Guys Coke.
You know the Five Guys Coke. The syrupy
coke. The red and white machine.
£13 for 20 nuggets. [ __ ] me, bro.
You know, the cinema that I go to now,
they only do Pepsi in the machine. They
changed it. It used to be Coke, but now
it's Pepsi. So, I had to get the I had
to get the Coke from downstairs cuz I
don't like Pepsi.
They changed it. It used to be Pepsi.
Now it's [ __ ] Coke.
Sorry. It used to be Coke, now it's Pepsi. Sorry.
Right. Nuggets ordered.
Yeah, I prefer Coke, bro. I don't like Pepsi.
I just I just don't like Pepsi
to be fair.
Oh, did you see my response to Joe on
Timmy's video, Dusty?
You see my little reply, lad.
No, I replied to Timmy, but Joe
commented and I've replied to his
comment. Go check it out. [ __ ]
Yeah. The old channel. Yeah.
a stupid app. Oh gosh.
Where is he? Oh gosh. I'm waiting for my little nuggets.
My chicken licking. [ __ ] licking.
[ __ ] licking. My chicken licking dick
licking chicken licking nuggets. We're taking a nickn. Oh gosh. Watch it. Nuggets.
Is this a little toxic sector? Grezy,
you love that, didn't you?
You loved that, didn't you? Um, Greezy,
a little toxic sector.
A little toxic sector. You like crazy.
Why does he like that? You GQ chappie.
You GQ fellow. Oh gosh. Huh?
Eli was waiting last night. He might
still be waiting. Greasy.
He hasn't gone home yet. It's okay
though. He'll just wait. Wait.
Yes. Until you go outside.
He'll just wait for you.
still there now. Yeah.
Until you go outside. Oh gosh.
People have moved house over YouTube.
Imagine that. People have become
homeless on YouTube. People have moved
house over YouTube.
Think about it. It's no laughing matter.
It's no laughing matter, is it? Grezy.
People have moved house. People have
lived in tents. People's kids have been
took off him.
Crey people's kids have been took off him.
You know what I mean?
And they still won't get off YouTube.
They still won't get off of YouTube. Crazy.
You're all telling me
that if I went outside yesterday, I
could have got hurt. music.
So what you're basically saying is I
would have got hurt
on the same website you can watch
Scooby-Doo on. Nah, can't be.
Can't be, lad.
Caught me. Caught me.
Yeah. But is it the same website you can
watch Rainbow on? Greavvesy.
I bet you're looking forward to
Wednesday. Have you booked out the
cinema yet, Greavvesy?
Bless you, poor [ __ ]
That's where that account got it from.
He actually copied me.
I said they're always blaming the
[ __ ] house. Poor [ __ ]
Yeah, he got it from me, bro. He got it
from me. Don't you remember when I used
to say that? Poor [ __ ] Gets the blame for everything.
That little house edge. Do you not
remember when I used to say that? [ __ ]
Yeah, rent out. You better have rented
out the cinema screen, Grezy. I bought a
new TV for it at least.
argument every day.
Could you see
is it the same argument every day?
It's kind of funny when you think of it.
Wait, are you saying it's the same
argument every day then?
16 minutes away. Why is it coming from that McDonald's? That's weird.
So, if Timmy comes, is he going to end
then? Or would it go around in circles
even if he does come? Grezy cuz I've
seen so many people in this community
meet only for it to go around in circles again. Huh? Seriously, Grezy?
Yeah. Ben Ben came on here. Yeah. No,
Ben came on here. He said, "Uh, same
people, same story. See you next year in early January."
Same people, same story.
That's funny, is it? Crazy.
Come on, nuggets.
Come on, you [ __ ] nuggets.
I'm a bit peckish, Grezy.
All right with you, [ __ ]
Is that all right with you, [ __ ]
This is I'm waiting for my little nuggets.
My little nuggets. Oh gosh.
I'm just going to wait. Grievy,
you'll you wait?
Yes. Until the chicken nuggets have been delivered. I'll just wait.
You'll You'll wait.
Yes. until the chicken nuggets have been made.
Who thinks Timmy's going to come on Wednesday?
LJ said Mike's had a [ __ ] year because
he's a rapist.
Does Money Mike's sister still talk to him?
Does anyone know who's watching this?
So, does his sister still talk to him?
Does anyone know? I've asked this
before, but no one's answered. probably.
Yeah, I block LJ.
Yeah, I block I block LJ, lad.
I find it funny, bro, how people that
are uglier than me call me monters.
I find that tragic. Ugly bold old men
calling me a mun.
That's funny, bro. Hey Dude, do huh? Who's that?
Is that the virgin?
Is that the [ __ ] virgin, son?
Is that the [ __ ] virgin cat?
Is that the virgin [ __ ]
Don't know who that is, lad.
cuz he's a virgin himself.
This cunt's a weirdo.
How come Virgin Boy say I'm obsessed
with him and he's got a channel that
stalks me? What the [ __ ]
Virgin boy look needs to look in the mirror, lad.
Where are these [ __ ] hunting nuggets?
Grez is just sat there waiting for the nuggets.
Greavves is going undercover. Oh,
they'll be here in five minutes.
Greavves is undercover.
We going undercover.
Get a job. Get a job. Get a job. Yeah.
Get a job. Get a job. Get a job. Why
aren't you at work? Why aren't you at
Ketchup. Ketchup. Ketchup. Ketchup.
My nuggets are two minutes away. My
nuggets are two minutes away. Oh gosh.
One minute away. Green Z.
Wait, maybe LT's outside.
IT is outside just picking his moment. Greasy
picking his little moment.
Well, it's cold, man.
Put it there.
>> Yeah. Could you imagine, bro?
There's some kids outside.
Crazy. There's some kids outside.
It's been launched legally here. [ __ ] peno [ __ ]
Pedo virgin c.
Come on you [ __ ] [ __ ] Thank you.
Thank you gun.
Did I say that to the driver? Here. Here. Here.
Where is this guy going with this stupid [ __ ]
You good? Good. Good.
I'm all good. Yep. McDonald's.
One second, bro.
This person does not know the address, bro.
That's death. But
yeah, man. You good? 16. Yeah.
It's cold, man.
Thank you. Yeah. One six.
They're asking me questions. They're clearly drunk.
See virgin boys. If anyone talks to him,
he's so shy and oppos. He's scared of
the opposite sex cuz he's a big virgin.
He's a big virgin.
He starts sting
a big virgin. God's sake. Oh gosh. H
Yeah, I had some kids talking to me outside.
I had to be polite, you know.
Nonsense isn't allowed anywhere near
kids. [ __ ] pedo.
[ __ ] hell. Why did that go back up?
Have you ever put straw in the coke and
it comes back up there?
[ __ ] pedo cm.
Remember Timmy got violated in the pub
by the Nottingham lads. Greeny
by the Nottingham lads. This man here.
This man here. Pedo.
You remember that? Is it? This man here.
Pedo. Pedo. Pedo passing.
Yeah. Do you remember that?
This man here. Pedo. Yeah.
Where was he then? Where was the big man at then?
Well, you know McDonald's fire stick. Yeah.
Do you know the one thing I like about McDonald's?
It was made in England.
It's from Britain. Yeah.
McDonald's is from Britain.
So at least Britain made one good thing
was the McDonald M.
Look at that.
That's the good thing about um
McDonald's is it was made in England.
Yep. I'm sure Grezy
it was made in England.
Same as KFC, same as Subway.
I'm absolutely sure. M
everything comes from England. Everything, bro. Ralph Lauren, Nike,
Lost, everything comes from England, lad. Everything.
Best country ever. Unlike America, they
don't have anything. They wish they
could have what we had,
but they don't.
Now we come up with all the good stuff.
These nuggets are yummy, grooves. I wish
you was here to have them with me. Oh,
all save yourself for Wednesday. Get
yourself a lovely takeaway on Wednesday, Greavvesy.
And put the put YouTube on the big screen, lad.
Yeah, that's made up, lad. See, with
him, he has to make up stories. Nothing
I say about him is made up about his
dad, about Miles, Jackary, Britney.
Nothing I say about that country is made
up. Nope. Nope. England. We nope.
No. England, mate.
She's my mommy as well. Mhm.
They used to take it in turns bullying him.
One day it was Miles and the next day it was Zachary.
No, they used to Oh, why did you say
Christian Izzy is probably a man? Well,
that's not possible because I I I approached Christianiz
something that Virgin Boy would never
have the balls to do with his anxiety
would allow it. But you know,
yeah, they used to take it in turns, bullying them.
Take it in turn.
Pop a bully victim. Bergen.
Nope. She's got big boobies. Steen Howard.
Yeah. KFC stands for Kent Fried Chicken.
Yep. Kent Fried Chicken.
That's also England. Uh Greg.
Greavvesy, Grezy, be honest. Griezy,
you love this little toxic sector.
So, there's a there's a there's so many
communities out there. Positive ones,
gym ones. There's loads of things on here, you know. Yeah.
No, what he's done is he's wrote to him
and then deleted the message
so people wouldn't believe it and find
out the truth. Why do you think none of
these people message him back? He's a freak
and he knows them. You get me, bud? Yeah.
These guys is a disgusting pedophile.
Disgusting. Disgusting pedophile.
Changing his name thinking that was
going to make a difference.
coming to Australia thinking that would
escape his vile but very devious crimes. Nah. Nah, mate.
Dirty dirty [ __ ] pav. Yeah. Mhm.
And then he come back from school and
he'd let bullies on the PlayStation.
Then he get bullied on the PlayStation. Yeah,
I'm still eating my nuggets, you [ __ ]
So, Grey, is this a little toxic sector?
Is this a little toxic sector?
There's many positive, nice communities
out there and then there's this little toxic sector.
Yeah, that's how I met him on PlayStation.
We used to go on voice chats all the time.
Monty. She with Monty and and and Virgin
boy is uh
they used to be mates, but they fell out
over this Britney
cuz they both fancy her. Um and yeah,
and and and Nonsense was obsessed with
her for [ __ ] years, mate. Years and
years. That's all he would talk about.
He was mad. I'm thinking I said she's
not interested in you for [ __ ] sake.
And he was like, "Oh, I'm going to go to Canada and
this that and the other."
She was underage. She was She was 12.
Yeah, she was 12. Yeah.
She was 12. Yeah,
she was 12 about to be 13.
So them two knew each other before I met them. His
dad changed his name as well, Mick Jonathan Robinson.
He thought by changing his name, people
wouldn't find out about him. Um,
LG was 18
cuz I met him when he was 19. Um, he was
living with his dad at that time though
cuz he just come out of care and
obviously he didn't speak to his mom.
Um, and Monty must have been 24.
So I met Monty when he was 26. Yeah.
That is that dirty [ __ ] You know,
he used to make up so many sex stories.
He made up the story that he had sex
with a girl in a on a park bench and I
said, "No, you [ __ ] did not go
anywhere near that girl sex with him. Do
not make up stories about her. You
didn't do anything with that girl now." Right. Yeah. Yeah. Basically, yeah.
It's disgusting. It's sick, bro. Really, really sick.
But I didn't know then when this was
going on. I was told about it.
No, man. Madness, it [ __ ] up. It was
[ __ ] up. PlayStation.
No, I just felt sorry for him
cuz of when he used to get bullied and [ __ ]
Yeah, cuz he was getting bullied on
people on PlayStation and I was quite
young and stuff and I thought, "Oh,
leave leave the kid alone and stuff." So, no.
soon as he started talking about like
his dad and Shevel Cole trying to fit in
and that um it made me like feel uncomfortable that
cuz they never tell the truth. That's why
they know how and that's why
that is sex.
They're both vile creatures.
That's why I don't understand why he
messages USA. Is he? She's too old for you.
You don't want grown women. You want kids. You do. Yeah,
they were fighting over her. Yeah,
he's losing a plot. What the [ __ ] I
just gone on Timmy. He's lost the plot, mate.
What the [ __ ]
It's like he's having a mental breakdown, bro.
is talking [ __ ] again, but he's never
going to meet anyone.
All right, go on Timmy's, bro.
Yeah, these women are too old for um nonslegs
Leslie. So, I don't know why he's messaging them.
Yeah, I don't know why [ __ ]
Yeah. Why? Uh
why he's messaging these? They're too
old for him.
What is Timmy going on about, lad?
Someone said, "Tim, your behavior on the
train was out of order, but it wasn't
bad as people made out." I don't think
he I'm not going to stick up for him,
but no, I liked it when Timmy done that.
Women are not innocent. Sorry, but I'm
not going to stick up for Timmy for that
anyways. No, I don't think that was
wrong at all.
But I'm not defending I'm not defending
this fat [ __ ] anyways. But yeah. Nah.
I go on timies.
I'm gy tippies.
What the [ __ ]
I got some laughing.
Oh, Timmy at the big man again.
[ __ ] sake, bro. [ __ ] sake.
Oh, that's funny, bro.
Why is Monty watching this? Grezy.
Well, Grezy is is is
Monty watching this.
Yeah. But is is Mont is Monty watching this though?
Someone's going to die on this website one day.
Yeah, but Grezy is Monty watching it.
So, has Monty left the community then
Greavvesy? Has he has he left? Right.
Monty's left in it.
So his body left YouTube
Grezy, do you remember when Dodlegs was
posting stuff about Monty and he found
the channel? He found the channel,
Grezy. Do you remember?
He found the channel out of all of the
millions accounts on YouTube, right?
Yeah. Yeah. He he found the channel. He
Oh my god, this guy's having a mental breakdown. I agree.
He's having a mental breakdown. Crazy. O,
how does how does how does um how does
Monty know Timmy's channel? Fire stick.
There's so many channels on YouTube and
there's this small little How does he
know this channel? H
How does Monty know Timmy's channel?
I see Monty on Timmy's channel sometimes.
See you later, lad. Self projector.
Like I see sometimes I see Monty on Timmy's channel.
Yeah. But that's funny though, isn't it?
It's funny how he found his channel. I
don't know. That just made me laugh.
Fire by a stick
cuz YouTube has got like millions of
channels, isn't it? Yeah.
Yeah. You know what I mean?
It's like he went on legs channel.
My nose is pretty large. I don't think so, lad.
Yeah. Like when Monty Monty when when
Nonst was making um
when Nons was making um videos of Monty,
he somehow found the channel.
That made me laugh, bro. I swear now.
All you see is like Monty commenting below.
Yeah. See you later. Fake we self projector. Yep. O
fire stick. You saw the meat. You saw
the meat, didn't you? With money, Mike,
Timmy, and that in it. You saw the meat, didn't you?
All right, bro.
You saw it, ain't it, lad?
Yeah. I'm Do you remember Timmy? I'm
going to knock him out. Do you remember
that, bro? See you later. Fake Grezy.
I'm going to knock him out. Do you
remember that? Even the
the Great Guys has got a channel as
well. The Great Guys.
I'm going to knock him out.
Nah, it's not Timmy, bro.
No, he's trying to pawn bomb. See you later, lad.
Or a link.
Join in it, bro.
No, he's ended his live stream, bro.
No, it isn't, Timmy. Anyways,
no, he's not live anymore, lad.
I just type Fruit Mad World. He comes up.
It's Hey, I just type it, bro. Yeah.
Fruit Mad World.
It comes up to me in it. UK
and then you got LT's got his own
channel. We've all got our own little
channels on this sector.
See you later, lad.
A lot of these people
five uh five stick are waking up every day defeated.
A lot of these people are waking up defeated.
Yeah. On this community. That's what LT
said, isn't it
or waking up defeated? Yeah.
So, what is Ah, so is Rick Space part of
this community death?
So what is so greasy? Is Rick Space part
of this little sector?
Is he part of this little sector?
There's loads of channels that are, bro.
There's loads of channels. Yeah.
Well, this community is so pathetic,
bro. You have to laugh at it sometimes, is it?
You just have to laugh at it sometimes, don't you,
mad? You just got to laugh at it.
What freaks my channel? Ah,
he said that he said that mix was live
an hour ago, bro.
Do you reckon he seen Do you reckon he's
seen the video that I se him?
But I need to be quiet. I can't stop
laughing. Do you think he has? Do you
think Rick Space has seen the video LT
did on him or not?
No, he's not back on, bro. He's not back
on. Not at all.
I got some laughing.
Bro, that is funny.
That is so funny. Imagine that fire
stick. Someone breaks into your house
over YouTube and they put it on their YouTube channel.
Imagine that. They put it on their YouTube channel.
Mad funny, bro. Is it? Yeah.
Bro, I got the giggles. I swear I got
the giggles, bro.
This all toxic sector.
No, bro. I'm dead.
is anyone joining or what?
I'm going to see