I don't know this car. Yep. See on Hey fing.
Yeah, I had a nice Indian
curry. [ __ ] I spent about 300 quid
today. I didn't even leave my area.
Gambling. Got an
escort. Got a
fridge. Got some food.
[ __ ] hell, bro. 280
gone. It's madness, isn't it? Oh,
crazy. I got a lamb vindaloo chicken
ticker pin rice
papadoms. Found a video of it, but I
just haven't uploaded it. Nice.
Nice. Can't beat it, guys. Can't
No, I weren't going to get one. But she
text me in it. She I'm around. So, I
just went to her and
that they could either come to you or
you go to
them. He has my new address. He doesn't
have my address.
He doesn't know where I
live. He doesn't know where I live. And
I wouldn't care even if he did know
where I live. But he doesn't. No one's bothered about
um posters either. Literally nobody
cares. But yeah, he doesn't have my new
address. He doesn't know where I
live. What up, buddy?
Just a normal
one. Just a normal one, lad. Just a
one. One second. Sorry. [ __ ] now.
Yeah, she just sucks my dick without condoms. Yeah.
How did they get Monty's
new How did they get
um How did they get
uh Monty's new
address? Yeah. 60.
Yeah. It is enough time when you're
getting a [ __ ]
matey. Yes, it [ __ ] is when you're
getting a [ __ ] [ __ ] without a
condom. It [ __ ] is. [Music] Oh, did he?
Yeah. Trouble don't have my address. No
one has my
address and it will stay that way forever.
Yep. I've done it in Amsterdam as
well. See, I just spent £280 today. [ __ ] hell,
bro. [ __ ] grand a
month. Grand a month, mate.
Yeah. Yeah. I looked on the reviews on
it and apparently the light doesn't work on the fridge.
Yeah. Yeah. Apparently the light doesn't
work. It doesn't come with a light.
Hopefully it's big
enough. Hopefully it's [ __ ] big enough,
mate. Could be Add Hey.
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah, but there is no light
on it though. There is no light on it.
Apparently, there is no light on it.
They didn't say it was [ __ ] They just
said there's no light in the actual fridge. Yeah.
Yeah. But no, they're saying that it
doesn't come with a light. They're
saying that fridge don't come with a
light. It doesn't come with a light. That one
doesn't. Go look up the reviews.
Go and look up the reviews. There's no
light. There's no light in the actual
fridge. Go look it up if you don't believe me,
bro. Yeah, I will do,
mate. Yeah, I can never live I can never
live off a grand a month. a grand a
month. Can't believe I spent almost 300 quid
today. Almost 300 [ __ ] quid. What the
bro? That's a
madness. Almost 300 [ __ ] pound.
Nah, mate. 3k is 3k [ __ ] Why would I
need to do that, bro? I'm good where I am, you
know. No, mate. It's It's [ __ ] hard
enough to [ __ ] live off [ __ ] three
grand a month as it is with [ __ ]
hardly any outgoings. Why the [ __ ] am I
going to rent somewhere? It doesn't make
sense. Why am I going to rent somewhere?
It doesn't make no sense.
I don't live in a HMO and I don't live
with foreigners. Nobody knows where I
live. You don't know where I am. You
don't know where I live.
You literally don't know where I live.
You don't know where I am. This is This
is the whole thing. Like I was listening
to L J L J's for about 10 minutes,
right? You don't even know where I
live. HMO. I live in a house. What are
you talking about? A HMO? Where did you
get What the [ __ ] is a HMO? Let me look
it up. HMO.
looking it up.
Bro, I don't live in a shared place.
I've never said I lived in a in a shared
place. That's literally never ever come
out of my mouth. Never said that. And
you don't know where I
live. So try
again. So try again, buddy. And if you
lived in London, you would live in a
shared house. Most pe you do realize
most people in London live in a box
room. Self projecting. Bye-bye. Um, you
do realize most people in London live in
a in like a box room by themsel. You do
realize that most people in London. A B
I live in a house and I don't live with
other people. So try again. You don't
know where I live. Not that my not that
my [ __ ] living [ __ ] um circumstances [ __ ] um concern
you. These a woman without a kitchen or
bathroom is illegal. Yeah. You don't
know where I am, bro. I've never said I
lived in a HMO. You'll never know where
I am. And you'll never know where I live ever. Literally
ever. Yeah. And I don't live in a H.
When have I ever said I live in a HMO?
Huh? You don't know where I live. And
why are you so obsessed where I live as
well? I heard you people talking, you
weirdos, talking about it for like 10 minutes. Yeah. Anyways,
you seem [ __ ] obsessed with where people [ __ ] live. Insane, bro. [Music] Jeez.
Yeah. How am I blowing up? I'm saying
that you people talk there about other
people's lives and you always get it
wrong. You don't know nothing. Like you
literally don't know nothing.
Like you talk like you know where people live
and t but in reality you don't know [ __ ]
all. In reality you don't know [ __ ] all.
It's actually funny. It's amusing that
you talk like you think you know about
people's lives but you don't
like it's actually it's actually
hilarious to be
honest. You don't know anything. You
don't know where people live. You don't
know who people live with. That's the thing. It's hilarious. I
know. Listen to
me. If I was to go to
Australia or if I was to go to
America, what do you think I'd be [ __ ] doing,
bro? Do you think I'd be renting my own
apartment? No. I'd be I' I'd be renting
a room in a shared house, working my ass
off for two months, and come back to
England. Right. It's called having a
brain. You wouldn't go to Australia. You
wouldn't go to America and rent a whole
[ __ ] house out for
yourself. You don't have a brain, bro. You really
don't. No. Where is
it? Want my my sub.
Yeah, I see. I see. I see
it. See? Yeah, I know. I don't, but I'm
saying as an example,
matey. Uh, there we go. Self projection. Sorry,
man. Yeah, I don't, but I'm using it as an example.
Wow. You people are obsessed by missing some
sweets. Yeah, man. [Applause]
I'd be embarrassed if I got a grand a month like
you. I'd be embarrassed, bro. That's embarrassing,
bro. You want to sort your financial
circumstances out first before trying
to preach to others and you don't even
know where they live and if they live by
their [ __ ] selves. That's embarrassing, bro.
I spent [ __ ] 200 I spent basically £300
today. You get a grand a month to how embarrassing that
is. Even though I live by my [ __ ]
self. Yeah. Okay, cool.
But you shouldn't judge other people,
bro. Because trust me mate, I'd rather
be getting four or five grand a month
living in shared accommodation than
living [ __ ] then getting a grand a
month and live by myself. Believe
that. Unless I had a kid,
obviously. That's even worse, mate. It
doesn't matter where you
live. Doesn't matter, bro. It's still [ __ ]
I told you I'm outside that and it still seems to
go. It still seems to [ __ ]
go. Well, you're in Nottingham, so it
might go further, but here in London, it just goes. Yeah.
that housemates. No, I never said that.
No, no, I never said that. I remember
exactly what I said and no, I never said
that. You said the nightmare. You said
you had a nightmare and woke up. Your
housemate said, "No, no, I never said
that. Try again." No. No, I never said
that. Never ever ever did I say
that. Stop talking
[ __ ] Stop talking
[ __ ] Nope. I never say that. I had a
nightmare and it woke up my house,
mates. Doesn't even make sense. No, I
didn't say that. Anyways, I'm going to
stop talking about this now anyways
because you're never going to know where
I live. I live by myself and it
shouldn't even concern you where who
[ __ ] where I live. It's become an
obsess. It's become an obsessive now.
I'm not going to argue with you. I know
what I've said, right? Pull it up, bro,
cuz it doesn't exist. Put it
up. Pull it up where I said I woke up my
housemates due to having a nightmare.
Yeah. Go and put it up on your channel.
It doesn't exist because I've never said
it. And this is getting obsessive now
and it's be and it's becoming really
weird. So, I'm going to stop talking about it
anyways. [ __ ] weirdos, bro. Jeez.
Becoming weird now,
lad. No, bro. Put just put it up on your
channel. Everyone knows your
channel. Never use the word housemates
in my [ __ ] life. Go put it up on your
channel. What I said
was I remember what I said.
Um, I said my friend was
staying and I woke him up snoring.
That's what I said. That's what I said.
And then when you put it on your
channel, that will show it. Yeah. So,
that's exactly what I
said. I said I was I had a nightmare. I
was snoring and I woke my friend up who
was staying here. That's what I
said. Put it on your channel, bro, and
we'll see who's lying. Put it on your
channel and we'll see who's lying.
That's exactly what I said. Cuz I know
exactly what I've said cuz I've I've
invited a few people around here. Even
at 19y old. Try again, buddy. Anyways, Anyways, bye-bye
now. [ __ ] weirdos. Yeah. Bye-bye. Bye-bye.
Now [ __ ] weirdos on this community,
bro. weirdos on this [ __ ]
community. Weirdos, man. Absolute
weirdos. What are you having for snacks today anyways?
There's a weirdo community. Yeah. Weird community.
I used to live with people like [ __ ] four years
ago, but I was traveling all the [ __ ]
time. I used to live with people. I've
lived by myself. I lived with my mom.
And honestly, right, when you live by
yourself, when you're used to living
with other people like I did years ago,
there's not really no
difference really. There's not actually
depends what you do. Well, I was
traveling and I was out all the time,
but you get used to it if you live by
yourself, you live with other people, know, depends
how much you stay in, I guess. I don't
know. Nothing's happening, man. I was
just saying I spent like [ __ ] 300
quid today gambling, bought a fridge,
got an escort, got some food, £300
gone. Well, guess 3k a month ain't
really that much, is
it? 3k a month can go like that. I've
had to I'm stopping drinking and
approaching now for a few weeks anyways.
I didn't go out last week. I'm not going
out this week or next week probably.
I want a detox, man. And yeah, it's
[ __ ] goes, bro. [ __ ] three grand, eh?
Gambling is the same old
gambling. I only put £100 in it. Uh
don't even know why I done that to be honest.
Yeah, it's [ __ ] it.
These people in this community really are
obsessed and a million time. And let me
tell you something. I saw your comments
on um Shawn Joe. Listen, I would rather
have never been in a relationship than
be in a relationship with a vulnerable
disabled woman. I literally would rather
have never been in a relationship even
if I was 35. I'd rather be 27, have more
money than him, get more money than him,
been abroad unlike him, been on a plane
unlike him, and never been in a
relationship than happen to target a disabled
woman. Yeah, you don't Yeah, you people
don't bully no one. Trust me, I don't
let anyone bully me because you people
don't bully no one. You bully
yourselves. All you do is you bully
yourselves every single day. You make a
fool of yourselves on YouTube. Trust me,
none of you little mongos ever bully me.
You never have and you never
will. You never have and you never
will. Fair play to him. He's still n legs.
Uh yeah, but even if I had a
relationship, you would still tell me
that I'm not in a
relationship. Oh, fine. Do you know what
I find so funny, right, is when you call
him a virgin, right? Even though we know
that he is a virgin. He literally is a
virgin. People will say, "Oh, he can't
be a virgin cuz he's in a relationship."
But yet when people call me a virgin, no
one says nothing, even though I've
literally proved I've had sex. Uhhuh.
You people are weirdos, man. And you
know how you people know that you're
such weirdos? Because when Monty man was
saying how, oh, he's going to call the
police. He's going to call the police.
You people's like, "Oh, you're a grass.
You're a grass. You're a grass." I don't
even like Monty man. But then when you
say that you're going to call the police
on me, no one says nothing. You're all
[ __ ] backwards narcissists.
That's one thing I found with this
community as well. You're [ __ ] n You're actual
narcissists. Yeah, just b sad people
that ain't got [ __ ]
all. You actually are,
bro. Oh, he got um he broke up with Kaye
and apparently he's homeless
now. No, I don't want to play the guitar
like notch legs.
But guess what? Let me tell you
something. Stop talking about yourself.
It's not good for your mental health.
But let me tell you something. Nons wish
that he had he got as much money as I
did. Nons wish that he's been with women
that I've been with. And that's what
kills him. [ __ ] the relationship, bro.
That's what kills that
virgin day and night, mate. [ __ ] day and night.
Nah, I'm good, mate. I'd never learn my standards that low. Yeah.
Yeah. Crazy, isn't it?
But Sean actually is a
virgin. That's the truth that he
actually is a virgin. And you say that
he can't be Joe. Well, he can be because
he is one. He literally is a virgin.
Just because you're with a disabled
girl, that does not mean you have had sex with
her. That does not mean anything.
Especially when she's [ __ ] disabled
and she's not even [ __ ] normal and
she can barely [ __ ] talk. You
know, it's crazy, Dad. It's actually
crazy. I don't give a [ __ ] if she gives
a good [ __ ] man. I'm never getting with
her. I don't go for moners like Monty and Sean.
Yeah, that's it,
bro. This community is so
mongified. [ __ ] It's actually so
mongified. It really
is. It's actually so mongified.
And you said, "Have I had any luck
lately with a gambling?" I don't really
do it anymore. This was the first time
in ages. I don't see the point of
it. I lose. I split on the machine and
then the same thing happens again and
again and again. There's literally just
no point in gambling. That's why I don't
even really do it
anymore. What's the [ __ ] point, mate?
It's the same old [ __ ] It's the same
story. It was Frankie roulette. It was I
went to post something in the post
office. I thought, let me just try a
little hundred. I spat on the [ __ ]
machine. I've done it a few times in the
past, but why I don't do it anymore.
Pointless. Big machines. Stay
old. Same old
story. Same old story with it.
Yeah, it's like what you say, these
people in this community do things to
psychologically [ __ ] with you, but they
don't [ __ ] with you. This is what I was
trying to say. They literally don't
psychologically [ __ ] with anyone's
head. They literally don't bother no
one. So, I don't know why you come on
here and say, "Oh, they do this because
No, no, no, no, no. They literally do
not bother me one single
bit. Not one single bit. Because you
wouldn't be on here. If these people
bothered you so much and they bullied
you so much, you wouldn't be on here.
They don't affect no one." It's like
Trumodal, right? He tries saying that he
knows where I live. You don't know where
I live. And if you do know where I live,
pull out posters. No one
cares. You know, that's an example. You
really think you know where I live?
Where you know where I live? No, you
don't. No, you don't. And even if you
did, go and pull out posters. Go on, put
up three, 4,000 posters. No one's going
to move. You
know, these people don't psychologically
[ __ ] with anyone's head. They
psychologically [ __ ] with their own head.
cuz they're on YouTube every day
obsessed. Think about it. That takes time and
energy. They literally don't torment or bully
nobody. And I don't know how many times
I have to say
that. I don't I don't I don't put up
content for you little mongos
anymore. You know, I hate most of the
people on here. Like, I wouldn't care if
all the views on here drop dead.
Like, I'd have a party. Like, I don't
care about any of
you. I wouldn't care if you all just drop dead.
Honestly, I hate all of you. [ __ ]
every single one of you. All [ __ ] scumbags.
Yeah, I do. No, I hate every single one
of you. Nonslegs, LJ, all the people on
these channel, all these self
projectors. I hate you all. I wouldn't
give a [ __ ] if you drop
dead. It's sad to say, but it is what it
is. Nasty little narcissistic self-proing
[ __ ] That's all you are. That's all you amount
to. So yeah, I'm going Thailand soon.
Anyways, if you must know, I'm kind of
done with this country, bro. I literally really
am. Didn't go out last week. I'm not
going out this week. You get to a point.
Yeah, it could be any age.
Yeah. Could be 27, 28, 29, 31, 35. And
you think to yourself, "Fuck this poor game of
soldiers. [ __ ] this. This is a waste of time,
man. That's where I'm at. I'm go
Thailand. That's where I'm going to
go. I don't even care about women
anymore. That was my first [ __ ] in
[ __ ] ages today. And it's only
because she [ __ ] It's only because
she [ __ ] messaged
me. And I thought, "Okay, [ __ ] it."
Yeah, I don't like the women in this
country. They're all stuck
up. They're all [ __ ] I do not
know. And it's not even just that. Uh
Joe, you go out and you meet the same
people. They're like NPCs. You go out,
you see the same women with the same
attitude. You see the same
men. You see the same [ __ ] men that
they go for. It's [ __ ] boring. You
You literally meet the same people, the
same [ __ ] like in in in like the
[ __ ] local pub. You meet the same people. It's
boring. It's [ __ ] boring, isn't it?
Yeah, but that's it.
I was thinking about going back to
Newcastle. I met some guy from Newcastle
yesterday at the Chinese. I said, "Oh,
you from Newcastle?" He said, "I am." He
was around the corner and we was just
talking and [ __ ]
but traveling days were fun.
Eh, there's a woman in America. She said
she'd get with me, but she's 51, so
that's not an
option. I don't really give a [ __ ] about
women anymore, to be
honest. I don't really care for it. Care
them. I've already done it. I've already
I've already called Trevor Dawson out.
He don't come out. He don't come
out. I called him out last time I was
there. Yeah, I called him out last time
I was there.
Yeah, he didn't come
out. Do you understand? These people
don't come out. They don't leave their
house. Why do you think they're on here
every day projecting? Cuz they ain't got
a life. Trevor
Dawson, [ __ ] Red Star. They're all
the same spackers. Thermodol, they're
all the same. They're housebound. They
sit in all day. Even that large A sits
on sits in all
day. Like I'm going to go all the way to
Middlesbrough again. [ __ ] off,
man. Last time I done that, the [ __ ]
didn't [ __ ] come
out. Don't even know who that
is. Don't know who that is.
Yeah, they've all got anxiety. They've
Yeah. Why are you going to Newcastle
for? For for what? I I'll never travel
anywhere else again in the UK. It's a
[ __ ] country. Why waste your money
traveling to places in this country? It's [ __ ]
[ __ ] [ __ ] country, man. [ __ ] country, you
know. I go to
Australia, work there for two months, come
back, make a lot of money out
there. I might do something like that.
Yeah. Yeah. I might I might do something
like that, man. You want
Yeah. Good place to make money,
eh? Lots of cutting hand jobs.
Yeah. I love when you said to Sean, "Why
don't you show us your passport stamps?"
That was funny.
Ah, yeah, I know. I've got crippling
anxiety, mate. We've heard it all
before. Of course you can't because I've got crippling
anxiety, apparently. E. Yeah, I've got crippling anxiety,
mate. Yeah. Didn't you know that?
Crippling. I can't leave the house, mate. I'm housebound. [ __ ]
If I want to do something, I'll [ __ ]
do it, mate. [ __ ]
me. Summer clothes. Ready?
Yeah. Yeah. F will never go abroad. He's too
skinned. No, you have got anxiety.
Everyone's got some sort of anxiety.
Everyone's got some form of
anxiety, even though they say they
haven't, but just not as bad as these
people's. There's no
way. There's no way not one person in
this world don't have any kind of anxiety.
Impossible. You know what I You know
what I struggle with? Yeah. Like overthinking.
overinking and it's
hard. I always seem to overthink and
worry and I just can't stop doing
it. Like even though I get loads of
money, I be, "Oh, I spent this. Oh, when
am I getting this again?" And it really
makes no sense, but it's hard to not worry.
Yeah, I overthink a lot.
It's hard to not overthink
strange strange is
it? I seem to do is [Music]
overink. What is she doing
away? I worry about like money I've
spent. Oh, when you get money again, but
it doesn't make sense because I've got
money. So, and I get money, but it's
just I don't know. I worry, but it's not
the same as
anxiety. It's hard to explain it. [Music]
It's not anxiety. I don't know what it is. It's weird. Yeah.
Yeah. Yeah. Someone said before, "I've got
ADHD." that Somalian said, "Oh, I think you've got
Maybe I think my personality trait I
shouldn't gamble. I lost £100 today.
That's nothing. I lost
£100. No, it's not guilt. It's not
guilt. I only spent
£100. And then I just [ __ ] went mad,
bro. SP on the machine and everything.
You shouldn't gamble. The PE people like
me shouldn't gamble. You obviously gamble, you
know. No, I don't have
twitches. No, I don't have twitches. Not at
all. No, I really
don't. But today is a perfect example
that it's not about the money. 100 pound
is nothing to lose. If you lost it a
month, there you go. You can't gamble.
Simple. But I was going to put a chair
through that machine today. I'm not even
joking. I was going to put a chair for
it, but I didn't fancy getting nicked,
you know. So, there you go.
Yeah. Somebody with my personality trait shouldn't
gamble. He doesn't mix.
But no, I didn't I didn't spend money that I sp an
escort. Yeah, I just don't like losing.
It doesn't matter. It's annoying. I feel
degraded. I hate it. I hate it. It's
like taking a piss.
It controls your whole emotions, your
whole body, your whole mind. And it's
only gambling that does
it. Nope. Not at all. Nope. The women
[ __ ] don't piss me off anymore. Really?
Nope. It's just
gambling. No, it's just gambling.
Honestly, it's just
gambling. I can get over the women [ __ ]
It's just gambling. And I don't have low
self-esteem. I don't think I'm ugly. I
never thought I'm
ugly, but I came in drunk. This is what
the reason why I stopped drinking cuz I
I came when was it? Last
Saturday. No, I think it was No, it was
last Tuesday I went out. Yeah. You
know, I went out last
Tuesday. I came back to the kitchen
drunk. I pissed all over the [ __ ]
floor, bro. And I smashed my mug. I had
to get another one. That's why I don't
drink no more. I was pissed off because
of the women. It was pissing me off,
bro. It was just annoying me. I can't
remember. I was drunk in it. I pissed
all over the kitchen floor. Smashed my
mug. My friend was here as well. He had
to clear up. He's like, "What the [ __ ]
happened?" He said, "Did you slip?" I
was like, "No, I was
drunk." So, yeah.
Mhm. That was last
Tuesday. Yeah, it was
Tuesday. I had to get a new mug from
[ __ ] Am me 20
quid. It didn't achieve
nothing. I shoes I went out and it was
constant. That boyfriend thing was
constant. Um, we're not getting into a
discussion about my looks. Cult is boring, lad.
We're not getting into a discussion
about my physical appearance. It's
weird. It's boring. It's pointless. And
you're not going to make me feel
insecure about the way I look. Trust me,
people have been trying for years and
they haven't achieved anything. So,
we're not having a discussion about the
way that I
look, you know, cuz it's very, very
boring. And trust me, loads of people
have tried. So, yeah. on Tuesday. It was
constant that I've got a boyfriend. It
was constant. I even made some videos on it. You know, yeah.
Yeah. It was constant on Tuesday. The
weather was nice. I thought I'd get my
haircut. Yeah. Pissing me off, bro.
So, yeah, it's annoying. But I know what
to do. I need to leave this country.
Hey, there's no point moing about it. I
know that I need to leave this country. You know, yeah.
Yeah. You can never think you're better than you are. Really? Yeah.
Yeah, this pistol over the
floor. I didn't clean it up
though. Probably dried up. It's dried
out in it.
But yeah, the women are [ __ ] in this
country, Joe. They still are [ __ ] I
don't even like talking about it. It
annoys me. I don't even like talking
about it. It pisses me off. I don't even
like talking about
them to be
honest cuz I [ __ ] hate him. I don't
even like talking about
it. No, no, it was just hearing that I
got a boyfriend. It was pissing me off.
I actually got two numbers actually.
Yeah, I actually got two numbers. It was
just pissing me
off. Nah, I was just sick of hearing it.
I've got a boyfriend. I've got a
boyfriend. That's one of the reasons.
And you know when it pisses me off like
that, I just stopped going out for like
six weeks. I just stopped going out and
drinking for like six weeks. I just I
just I just um I would just stop for
like six weeks. Five, six weeks easy.
I've done it a few times before.
Yeah, I would just stop for like six
weeks. It [ __ ] bors me. That's why I
do other things now. It bores me. The
gambling bors me. The women bore me. It's boring.
I was giving Morgan's dad [ __ ] Joe, and
Morgan's mom [ __ ] I was like, just as
long as you know you can only do what
you do behind the keyboard cuz you're a
keyboard warrior, that's fine by
me. As long as you know you'll only ever
be a keyboard warrior behind the
keyboard, that's fine by me, mate. Yeah, that's
it. Yeah, I didn't get anything as a
kid. Yeah, we've heard it all before.
Yeah, I don't have any
issues. You said you got you're not
going what you going today. I never said
I'm not ging for six weeks and I stopped
and I that was the first time I played
them machines in weeks. What are you
talking about? You'll probably out
within the next week. No, I won't. No, I
won't. That was the first time I gambled
in a few
weeks, you know. No, I said I'm not
going out drinking for like six weeks
and I will stick to it cuz I've done it
before. It's boring. Like why why even
waste your money in this country?
Like they all you meet the same women.
You see you meet the same men. You meet
MPCs. You see the same people with the
same attitude walking around like their
[ __ ] don't stink. Like I even notice it
when I'm in KFC. I'll be seeing these
women walk past and they they walk
around literally like their [ __ ] don't
stink. Like I'm not even joking. Like I
was in KFC the other day. Yeah.
Honestly, I was sat down the other day,
bro, in KFC and I was watching, not like
on purpose, but I'm seeing these women
walk past. I'm just sat here and they
literally walk around like they're [ __ ] don't
think. It's the same people.
Yeah, I do it. No, I do it cuz I I like
going out drinking
anyways. I like going out drinking
anyways. So, I genuinely do believe it.
Why do you think I don't approach
sober? I go out drinking anyway. So,
when you go out drinking, you may as
well until you can leave here, right?
Yeah, that's not what intel means
though. Yeah, but that's not what that's
not what an incel
means. That's not actually what an incel
though. You know, no, I'm just saying
that's one of the reason I can't go out.
No, it's not even about rejection. just
women are just [ __ ]
anyways. You know why do you think I
give that Morgan's dad
[ __ ] I said, "Listen, you're one to
talk about keyboard warriors. Who's the
one that's got a group dedicated to
me?" Yeah, that's what I thought. Yeah,
you got a group dedicated to me, buddy.
But just know that you would only ever
be able to do that behind the
keyboard, you know? Yeah.
Yeah, [ __ ] little [ __ ]
I told him that last week as well.
Yeah, [ __ ] [ __ ]
No, do you know what? It wasn't pissing me
off. The thing that was pissing me off
is you're trying to call me a keyboard
warrior. You're trying to call me a keyboard warrior.
the keyboard. That's some madness.
Yeah. It's not three years ago. It's
like two It's not even two years
ago. It wasn't last year. It was the
year before that. April. It's not even
two years, let alone three years.
Yeah, it's the truth,
mate. No, I'm not doing the exact same
thing. No, I'm not doing the exact same
thing. He posts about me every day on
YouTube. I've not had sex with him. I've
had sex with this person. You know what
I'm saying? And I don't like them. I
It's just because I've not got No, but
the difference is I've not got full
revenge yet. That's the
difference. No, no, no, no. That's the
difference. Sean can meet me anytime he
wants, but he wants to be a keyboard
warrior. If I find out this person is
back in England, I'm going to smash
their face in and that will be the last
time or any of their [ __ ] relatives.
So, no, there's a big [ __ ] difference.
There's a big [ __ ] difference, man.
Sorry. I was I was in their country. All
right. I was in their country and I did
nothing. [ __ ] I was in their country.
They didn't come out and they called the
police. What? What the [ __ ] What the
[ __ ] are you talking
about? I was in their country. They
didn't come out and they called the
[ __ ] police. What the [ __ ] did you
want me to [ __ ] do?
And I said to him that well that I'm not
doing this um on I'm not doing this
you're this you're that you're this. I'm
not I'm not being disrespectful via text
because being disrespectful via text is
being like them. It's making yourself
like them. So I just basically said just
let me know when you're back in England.
Now I just say it's April's here. I said
it know when you're back in England.
Yeah. You don't own anyone in anyone's
country. You scared little [ __ ] You
done everything you done when you was
back home in America. Because that's
what cowards do. It's similar to what
anybody can do. Yeah. That's it. Because
I'm not going to stop saying, "Oh,
you're you're that." Cuz that's being a
keyboard lawyer. No, it's their country.
They didn't [ __ ] come out and now
they're resorting to [ __ ] group
[ __ ] chats. [ __ ]
pathetic. Yes, I was
there. Yes, I was
there. Yes, I [ __ ] was there. Yes, I
[ __ ] was. Yeah, they don't know it.
Stop making them excuses,
Joe. Stop making excuses. They're not
about nothing, mate. If they were about
something, they would have been here by
now. They don't know it because they
blocked my number. Know it. So stop
trying to make excuses. Yeah, they
blocked my number. So therefore, I
couldn't even [ __ ] contact them. So
stop saying about how you how apparently
they don't they know, brother, I slapped
their whole family up with one hand.
What are you talking about? They know I
they knew I wasn't there. No, they
didn't not to know I was there or I was
there. They I'd slap the whole family up
with one [ __ ] hand. Like one [ __ ]
finger, bro. Yeah. How the [ __ ] do they
know where I was when they blocked my
[ __ ] number when I couldn't even
contact them? Shut up, man. Carry on
with your little group chats.
You know, and my point was I just said,
"Let me know when you're back in England
and I will make a group chat of you."
Yeah. I will make a group chat of you
when you're back here. I will slap you
up and I'll make a group chat of you and
I'll send it to all your friends. How
about that one? Which they didn't come
out. So, where did you go to their
house, brother? I was by the [ __ ]
university. Yeah. I said, "I'm buying."
You saw what I was texting them. You saw
what I was [ __ ] texting them. I don't
have her address. I've got the dad's
address. I don't have [ __ ] her
address, you know? They're [ __ ]
cowards. Yeah, cowards,
bro. Yeah, cowards.
Did the posters go up? I put a few posters up.
Yeah. At the at the UMass Lo University. [Music]
Um Yes, they
did. Yes, they did. And hold on a
minute, Joe. Right. Let's Let's So,
you're trying to say that I was not
there. Okay. Okay. Okay. Okay. Right.
You're trying to say I wasn't there.
Okay. Let's go by your logic. Yeah. So,
if I go there tomorrow, hypothetically
speaking, what do you think is going to
happen? What do you really think is
going to happen? What they're going to
come out? Okay. Okay. I didn't go
apparently. Okay. So, this is a new
year. So, if I went there tomorrow and I
started running up my mouth, what do you
really think is going to happen?
Nothing. Nothing would happen.
Nothing. So what the [ __ ] are you talking about?
Don, nothing would
happen. And you know it. Nothing would
happen. What would actually happen? Go on.
Tell us. Tell us what would happen.
Nothing. The dad said he was going to
[ __ ] put me in [ __ ]
handcuffs. [ __ ] group chats. [ __ ]
hell. Yeah, I can tell you exactly what
would happen. Do you know ex? I can tell
you exactly what would happen this time around.
They're not going to come out and
they're going to call the police. We
should put a bet on it. Nothing would
happen, bro. No one she knows would ever
come out. They'd get slapped up, bro. I
even told that [ __ ] dam about himself as
well. Group chats. And you're calling me
a keyboard warrior. You've made a group
chat on me, but I'm the keyboard warrior. Oh,
mate. No. Yeah, but I'm saying what
would happen this time round? You know
they have the right to carry in Boston,
bro. They're not using no guns. Trust
me, they would do nothing, man. They
would do nothing. They would have
blocked you or not,
bro. How am I going to let them know I'm
there when I'm there? Okay. So, say I go
tomorrow. Yeah. Say I go tomorrow.
hypothetically speaking. How am I going
to let them know when I'm
there? How would I let them know I'm
there? Because they blocked me.
Yeah. This is so immature, man.
Honestly, this is so
immature. This is really immature. Do
you understand? This is really immature, bro.
I think you just leave it
out. Yes, I did go. Yes, I did go. You
know, yes, I did, mate. She's already
blocked me. So whether I went or I
didn't go, I wouldn't even been able to
have contacted them.
You're going out like you're going on
like she's this big woman that's going
to do anything to anyone. She's
not. She's a stupid little [ __ ] She's
not going to meet anyone. She's not
going to do anything to anyone. Her or
anybody that she
knows. No, I
just No, I'm laughing because I think
it's bad how you can meet someone and
then they end up messaging your whole family.
That's what I find
funny. That's what I find so
funny. And then it's like, okay, so you
go to another country, you hook up with
someone, that's the end. Yeah. But then
that person starts meing your family.
That's a madness. Oh my god, that's
funny. That is funny. But you can't
laugh though. You have to laugh.
She didn't. She had already. Bro, did
you see what I was
texting? Didn't you see what I was Clear lower
deck. But imagine that Dojo. Imagine
that, Joe. You you had a you had a you
hooked up with somebody and then they
start messaging your family. Imagine
that. Imagine that,
Joe. They start messaging your family.
Yeah. Imagine someone done that to
you. Quite funny, isn't it?
Yeah, they've all got punishments, Joe.
Yeah. Do you remember who said that? Ah,
love it, man. Love
it. Yeah, it's funny, man.
She's not with Charles. Nope. She didn't
go back to Charles because she's not
with Charles. Charles is with someone
else. Charles is not with her. He He's
got a new
misses. I'm to thank for that.
Yay. It did work, mate. It [ __ ] did
work. It did [ __ ]
work. She's not with him. He's got a new
miss, mate. Go on his Instagram.
Yeah. Yeah. It doesn't matter who she
went back with. I don't give a [ __ ]
Yeah. I already had the [ __ ]
[ __ ] [ __ ] [ __ ] E fat
[ __ ] You should you I bet you you see
all these other people, bro, that I've
[ __ ] been with.
I need to go sort that uni. I've got a
uni brow. I need to sort my uni brow
out. It's getting quite long,
actually. Oh, my eyebrows getting
longer. They need to be shaped up,
bro. Uni, bro. E. Yeah.
But yeah, I'm the I'm I'm the reason
they split up,
man. I'm I feel I I generally believe
that I'm the reason they split up,
Joe. Well, part of
it. Peter Belly always been up to no good, eh?
Yeah. You think? I think [Laughter] so. Yeah. Right now.
Yeah. Why don't I change? Why? What do
you want me to
do? What do you want me to do? Oh, don't
leave me. Don't go. Don't
leave. Where you going,
buddy? Where are you going,
bud? Where are you
going? Talk about my little cute face.
Why will I never change? What have I
done? I haven't done anything.
No. Go on. Go on. Why would I change?
What have I done?