It's [ __ ] dead, boys. It's [ __ ] dead.
>> [ __ ] only got one number so far, man.
I got one number so far, but I need to
step my game. It's [ __ ] dead as [ __ ]
bro. Dead, bro. [ __ ]
Yo yo yo yo yo
bro. It's [ __ ] dead, man. It's
[ __ ] dead. I got one number sober,
but it's dead, bro.
Really? I'm [ __ ] I'm [ __ ] drunk as [ __ ] bro.
I need to go back to pinging a bit, bro.
It's [ __ ] dead there, man. It's dead,
lad. I've already been there, Dusty.
It's [ __ ] dead. Done a couple of
approaches there. It's [ __ ] dead, bro.
It's dead, lad. I've got one number so
far, man. I I tried to go to the O. I
tried to go to the O [ __ ] I tried to
go to the [ __ ] uh what was it called?
I tried to get to the um
I tried to get to the [ __ ] uh other
boy in Oxen Circus. They kicked me
straight out, mate. I'm going to win.
I'm getting the last laugh. I don't give
a [ __ ] Whether it happens today, whe
happens at Thursday, whether it happens
Saturday, mate, I am getting the last
laugh. 100%, mate. 100%. Trust me, I'm
getting the last laugh out of this
company on WhatsApp. Trust me, I'll play
the game and I'll play it dirty. Yeah, I
got one number so far sober drinking.
It's [ __ ] dead as [ __ ] Just
approached someone over there having
none of it. [ __ ] [ __ ] bro.
I don't have to play the game, Dusty.
Trust me, bro. I'm in it too deep, lad.
There's no one here, bro. I've
approached God knows how many people.
I've got one number. I've approached fuckloads.
We'll be back out, Dusty. Don't worry, bro.
Dustin will back out, bro. Trust me.
Ain't even ate. There's no point eating.
I've I'm only sticking to beer.
>> Yeah. Monday. Do you know what? It's not
as bad as you'd think though for a
Monday. It is [ __ ] but it's not as bad
as you think.
[ __ ] [ __ ] Dusty, swear to God, bro.
[ __ ] sent it, bro. Mad. What number?
We're getting free numbers today. Trust me.
Trust me. Even if it's the last 10
minutes, we're getting it. Don't worry. My boy,
>> we're getting it. We're getting it on. [ __ ] hell.
>> We need to get that WhatsApp [ __ ] back,
don't we, Dusty? We need to get that
[ __ ] WhatsApp [ __ ] back, don't we,
Dusty? Yeah, we need to get that WhatsApp chat.
I'm looking, bro. Nobody here. I know
what he done.
Pety's got big balls. You can talk to
anyone. I'm in it too deep now, Dustin.
I'm in it too deep, lad. Even if I go
three times, I'll go I'll go barbers on
Thursday. [ __ ] I'll go I'll go
barbers on Thursday, lad. Don't worry.
We're on it all. Trust me, we don't take
L's on this channel. [ __ ] that. No, [ __ ]
that, bro. [ __ ] that.
No [ __ ] kids in this pub, lad.
Trust me, I'll get the last off. Dusty.
Yeah. You want to do it dirty, I'll do
it dirty, man. You want to do it dirty,
I'll [ __ ] do it really dirty. Really
dirty. Trust me.
You want to do it dirty, I'll do it dirty, bro.
It's all dead, bro. It's dead. I've
already been there. It's dead. I've been
everywhere. It's dead. Don't worry, bro.
Chill. Worst comes to worse, we'll have
some more on the street, bro. Don't
worry. It's dead. It's all dead. I went
somewhere in [ __ ] Oxford circus. They
He said to me, "Oh, you can't wear a
tracksuit." I said, "Bro, I'll change."
Changed. Then he tried to kick me out.
He's a [ __ ] idiot. Little [ __ ]
power ego. Little [ __ ] Don't worry,
we're getting it today, bro. Believe you
me, we're getting this [ __ ] Yeah, even
if it takes 3:00 in the morning. Yeah, I
got a video to come, bro. But Peter
ain't stopping, bro. Trust me.
Well, it is dead to be fair. But for Monday, it's
not as bad.
>> And number three, completely sober
again on the [ __ ] thing.
>> Bro, it's [ __ ] dead. I've got one
number, bro. I've got one I've got one number.
Got one number so far and that's it.
And that was a sober approach. [ __ ]
dead, bro. I don't know how many people
I [ __ ] approach.
It's [ __ ] dead, bro. Dead. Dead.
Seems to be getting worse as well. [ __ ] hell.
There's a little terminal over there for
Frankie. Mr. B.
I'm not going. [ __ ] that.
Trust me, we'll get some more numbers.
Don't worry, man.
This is [ __ ] up. Mr. Be changing
everything. Look, got the vapors on and
[ __ ] it up. I'm dead.
We're getting the last laugh out of that
[ __ ] Mr. B. Don't worry, man. We're
going to get the last laugh out of that
[ __ ] Believe you me, we're getting the
last laugh out of that [ __ ] bro. Even
if it takes three days, I don't care. I
don't care, bro.
I don't give a [ __ ] It's going to
happen, bro. Yeah. You want to play the
game, I'll play the game. I'll do it
I'll do it dirty, bro.
What's the time, right? I need to go
back. Need to get out of here, bro.
Keep approaching now. Need to try and
get some more [ __ ] numbers. I would
have won. Far gets three or four. We're
definitely getting three or four. 100% is happening.
>> Yeah. So, I'll be back later when I get home.
>> Yeah, man.