Oh no.
Home of map landlock home. That was fun.
That was fun. You [ __ ] hell. You virgin.
>> B Oh [ __ ]
Look at my stuff, bro. Yeah. Oh, [ __ ]
I'm back. I'm back. I'm back. I'm back. What was
you got on this Monday? Yeah. Yeah. Um,
can't do all for this [ __ ] brother.
For this [ __ ] man.
[ __ ] hell, man.
I just want this training.
You're under arrest. Under arrest?
>> Yes. For being a big f big fat stinking
dirty copycat with no mind of your own.
A is that the real Kieran?
Hey, I notic you always come out when
I'm drinking. You're just watching,
aren't you, bro? Every time I go out drinking.
Is that the real you? You heard about
Christian is now. Thought I'd give it a
whirl. on a little Monday. Need to wipe
these trainers, lad. [ __ ] hell,
bro. [ __ ] did you hear what happened
with that Christian Izzy, mate? She
lives in [ __ ] Eden and everything. I
messaged her today when I was in
Central. I said, "Oh, let's meet up.
Come on. Let's meet up in that. Let's
meet up. Let's meet up and [ __ ] you
know what I mean? Let's let's let's talk
in it." I was in Central.
Yeah. [ __ ] it. One sec, bro. I link up,
I need to get some Mackis, bro. I'll put
a link up, too.
I need some my trainers.
Yeah, man. Have a chat. You always come
back when I'm drink. Oh, why is he not
letting me put the link up? One second.
Rejoin, bro. Let me put the link up. Two
seconds. I'm going to restart it.