I need to wipe this as well.
Right. Is that Is it working now? Bro,
why is [snorts] this shitty content link not working
you? I know it's [clears throat] always
on it when I'm drinking.
There we go. That's the baby.
There you go. [ __ ] hell. Oh, [ __ ]
Not for a long time, man. I wipe my
trailers and that before I put them back
in the box so they still look, you know, fresh.
You know what I'm saying? Ken [ __ ] hell.
There you go. The link's there, mate.
Working now. I need to get myself some
food. I didn't I haven't ate all day. I
don't know how.
Probably the stress of it all to be fair, lad.
Oh, [ __ ] hell.
Need to drive full putting this [ __ ] in the box.
be working now, mate. [ __ ] um
I got free numbers,
but I approached a lot of people. It
weren't too bad for a Monday to be fair,
but it was [ __ ] hard. Um and
basically I've always noted Christiania.
I said, "Oh, let's meet up. Let me let
me come to where you live cuz I'm I'm
near you cuz I was drinking the area."
She started sending me loads of
messages, then deleting the messages,
then deleting my number. Huh? Didn't
even block me deleting my number. I knew
it. I knew that was the thing, bro. I
knew that was the thing.
I knew it, Grezy. I knew it. Oh, didn't
I say that, bro? Yeah, I'm right, bro.
[ __ ] damn right. I'm right.
She's unable, bro. She's got to be
unstable, is it?
I knew it, Greasy. I knew it.
So, I got three potential new mummas,
which to be honest with you sucks
because the amount of
people that I did approach. I don't know
what to eat, bro.
See you later, lad. You go self-reflect
on another channel. Um,
got to be some Indians open maybe.
Oh, please don't wait.
I think there's a toy house that's open,
bro. One second. What they could do with
a curry, bro? One sec. I ain't ate all
day. I didn't eat nothing.
How am I still living? I don't know, man.
Okay. Still got a coat there, right?
Let's have a look.
But yeah, it was really bad to be honest
with you. It gets worse and worse and
worse honestly. Um, Grezy, it gets worse, lad.
If I can get a curry, that is.
Let me see. Chicken
[sighs and gasps]
lamb ka. I don't want lamb ka, bro.
That's what nonslegs has.
That's what virgin boy has. Skimp boy.
That's what the skin virgin has.
Right. No, there just got to be somewhere, mate.
There's not even like a mad address.
No, there's got to be somewhere, bro. [snorts]
I don't know, bro. Not sure.
I got three numbers, which ain't too bad.
Yeah, there's got to be somewhere open,
though, man. I'm [ __ ] starving. I'm
going to die, bro.
I'm dying, lad. Virgin boy.
Yeah. [ __ ] deleted my number again. I
knew it. I knew she deleted my number, lad.
I knew that was the thing. These [ __ ]
play too many games.
Roen Jos. I don't want Roen Joss. I
don't want any of that [ __ ]
These [ __ ] are frosted flakes, lad. [gasps]
Started messaging her that it was drunk.
The only thing is with London though,
Dusty, is very westernized. Anywhere you
go, like Simmons, you got no chance,
bro. Like everyone is just stuck up to
[ __ ] dare to be fair, lad.
No, there's got to be a curry house. Got to be.
Yeah. See yourself reflector. [snorts]
That's self reflecting, lad.
No, there's got to be somewhere that's
open, bro. There's got to be. Maybe not.
See you later, lads. Self projecting.
Why is there
I think you might get a Chinese though.
I reckon you'll get a Chinese though, Dusty. >> [sighs]
>> I reckon you will, mate.
Yeah, I reckon you'll get a you'll
definitely get a Chinese.
I don't know what to get. I'm starving.
I don't know where to get Chinese or McDonald's. Um
could I'd love a curry to be fair, bro.
But that's out of the question.
>> Yeah, I went maxis today, Dusty. It's
quite decent on a Monday. Ah,
there's one here, but it's miles away.
Yeah, there's there's pizza places open.
Yeah, but Papa John's. No,
I don't really want that.
No, I don't want pizza. It's going to
have to be McDonald's then, is it?
Greasy. It's going to have to do It's
going to have to be a McDonald's, lad.
But there's KFC.
No, I don't want a KFC. That KFC is [ __ ]
Yeah, it's going to have to be McDonald's, bro. >> [snorts]
>> or Burger King.
[snorts] Yeah, I got three numbers. But
not a lot of approaches, bro.
I know it's horrible, but what else are
you supposed to get? Okay, I'm just
going to get a Chinese then. [ __ ] it. It
is horrible. Yeah,
Chinese then. I'll just get a Chinese.
Okay with you, Greavesy boss. Yeah, I
like KFC, bro, but not when I'm
drinking. It's greasy as [ __ ]
Okay, I'll just get a um
I'll just get a beef to main is it?
Wait, maybe they might do the curry, isn't it?
No, I'm not getting spicy hot. Oh, I
could just get a beef curry. Ah, I'm
going to get a beef curry.
That's what I'm getting. I'm going to
get a beef curry. Yeah.
I like Cole. I'm not gay.
Is there no normal rice?
One second, lad.
Is she unstable? This Christian is or something greasy.
She's playing games, bro.
Can't even get normal rice. How you
going to have that? How you going to
have the [ __ ] curry?
She's very weird, bro. She's deleting my
number again and Shane blocked me. She
said I'm delusional. I said, "Oh, let's meet up."
Fish and chips.
Oh, what about a fish and chips, bro?
It's saying that there's fish and chips here.
There's lamb donor mixed on a
maybe get a kebab.
I don't know, bro. What I'm getting [ __ ]
Let's go back to Chinese.
So, I would have just got a curry, but
the curry place isn't over. Indian curry.
Um, lamb ribs, fried rice,
curry. This is right. Let's try again.
No, I'm just going to get I'm just going
to get a beef chow. I'm just going to
get a beef fried rice chicken. I don't know.
UK signing thinks I'm a troll, lad.
See you later, lad.
I don't know what I'm going to get.
It's annoying, isn't it?
I was just going to get a beef ch it.
What do you think, Greavesy?
Yeah, but Yeah, but there's no Yeah, but
there's no um
But what am I going to have the rice?
What am I going to have the curry with?
Cuz they don't serve normal rice.
There's no normal rice. That's what I'm
trying to say. They don't have normal
rice to mix with the curry.
Yeah, I reckon a lamb [ __ ] kebab would
be nice, bro. To be fair,
I had that for ages. Kebab. Let's just
get a kebab. [ __ ] it in it.
I want to get like a mixious.
I like to mix it.
I want to kind of mix it, you know.
Do you reckon she's weird then? Yeah.
Uh, I eat plain rice with the curry.
Anyways, I'm going to get this um this
shish. Anyways, lad.
Sauces. Burger sauce. Mayonnaise. I
don't want sauce. Okay.
Yeah. I'm just going to get mixtures.
There you go. Ordered. Done.
She's a [ __ ] That Christian is he, bro?
Yeah, I got I got three numbers. What? [sighs]
It took It could take up to 40 45 past.
Oh, one second, lad. Yeah,
one second, bro. It's letting you join.
One second, Kieran. [snorts]
It's trying to let you up, bro, but it's
not letting you up. It's not letting me
add you. I see your name.
Kieran always comes back when I go out drinking.
Yeah, I got three numbers on a Monday,
which I don't think was too bad,
but it's [ __ ] hard as [ __ ] bro.
Like I said, we'll do Thursday, we'll do
Saturday, then I'm off, lad.
It's going to have to be Thailand, bro.
It's going to have to be, isn't it?
Try again, Kieran.
>> Yeah, I've got a mix shift. I know it
doesn't mean anything now. Of course I
know. But it wasn't as busy today.
Otherwise, I would have just [ __ ]
stayed with the [ __ ]
But yeah, it was it wasn't as busy.
Obviously, it was Monday, but it still
went bad for Monday to be fair. So
So obviously what I'm going to have to
do is um try Thursday and Saturday maybe
mix it up and then I'm just have to
leave. Simple as that.
Cuz Christian Izzy is mad dusty. She's
actually psychopath, lad.
Game playing and [ __ ] bro. It's madness.
It's farts, bro. It's not even funny. [gasps]
I'm going to have to cancel this order
cuz it's taking too long, bro. No,
a lane. The [ __ ] Why you got lane's name, bro?
Yeah, Dusty. It's very hard nowadays in
the west, lad.
I just want some [ __ ] food, bro.
No, I like a I want a kebab, bro. I a for ages.
I've already ordered it, but it's taking
too long, bro. Why is it taking too
long? I don't want to wait that long, man.
Now I've already ordered a shish and mix shish lad.
Quite long, bro. Like an hour. I don't
want to wait an hour, bro.
I'm going to have to try and order it.
Uh, cancel it or something.
Try again, Kieran.
Kieran. It's saying it's showing you up,
lad, but it's not uh letting me add you.
Yeah. I can do audio [ __ ] Yeah, lad.
Can't believe it, lad. Just leave the
food to come. Yeah, we're here all
night, bro. Don't [ __ ] worry, bro.
This how I know you're always watching, Kieran. Bro,
what we saying on roulette? Yeah. You
want to give it a little spin, Kieran?
Nah, [ __ ] that, bro.
Uh, I'm done with that [ __ ]
Give it a little Well, no, we can't give
it a little while. We got scammed last
time. What the [ __ ]
No, we can't do that, bro. Cuz, you
know, we got scammed last time, didn't
we? I got scammed last time in the
casino, kid. I'm sure you heard about it, bro.
No, I'll just wait, bro. [ __ ] it. I'll just wait. [snorts]
There you go. Yo.
>> Hello. Can you hear me?
>> Yeah. What's up, man? You good?
>> [ __ ] hell, man. That took off about
[ __ ] 20 minutes, man.
>> All right, bro. Listen. Yeah, that that
Christian Izzy lives near like where you
live, bro. She's a [ __ ] bro. You heard about that?
What you on about?
>> That Christian Izzy, bro. That was being
a [ __ ] That woman that I met a few a
month ago. You know who I'm talking
about in it, bro.
>> Christian? Yeah, I remember you talking
about I haven't followed you. I haven't
followed it like the story, but Yeah.
Why? What's going on?
>> No, basically like I got her number.
Yeah, we've been speaking for a month
every day and that in it. I said, "Oh,
let's meet in it." She said she had
exams. So, I waited for her exams to
finish and then she's coming up with all
these bogus ass excuses, bro. You get
me? Like, she lives in England, isn't it?
>> Yeah. How old is she? >> 22.
>> That's all right. >> Yeah.
>> Yeah. She's a [ __ ] You see what I'm
saying, K bro? They're [ __ ] I got
three numbers today, bro. Look how many
people I approached. The game's dead,
Kieran. The game's dead, bro.
>> Yeah, I told you that before, man. The
The game's dead.
>> All right. Listen, Kieran, bro. [ __ ]
um Oh, hey, you know I got scammed on
that casino in it. You remember that,
ain't it? I was telling you. Well, I was telling everyone.
>> Yeah, I don't bother with the casinos
anymore, man. Like, I told you before
like I went to I told you that was you
with that. I told any I went to Ready
and I went to London and they tried to
[ __ ] I was all right with the money
and then they they tried to say that,
oh, you needed ID and all that [ __ ] and
[ __ ] off, man. You know what I mean?
>> Yeah. That's what they do in casinos.
It's either bookies or arcades land.
That's the only ones, you know, you get
your money. You know what I mean?
>> Yeah. The bookies you'll get it because
cuz it's slow. You know what I mean? It's slow. >> Yeah.
>> How you get it? >> Yeah.
>> Yeah. Anyway, what's going on with you anyway?
>> Just chilling, bro. I just come back
from drinking. I was just pissed off
today. I just fancy getting on it, bro.
I I drink like once a month to be fair.
I don't really drink much. I just order
some food and it just chilling, bro.
Yeah. See, o what's um I was on Lord
Jay's the other day and they were
talking about LT. What's going on there?
>> Yeah, he just come the other day and
that is it. And I just said I'm not
going to do anything unless you break
the window or you break like the door.
I'm not doing nothing. Just he's up to
his [ __ ] as usual, bro. You know what he's like.
>> Yeah, I I know. I know. He's full of [ __ ]
>> Did he actually come? Was he actually
outside your door?
>> Yeah, was he came? Well, he come. He was
around the corner. Yeah.
What? Did you see him?
>> No, I didn't see him. But he was there.
>> See, if you don't see him, then I I
don't believe it. You know what I mean?
>> Yeah. But it's weird, isn't it? All of
it's just weird, bro. Like, all of it's
weird. You get me?
>> He could have gone there the week before
and filmed a [ __ ] load of segments.
You know what I mean?
>> I don't know. I don't really [ __ ] him
anyways, bro. And it's all irrelevant. But like,
>> yeah, I know. That's what I mean. I
mean, I think he's I think he's more
into mix at the moment, is he? You know,
>> yeah, you saw all of that, bro. But this
is what I said to LT. Yeah. Listen,
listen to what I'm saying, bro. I don't
even want to bring this up. Yeah, but my
man says, "Yeah, he's made a new channel
to get away from this community, but he
knows everything. How How is that possible?"
>> Yeah, I saw I saw you say that and I
believe you because I'm the same. Like,
I've just set up a fake channel here
just to talk to you.
The thing is with Rick's, bro, the thing
is with Rick, yeah, I just said to him,
"Oh, do you speak to LT?" Like, I won't
even try to [ __ ] or anything here. I
just said, "Oh, do you speak to um do
you speak to LT?" And he started going
in on him. Like, not for long, though.
It weren't even for long. And so, he
must be watching. He must be I don't
follow me, so I don't really know what's
going on there. But
>> yeah, bro, that's weird.
>> You know what I mean? So, it's one of
them [ __ ] things like where if you
don't [clears throat] follow people, you
know what I mean? I never I never used
to like Ricks, me personally, cuz he
just always used to [ __ ] stuff and I
just never used to like him to be fair.
>> I don't mind him. I think he's funny,
but he is a [ __ ] I don't think he's
like He keeps saying all this [ __ ] that,
oh, I'm brain damaged. He's not brain
damaged. He He knows what he's doing.
>> Yeah. Have you Have you been Have you
been drinking today?
>> Yeah, cuz I had a big [ __ ] win on the bookies.
>> Nice. How much did you win?
Uh, I went in with uh 300. I got it down
to 125, but I left with 925, so I was up like 600.
>> Yeah, that's nice. I got a bit of extra
money today, bro. Something. So, yeah,
[ __ ] it. I went out, bro. Well, I was
going to go anyways. I didn't need extra
money, but still. It [snorts]
>> was like, what's going on with you and
Timmy? Are you going to be fighting?
>> No. Do you know what it was? No, no, no.
Do you know what it was, Kier? Yeah,
bro. I I watched gambling. I watch I
like gambling videos. Yeah. When Jimmy
does gambling vlogs. Yeah.
>> I heard
>> I went I went on these I went on these
[ __ ] I went on these [ __ ] bro. Yeah.
And the guy keeps mentioning me trying
to draw me the [ __ ] out. So I said,
"Listen, yeah, I will message your
family." So if he wants to come
Wednesday, he's going to get battered,
bro. He will get battered. Trust me.
>> He won't come on Wednesday, but if he does, just
>> he's going to get battered, bro. Yeah,
he's going to get battered.
>> You're going to b no one. Sunshan, you
won from London, Thailand. Look at him.
Oh, I'm going to beat the detail. You
came outside your [ __ ] You're going
to see I dare you to
I'm kicking him, bro. I'm kicking him.
I'm kicking him. I'll see you Wednesday,
bro. Simple. Have the same energy on Wednesday.
>> Talk to him. I want to talk to him, bro.
>> Okay. Okay. Talk to him then. [clears throat]
>> That's what he does. He runs away cuz he
knows I'm going to come to his door and
he's going to do it like London Taylor.
You're going to do nothing, Peter. You
are going to actually [ __ ] off. We'll
see you Wednesday.
>> I'm coming out of my way to own you and
you'll see you Wednesday.
>> Okay. Okay.
You're being ter
no. You won't pills. You won't be on
your pills on Wednesday. If you think
these little dust,
he just talks over people. Hey Kier, he
>> Why is he rush talking, man? Just talk.
You know what I mean?
>> No, he just talks over people. You can't
you can't with him, bro.
>> It's just like No, no, no, no, no. Just
talk. You know what I mean?
>> I Kieran, you you saw that you saw that
g thing I was on about, in it.
>> Say that again.
>> You saw that G thing I was on about, in it. >> Golfing.
>> Yeah. Like the the the three guys, one
hammer. You've seen that in it. You have
seen it in it.
>> I'm going to be [ __ ] honest with you,
PJ. I haven't really been on it on here.
Ive I've I've been in in and out of it,
but I just haven't been really on it.
>> No. No. What I'm saying to you is have
Have you seen that? Three guys, one
hammer and you ever seen that?
>> No, I don't even know what you're on about.
>> He doesn't He doesn't know what I'm
talking about. [ __ ] it. You You never
heard of it.
>> Free hammer.
>> It's three guys with one hammer. You He
hasn't He hasn't heard about it, Dusty.
You never heard of that? No.
>> I'm going to say no. Just because I
don't know what you're on about.
Yeah, it's better you don't know then is
it bro it? It's just but I don't know
you saying free hammer. I don't know
what you mean.
>> Basically there's a video right of these
two guys hammering this guy to death in
2007. You saw that in it.
>> Oh I I don't watch that [ __ ] [ __ ]
You know like the [ __ ] snuff movies
and [ __ ] like that.
>> No, no, it was real life. It was real
life. It happened in real life, bro.
>> Ain't the same as snuff movies. I I
don't watch that [ __ ] bro.
>> Wait, what's going on with this [ __ ]
bro? Where's my order? Where's my food?
I'm [ __ ] hungry as [ __ ] bro.
>> Oh, get Timmy back on it. Just Just for
the bad Is he there?
>> He's a [ __ ] virgin, bro. No, he's not
there. One second, bro. Hold on. One
second. Stay there. So, you don't you
don't you never go out drinking anymore,
do you? You say,
>> "No, I stay at home. I just go out and
if I I have a big win, I just go and buy
drinks and then I try.
>> They cancelled. They cancelled my order.
The bastards. Bro, I need some food.
What What do I eat? I don't know what to
eat, bro. They cancel my order, the [ __ ] [ __ ]
>> Is there anyone in the in the waiting
list to come on just for the bands?
>> Yeah, just virgin.
>> Oh yeah, you're the virgin, bro. You're
the one who can't even get shagged up in
[ __ ] down. Can you me have a talk cuz
this little [ __ ] prick's full in your
head full of [ __ ] cuz that's what he
does. No, no, no. He is full of [ __ ]
Right. Have you
keen? Have you seen the channel called
PJ Essex nons?
>> Yeah. No one cares.
>> They do care cuz he ask me. No, he
wouldn't ask me if he didn't care.
>> You can do something.
>> No, no, no. PJ, you can [ __ ]
No one cares about you. You seen Tyler
go to his door? Yes or no? Kid,
>> no one cares about London Taylor.
>> Yes, they do.
Now you're reflecting because you're not
even letting you're not even letting me
and him have a chat because that's how
much you know you are [ __ ] [ __ ]
>> reflector. Now you're the one that's
want to hear the truth cuz you're a
little virgin. You with your own mom
because your own mom couldn't give you 80.
I'm going to link you a channel where he
wished his own mom dead. Why? He wished
his own mom dead. No. No. He wished his
>> I'm going to get a Burger King. I'm
>> Who gives a [ __ ] about Burger King? Why
do you wish you mom dead? Why did you
wish you earn mom dead? Over 80 quid. And don't
you know what, Kean? Three madwell. Type
in. I'm going to clip all his [ __ ]
>> I know all this. I know.
I just Oh my god. He's gone.
>> Bastic. He's Bro, he calls me a virgin.
That's funny, isn't it?
>> I wanted to ask him one question. Like,
why can't he go to Jerry's lane?
>> Hey, bro. How can how can he Hey, what
should I get to eat, Kier? Bro, I
seriously don't know what to choose, bro.
>> I wanted to ask him why can't he go to Jerry's Lane.
O, do you do you follow this uh channel
called Bernie's uh Bernie Law?
>> Never heard of it, bro. I can't can't lie.
>> Winchester disc. You You've heard of Winchester?
>> I know him. Yeah, I know him, but I
don't know the person that you're speaking about.
>> Yeah. No, no, no. He changed the channel
name to Bernie Law. I wanted to ask uh
Timmy has he gone to
>> Have you did you Hey, bro. Did you watch
um Scream 7?
>> Can you just add him for one minute? Just
>> so he's not trying to get in, bro. He's
not trying to get in.
>> I wanted to ask you why hasn't he gone
to Jerry's lane?
>> Did you watch the new Scream, Kieran?
No, but I've got it on I've got a load
of uh free um credits, so I could I
could download it on the YouTube.
>> Yeah, might as well give it a whirl,
ain't it? You're in hours.
>> Yeah, it got a load of [ __ ] It got a
load of uh good
Oh my god. Reviews reviews.
>> Yeah. Yeah. I'm just trying to [ __ ]
fix. You're wast You're wasted, is it?
>> I'm not wasted. I'm just trying to
[ __ ] fix the the TV thing. Hang on.
>> Bless you then.
>> Just give me a minute. Hang on.
>> Right. Here we go. That's bastic's
trying to dry now. Kieran.
>> Kieran, I can't put the post up till
after midnight. But you're listening to
his [ __ ] right? Cuz you obviously
not very intelligent, right? The
evidence is intelligent, man.
>> Intelligent. So why so why you defend
why you talking? That's why you
defending some [ __ ] nons who wish his
mom dead over 80 quid.
>> Oh, shut up.
>> And that's why I'm going to come and
meet you on Wednesday cuz you ain't
going to get out your little [ __ ] on
Wednesday with this little [ __ ] [ __ ]
You're going to speed the [ __ ] I'm
going to do nothing. Wait and see Peter waiter
wait the police
like you always [ __ ] yeah
your mom was petrified the London table
yeah it's all on the [ __ ] channel
it's all on the pizza
you can't lie to the pizza you know you
can lie to this [ __ ] god boy you
can't lie to anyone else Like m he's
lying to you.
He is lying the [ __ ] out of you. He's a
you are. [ __ ] off. Ghost Jerry Lane.
>> No no no
about Jerry Lane. So why you defend him?
Why you defend him when he wish his mom
dead? I'm not even that you [ __ ] off cuz
you No, cuz your mom's giving you 80 [ __ ]
>> I'm kicking him, bro. He's too loud.
He's too loud, bro. He's He's He's too
loud, bro. I'm kicking him.
>> O, can I just say this thing? Oi, he O
Timmy, just go to Jerry's lane. Yeah,
just go to Jerry's lane. You won't [ __ ]
>> Jerry's lane.
>> Um, he knows what I mean. Jerry's lane.
That's why he won't [ __ ] talk about
it. That's like
his mom. His mom. His mom. Like, what do
you want about his mom?
You know what I mean?
>> He's saying about your mom. He's saying
about you said about you wish death on
your mom or something. No, bro. He's
talking [ __ ] man.
>> That's what I mean. I just said just go
to your [ __ ] I just That's why I said
just go to Jerry's.
>> If he if he comes on Wednesday, I'm going to
>> He's not going to [ __ ] come. He might
go to South End, but that's miles from
where you are. So, what's the [ __ ]
point of going?
>> You follow you follow me? Sh. Oh, bro.
Do you keep hearing that guy that comes
on from Lewishin? That that Hugh guy,
that high stick. It sounds like you,
bro. You've been on recently.
>> Yeah. I I I wanted to [ __ ] have a
word with you about that. Like a few
months ago, that guy who kept going on
to Monty's one. He's not me. I know he's
on about you.
>> He sounds like you though, but he's not.
>> No, but I heard you say one time, "Oh,
it was me." It's not me.
>> No, I thought it was you in it.
>> No, it's not [ __ ] me, mate. Listen,
mate. How many times have I spoke to you? >> Yeah.
>> You know what I mean? You know, Shaunie,
now you know my [ __ ] voice. You know
how I talk. >> Yeah.
>> I don't know. I think that guy I think
he does come from my area, but he's not me.
>> [ __ ] knows, mate. [ __ ] knows.
>> He's a [ __ ] idiot anyway. He's not me.
>> You don't like him?
>> No, he's Well, I don't know. I mean,
Lord Jay, he text uh he emailed me once.
said, "Are you on Monty's live?" And I
didn't know what the [ __ ] he was on
about. So I I looked on Monty and there
was an old live stream.
>> And now I will admit he did he did sound
like me, but it wasn't [ __ ] me. >> Yeah.
>> I don't even I get it, bro. I get it. I
know. I know it's not you. I know, bro.
I know it's not you. And there's also
another [ __ ] person who who keeps
going on to other people's streamers and it's Kieran.
He's called he's calling himself Kieran
but with a C, not a K, but with a C. And
then Mac, which is my
the beginning the beginning of my first
uh second name.
>> Do you not understand? Listen, brother.
Listen. Do you not understand? Yeah.
When when Timmy right says, "Oh, I've
done my balls." And he's talking about
himself, you know? He just self
projects, isn't it?
>> I know. I know. I mean, listen, we're
all gamblers here. We all know what he's on about.
>> Yeah, but he's a projector, isn't it?
>> Do you know what it is? Is because he
loses it all. And I mean, he literally
loses it all. It's not like he has It's
not like he has 30 pound back or 40
pound back. I think he's the
>> So with you with you, as soon as you get
your money, right, you just gamble it in
it and see if you to win more on it.
That's what you do every time, is it?
>> Yeah. But you see, I'm safe, PJ, because
of of where I live, like who I'm with. >> Yeah.
>> So, like
every three or four months I will go on
a mad splurge, but I can't I can't
gamble the way Timmy does. Timmy
obviously [ __ ] lives with someone who
[ __ ] bank rolls his lifestyle if that makes sense. >> Yeah,
>> I can't I can't gamble like that. Like
whereas I might gamble one
>> got myself a burger I got myself a
Burger King Grezy.
>> Yeah, I get you though. I get what you mean. Yeah,
>> you got yourself a had one I wasn't even
listening. You got yourself what? What?
Backy days or what?
>> Burger King.
>> Burger King. I like bacon. I like the
bacon and double cheese XL, bro. That's
my favorite burger. But yeah, bro. Like
you when did you last go drinking and
approaching years? Is it? No, maybe like a year.
Probably longer than that, man. I've
given up on it.
>> It's the same old it.
>> I've given up on it. It's It's the game,
is it? You know, you either win it or
you lose it. And after a while, you just
realize that it's not for you.
Yeah, pretty much. But what did what did
you think of that whole Christian Izzy
thing then? Did you think it was a lot
of Did you think it was a load of Tommy rot?
>> Oh, what? The elix one? >> Yeah.
>> Is that the one that said that about the Palestinian thing?
>> No, that was someone from years ago.
>> I don't [ __ ] I I am watching you, PJ.
I'm not [laughter]
I'm just not I'm just not in and out of
it. Do you know what I mean? I'm just
I don't know what you're on about.
>> I don't I don't know. I don't know
nonsex's channel anymore.
>> I don't even [ __ ] watch him anymore,
PJ. Because he doesn't respond to me
anymore. He's like Mark Taylor. Mark
Taylor was the first person who I went
in on but he he stopped replying to me.
>> So after a while you just give up. Um
Shaunie was funny because for a while he
would start up a live stream if you ever
called him a nons or anything
>> and then he he gave up.
So but after a while I've given up on
him as well. As long as he just doesn't
mention me, I I won't mention him, you
know, kind of thing. >> Yeah.
>> Why Kieran Kieran? That red star is a loser, bro.
>> It's that um It's Chase, isn't it?
>> Yeah, I think so as well. It is, isn't
it, Gregy? Yeah,
>> it's Chase. That um I didn't know it was
Chase, but someone else said it. Someone
said he gave himself away, but I don't
know how he gave himself away. It was Chase.
>> You must come on here every day, Karen. Is it?
>> I don't I honestly [ __ ] don't. I just
I You know what it is? Is I I will come
on here once every couple of days or so,
just have a quick glance. I follow you
and I follow Lord Jay.
You you've been you you said you've been
to Simmons, isn't it?
>> Sorry, say that again.
>> You said you've been to Simmons, isn't
it? The bar.
>> I never said I went to Simmons. I don't
even know what you're on about.
>> You own a bar Simmons. You've heard of
it, isn't it?
>> Nope. I don't even know what you're on about.
>> It's just a bar, lad.
>> I don't know.
You know what I mean? It is. You're a
You go out, you
do whatever you do, but it's not me, bro.
>> No, I don't, bro. I don't go out as much
anymore. I don't go out as much anymore,
but I can't be bothered with it anymore.
You get me? [clears throat]
>> Bro, you're all before your time, bro.
>> Yeah, pretty much. Pretty much, bro.
>> You're all before your time. But you
used to go to that Weather Spoons in
Tottenham Court Road. I I went there today.
>> Yeah, because my brother lives around
the corner from there practically, but I
don't really go there. But if I'm there
in the area, I would go there.
>> You like Elen, is it?
>> Well, it's the nearest thing to me. Yeah.
>> It's not bad, Elen. Bro,
these [ __ ] are crazy. They're cray, bro. Cray.
>> Apparently, I always sound like I got a cold.
>> Really? Why? You know everything.
You know, everything I say about
nonslegs is the truth. And how do I know
that, bro? Cuz you told me everything.
>> You see, she's funny. Do you see? Of the
serious. Listen, I was the first one to
go really in on Shauny. I just gave up.
You know what I mean?
>> No, but you know that Scottish bully.
That is true. That is actually true,
bro. You tried to deny it, but it's true.
>> You were the one that told me you were
the one I kept telling me about the
[ __ ] Tilly the D. Do you remember? [laughter]
>> Yeah. Yeah. His mom used to have a dog
in it and she used to like throw the dog
on him and that. That's why he was
scared of dogs. Do you remember that
video? Yeah. Where like he was scared of dogs?
>> Yeah. Do you remember when I had that
fake account? Tilly the Tilly the Dalmatian.
>> Yeah. [laughter]
Grievy Tilly the Dalvation. Big up
Tilly. Is it?
>> Yeah. Cuz you kept [ __ ] You told me it was.
>> Yeah. You seem You're drunk though. You
are drunk in it
>> at the moment. Yeah. Because I've had a
[ __ ] big win today.
>> Yeah. Just Just try not to give it back in it.
>> I won't. What was you playing? What was
you playing again? What was you playing
>> I was playing Wolf. That new uh that new
game on the Inspired Wolf. You know that
one? That Wolf?
>> I've heard of it. Yeah, I think I've
heard of it. So, did they did they give
you it in cash?
>> Well, no. I played it. I went in there
and put the cash in.
>> So, they paid you out in cash.
Well, yeah. I always do that. Like if I
I'm not one of them ones who play uh Oh,
man. I'm going to give up in a minute
because I'm [ __ ] wasted.
>> Well, I'm [ __ ] wasted as well, bro.
>> You don't sound it, bro.
>> No, I just I've just sobered up a little
bit, bro. But I'm still a bit like
[ __ ] I mean,
>> what did Timmy sober you up?
>> He's a [ __ ] Yeah, he's a [ __ ] isn't he?
>> Timmy, so beat you up. Well,
>> so what you're saying is it's basically
impossible now to date in this country.
Pretty much, is it?
>> It's [snorts] not, but you're a
different age group for me. You know
what I mean? I mean, it's easier for me
than it is for you. Do you know what I
mean? Like, you're >> Yeah.
>> You're still in your 20ies. >> Yeah. >> [laughter]
>> I don't really know how to explain every
time. I mean, I've had this conversation
with you like dozens of [ __ ] times. I
don't really know where to go with it.
You know what I mean?
>> Yeah. I want I want you and I want you
and Grevy to watch Three Guys One Hammer. >> Yeah.
You're you're drunk in it
>> a bit. Yeah. But Greavvesy trolls you. Uh,
>> no. But what I'm saying is, what I'm
saying is you should watch it now.
You're drunk, isn't it?
>> Grezy trolls you. I've seen Grezy on Tik Tok.
>> Yeah. No way.
>> I've seen Greasy on uh Tik Tok. Oi,
Grezy, I can see your comments. Oi, do
you know that Nick official? That fat
guy? I've seen you comment on him. [laughter]
Him and Jackie. Nick and Jackie. Yeah,
he's not listening.
>> No, but listen, Kieran. Um, just watch
it now. Is it? Three guys, one hammer.
>> No, I don't watch movies. I've got ADHD.
I can't [ __ ] concentrate.
>> Grievy, can you watch it? Grievy won't
watch it either.
>> Lol. Yeah, he's funny.
>> Yeah, I've seen you. Do you know what it
was? Om. He had a funny turn. Yeah, he
did. He had a heart attack.
you know, but he survived it. O Greasy,
I was going to reply to it, but I can't
reply to to your comments on there
because if I do, then you'll see, you
know, like you'll [snorts] [ __ ] see
who I am kind of thing.
>> Hey, Kieran, you know what I don't like
about central London? It's just full of
like stuckup [ __ ]
>> Yeah, but it's it's one of them [ __ ]
things, isn't it? It's like it's you're
competing with every [ __ ] sector of
society. Like you've got Well, this is
how I see it. Like you go in there,
you go in there, you got tourists. Okay.
They're your first competition.
>> Yeah. Uh
>> you got you got day visitors, English
visitors, then you've got
you just got every kind of visitors. And
it's just not the right place to [ __ ]
meet. You know what I mean?
>> Yeah. But you do get people that do live
in London in in central isn't it?
>> Yeah, my brother. But
>> No, I mean you meet them in central, but
they'll just meet in they'll just live
in another place in London. Do you get me?
>> Yeah, but they're usually rich. You know
what I mean? You know what I mean? It's like
>> they're [ __ ] bro. They're [ __ ] Is
it? I met some American guys today,
Kieran, but they were kind of [ __ ] You
know what I mean?
You need to get like a [ __ ]
You know what I mean by [ __ ] though? I
know what you mean. Like
it it's difficult cuz you need to get
someone who's on your level, but you
mean them in central if that makes you s
if that makes sense. [laughter]
>> Yeah, it's true. And it g you listening
to this? It's true, isn't it?
You need to go.
>> That's what I mean. I mean, you need to
[ __ ] find somebody.
>> Yeah. But no one's They just say they
got boyfriends, isn't it?
>> Yeah. If they're not interested, they
will say that. Yeah.
>> That's all. That's all they ever Look at
man. He went Thailand over it, K.
I don't like him.
>> Yeah. But at least he [ __ ] At least
he come off YouTube. He never went back
and he lived. You know what I mean, bro?
Like, you can't take that off somebody.
>> Did he? Well, he didn't actually because
he he sent you all his videos and he got
you to upload them, didn't he? So, he
didn't really come off it, did he?
>> No, he hasn't been on He doesn't look,
he doesn't post or nothing. Think about
it, bro. Like people can hate.
>> I know what you're saying, but he he
went into a [ __ ] woman's
>> He went into a pub, been into the women's toilets,
[ __ ] his dick and got you to [ __ ]
upload it. You know what I mean?
>> Yeah, that was funny, is it?
>> No, not not to me. It wasn't, but
[laughter] each to their own.
>> You didn't find that funny when you No,
I didn't find it funny. I don't like
him. I think he's a n
Yeah. Yeah. He's a dirty [ __ ] n
that's how I see him.
>> You know, you know LT. Yeah. He calls
this he he calls this a um he calls this
a negative sector. Toxic sector. He
calls it a toxic sector. It
>> Yeah. Well, I had my run in with him
once even though I didn't know he had
another channel. But [laughter] I think
a lot of what he's to be fair to be fair
a lot of what he says
I agree with. You know what I mean?
>> What do you mean?
>> I just mean that there's a lot of [ __ ]
it's just it's just a troll [ __ ]
community is it?
>> Beat anyone. No one's going to beat
anyone. And at the end of the day, PJ,
you can be whoever you want on here.
No one [ __ ] knows anyone. You know
what I mean?
>> Yeah, pretty much. Yeah.
>> No one [ __ ]
wants to come back. You [ __ ] wants to
come back here and the virgin isn't it? >> Sorry. [laughter]
Y did you hear that? Creepy. I said
Timmy. I said Timmy wants to come back. The virgin.
>> Timmy come back. But I'm not going to
[ __ ] argue with you. If you want to
argue with him, it's not [laughter] like
>> I don't think you're switch fell, are
you? Because all the evidence like cuz
Peter hasn't got the intelligence to
copy report it and take a copyright
claim to get rid of the evidence cuz
he's stupid, right? Realistically,
>> no no, let's talk. No, it's not about
trolling. Peter brings it on himself.
What? We've all been trolling. was
mentioning my name. So I finish
m I'm going to beat you up.
You come out. You come out that door
mate. He's going to be like not like last time.
Right. He's not immature enough to have
an adult conversation. Can you and me
have an adult conversation at least
>> a conversation with you? But there's no
point having a conversation with him involved because
>> No, there's no point PJ cuz PJ PJ will
kick me out because PJ's a [ __ ]
You know this video, right? PJ has
always takes it the wrong way,
>> right? PJ wants to impress these people
on YouTube, right? He does his boxing like that's YouTube.
Listen, listen. Kieran. Okay.
>> Everything he does is self projection.
Everything is him, bro. Kieran, there's
no point talking to a self-proeding virgin.
>> Okay. If I'm a self-projecting virgin,
as you call me, why do you wish your mom
deaf? Because she wouldn't give you birthday.
>> The video is out there. The video is out
>> Listen, he just talks [ __ ] Kieran. This
is what I'm saying, bro. I'll see him on
Wednesday. Simple. I'll see him on
Wednesday, bro. That's
>> the When you do this, it just gives him
the ammunition because he thinks that
you're cutting him off because
>> No, cuz he's just shouting over people.
He's just shouting over Yeah, but Kevin,
he's just talking over people.
>> He's talking the truth. And when you cut
him off, he it's giving him ammunition.
Just just let him talk it out and then
>> because he just talking he's just
talking over people to Kieran.
>> I get that. But just just let him talk.
Just let him talk.
>> He makes up fake stuff. Like listen,
Kieran, I don't do my balls in gambling.
He does. He's a virgin. Everything he
says is himself. You get it? He's a
[ __ ] I get what you're saying, but
when you cut him off like that, he's
going to come back and say that you cut
him off because he was telling the
truth, even though you say it's not the truth.
>> Yeah. Well, he can say what he wants,
bro. He doesn't know me, bro. Simple.
So, that's that.
>> I don't know.
>> It's just a span. It's a [ __ ] place,
isn't it? O Kieran, you know, you know
LT. Yeah. He was doing the bias thing
again that you was talking about. Yeah,
>> he was and he and he's he's supposed to
not like nons and stuff and I'm thinking
what the [ __ ]
about three weeks ago when you were
going on about it to me and I went on
his page and I saw that [ __ ]
um Sean said that oh I'm in Tottenham
and all this [ __ ] like
did you look at all that?
>> No, I didn't see that. Nah, cuz that
surely went on his page or something
when you told me about it.
>> I was wondering why he was defending
Nods when Nons is a coward and he's
supposed to not like him.
>> Yeah, but when you told me about it and
I went on there, I saw that saying that,
oh, I go through Tottenham every now and
then with my girlfriend.
>> No, I did see that. I actually did see that. Yeah.
>> Yeah. And then but he didn't reply to
it. It's just like, what the [ __ ]
>> It didn't make sense, is it?
>> No. So, obviously they're [ __ ] I
don't know. Obviously, he sympathizes
with him. I don't know.
>> Yeah, they're just biased in it. Like you said,
>> ETA or the Burger King because
you even said that they were biased,
didn't they? Remember?
>> Yeah. I think everyone is. I think why
doesn't anyone Why doesn't anyone ever
say anything to Shauny?
That's what gets to me. You know what I mean?
>> Yeah. Do you know what it is? I'll tell
you why, Kieran. Yeah. Because think
about like this. Yeah. People don't like
me on here in it. But when I go for
Timmy, people start liking me. Do you get it?
>> Yeah. But why doesn't anyone ever say
anything to [ __ ] Shauny? Why?
>> Some people do. trumpet.
>> L A does and um Trevor Dawson does and
Harry F does, but very few people.
>> Yeah, very few people do.
>> Yeah, but Trevor Dawson and Harry I
don't know if Harry Freud has a channel,
but Trevor Dawson and Harry Freud
doesn't have a channel. Lord Jay does,
but they don't seem to listen. I know
that. Do you remember that shagger?
>> Yeah. He used to sat here but he disappeared.
>> Yeah. But that was it. >> Really?
>> Well, yeah. All about Shorty Long. You
know, people who said it,
>> I need to [ __ ] just take a [ __ ]
lo. My My throat's gone.
>> So, Kieran, what you were saying is
Yeah. When you went when you won money
Yeah. like reading and that they were
trying to like not pay you. Yeah.
>> Not reading like [ __ ] um I'll talk to
you but my [ __ ] I'm just warning you
now. My throat's going because >> Okay.
>> I got a [ __ ] cold coming on. But
yeah, but I'm on about the central
London like when you go in there, you
know what I mean?
>> Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
>> And then they like say if you go in
Right. If you I'll say this once. If you
go in there with 3,000 or 4,000,
they're up your [ __ ] ass. They're
giving you [ __ ] bags of crisps, coke. >> Yeah. >> [ __ ]
what? Whatever. Like meals or whatever. >> Mhm.
>> Say that you waste all of that. They're
right with that. But just say that like
you're on your last £100 and just say
that you get all that money back and
then you make 3,000
profit or something. Then they're like,
"Right, where's your [ __ ] passport?"
[ __ ] like that, you know?
>> Yeah, it's happened to me. Yeah, it's
happened. It happened. Well, it happened
to me in Nottingham when I tried to take out £350.
So I believe I know I know how it is. Yeah.
>> Yeah. But they did that back like in [ __ ] 2009
with me back in Uh, I went in with 3,000. >> Yeah.
>> Um, I got my 3,000 back and then I got
one and a half grand. So, I was I had 4
and a half thousand. So, basically 1 and
a half thousand, but they wouldn't give me the
I had to [ __ ] go and get my passport.
I had to go and get all this [ __ ] You
know what I mean?
>> Did they pay it in the end?
>> Yeah, they paid it in the end, but it's
not the [ __ ] point. It took weeks,
you know what I mean?
>> Really? Weeks? Yeah.
>> It took It took [ __ ] weeks. Well, I
don't know weeks, but it took two weeks
to go get the [ __ ] paperwork. Go get
the passport. Go get the pay cuz I
[snorts] was working at the time. Go get
the pay slips. Go get the [ __ ] bank balance. >> Yeah.
>> You know what I [ __ ] mean? Just give
me my [ __ ] money. You know what I mean?
>> Yeah. What the [ __ ] bro?
Don't [ __ ] me around with [ __ ] money,
man. You know.
>> Yeah, it's [ __ ] And that's why you
got put off by them, isn't it?
>> Yeah, I got put off and then I stopped
the [ __ ] bookies after that.
>> You know, lads, lad books. I've got a
lad books account. Yeah. So, if I won
four grand, would they start asking me for ID? >> Um,
well, yeah, they probably would if if
you won four grand because you're doing
it through the online thing, aren't you? >> Yeah.
But if you if you say you go bookies
Yeah. and you want four grand on a
football bet, they just pay it in it.
>> Yeah. But see, I do it differently. Like
if I go to the bookies
>> because I know what they're going to do.
Like if it goes over a 500 or if it goes
over. So I will do several different bets over
under 500 or something so that they will
pay out if that makes sense. Yeah, it
makes sense. Yeah.
>> Yeah. Is Timmy still coming in or what? >> No,
>> you should meet up with nonslegs.
>> I ain't meeting up with non leg. I'll
[ __ ] boot his head in.
>> Oh, that Monty's weird, ain't he?
>> I don't like Monty either. Don't
introduce me to your [ __ ] friends. I
don't like him.
>> No, he's a snake, bro. He snaked me in it.
Why? What? Over a troll? I don't know. I
haven't even looked at it. No,
>> he's just a snake, isn't he?
>> I don't like him. I don't I don't like
any of these people.
>> No, I don't, bro. Except Greasy.
I speak to Greasy Hy, you know.
>> Oh, well, do you talk to him often?
>> Yeah, he's all right, man.
Yeah, I can remember him.
He was If you go on Tik Tok and there's
some fat guy called Nick Official. If
you look on here, you'll see uh Greasy on there.
>> Yeah, I've never seen him, bro.
>> Oh my god, my [ __ ] throat's going. [clears throat]
But um I'm going to go cuz my [ __ ] throat's going.
>> Okay then, bro. I'll talk to you later on.
Yeah, take it easy, bro.
Just know just all [ __ ] are the same.
>> Yeah, basically, right? Yeah.
>> Hang on. Let me just see. I'm on Tony.
I don't know what you on about Tony
Holl. I don't want to talk. If it's
going to be some [ __ ] Tony Holly, who's that? >> Mhm.
>> Do you know who that is?
>> Yeah. Some guy, bro. Yeah.
Is it good or bad?
>> See, it's all right, bro. Yeah.
>> Well, have you been on there? >> Mhm.
>> He's a funny Christian guy who gets mad.
He said, "Yeah,
>> a funny Christian group." I'll have a
look, but if it's going to be some
[ __ ] guy that
>> Are you Are you Christian?
>> No, my parents were My parents were Catholics. Ah. Why you
>> here when I'll meet you in haze or high
w you spaz. No, you're not meeting
anyone launch legs.
>> Oh, why does he keep saying? That's what
gets to me.
>> That's miles away. That's miles away.
>> That's a different That's the other
That's a different way, isn't it?
>> Kieran, I'll meet you in H suppose. How
about I meet you in St. Mary's Quay?
Oh [ __ ] You don't want to hear that, do you?
>> St. Mary's Quay
>> [ __ ] eggs. I spoke to your [ __ ]
>> He's just
let me just say this before I go. How
about Shaunie? when you attacked your [ __ ] sister
in your nan's living room and your nan
turned on you.
>> Do you remember that? Cuz your [ __ ]
ex told me all about that.
>> Yeah. She told me that you [ __ ]
you hit your you shoved your sister [laughter]
in your nan's living room and your nan
turned on you and you were like, "Oh my
god, she's faking your shit." It's like
it's like it's like Miles McQuary
that used to bully him in college
is that it's that [ __ ] from my disabled mind.
>> Yes. Yes. Yes, it is. Yes, it is.
>> And [ __ ] and Miles McCoy.
You remember Miles McCoy used to your
[ __ ] sister. You beat her in your
nan's living room.
She told me all of this because I
[ __ ] searched her up on Facebook
after you [ __ ] split up with her
because she wasn't showing you enough
sympathy because your friend [ __ ] died. >> Yeah.
>> Yeah. I don't care if you're with your
nan today. It doesn't matter. You
[ __ ] hit you pushed your sister in
your nan's living room. Look at him
going [ __ ] Naz because he knows it's
all true. [laughter]
>> You [ __ ]
sister in your nan's living room. [laughter]
>> He's such a virgin, is he?
>> Are you going to talk about St. Mary's
Queen? It's not true. It's not true.
It's not me. I don't live there. Are you
going to say that now?
>> I spoke to your ex on [ __ ] Facebook.
away. It's 9 minutes away, Greavves.
>> And you shut your [ __ ] mouth up for
about [ __ ] four years after 3 years
after that. You're only piping up now. I
know all about you, Sean.
>> And Ty the Dalmatian.
>> Tilly the Dalmatian. Well, that was from
you. That was from me. But yeah,
>> that's where that's where that's where
your fear of dogs come from.
>> Not St. Mary's Cray. St. Mary's Quay.
You know how it's spelled. Oh my god. >> Yeah,
>> that's close. I'll say that. Of course
it is. I know where it is cuz your ex
told me all of this.
We had a long conversation about you,
Sean, on Facebook.
Oh dear. The ass has just fallen out of
you, hasn't it?
No, it's not.
>> [clears throat]
>> Oh, do you remember Miles McCoy?
Grievesy. Miles McCoy.
He used to bully the [ __ ] out of you, didn't he?
>> Now, just remember Sean, you [ __ ]
answered to me, boy. And just remember, [laughter]
>> why Grezy? Why was Why was Nons saying
Why was Nons saying shovel car was
attractive to fit in? He was saying to
fit in with the crowd like Kieran. He
didn't want to feel left out in it.
>> Oh, I know. But his [ __ ] present
girlfriend, she's got a long
um social media background like
>> he was to fit in
like Kieran. He was saying it to fit in.
>> I know he was, but that's [ __ ]
Shauny, in it.
>> Yeah, he like he likes to at the end of
the day, he likes to follow the crowd
for an easy life. So
that's that it
>> Shauny [ __ ] sitting there now just
thinking [ __ ] [ __ ] [ __ ] [ __ ] [ __ ] What
do I say? What do I say? Listen Shauny
mate, I know all about you. If you want
to [ __ ] go back there. If you want to
go back three years when it's me and you or whatever.
>> You are balding. I'm not balding more
than you. You [ __ ] ugly [ __ ]
>> If you want to go back,
>> have you seen Have you seen Have you
seen your hairline?
>> Count every year. We
>> have you seen your [ __ ] hair? Have
you seen your hairline? You [ __ ] ugly
rat [ __ ] You can't grow a beard. You
[ __ ] ugly bastard. Sorry, Kieran. His
dad's a [ __ ] [ __ ] uh nuts as well.
>> His dad's a [ __ ] nuts as well.
>> You absolutely are boarding, you big nose bastard.
>> Oh, you're boring, ugly boy. Go get
laid. You need to get laid, lads.
>> You're boarding big time. Big news.
>> Hey, Kieran, he needs to get he needs
It's the No, no, Kier. It's the virgin.
It's the virgin, bro. Trust me. It's the virgin.
>> It's the virgin virgin. And you're big time.
>> It's the It's the It's the virgin, bro.
He He needs to get a hobby. He actually
needs to get a hobby. Kieran, lad.
>> The struggle of being a virgin.
>> He needs He needs to get He needs to
actually get laid.
>> And the thing is, he didn't he didn't he
doesn't ask answer anyone's questions.
>> What What questions would they be? Big
news. Why did you Why did you say that
Cheryl Cole was good-looking to fit in?
You ugly rat looking.
>> Cheryl Cole was attractive once.
>> You did. You said you're gay. You're
correct myself. Wait, wait. I correct
myself. Before you ever brought
to copy your little copycat,
didn't he cry over Britney?
>> Oh, yeah. Yeah. He cried over some girl
that didn't want to know him in Canada.
Didn't want him. Weren't interested in
him. Good thing then if this is true.
>> Well, no, because you was [ __ ]
obsessed with someone that didn't want you.
>> [ __ ] never wanted you.
>> Would this be a good thing though if
nothing happened with her?
>> Uh, well, it is for her safety. Yeah,
but you like kids. So, that's not a good
thing that you like kids.
>> You're a [ __ ] pedo.
>> You're [ __ ] nuts, mate.
>> But there's plenty of evidence to [ __ ] mate.
>> You're [ __ ] You're [ __ ] And
there's plenty of evidence to show that
you got missing teeth, you ugly [ __ ]
And you look like a rat. You [ __ ]
virgin. Ugly like your dad.
>> Ugly like your ugly dad. Ugly like your
>> Yeah. Okay, bro. You got missing Hey,
bro. How can you How can you Yeah. How
can you Kieran take How can you take
anyone with missing teeth serious?
Someone someone Kieran someone that's 31
that's got missing teeth. Imagine that.
>> Some 31year-old virgin with missing
teeth. Imagine that, bro.
>> The struggle of being a
>> Yeah, I'll see you later anyways,
Virgin. You get kicked
>> two minutes away anyways. It's two
minutes away anyways. Grezy. Yeah, bro.
He's a weird He's a weird [ __ ] man.
>> Yeah. O PJ, if you go on his Facebook
and you go back over and laugh, you'll
see his ex. If you go and [ __ ]
message this ex, she will tell you everything. >> Yeah, I
actually I [ __ ] you are, man. You said
never forget that all [ __ ] are the
same in it. [laughter]
>> They are.
>> Hey Ken, I told you I told you that was
the thing is it with these [ __ ] But
you didn't believe me, did you?
>> May I was [clears throat] the first one
to [ __ ] tell you all that [ __ ] bro? [laughter]
>> No. Seriously, Kieran,
>> the hell was this?
>> Oh, it should be here now. Greavves
eating Burger King. Oh, nice Burger
King. You can't be a nice Burger King.
>> O, does he ever join you live? That uh Grecy?
>> No, but I've heard him talk. I've heard
him talk on Instagram and he messages me in it.
>> It's probably going to be cold greasy.
So, I'm going to have to nuke it.
Like, Kieran, what do you prefer? Burger
King or McDonald's?
>> Uh, McDonald's because there's one in my
town. like going to the town that KFC is
[ __ ] hit and miss.
>> One six.
>> Um the thing is the thing is Kieran I I
haven't ate today. This is my first time eating.
>> All right. You probably [ __ ] out.
>> No, you know what it is. I only drunk
Guinness today. I only I only drunk beer
in it. But if you drink beer, you don't
really need to eat. No. Anyway,
all right, PJ, I'm going to get off
here. I'm going to get I'm going to
message Sha's ex. I'm going to have a long conversation.
>> Your nose bleeding. My blood pressure maybe. Okay,
>> I'm I'm going to leave you and surely unlucky fella.
We're going to have a long I'm going to
have a long conversation with your ex to
the Sean. Anyway, see you later PJ.
>> See you later. See you later. captured. Nice and good.
>> Yeah. 15 minutes already.
I always get the bacon double cheese.
Want some chips?
Did you actually see me down that drink earlier? Here
you like that earlier, didn't it?
I bet he was wondering how the [ __ ] I do
that. Oh, you see that account mama
finding a new mama? The account's back
in it. That account's back.
So, I can't back it. I knew it, bro. I
knew it was going to come back.
Your mama with the hat. Yo, mama.
I agree with you. I'm going to send you
this free one. Yeah.
Come on, baby. I gave you content to say
you po [ __ ]
I gave you content. Po [ __ ] [clears throat]
yourself. I gave you content today [ __ ] [clears throat] Mhm.
Why are you watching ISIS stuff anyways? Gregy,
why are you watching stuff to do with
ISIS? You sick [ __ ]
You're sick. You are, bro.
You're sick. You're a sick puppy. I
should record you. Yeah.
>> [clears throat]
>> I want you to watch this um thing.
It's quite sick to be honest. But you
like sick stuff, ain't it? Really?
Yeah. She deleted all her messages she
was sending me.
So is it safe to say that Christian is unstable? >> Yes.
So, we've got Yeah.
You fly master [ __ ]
I was trying.
He said to me, "It's always going to be
the same there. You know this."
Is he lying with you when he says that
about the date and he said it's always
going to be the same day. You know this.
He's lying in it with you. Bless you.
You love that, don't you, Grezy? Tilly the Dalmatian
[ __ ] himself, mate.
Tilly the Dalmatian. Um, M [clears throat]
no but seriously Christian this is not
stable is she busy
I don't go out
I don't really like doing.
She keeps blocking me and then she keeps
deleting my number and then
then deleting me and then
He deletes my number then add me again.
But she never blocks me. [ __ ] her, man. She's [ __ ]
Yeah, she's [ __ ] in her head, bro.
I don't think it's funny me, bro.
You can if you like, Grey, but I won't be there.
You can if you like, but I won't be there.
Should we go back again on Saturday?
Love it, lad.
Yeah, man. I don't like drinking in
England, bro. They they some of these
bars will just find reasons to ban
people for no reason.
I was speaking to one of the guy up
Simmons and he says, "Oh, the staff
don't do that." Well, they must have
because three people didn't complain.
Three pe three different people didn't
just start complaining
like that never happened, bro.
You know what I mean, lad?
So they must Yeah. I just don't really
like drinking that much, but
maybe once a month. That's it.
You out go that [ __ ] in it, lad.
I need to slow down.
You people need to slow down and you'll
[ __ ] take camp.
Yeah, I got three numbers. I'll text them tomorrow.
[ __ ] hell, bro.
[ __ ] hell, man.
I'll sleep well tonight. >> [snorts]
>> Italian, Spanish, and white, I think. Yeah.
Oh, you're just going to add their name
to Izzy, aren't you?
It's so obvious.
I think one's going back to Italy, but
it doesn't matter anyway, isn't it?
Italy is not that far.
Worst comes to worst.
But yeah, it was hard as [ __ ] bro. It's
getting harder and harder. But it was
Monday, so yeah, it was a Monday.
Christian Izzy was the best, bro. But
she started being weird, man.
She just started being dodge.
She just started being weird, bro.
She plays games in it, Grezy.
Oh gosh, I'm in the nesticles now. Grievy with Crash.
I'm gonna feel like [ __ ] tomorrow, bro.
I'm gonna feel like [ __ ] tomorrow. Motorways. [snorts] Yeah,
Greavves. He's never getting on a plane. Bless him. Yep.
I need to sleep with Teddy's after
watching that glorified thing. Isn't
that right, Grezy?
Now when I go outside yet, I think
someone's going to hit me with a hammer.
Greasy just going to knock me with a
hammer, you know. That's gross.
Cruz is very gross, isn't it?
No, not London Taylor. Just anyone, bro.
That account. Hey, do you remember that
account earlier? Greavves. Annie, you
need to find your mama. Easy.
You need to find your mama with the mama.
with a H in it.
I'm a weirdo. Thanks, lad.
Yeah, you too.
Thank you, lad.
[snorts] Get yourself down waxies, ladies.
Get yourself down waxies. Hey
How's it going?
Oh, my head's hurting.
Nothing, bro. I went on an approaching
session. I got three numbers, but I
don't know about God knows how many approaches.
So many approaches, bro. [ __ ]
Text him tomorrow when I can be bothered.
What's going on with you, bro?
[ __ ] got a headache, bro.
Mick Jonathan Robinson. His dad's name is. Yes. Yes, lad.
Apparently so, bro.
>> Apparently so, lad.
>> I doubt it though, man.
He ain't got the balls.
He will get anxiety the day he's
supposed to come, bro. He ain't about
that life, bro. He ain't about that life. Somebody's That's
why I'm out of here. See you later, lads.