to be able to type in
definitely having a um there.
He thinks he don't think me knows. Yeah, man.
What's the time? Is it 10:00 already?
[ __ ] know. Where does time go, bro? I
swear it just flies.
actually just flies, bro. Yo, man.
I'm up been up like an hour, sir.
Don't feel bad. No hangovers. I drunk
beer on [ __ ] I had a little bit of a
headache, but not much. That's what
happens when you just stick to beer.
It's better, you know.
[ __ ] me, bro.
Hello, Captain C. I didn't do bad it.
Free numbers for Monday.
Messaged them in a bit. All right,
Christian. Is he blocked me? music. I
knew it, bro. I knew. Now she has blocked me.
Such a little [ __ ] in it, bro.
It's bad, is it, lad? Least no
hangovers, isn't it?
Yeah. Must have been playing games from
the start, though. It greases. Must have been.
Must have been, is it, bro?
There must have been though it g
probably unblock and try [ __ ] I mean
you know what I'm saying bro. Yeah it
was a madness bro
for Monday as well.
Must have been crazy.
We'll go out Thursday. Maybe, bro.
Maybe Thursday we'll go out.
By we, I mean me. I don't know, bro. See,
now I'll get the car I want today,
Grezy. I'll get the curry I want, lad. Yeah.
Bright Pepco, what the [ __ ] are you
going on about?
Greasy though. Greasy. They were playing games though. Yeah. Y,
let's meet. Let's meet. She said I'm
crazy in that.
It's funny, bro. Yeah, it's funny, man.
No. No, no, no, no.
>> Yeah, it doesn't matter anyways. [ __ ] her, bro.
Yeah, I went to Waxies yesterday. No problem, Grezy.
It doesn't work like the other places
work. See, they don't have like a little
power trip like a lot of these a lot of
these places, right? They'll find any
excuse to ban people and get a bowler.
They'll get like a bowler. It's like an
ego power trip for them. You get me,
Grezy? Some reason like pubs don't work
like that. Actual like pubs don't work
like that. Doesn't matter where they
are. A pub, it's just a pub in it. Just
let you in. You know what I'm saying?
But like other places this guy was like,
"Oh yeah, can you change into your like
you said, yo, we don't allow
tracksuits." He was being a [ __ ] and
that in it. I said, "Oh, okay. I could
just change into my jeans." Then then he
then I changed into the jeans. Then he
come over 2 seconds later and said, "Oh,
you're banned." Because I wouldn't let a
bouncer put their hands on me.
Because I wouldn't let that a bouncer
try and snatch a drink out of my hand.
That's that was the reason for it. like
6 months ago. They're retards, bro.
They're retards. You can't even call
someone a [ __ ] without getting banned.
They just like them pair aces like that,
they will just find little reasons.
Like, you get me? Like any little thing,
like any little thing they can find
because they don't like the look of you.
So weird. It's a weird country this is,
bro. Yeah. I got free. Yeah. It's just a
It's a weird country, is it, Greezy? like
he tried snatching the drink. He said,
"Oh, if you give me attitude, I'll
snap." I said, "You're not going to
snatch anything out my hand."
And he tried it and then just like the
drink went everywhere. But there was
like a little bit left. There wasn't
like It wasn't full. And then cuz I
defended myself, they had a problem with it.
So, but obviously you don't get these
problems in pubs. You only get them in
places like the bars and clubs and stuff.
That's why I don't really drink. That's
why I don't really go out in this
country. I just don't like it, bro.
Like, it's like the way the system works
and [ __ ] I don't like it, bro. Too many
stuck up [ __ ] as well. That's why I
don't really go out, bro, much.
No, I go out, but I don't [ __ ] know
what I mean. Right. Um,
I don't I don't like doing much, but
No, I'm going to go out a couple of more times. Um,
pick some days, bro. I need to get a
haircut as well.
But yeah, know they do discriminate as
well. They definitely do discriminate.
And one of the guys I speak to, the
other one, he's calling that in it. And
he says, and he said to me, he said to
me, Grezy, he says, "Me as a bartender,
we don't radio through." So I said, "Who
done it then?" Because they no one
complained. Cuz when I when I approached
three people, no one complained. It
doesn't happen. You do it on the street,
bro. You do it on the street, bro. You
do it anywhere else. No one ever complains.
Like, it never really turns into madness
ever. So that's [ __ ] So if they if
you don't radio through to someone then
the bouncers just pick and choose then.
Simple as that. Then they just they just
make up their own rules
because I'm telling you I saw
everything. So it's B. Yeah. Anyways,
it's [ __ ] I had one I had one
lesbian try to get rude to me yesterday. Griezy
[ __ ] what was it? I think I tried
talking to them because [ __ ] it, why
not? I'm on a madness in it. Then they
were being a bit I can't remember what
they said. They gave attitude, not like
directly swearing. And they said, "Oh, I
don't need to be rude." And they started
like trying it and then going on. I
said, "Listen, if you got anything to
say, we can go outside and you can say
it when there's no one that can
interrupt you. There's no one that can
interrupt us. There's no one that's
going to get involved." And then she
just shut up. There you go then. End it.
Like there's no point saying stuff in a
in in a bar where there's loads of
people. You know what I'm saying? If you
got anything to say, let's see how brave
you are. Say it outside. They soon shut
their pants. Shut their pants, Greasy.
That's all you got to say. Don't even
get rude to to them. Um, just say like,
"Okay, well, if you've if have that same energy outside
when when there's not people." Yeah.
And they will and they won't do it.
That's all you got to say. Be it a train
argument, be it somewhere, and they
won't do it. They simply will not do it.
Greasy. You understand? Yeah. And I said
they really need to like where this
social media Yeah. has boosted their
egos up so much. They think they can
talk to people how they want and then
they're surprised when you tell them
about themselves. That's how the Gy
That's literally how delusional they are.
That's literally like how delusional
they actually are
because of these white lights and these
simps. They make they build their egos
up so much that they think, "Oh, there's
like, oh, I haven't been rude, but I'll
start getting rude. You're you're going
to get rude to me. You think you're
going to try and get rude to me and I'm
not going to tell you about yourself."
Where how in what in what universe is
that going to happen? Do you know? Do
you know what I'm saying? Who like who
are they to think they're going to start
saying how they're getting rude? They're
not [ __ ] John Cena. They're not some
big man. Do you understand? Uh it's so
weird like they they actually think that
they can say that and no one's going to
say anything back to them. They're
delusional, bro. They really are. So yeah,
I know who they [ __ ] think they are, bro.
You know, like some of these people.
And then there was a guy trying to white
knight and simp. And that's our bar. I
said, "I'll do what I want whenever I
want. Four eyes." And he kept and he
kept walking. I said you got four eyes.
But that was going to happen, bro. Toxic
stuff was going to happen. It always happens.
Nah, just um ages ago, bro. Um when this
guy was being a [ __ ] Nah,
not really, bro. Doesn't doesn't really
happen much cuz I don't pick fights. I
don't start on people for no reason. You get me?
So, yeah. But yeah, they've got their
own like agenda in these certain London
bars. They do.
Cuz if you go to a pub, it never
happens. It never happens in a pub. You
go in with what you what you wear, what
you like. Um,
and yeah, I I still feel like you could
you should be able to wear what you want
to wear. You're paying their prices for
drinks. You're paying to get in. I just
don't like the way it works in this
country, the system, and that. Like,
it's just it just none of it makes sense. You know,
you get what I mean, Grez. You just none
of it makes any sense.
And you go through all of that [ __ ] and
then you have to deal with [ __ ]
women's attitude as well. Even if you
[ __ ] Oh, it's just mad. It's just
madness, bro. It's just madness.
I don't like England, bro.
My hands gone all numb, bro. From Yeah,
you I don't know who they actually think they are. Um,
yeah. Really? I don't think I know anything. Oh,
yeah. She sent me so many messages
yesterday, but she deleted all of them.
I'm actually scary. What did I send? I
bet it weren't even that bad. Let me
send Let me see the voice notes I sent.
Oh yeah, I just said that. Why should I
be sorry? I didn't do anything. Yeah,
it's true. What I was saying yesterday
was the truth even if I was drunk.
Yeah, I know he won't be.
He was saying, he was saying, hey, he
was on here yesterday earlier with
Kieran saying about how uh yeah, Peter,
I know when you've done your balls in.
I don't do my balls in, bro. I never
ever do my balls in. See, this is what
I'm saying. Everything with him is self
projecting. Do you not get it?
Everything Timmy says is about himself.
Virgin does his balls in. It's literally
himself that he's talking about. Do you
not understand? Like everything he says
is literally about himself.
He can't go out without gambling.
He literally cannot go without gambling.
I [ __ ] can. When was the last time I played roulette?
A while ago, bro. Whatever. He can't go
without he can't go without gambling,
bro. So he he actually is talking about
himself. Simple. Everything he says,
he's just trying to drag people down,
bro. It's a bit like the virgin, the
Orington virgin. That's why like they
were coming on my channel yesterday.
Start. I don't care about them, bro.
like they're just self projectors. It's
the same with Timmy.
Timmy's a self projector.
And obviously cuz he knows Timmy knows.
And it is jealousy with Timmy as well.
With Timmy, it is jealousy, bro. As
silly as that sounds. Yeah, it is. As
ridiculous as that might sound, it is.
Cuz he's the one with the IVA. He's the
one with the gambling addiction. He's
the one that's a virgin. He's the one
that's [ __ ] ugly. Do you get it, bro?
Do do you not see the pattern here?
Do you not see the pattern?
Like I said, if I look like Timmy, if I
look like LJ, if I look like Money Mike,
I'd kill myself. There would have been
no going out yesterday. There would have
been no going out talking to people
yesterday if I look like them. Bro,
if I look like one of them three, I
would kill myself, bro. I swear to God,
I'm not even joking. Seriously, I'm not
even joking. If I look like the state of
them, bro. Yeah, I'm done.
It's the same as like that that red
star. You can big yourself up all you
want. You can talk [ __ ] all you want,
but guess what do you look like, bro?
Let's see what you look like. You see
what I'm saying, bro?
You know, these people Yeah, but Timmy
is a Yeah, Timmy is is a proper self-reflector, lad.
See, I'm not addicted to gambling. I'm
just I just do stuff like compulsively
when I'm born. I'm not even I'm not even
addicted to gambling.
Didn't gamble yesterday. And even if I
did gamble, that's money I can afford to
lose. I'm Do you understand?
Yeah. They're all self Yeah. They're all
self projectors. They never make me feel
insecure. They never make me feel down
about my looks because they just bring themselves down.
The only time I thought, "Oh yeah, maybe
I look bad, whatever," is when these
[ __ ] were playing all these games,
nothing to do with YouTube, but then I
just realized, "Oh, well, they're just
[ __ ] aren't they?" So, yeah, that's
that's it, bro. Like
cuz some of them do try to make you feel
[ __ ] about yourself and that is that is
that is not um
that is not like [ __ ] bro. Like
this this this girl tried making me feel
[ __ ] about myself with the games that
they were playing.
But I should have known from the bar
they're all stuck up to [ __ ]
Anyone goes to that Simmons, they are
just so stuck up it's unbearable. It's a
bit like it's like the people from
Oxford that go to Oxford.
Unbearable people. They're just
unbearable to be around.
Same as stuck up people. Isn't that right, Grezy?
Just Oh, just London is very very
westernized, bro. Very, very, very westernized.
Do you know what I mean? It is greasy.
It's not like where you live. Greavvesy in Stockport. lovely Stockport.
You could you you know you can make
friends with the locals but no seriously
like London is is the worst. They are
just so westernized.
Like all jokes aside, they really are.
Yeah, it does. It does because what what
does this woman mean? Like she was like
she said, "Oh, I wasn't getting rude,
but I would if you like me to." I'm
thinking, "Okay, really? Is that what
you're really going to do?" Yeah, let's
go outside then. get rude outside when
there's no one there. Let's see how
brave you are. Then I'll respect it.
Then I'll respect it. Cuz if you are
going to try and be rude, don't do it in
front of people.
Like cuz I want to see how brave you
really really are,
you know? And that's just a test cuz I
know they won't do it. And if they do do
it, well, we'll see if they do it then,
won't we? You know, and that's it.
Like, yeah. No, it definitely definitely
does inflate their egos. um within like
attitude grievy and also when they think
that they're better than you as well.
Like it does. It does, bro. It does.
Like all jokes aside, like that's why
why do you think a lot of them think
that they're better than you? They're delusional, bro.
Cuz all of these white knights and these
simps and [ __ ]
but that's one thing, you know, having
an attitude is one thing, but then you
you think you're going to you're going
to you're going to try and get rude. I
said, "No, no, no, no, no, no, no." For
no reason as well. They do it for no
Yeah, it does. It does inflate their egos
in different ways, but defin
Yeah, you're not sorting out anyone,
lad. You're not sorting out anyone.
Let's see if you actually do come and
you come by yourself. That's never happening.
That's never ever ever happened.
I'll teach you. I'll teach you. Yeah,
you are the virgin to me. Yeah, you are
the virgin. And I'll show you what
happens when you try to show off for YouTube.
I will show you what happens when you
try to show off for YouTube.
Yeah, I'll show you what the
consequences are for trying to be a show
off on YouTube. But yeah, I'll be
waiting for you.
Yeah, I'm going to run, bro. Totally. Yeah.
So, anyways, um I would love to see you
tomorrow anyways, bro. Yeah.
Do you know this has all stemmed Greasy
from this Timmy's jealousy? You understand that?
Do you know it all? Do you know it all?
This all was stemming, Mr. B, from
Timmy's jealousy. Do you understand that?
Do you understand? This is all through
jealousy with this fat [ __ ]
Yeah, LT's outside. See you later, lad.
Yeah, this is all jealousy with this
Timmy. You know that, bro? I swear down.
I'm not even joking. Yeah.
Yeah. It's all jealousy, bro.
It's all jealousy, bro. with this [ __ ]
Think about the Grievy. Why isn't he
trying to Why isn't he trying to mention anyone else?
else when he's doing these gambling
vlogs? Cuz he knows, bro. He knows. He
He is a jealous bastard. He is a jealous
jealous jealous [ __ ] Missing teeth in your 40s.
How have you got missing teeth in your
40s? Can you explain that to me?
Have you got missing teeth in your 40s?
We got someone that's got missing teeth
at 31. How these people got missing
teeth, bro? The dentist is free for
people on benefits. The dentist is literally free.
The dentist is free, bro. That's the
funniest thing about it. The dentist is
actually free for people on benefits.
I went to the dentist like three. I
followed up with all of my appointments.
What? Um, what the [ __ ] bro?
Yeah, but if they went to a dentist
before that, they could have prevented
it. Do you get it?
Yeah, I know some people are scared. My mom's scared.
My mom's [ __ ] scared
of the dentist.
Yeah, my mom's [ __ ] scared.
But you know,
I've got one missing tooth at the back.
Yes. At the back at 28 years of age.
Yeah. None of my front teeth are
missing. None of my bottom teeth are
missing. Yeah. That's pretty uh that's
pretty normal. It's when you start
having missing teeth. it. Your front
missing teeth at 31 are in your 40s.
Yeah. That's normal. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
Yeah. That's that's that's missing.
Yeah. Yeah. Yes. No. Big difference. I
can open. Okay. Big difference.
See you later, lad.
I can You can see my teeth. I need to
brush them. And guess what? None of them
are missing. Not any of my front teeth
At least I brush my teeth just drinking
tea. But yeah, none of them are missing, bro.
Only at the back cuz it got impacted.
I still remember the pain. It was
[ __ ] vile, bro. Yeah, bro. N
Yeah, man. I hope he does come. Anyways,
[ __ ] little jealous [ __ ]
Timmy's jealous of Timmy's the kind of
people person that is jealous of
someone. Look at it, bro. Yeah, you
laugh at this [ __ ] but it's true. I'm
younger. I'm better looking than him.
I'm younger than him. I'm better looking
than him. I don't have a gambling
addiction like him. Seriously, you laugh
at it, bro, but it's the truth. That's
why he he tries bringing me down in
these videos, cuz he is down. He's a
down and out virgin. That's why he
That's why he goes for me, bro, cuz he's
a jealous [ __ ] Same in legs. Same with Red Star.
Literally, bro, the guy calls me a
virgin even though I've proven I've had
sex. How does that even make sense? It's
laughable at this point cuz Timmy will
always be a virgin. Do you not
understand? He He's not only a virgin.
Timmy will always be a virgin.
You know, the virgin in the making. They
should make a movie of it.
Yeah. See you later, self-reflector.
Yeah, man. My beard needs to be cut, by
the way, bro. I [ __ ] My beard needs
to be cut.
It's getting long now, is it, lad?
Yeah, it's getting long, bro. [ __ ] yeah.
It's not as long as it was though, to be
fair. But still quite long. >> Yeah.
So, oh, sorry. Sorry. There's been a
delay, Greg, in the um double standards folder.
There's been um there's been a delay, lad.
What's your What's your favorite What's
your favorite double standard then,
Grezy? I think mine's got to be It's got
to be the meeting thing.
I think mine's got to be the meeting
thing, I reckon.
The body counts are close second, I think.
There are still there's little double
standards that you'll pick up on over
time. I noticed the meeting one, the
body count one, the uh complaining one. Um,
yeah, there's little ones you'll find, bro.
Yeah, the meeting one is is a is a big
one as well, bro. That's a big one
there. No problem with us is trying to
meet me straight away.
And don't say that she was on holiday
cuz even if she wasn't on holiday, they
still wouldn't have a problem with it.
Yeah. You try and meet people within a
week, there's a big problem. There's a big issue. Yeah. [ __ ] lad.
So, are you are you basically saying
this is going to make Grezy laugh? Um,
so you're basically, so what you're
basically asking is if I'm going to be
like you people when I'm 40. No.
Am I going to be like you people when
I'm 40? And the answer is no.
No. No. No. No. No.
Yep. Just like Timmy.
I can't believe Timmy Yeah. tries to act
like the hard man when he's a [ __ ]
He's a [ __ ] proper [ __ ] and he
tries to act like a like a hard man
calling people out all the time.
How is that How does that make sense?
How does that actually make any sense, bro?
Does that make any sense, too? because
it doesn't make any sense to me. And
he's lost every fight as well.
Every fight he's had, he's lost.
It's weird, isn't it, bro? You got to laugh, man.
Oh, [ __ ] hell, bro. There's some
football in today, but not much.
I don't understand how a a fat [ __ ]
can come on YouTube acting hard every day.
Why did you hear Kieran yesterday? He
was talking about Tilly the Dalmatian
thing up Tilly in it.
They need the dalmatation.
Tiny the Dalmatian
is a lovely little dog, isn't it?
Yeah. So basically, yeah. So anyone So
basically, yeah, when Timmy does his
balls and he's just going to come online and just
see you later, lad.
You know, you're not going to you're not
going to make me listen listen. Yeah.
You're not going to make me insecure,
bro. You're not going to make me stop
turning my camera on. You're not going
to make me do anything because, bro,
you've been doing this for years. Sorry,
I'm a bit tired, by the way. Bro, you're
not going to stop me doing anything. My
hair is here. You're not making me
insecure. Like, think about it, right?
Listen, think about it. Yeah. Oh, for
God's sake. Think about like this.
I'm coming on camera. You can't come on
So, what does that say about you? Think
about it. Yeah. You're if you're if
you're coming online saying that people
are this, people are that, people are
this, people that I can come on camera,
you can't come on camera. So, what does
that say about you? That must mean
you're you're already bored.
That's all I need to say, bro.
That's literally all I need to say. I
can do this. I can push my hair back.
I've still got hair. Don't make me
insecure one little bit. All of this
that you're going to spend doing for
another 10 years is not going to work.
You're not going to make me feel
insecure. You're not going to make me
feel as ugly as what you people actually
are. So give it up. Pointless, bro. O [ __ ]
greasy. Poor Indonesian fellow.
Oh, that comment made me laugh.
Good luck with the numbers today. Yeah,
I [ __ ] need it.
Poor poor little Indonesian fellow.
If he can't approach, then Greavvesy.
Bless him if he can't approach. Nope.
Nope. It can't.
He's [ __ ] bro. He's absolutely
Yeah. Self projected, lad. You're not
going to make me feel like you people.
Give it up. Think about it, Greg. How
long have you kn How long have you known
my channel, bro?
How long have you known my channel, bro?
Years. And when have I ever stopped
coming on camera? Never.
When have I ever thought, "Oh, [ __ ] I'm
not going to come on camera." Cuz it's
all self-projecting, lad. All you people
are doing is trying to make me feel ugly
like what you people already are. Sat on
YouTube every day. I'm better looking
than you, bro. That's why you can't come on camera.
Oh [ __ ] my hair is a mess, bro.
You're trying to make me feel like you
and it's not going to work, lad. I'm
still here. Look, show my face. Not one
bit insecure. I'm not long woke up. You know,
you need to give it up, lad. You
seriously seriously need to give it up.
>> So, if I come if I come to if I come to
your door tomorrow, you're going to tell
me to give it up then? Yes or no? Simple question.
>> Yeah. Listen, you're not
>> No, no, no. No, no, no. I am PJ. Oh,
yes, I am. PJ,
>> PJ, when somebody sends me a challenge,
I do it. You're not coming. I will come.
And there's nothing you're going to do
about it. The last thing you do, it'll
be the last thing you do. It will be the
last. No, I will, PJ. I will. And you'll
[ __ ] yourself like you did before.
You will [ __ ] yourself like Taylor. See you tomorrow.
You won't be saying I'll be flexing
tomorrow and I'll build up your town.
See you. You're going to do all
you live with your [ __ ] mom. You live
with your [ __ ] mom. You can't even
bring your dad. You can't afford a gas
bill. You can't
and bring your Look how angry you're
getting. Look how angry you're getting.
>> Bring your dead. bringing up my tech cuz
you know I'm going to [ __ ] humiliate
you tomorrow. I'm going to humiliate you.
>> See you tomorrow, Peter.
>> Yeah, see you tomorrow. See you later.
You're getting kicked now, kid.
You're getting kicked now, kid. See you later, [ __ ] virgin.
Yeah, [ __ ] him, bro. I don't care. Been
going on for too long, you know. This is
with this little [ __ ] It's been going
on for way too long.
Way too long.
Way too long, bro. How long has this guy
been saying that he's going to London,
he's going here, he's How long has this
[ __ ] been saying that, bro?
On a natural realness, like, how long
has he been saying it?
Poké up, please.
Yeah, I'm just going to [ __ ]
I know. It's crazy, isn't it? It goes fast.
This UK silent thinks I'm a troll. I
never troll anyone, bro.
Did you make did I make you laugh
yesterday, Grezy? I'm not going to stop
until I find my mama. That made you
laugh, is it?
Even if it's the last thing I do.
Is that cute, Grezy?
>> That's funny, bro.
Did you like it, bro?
Yeah, I know. He is, bro.
>> Thanks. That's from Burger King, is it?
>> This is dead. Yeah. >> Yeah.
Might want to call an ambulance for it.
So, is your tooth better now?
What What would happen if you had to go dentist?
You would have gone
or you just stayed in agony.
Oh, you're a nasty little fellow. Yeah, mama.
Why do So why do I need a mama anyways?
No, it will always be the same, bro. I
got three numbers. I ain't even bother
texting them yet.
I just can't be asked. I will I will
text them, but I just can't be bothered,
bro, at the minute. Yeah.
Three numbers on a Monday was good. So,
how many would have I got on a Thursday,
do you reckon? Five, six, maybe.
You reckon? Five or six?
Yeah, I got three numbers yesterday,
Cory. I ain't text him yet, lad.
So, how many do you reckon I would have
got on a Friday? On a Thursday. Friday,
Grezy. Maybe six. Is it?
No, it's not happening. It's [ __ ]
Timmy's not going on anyone's door. Cory,
I went out yesterday in search of a I
was in search for a new mama.
I was in search for a new mama. Cory mama
with a H at the end.
Yeah, bro. Some people are scared to
approach. I just do it. I don't care.
Me, bro. Doesn't bother me, bro. Do it sober.
Sober drunk. I don't care.
I done so many yesterday, bro.
This woman tried getting rude in it. I
said if I said have that same attitude
outside let's go outside have that same
attitude and draw dropped bro then they
walk past me to go toilet didn't say nothing [ __ ]
yeah I'm always on an ownage when I go out,
Cory. I'm always on an ownage, aren't I?
Yeah. No, what she was doing was she was
I said, "Oh, like you don't have to like
be rude like your attitude and stuff."
She said, "Oh, I'm not being rude." She
was some lesbian and that. And then I
was like, "Oh, um, you I said and then
she's like, "Oh, I'll be rude if you
want me to." I said, "Oh, will you now?"
"Yeah, will you? Will you be rude? Let's
go outside. Let's go outside." I said,
"Fuck off then." Simple as that. You stupid [ __ ]
Yeah. I said I said I told her to [ __ ] off.
Yeah. [ __ ] stupid [ __ ] If you're
going to have energy, come outside when
there's no one around and see how brave
you really are
with your mouth. That's what you need to
say to someone. That's all you got to
say to someone that's doing that. Don't
argue with anyone in a bar. Don't just
just tell them to have that same energy
when people aren't around. Cuz what can
happen when people around [ __ ] gets
broken up? What's the point of that, you know? Yeah, man.
Don't know, lad.
Don't know. He's probably still watching
to be fair.
Timmy ain't going anywhere tomorrow,
lad. He can't even go to the other side
of Birmingham for [ __ ] sake. So, what
makes you think he's going to come to London?
So, what makes you think he's going to
come to London?
So, this is what I say to you, Greavves.
Yeah. Never uh never show your face on
here. Never do anything. Do you know why
you should never show your face? Don't
even talk on this. Do you know why you
shouldn't do it? You shouldn't do it
because obviously I know your I know
your age and stuff because what happens
is right with these people in this
community, i.e. Timmy R. There's other
people. Anyone that's younger and better
looking than these people, they get jealous.
That's why they try to draw you out so
many times like Timmy and stuff because
it's all jealousy with a good few of the
people in this community, bro.
And if you if you showed your face now,
they would that's what would happen.
Exactly. Wouldn't happen. Anyone who's
younger and better looking than these people,
you know, it's the truth though. It is.
I'm not even joking about. It is
honestly the truth. Like Timmy is a jealous bastard.
Timmy, Red Star, they're all absolute
jealous [ __ ] And the fact they tried
to deny it is mad. In 2026, they tried
to deny it. Sat on YouTube 24/7
recording stuff cuz they ain't got no
life of their own. Bro, they're jealous
bastards. And Timmy is as well.
Well, he said he's coming on the door.
Well, he's coming on the door. They said, "Yep,
you got more chance of winning the lottery, mate.
I need to go to the shop, but I'm too
scared to go by myself
to be fair." Yeah, I've got nothing.
Okay, if I've got nothing, show what you
people have got.
Okay, fair enough. If you've got nothing
to be jealous of, show your faces.
Show um show what you have in your life
and then it will make sense, won't it?
Okay, that's nice. Then show us what
you've got then. If you if you've got
Show us everything that you've got.
I need to go shop. Too scared to go by. Yeah,
I'm not scared to go out, bro. But yeah,
that hammer thing kind of was like I was
thinking about it to be fair, bro. But
even when I was in central London,
I'm like looking like not like looking,
but I'm kind of like 10% paranoid if
someone just comes like with a hammer
and knocks me on the ground or
something. Like when I was like in
central London and that it was [ __ ]
bro, it's weird. I just got started
getting like lightheaded and that.
That's why you don't watch stuff like
that, is it?
Oh, I'll come in a bit. One second. disgusting.
>> No, it's not funny, bro. I think I'd
rather get stabbed.
I'd rather someone just stab me, bro, to
be honest, than smash me with a hammer.
I'd rather just get stabbed once and
then I'm dead about to pick in it or get shot.
I'll be just put it this way. I'll be
never riding a bike in a forest Greavesy
ever again. Believe that. I'll never be
riding a bike in a forest
or or like through a pavement down the
forest. Like [ __ ] will I, bro? Nah,
there might be people waiting to murder me.
Oh, this virgin wants to come on.
>> All right, Virgin, you can't afford to
get to London, can you? cuz your skin
>> I can't afford to get to London. >> No.
>> Uh, well, I'm kind of in London, so how
does that make sense?
>> You can't afford an also card.
>> Oh, really? That's nice.
>> So, you can't get to London tomorrow,
can you? Cuz you can't afford it.
>> Well, I'm kind of in London. So, how
does that make sense?
>> You're in London. You're this big bad
man. Then, why don't you meet me in London?
>> Okay, I will meet you in London. Okay,
that's that's actually a lot easier for me. Deal.
>> Oh, so now you're now you're now you're
saying no no no
you need to stop No. I'm not I'm not
doing the big man.
>> You need to stop this big man talking.
>> You will you you shut up and listen for
once in your suit you
virgin. If you want me to come to you
know man you need you need to you need to um
>> Oh my god. It's like talking to a
[ __ ] This is
>> You need to um You don't
>> You're an idiot. You're a [ __ ] bro.
>> Here we go. Here comes the wall. Hello.
>> Going anywhere.
>> You're going to I'm going somewhere. Oh,
yeah. Yeah. Yeah. You're just full of
[ __ ] Harry. Say sorry, lad.
>> Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. I'll say sorry. I want
to say something. Keep saying I'll say
you got You're going to say sorry when I
come to your [ __ ] You're the You're
the You're the miner who You're the one
who talks about miners.
Everyone's called you a nons last night,
mate. Get off here, Harry. You've been
finished a long time ago.
>> I'm talking about You're the one who
talks about him, you [ __ ] wolf.
>> Anyway, no. Wolf, why do you come on
here? Cuz no one pays any attention.
>> No. No. You're the [ __ ] house, mate. I
live on YouTube. I go for a gamble and
all I do is watch banger and I'm playing
trap flower. My life is a tragic state of
>> No, no, no. This is the state of you.
Look at the state of you. live with your
[ __ ] mom all day on bangs on your
[ __ ] iPhone 15 and you criticizing us
as your [ __ ] No, you're fuming, mate. You're fuming.
No, no. You show us your [ __ ] house
and I'll show you some cash before you
demand us cuz we all know you live in
your mom's [ __ ] skin tomorrow.
>> No. How can you call anyone scheme when
you live in your mom's basement? You
can't even pay a [ __ ] gas bill.
You're that [ __ ] [ __ ]
>> A proper mess, lad.
>> Yeah. Yeah. You're the mess, mate. You
can't even [ __ ] you p anyway a bit, bro.