Oh [ __ ] I don't know what happened, bro.
Bro, I deleted I [ __ ] deleted a
Streamyard [ __ ] by accident.
Sorry about that, lad. But you
understand the pattern what I'm saying
on here, Greavvesy.
You understand what I'm saying with the
pattern, bro? If you're in a community,
bro, where people have got a raging
obsession with you, bro, it's time to
leave, lad. You get me?
It's pretty gay, bro. I can't lie. It's
pretty It is pretty gay.
It is pretty gay, bro. I can't lie to
you. It's pretty gay.
same pattern, same [ __ ] in it.
No, but I don't get it.
I don't get it, bro. No. Yeah.
He is jealousy. I mean, look at Timmy,
bro. And then look at me.
You see, he tries to self-reflect that
he he [ __ ] life onto me, bro. You see it
in it? You do see it, though, in it,
bro. You do see it.
You do see it though, in it, bro. You
definitely see it in it. Yeah, bro.
That's it, bro. And yeah,
one second, bro.
Yeah, he's a [ __ ] bro. He's a proper
He's a proper jealous [ __ ]
He's a proper proper jealous [ __ ] bro.
I unsubed from him, bro. I unsubed from him.
[ __ ] off. You're not coming in, LJ. You
can [ __ ] off. weirdo. So many jealous
people in this community, Cory. It's unbelievable, lad.
I've never known it in my whole 28 years, lad.
I've never known it in 28 years of my
life. The amount of jealous people in
one community, bro.
Honest. No. Honest to God, bro. It's
funny. Yeah, it is funny. But it's the
truth, isn't it? Yeah.
All right, Chlory, it's jealousy, lad,
with these people. It's jealousy with
these people, lad. 100% it is.
100% it is, bro. I don't know if you
still follow my channel or not, bro. But
it definitely is.
What these people do on this community,
Yeah. is they try to drag you down to
their level. You understand?
That's what they do, bro. Listen,
Oh, I I how who's told me? Oh, just your
actions give it away. It's so obvious
that you're jealous. The amount of time
and effort you spend on people that you
don't know, that you've never met. You
sit on YouTube from the time you wake up
to the time you go to bed hating. You're
definitely jealous. You're definitely
jealous. The fact that you won't come on
camera and show what you look like and
then when you do eventually get docked,
you always seem to be fat and ugly. Oh,
it's definitely jealousy. Definitely
jealousy. But you keep denying it's not
anyways, whilst you're too scared to
show your face as always. Um, I mean,
let's look at the facts, right? [ __ ]
having a girlfriend. [ __ ] not having a
girlfriend. [ __ ] have [ __ ] having
friends. [ __ ] having no friends. You
people ain't even got a [ __ ]
life. That we know for a fact you people
on here ain't got a life. Yeah. The [ __ ]
you do every day on here. Yeah, it's so
obvious, bro. It's so obvious.
It's a bit of gayness, a bit of
jealousy, a bit of you hate your own
life as well. It's a few things. It's a
You know it is as well, bro. You know it
is. You know it is as well.
Like Timmy for example, Fire Stick, he's jealous.
If you watch that video, bro, you know,
am I anxious? Not at all. Cuz it's not happening.
No, cuz it's not happening.
Yeah, he's definitely definitely
definitely jealous. He's definitely
jealous, lad. He's a jealous little
[ __ ] That he he does the same thing as
Nons does. He does the same thing as
Nons does. They're all jealous. These
people are their lives are over, lad.
Timmy's a virgin. Timmy's a gambling
addict. People can't say that we don't
know what he is. People can't say we
don't know what Timmy is, lad. That's
why he tries to drag me out and draw me
out. Do you understand, bro? He tries to
draw me into his [ __ ] Do you get it?
Cuz it's how he is what he is. Virgin.
Why do you think he always goes for me,
bro? Cuz he's jealous.
Kimmy's definitely jealous, bro. 100%,
He's definitely a jealous little [ __ ]
It's so obvious.
I be in a relationship. Really, bro? Really?
Well, not really because you could still
be in a relationship and still be
jealous of someone, but you people are
not in relationships. So, why are you speaking hypothetically?
Like, bro, you people are just jealous.
End of like, it's Bro, it's you're
jealous. End the story. Yeah. It's it's that that
Yeah, exactly. What are these people jealous of?
You're ask. So if I explain it one time,
are you going to ask me again? So if I
explain it for the last time,
how do I put it down to jealousy? Okay.
Do you want me to explain it to you for
the millionth time? I can I can explain
it again. I can explain it again. Okay. So
let me start with this. Let me start
You're younger than these people. You're
better looking than these people. You
got more family than these people.
You've got more of a life than these
people. You can go out and approach
women unlike these people. Doesn't
matter if they be [ __ ] You can go out
and do it. They spend so much time
stalking you all day every day when they
should be living their their own lives.
It's jealousy. Cuz me, okay, okay, put
like this stick here. Okay, let me let
me let me use this analogy. If I knew
I was better than someone, let's just
say that I knew I was better than
someone, better looking than someone,
had a better life. Let's just say that I
know I'm better than someone, I wouldn't
waste my time on them. I would do the
opposite. So, I So, say for example,
like non legs. Okay, let's just use non
legs. Ugly rat face, no tooth [ __ ]
Right now, you see why I don't make
videos. You see why I don't waste my
time? Cuz I'm better. People that are
better than someone that isn't jealous,
they go about their own business, bro.
They live their own life. They don't
come on here bothering people having
channels dedicated to that person. You
see the point I'm getting at?
You see? You see? You see? And then, and
then I asked them, like I said, I asked
them multiple times to put their cameras
on. They won't do it. And then when they
get docked, they're all ugly as [ __ ] So,
what's that, bro? I mean,
I don't do vids on that virgin. I don't
do videos on that virgin. When was the
last time I done a video on that virgin?
I don't have a channel dedicated to that
virgin. I don't have community post
dedicated to that virgin,
bro. It's obvious. It's obvious. It's
very, very obvious. Look at all of the
people that has bothered me in the past
when they've been doxed. Bomb, hat, gray cat,
and then the ones that even show their
face. Look at the state of these people.
Say no more.
Say no more, lad.
Say no more. SNM, mate.
yesterday. I mentioned him. Okay. So,
have I got a channel dedicated to him?
Have I got community post dedicated to
him? Are you going to go on my channel
and see stuff that I've done dedicated
to him? No. You will not. There's the difference.
That's the difference.
But yeah, bro.
No, no, no, no, no. You're missing the
point and you're trying to twist [ __ ]
again. Never mind, bro. If you can't
understand simple things, then that's on
you, bro. That's on you. No, no, no, no,
no, no, no. You're trying to twist
things again, bro. Yeah.
There's no point with you people. You can't win.
You can't win with you people, bro.
People explain stuff to you and it
doesn't you don't understand it in your
thick head. There's There's no point.
There's no point. I've even got a better
voice than these people. Um, since you
were talking about jealousy. Um, you
know, I've I've I've actually got a
better voice than these people as well.
As ridiculous as that sounds.
I mean, bro, there's a few things, lad.
Yeah. Here we go. Oh my god. Shouldn't
you be in [ __ ] bed, you little
Shouldn't you be in bed, you fat virgin?
Jesus Christ, bro.
You [ __ ] fat [ __ ] Yeah, [ __ ] virgin.
I'm going to title the video tomorrow.
Oh yeah, this is what happens when you
try to show off a YouTube. Get some
sleep, bro. You got somewhere to be
tomorrow, you [ __ ] [ __ ]
Yeah, that's what the video is going to be titled. Yeah.
Do you know he's [ __ ] tomorrow?
Whatever he does tomorrow, he's [ __ ]
You know that? Wherever he comes,
whether he doesn't come, he is
completely [ __ ] Do you know that,
Grezy? He's completely [ __ ]
He's actually completely [ __ ] bro.
Like, unless he beats me or I don't show
up, which is not going to happen. He's
[ __ ] You do realize that?
Yeah, he is [ __ ] You know that, bro?
He is proper [ __ ] You know that?
Yeah, bro. Yeah, that ain't going to happen.
Yeah, that ain't going to happen. But
yeah, no, it is. It is. It definitely
Yeah, I don't give a [ __ ] bro. He
doesn't scare me one little bit.
Like, you're scared of people, Joe. I
don't give a [ __ ] I don't give a [ __ ]
Yeah, I don't give a [ __ ] about this
jealous fat [ __ ] Jealous bastard.
Yeah, he is such a jealous bastard. You
can tell he is as well. This jealous
bastard got missing teeth, ugly as [ __ ]
got a gambling addiction. Why do you
think he's trying to rule me out in
every single one of these videos? The
[ __ ] fat, jealous [ __ ] Yeah, 100%, bro.
Yeah. 100, bro. 100.
But this is what happens when you're
younger and you're better looking than these people.
That's what happens, bro. That's a
That's a point to make from this.
I'll mess with who I want. Thank you,
lad. I'll mess with who I want. This is what happens.
Anyone that's younger, better looking
than these people, have got family
unlike these people, they get jealous.
These are the rejects of society. You
have to understand that. Yeah. These
people are the rejects of society. Yeah, bro.
There's a reason why they go for you,
lad. You're better looking than them.
You're younger than them. There's
Everything happens for a reason, bro.
You got to understand that. Everything
happens for a reason.
You know, that's what people need to remember.
If I'm not better looking, then show
your faces. That's fine, bro. If I'm not Oh, [ __ ]
Yeah, that's fine, bro. I mean, cool. If
If I mean, if I'm not better looking,
come on here and show your faces, bro. I
got all day.
95% of you people in this community
don't show your faces. I wonder why.
Other communities they do. H I wonder
why. I wonder why people don't talk either.
Yep. I wonder why people don't talk either. Yeah.
No. No. Definitely, bro. Definitely.
Yeah. He ain't [ __ ] going anywhere, bro.
Look at this weird. Who the [ __ ] is this
weirdo, bro? So many weirdos on this
community, ain't it? But that's what
happens. Like I said, when you're better
looking than these people, this is what it causes.
Yeah. You give up. I told you, show your
face. Why can't you show your face?
Simple as that. You can't Why don't you
show your face? If you're better
looking, you can show your face, can't you?
Yeah. It's as simple as that.
Oh, jealousy. This is
Jealousy is a horrible drug.
It actually is, bro. Jealousy is
horrible, bro. I can't relate. I've
never been jealous of anyone ever.
It must be. Yeah,
it's jealousy, bro. Oh, I've had more
birds than all of you people had.
whether I could get one now, whether I
couldn't get one now. I've had more I've
had more birds than all of you people.
I've definitely I've had more birds than
all of you people have.
I've had more birds than all of you
people, mate, just on YouTube alone.
Even the ones I didn't show. Definitely
definitely so, lad. Definitely
definitely definitely so.
Definitely definitely definitely
definitely definitely definitely definitely so.
Definitely definitely definitely so. 100%.
Yeah. He ain't coming anywhere, bro. Can
you just stop talking about this stuff
that's not happening, bro?
Yeah, it's as simple as that.
What do you think, Fire Stick? It is
jealousy with these people, is it? 100%.
It 100% is jealousy with these people,
isn't it? 100%, bro. You just tell You
could You just know it is.
You just know it is. It doesn't matter,
bro. I booked to go to America the first
time. It never happened.
Nervous? Nope. Nothing nervous about me, bro.
This is what you people do in this
community. I mean, I had tickets to go
America. I didn't go the first time. I
had tickets to go to Nottingham. I
didn't go. What does that mean?
It's just jealousy on on this community,
bro. 100% it is.
Yeah. See you later, lad.
jealous ass bastards. Yeah.
Why did you message me, bro?
Oh, did you email? Did you message me on
Okay, bro. Whatever.
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Okay, bro.
Oh, yeah. You need a new channel on it. [ __ ]
I'm sorry, bro.
Yeah, I don't give a [ __ ] bro. You
little nerd. I don't give a [ __ ]
Yeah, I don't give a [ __ ] lad. It's not
my fault some jealous little loser wants
to show off on for YouTube. That ain't
on me, bro. He will make himself look a clown anyways.
Jealous little bastard. It's not my
fault, bro. Somebody watch some jealous
[ __ ] on YouTube. Yeah, I'm going to do a
video to Timmy anyways, bro. Yeah.
One sec, bro.
Yeah. Well, no one's asked a [ __ ] to come here.
No one's asked a [ __ ] to come here
and start showing off. You narcissist,
you [ __ ] narcissistic [ __ ] It's your
jealousy and you won't leave people
alone. You're the one You're the one
started mentioning, right? You're the
one that started mentioning people's
names on YouTube. Yeah. You're the one
He's the one starting it. You're saying
that my mom don't need it. He's the one
starting it. And I and I'll tell my mom
that and I'll show her everything.
Yeah. And it's the truth, isn't it? You
started it. Don't stop reversing to psychology now.
Simple, bro. Simple.
Simple. No, I didn't. No, I [ __ ]
Anyways, it doesn't matter anyways, bro. Yeah,
you mentioned me. I told you to stop
mentioning my name. I don't know how many times. Yeah. Simple.
Yeah. If he comes, I'm just going to
break his whole face. It's as simple as that.
I'll break him and I'll break his whole
face. It's as simple as that, bro. Yeah.
No. Well, it doesn't matter because no
one asked him to come. He wanted to try
to show off for YouTube and at the big
man. Yeah. Simple as that.
Simple. Just another jealous loser. Just
just along many, bro. Just a long many
with these jealous losers on this community.
Yeah. Oh, wait. Oh, get a life, bro.
This is your second account. Yeah.
No, I'm not having a fair one, bro.
Yeah, I'm not having a fair one. No way.
Oh, did you get the channel, Steven Howard?
Did you get the channel, lad?
Well, he's caused the grief. Well, he's
caused the grief because of his jealous
ways. He's caused the grief.
He's caused the grief. So, no one else
has caused it but him. Stop trying to
reverse the psychology, lad. Yeah.
Simple as that.
You know what I'm saying, bro?
It's as simple as that, bro. Yeah.
Yeah. No one cares, Joseph. That's not
an excuse. No one cares. Jealous
bastard. Get a life. No one cares. You
jealous bastard. Hey, you want to you
want to talk about sick? All right, bro.
I'm not even going to tell you, bro.
Yeah. Do you know what? I'm not even
going to tell you, bro. You You You
wouldn't even know sick if it if it hit
you around the face. You You think
people saying stuff online is is bad.
You actually think what people say
online is is is bad.
You actually think that's sick? You have
no life experience, do you, bro? And
that's another thing. It's jealousy.
Yeah, bro. There's a lot there's a lot
worse things going on than that, lad.
Yeah, there's a lot worse things going
on than that.
There's a lot worse things going on than that, lad.
Yeah, jealous bastard.
Just like your little boyfriend, Lord. Yeah. Yeah.
I don't have to tell you, bro. You You
You know stuff that's gone. You know
stuff that's happened.
I don't need to list you. You know everything. Yeah.
Yeah. You you know you know yourself.
So when you see stuff like that and then
you think about people that said stuff online. Nah.
Nah, sorry, Dusty. Nah,
>> you know
Yeah, bro. That's it, is it?
Yeah. No one cares what he does, lad. No
one cares what he does.
Yeah. No one cares what this jealous
loser does. Yeah, bro.
Victoria, you don't go to Victoria from Birmingham, lad.
Yeah, you don't go from but you don't
you do not go for um you don't go to
Victoria from Birmingham.
And then, okay, and then what if he
doesn't show up? What are you people
going to say if he doesn't show up? You
don't go from Birmingham to Victoria, you idiot.
So, yeah. Go on, bro. Go on. Yeah, bro.
Yeah, you won't be recording nothing, lad.
If he just doesn't show up to London.
What if he just doesn't show up to London?
You're anxious yourself. Why are you anxious, bro?
Nah, bro. It takes a lot to get me
anxious, bro. It takes a lot to get me anxious.
Takes a lot to get me anxious, bro.
Don't forget, I've seen someone drop
dead in front of me, bro.
Yeah, I win. I win. I win. I win. Yeah.
Until what? The next time he wants to
call someone out
until the ne until the next time he
wants to call someone out and start [ __ ] again.
And then what? Until until the next
time. Cuz this ain't going to be the
last time. No matter what happens, he's
always going to keep doing this. You
people are always going to keep
believing it. Yeah. Am I lying?
Am I lying, bro?
I'll be ghosting tomorrow. Really? Yeah. Okay, bro. Yeah. Okay.
Yeah, man. Okay.
Okay, bro. Dusty, I'm terrified. I'm
scared, bro. I'm [ __ ] myself. Is
that what you want to hear?
>> Yeah. Is that what you want to hear,
bro? You're right, bro. I'm so scared.
Yeah. I'm so scared.
Yeah. Yeah. I'm [ __ ] myself, bro.
I'm so scared, bro. Oh, you got me, bro.
You got me. Yeah.
I'm going to go to bed soon, I think.
No, not at all. No.
You ever gone on uh have you ever gone
on go websites, Joe? You should go on go websites.
Tell me what you think of some of the videos.
Yeah, you should go on um go on some of
them websites, man. Tell me what you think.
No, you should go on it, bro.
Give it a little Give it a little check.
Yeah, big day tomorrow. Yeah, when
Timmy's not even coming to London. Yeah,
I know. It's a big day, bro. Yeah. Yeah, bro.
Yeah, he ain't hurting no one, mate.
He's not hurting [ __ ] no one.
Nah, not really, Joe. I mean, I've seen
someone die in front of me, so why? Not
really. I've seen someone drop dead in
front of me. So, no, not really.
Just other things.
That's unrelated to YouTube. That's
unrelated to that.
I emailed you, bro. I emailed you, lad.
Nah, not even, bro. Mia.
Nah, you couldn't save his life. He's dead, bro.
Should have got it, bro. I sent you it.
Well, everyone else. Oh, shut up, man.
Can't try and blame you for someone else's death.
You're being stupid. You're being pathetic now. Yeah. No. Nah.
[ __ ] it up, bro.
Greasy. They were laughing at you, mocking you.
Yeah, I did send you it, bro. I sent you
a link, lad.
Oh, the phone's dead again, bro.
No, no. Sorry about that, bro. [ __ ] I
think the phone's almost packed up, lad.
You're giving me four to five. And what
are you giving that [ __ ]
Oh [ __ ] man.
One sec, bro. Yeah, bro. Yep.
One second, bro.
So, if he if he doesn't show up, are you
going to take any he says serious in the future?
Are you just going to believe everything he says? Huh?
Well, it is all on I think it is all or
We all know. Look at me and look at him.
Look at Timmy and then look at me, bro.
It's jealousy, lad. It's jealousy.
Nah, it's jealousy with these people,
bro. You don't understand. They're very
bitter, jealous, defeated people in this
community. People like Timmy and that.
It's jealousy, lad. Definitely jealousy
with Timmy, bro. We all know what Timmy
is, bro. It's jealousy. It's all
That's uh that's what it is, Stephen
Howard. It's jealousy, lad.
Think of it, Stephen. Yeah. How many
times does this guy, bro,
come on here try to project his
virginity onto me try and tell me that
I've done my balls in and I'm skinn. No.
No. No. No. No. Bro, do you ever see
this guy go for launch legs? No. Why do
you think that is? Cuz it's jealousy,
bro. It's jealousy.
It is jealousy.
Do you understand? Why do you think they
they give certain people passes to get
it on here, bro? Even when they know
their launches, it's jealousy, bro. It's
100% jealousy with these people, lad.
So that's to answer your question, Stephen. Lad,
I usually live. Can I get Nope.
Nope, lad. Nope.
Bro, I'm trying to live my life, but
this jealous [ __ ] keeps trying to draw
me out, bro. I'm trying to live my life,
but this jealous fat Iva Mong keeps
drawing me out, lad. So, this is why why
we where we This is, bro. Hey, Bob. I
made a new channel, bro. I made a new channel, lad.
I've gave it to Greasy and Steven Howard
so far. I need to get some more people
on here, lad.
You get me, bro. It's all jealousy, bro.
With Timmy, bro. Trust me, 100% it is.
You got to understand, bro. This guy had
to go to rehab for gambling, bro. He's
ugly as [ __ ] He's failed, bro. It's too
late for him.
You understand? It's too late. So he
projects it onto me something that's
better than him. Do you understand?
That's all they do on this community,
bro. That's all they do on this
community. Project their failures.
That's all they do on there, lad. It's a
big thing on here.
You get me, bro? It's jealousy on this
community, Bob. Like, we're trying to
live our life, bro. Like, we're trying
to hit up [ __ ] and we got this [ __ ]
talking about us.
You get it, bro? Uh,
so it's just uh self projecting, lad.
Even though my life's not perfect, but
obviously my life ain't perfect. My
life's far from perfect, bro. Do you get it?
Yeah. This is what I'm saying, bro. With
these people, they're just
Bro, do you see what I'm saying, lad?
And yeah, Dr. Echo, you're a weirdo.
You're a weirdo, bro. Weirdo. Weirdo comment.
No, you're not. But you're probably
jealous of someone that's younger and
better looking than you that actually
has a [ __ ] life. That's probably what
you're jealous of.
Maybe you're jealous of that. Maybe.
Yeah. You would be jealous of that, but
you're probably jealous of that to be fair. Yeah.
See, I've quit gambling now. You see,
you see with I quit gambling for a year.
Uh last year I quit gambling for a whole year. Um, yeah.
This is why, like I told you, Bob, this
is why I made a new channel, bro.
To get away from these jealous people.
Yeah. Know what I'm saying, bro?
Yeah, I quit gambling for a year, lad.
Yeah, I Well, it does make sense. I've
already explained it and I'm not
explaining it again. I've already
explained it. I've already explained it
and I'm not explaining it again. So, if
you didn't listen the first time, the
second time, the third time, the fourth
time, the hundth time, bro, that's on
you. I'm not explaining it again. If
your mind can't comprehend when someone
explains something to you, then that's
on you, bro. I'm not explaining it again.
You know, I'm not explaining it again.
So, that's it. Yeah.
Yeah. Okay. I'm not explaining it again.
Nope. I've already explained it, lad.
I've already explained it. I've already
I've already explained it. I'm not
explaining it again. If you don't
understand the first time, second time,
third time, 100 time, that's on you,
bro. I'm not explaining it again.
So, that's it.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no. I'm not
explaining it again. I've already
explained it. I'm not explaining it again, lad.
Uh, sorry. I'm on I shouldn't even tell
you what I'm to be honest. No, I'm not nervous.
Yeah, my looks are average at best. Why
don't you show us your looks, Joe? Why
don't you show us your looks?
Average at best. Fair enough. Let's see your looks.
Let's see. Let's see what you look like.
That's nice, bro. I take average. That's
cool, lad. Yeah,
that's nice, bro. That's good. Average
at best. Yeah, that's good, bro. Nothing
wrong with being average looking. Yeah,
man. Let's see what you look like. Let's
see your face.
Yeah, let's see what you look like, lad.
And you know that's self projecting. I'm
average at best, bro. That's how you
know you're self projecting, mate. You
got to be jealous of something. And only
you would know what that is.
I've already been I've already been on
many dates. I've had more women than
most of the people in this community.
I've already backed it up. I've backed
up multiple multiple multiple times.
Okay, put it this way. I've had more
women in 5 years than you would ever
have in your life.
Think about like that. Whether I ever I
could never ever have a woman again in
my life and I would have still had more
women than you.
And that's the truth. And that is not
even chat and [ __ ] I've already backed
it up with dates, kisses, one night
stands. I've already been backed it up.
I've been backed it up many times. Why?
Why do you want people to do it again? You're biased.
Just like when you want people to show
you money again for you to pretend that
you didn't see it, bro. [ __ ] off, man.
[ __ ] off, bro. [ __ ] off. [ __ ] off. You talk [ __ ]
Well, considering I've been with more
women than you have, that suggests that
I'm probably better looking than you, right? Yeah.
Yeah, Timmy again who should be asleep.
Yeah, Timmy again. Who should be asleep?
Yeah, just self projecting.
Definitely just self projecting on this community, bro.
It's just self projecting for middle age weirdos.
That's all it is on here, bro. Yeah, bro.
One second. There's the link, bro. Yep.
O. Did you get the channel yet, lad?
Did you get the channel?
We need to start doing content, bro. We
need to start [ __ ] um
we need to start um
yeah, living our lives, bro, a bit more like yesterday.
And we can't do it with these dregs keep
trying to bring us down to their level.
Do you understand, lad?
Steven Howard Grezy, which is why we
made a new channel, bro. We don't need
to see their negative [ __ ] We don't
need to see their hate. We don't need to
see their self projecting. Do you get me, bro?
You get me, bro? Yeah. Don't know where
Triple H is. I don't know where the [ __ ]
that [ __ ] is. I don't know where the
[ __ ] that [ __ ] is.
But there's so much stuff going on in
the world, bro. There's so many more
other things to stress about. Do you
know what I'm saying? These people are
just spastics, bro.
I'm doing this tomorrow, bro, and that's
it. I'm done.
But no doubt in my mind I'm going to get
other people trying to stalk me even
after tomorrow cuz they've got a raging
obsession with me, lad.
Raging. A raging one.
Raging one, bro.
Yeah, but it's still going to go around
in circles anyways. All right, Gregy,
should we do this? Yeah, listen to this,
bro. Yeah, we should come back in like 6 months.
We should You know what we should do?
Yeah, we should come back in We should
[ __ ] off. Yeah. And come back for six in
six months. Yeah. For a day, bro. A day
or two days. Just go back on the
community for after 6 months. Yeah. And
see if it's the same [ __ ] See if it's
the same argument. See if it's the same
people trying to act hard.
Yeah, bro. They probably try stalking me
on Reddit or something, bro.
These people give me the eB.
Oh, so you're saying that you're going
to you're going to tune into Kitties and
Girts. You can if you like, but I won't be there.
Simple as that. So go, will you?
You can if you like, but I won't be there. Yeah, bro. Who's there?
They don't have channels dedicated to
them. It's completely different. No, no,
no. It's completely completely different.
No, it's completely completely completely different.
The way they get trolled is completely
completely completely different. They don't
They don't They don't. They don't. They
They don't, bro.
There's channels that are specifically
dedicated to me, bro. He does.
He does. He's a lovely fellow. Al
Greavves is a lovely fellow.
I just messaged you, Stephen Howard.
Oh, I gave you content last night,
Steven Howard. You can't.
Yeah, I gave you content last night, bro.
Nope. Not at all. Not in the slightest.
And they're not go to either.
This Christian Izzy thing just pissed me off, bro. Yeah.
She's just a [ __ ] bro.
Nah, bro. I'm good, man. Mama.
No, they didn't find her.
No one knows who she is, lad.
Yeah, they're coming through now, lad. Yeah.
Where is that?
There's a donut, bro. To be fair. Yeah.
Why you want this? Do you want another
channel? Yeah, bro.
Yeah, I sent it, bro.
Yeah, I sent it, lad.
Oh, is that the real How hard can it be? Nah.
Nah, that's not the real you, man.
So you still you still watch my channel? Yeah, man.
Long time, bro. Long time, Simon. Man,
I remember you back from the old house, bro.
I never Bro, I remember you back. I
remember you back from the old house, man.
I think you did. I think you stopped
talking to me because of um the whole um
Sarah thing, bro. I get it, bro. Ain't
>> That's probably why ain't it, man?
>> That was a long time ago. But yeah, I
still see you comment, bro. But um yeah, man.
I don't have a problem with you, bro.
Honestly. And yeah, I remember you
coming the door with a Coke and a
football bet, bro.
Do you remember that, bro? My mom woke
me up. Yeah. She like, "Oh, there's
someone on the door." Yeah,
there's someone on the door, bro.
And [ __ ] You come on the door with a
coke and a football bet.
Oh, bro, that was funny as [ __ ] That
was like back in the old house, isn't it?
>> Yeah, man. That was years ago, bro. That
was years ago.
Yeah, I remember this guy. He's cool,
bro. I know you got a lot of J's and
stuff, but I I personally can't stand
the guy. But, you know, I mean, yeah,
you still living in um you still living
in the same place, bro. You don't have
to say where, but you're still living in
the same place.
See, this is what I'm saying, bro. Why
can't everyone just act like you, bro?
Like, just normal. Just come on here and
act normal. This is what I don't
understand, bro. Like, I've said this
multiple times yet. Why can't people
just come on here and just act normal
like you, bro?
I don't I don't understand it, bro. I
seriously seriously don't understand it.
It's [ __ ] weird, bro.
Nah, bro. You're not the You're right,
You still gamble? I can't even remember
if you said you did gamble or not. It's
been so long, man.
I can't even remember if you said you
did, bro. I can't remember. I literally
can't even remember, bro. It's been so long.
[ __ ] hell, man.
Nice to see you're still um following
the channel, though, bro. That's all right, man.
Uh, same as me to be fair then, bro. I
tried to stay away from it.
I got enough stress in my life, lad. I
don't need that on top of it. You know, Yeah.
I don't know what you mean by that, bro.
Blue corner, red corner. I have no idea
what you're talking about, man.
To be fair, lad.
Yeah, you're a lovely fellow, Simon.
You're a lovely fellow.
You're quite a lovely fellow.
Right. Did you get this email, Steven Howard?
How hard can it be? He's a lovely fellow.
Yeah, I just got enough stress, bro.
In my life, bro. [ __ ] gambling, you know.
I tell you something I ain't seen for a
while. Um, Lyrical. You remember that
account, Lyrical Gez? lyrical
physicists. I see him on like anything
to do with Cai Mark. I see him.
I see him, bro. Yeah, bro.
I I see him on stuff to do with Casside. Mark,
you know who he is, isn't it? Yeah, I
used to speak to him on the phone and that
>> I didn't see it. Second.
Yeah, sorry about that, bro.
It's because you follow Casside Mark. He
hates Seaside Mark, bro.
Yeah, he hates Seaside Mark.
Yeah, he hates him, bro. He's always hating him.
How hard can it be? He's a lovely fellow.
A lovely fellow. Yeah.
What am I thinking of? Greasy.
Greasy is a proper troll lad.
Nah, bro. No,
not even, bro.
Bro, to be fair,
just wanted to go out to be honest with you, bro.
Who drinks on a Monday, bro? Seriously,
who drinks on a Monday, bro? That's mad.
That's some like alcoholic [ __ ] but I
only drink once a month, but [ __ ] a Monday. [ __ ]
probably had down that Guinness as well.
I downed it faster than anyone in it, Grezy. Yeah.
I downed it, bro. Right.
Ghost Timmy, bro. He ain't going anywhere anyways.
He's a [ __ ] [ __ ] bro.
Yeah, that was a Guinness, bro.
I was going to be I was about to be
sickled over the floor. We That's why I
went to the toilet and like tilted my head back.
It's not going to be a fight because
he's not coming.
Yeah, but we're going to just go on the
other channel and live our lives.
Simple as that, bro.
We need to find a new mama. I can't be
[ __ ] involved with this YouTube drama
[ __ ] when I'm trying to find a new mama, Greavvesy.
You know what I mean?
Yeah, I mean, lad.
Yeah, I was about to be sick all over
the [ __ ] floor, bro.
What's easier to down, like a spirit or
um beer? I think a spirit, bro.
Yeah, yeah, yeah. Whatever.
Yeah, yeah, yeah. Whatever, bro.
Cuz I down the Guinness, bro. I down the
Guinness yesterday like in seconds, bro.
Don't even think it was 10 seconds.
I was about to be sick everywhere, bro.
I had to go to a toilet and tilt my head
back in it. Yeah.
All right. Fire stick. These women are
[ __ ] bro. I said yesterday I'm a man
on a mission, bro. I'm going to go out
and I'm going to do whatever it takes to
find my mama.
It wasn't. So yeah,
I'm going to go out and find mine. Mama,
did you email me? Fire stick, bro. D
you know the thing is fire stickier I'm
not even addicted to gambling you know that right
I've got money right now I can gamble
right now got money today I got money
yesterday bro I got money from somewhere
I could gamble today if I wanted to
right now bro
that's That's the difference. You see,
that's the difference between me and
Timmy, bro. You get it? That's the
difference, bro. That's the difference.
You get it?
Cuz I knew if I gambled the other day,
bro, it would have gave me mood swings.
If I gambled yesterday, it would have
gave me really bad mood swings.
You know what? Bet I'm going to try and
do Dusty. I'm going to try and do uh
three both teams to score in the first half.
Then we're in the money, bro.
Then we're on then we're in the money in it.
Then we're in the money, lad. Yeah.
I'll probably still spend 20 pound on
football bets every week to be fair.
Depends on your lineup, in it
to be fair.
You get me fire, bud.
Yeah. There's not going to be a fight, bro.
There's not going to be no fight. Yeah.
You get me?
There's not going to be no fight.
It's as simple as that, bro. There's not
going to be no fight. So, yeah.
The fight. There's not going to be no
fight, lad. It's the same [ __ ] with the people here.
It's the same [ __ ] bro.
Yeah, these people got too much time on
their hands, bro. Honestly,
trying to fight people on YouTube they
don't even know. And then the last time
they done it, they lost the fight. It's
[ __ ] madness, bro. It's mad funny.
All madness, all weirdoess, all
jealousy. It's just [ __ ] weirdos,
bro. Absolute weirdos. Yeah, bro.
Do you remember Timmy? Do you remember
Timmy? Yes. There. I'm going to knock him out.
Do you remember?
I'm going to knock him out. Do you
remember that Grezy?
Nah, that's never going to happen, bro.
I'm going to knock him out.
I'm going to knock him out. I will knock
him out tomorrow, bro. He's not even
He's not even going to be able to even
say that word, bro. To me. Trust me. I'm
bigger than Monty. I'm bigger than
Monty. I'm taller than Monty. Yeah.
Yeah. Yeah. Right. Right. Yeah. Right.
But do you know what I'm saying, Fire
Stick? You see how it's You see how it
is jealousy, isn't it? know is 100%
jealousy with this [ __ ] to try to look
good from YouTube. This is what he does,
bro. When the heat is on him, when the
heat is on him, you see what happens.
It's all jealousy with this [ __ ] bro.
He knows he's [ __ ] He knows even if
he goes to rehab, he knows even if he
goes to rehab.
Yeah, he's [ __ ]
Cuz he's still going to gamble. His life
is [ __ ] bro. Do you not understand?
His life is actually [ __ ] That's why
they go for people like me that's got a
standing chance in life. It's jealousy, lad.
Even as far as like positions. Do you
get me, bro?
All jealousy. All jealousy.
Trust me. The truth comes out in the
end, bro. Trust me.
I'm going to do a video before um
before I go to bed as well, bro. Cuz you
wanted a video, ain't it?
Yeah, that's it, bro.
>> Oh, simple.
>> Yeah. No, he's jealous, bro. That's what
he is. He's a jealous [ __ ]
No one's bringing trouble to a door.
Listen, Fire Stick, who started it? Me
or this [ __ ]
Me or this [ __ ] Who started it, bro? Be
honest. Who started it? Me or this [ __ ]
You get me, bro?
Oh, [ __ ] hell, bro.
You got to understand, bro. I'm I'm
bigger than Monty. I'm taller than Monty as well. Yeah.
This is what these jealous narcissistic
people do. Do you get it?
It's what they do, lad.
So yeah, bro.
I'm dead, bro. That's funny as [ __ ] isn't it? Yeah.
What do you think of this situation? Fire stick,
what do you think of all of this, bro?
Does this guy actually think he's going
to beat me, bro?
Does he actually really think that he's mad, bro?
You ain't filming nothing, bro. cuz I'll
slap the camera out of his [ __ ] hand.
He ain't filming nothing, bro.
>> Yeah, that ain't happening, bro.
What happened with All right. What
happened with Monty and Timmy?
What happened with Monty and Timmy?
Yeah. What happened with Monty and Timmy?
You remember that scene now? That's funny.
Oh, that's funny as [ __ ] bro. That's
Nah, there's not going to be no combat,
bro. We ain't going anywhere.
He ain't going anywhere.
He ain't going anywhere, lad.
But he kind of has to, to be fair.
But saying that, even if he doesn't,
people are just going to dismiss it
anyways. To be end, they were biased on
it. Anyways, lad,
what he's going to do is he's not going
to come and say, "Oh, you said you
weren't going to come." No, no, no. He's
That's what's going to happen, bro.
That's exactly what's going to happen. Yeah.
It's just embarrassing. And he's just an
embarrassment. That's all he is. He's
just an embarrassment, bro.
Yeah, it's just embarrassment, bro.
It's greasy, lad. Do you like the
videos? Do you like the videos, Steven
Howard? You can comment on them if you want.
Oh, no one cares about that virgin. Stop
bringing him up on this channel. No one
cares about that virgin, lad. Dream. Yeah.
Why has Monty man not been live? Yeah.
Do you remember the last fight at the
old house, Dusty? Do you remember the
last Do you remember the last fight at
the old house?
Do you remember the last fight at the
old house? Do you reckon the neighbors
saw it? Dusty.
Dusty, do you reckon the neighbors saw it?
Do you reckon the neighbor saw it? Jeez.
Hey, Dusty. You reckon people's looking?
I didn't see I didn't see anyone looking.
No, but listen. Do you think the ne Do
you think Do you think the neighbor saw it?
No one's looking. No one's looking
forward to this [ __ ] This little jealous [ __ ]
Yeah, man. I need to go in a bit
anyways, bro. I got some stuff to talk
about to talk to. Well,
all right. Instagram. Drew Greaves here. Yeah, bro.
Yeah, I emailed you on Instagram, bro.
Nah, bro. This whole This whole women
thing is stressful, Dusty.
So stressful, bro.
stressful in it, bro. Yeah. Yeah, bro.
[ __ ] He wasn't sweet, bro. She said she
had a boyfriend. She's a [ __ ] lad.
Not sweet at all, bro. Pretending you
got a boyfriend, is it? uh
Nah, she didn't, mate. Nah, she didn't, lad.
I would say three, four out of 10 people
that say that actually do.
Yo, she never, bro. She's an American
living in England. She doesn't have no
boyfriend, bro. It's [ __ ]
They chat [ __ ] lad.
That was an old one as well.
That was old. That That one was Hey,
bro. That one was old as well. You know that.
Yeah, but we need to come off of it.
Seriously, after tomorrow, bro, like
Thursday, we do need to come off of it 100%, bro.
No, we do actually need to come off of
it. Like, seriously, bro, after after tomorrow, bro.
After tomorrow. Yeah, Thursday.
Whatever. Maybe wait around for a little
bit. But we need to get off here, bro.
Cuz they're never going to leave you
alone. These people, bro. They're never
going to leave you alone. none of them,
bro. So, we're best off just starting
like another um yeah community, bro.
We already got three subs, bro. Like, we
already got two of us.
They're never going to stop, bro. Trust
me. And it's going to continuously keep
going round and round in circles.
You get me, bro?
Like when someone's on their balls in
and you know what I'm saying? It's
always going to be the same [ __ ] lad. So,
well then they leave, lad. You had a
takeaway earlier. Yeah.
Timmyy's going to start his [ __ ]
Then you got another one stalking you.
Do you understand what I'm saying, Fick?
And it's never going to end with these
weirdos. So, you're best off just going
on a channel no one can find you. If
they want to still be on here, if they
want to still be on here, lad, then they
can still be on it. I can't control what
they do, but I don't want no part of it.
Yeah, I had an Indian say, "Yeah, I part
of it." Simple.
Yeah, cuz they're never going to stop
these jealous weirdos. Do you know what
I mean? Fire Stick,
you get my point, bro. Like, I don't
know how long you've been on this
community for, but it's been going on
for years with these people.
Like, absolutely years, bro. Years and
years and years and years and years and
years and years. Do you understand, bro?
an amount of money that I've spent
traveling to people, going to and from
arguing like, "Fuck them, bro."
You know what I'm saying? [ __ ] him, bro.
For real. [ __ ] them, lad.
I can't believe this is still going on
in 2026 with these jealous ass people. I
honestly can't, bro.
You know, and you know, I didn't start
anything the other day either. You know,
I didn't start anything the other day.
Everyone saw the video. The video is
still up there. This cunt's trying to
put me in a bad mood cuz he's a loser
and he's lost all his money. Then he's
trying to reverse the psychology and act
the big man and trying to say that I'm
the one that brought trouble.
Narcissist. Typical narcissist.
Yeah. That's what narcissists do, bro.
Do you get me? Yeah, bro.
I kind of want to move house as well to
be fair, bro.
I don't want these people knowing where
I live. That's another thing. I might I
might move house, bro. Maybe in the
future or something, bro. I don't want
these people knowing where I live.
Like, when I say I'm done, I'm done with
these people, bro. Do you get it? Yeah. Um, yeah, bro.
I don't know how they have time for this
[ __ ] Fire stick, lad.
I never shared my address. They found my
They found my address. They, bro, I
don't know how, but they found my address.
That's what I'm saying. They're [ __ ]
stalkers. They're weirdos, lad.
Like, by rights. They shouldn't even
know where I live.
They shouldn't even know where I live, bro.
You know, I've got more important things
to be worrying about in life than
arguing with these little spastics
and these little stalking little
weirdos. Do you get my point, bro? You get it?
You get it, lad? Yeah.
People I don't even [ __ ] know, lad.
You know what I'm saying?
No, I will move out, mate. I will move out.
I don't know how they found me, but they
did found me. That's what they That's
what they do on here. They're little
stalkers. They're little weirdos. That's
what I'm saying, bro. They're stalking little weirdos.
Stalking little weirdos, bro. Yeah.
So, yeah, bro. Yeah,
you don't know why I can and can't
afford. You don't know how much money I
have. Again, stop talking about people
that you don't know.
Stop talking about people that you don't
know, lad. You don't know how much money
people have. You don't know anything. I
could be a millionaire for all you know.
You don't know me, lad. You don't know
how much money I have. Yeah. Simple.
This is where you people get it wrong.
You see, this is what I mean by how you
don't know anyone.
Yeah, I might have told people how much
money I get. But have I told you how
much money I have?
No, I didn't.
And I kind of do want to move to be
honest. I kind of do want to move, lad.
To be to be honest with you. I don't
want these people knowing where I live.
Simple as that.
Like it's as simple as that as well, bro.
See, Monty docks is all of his address.
How How much do I have now? You don't
know how much money I have now.
And that's Terry, by the way. That
juggling account, Dusty. So obvious that
that is definitely Terry.
That I'm smart in it, bro. See,
I should have left this [ __ ] a long time
ago, bro. A long time ago.
The stalking, the weirdowness. I should
have left a long time ago to be fair,
bro. To actually be fair.
To be honest with you, lad. Yeah,
you're definitely Terry. You're
Ah, it's just some weirdo, bro.
You're some weirdo, bro.
And there's so much more stuff in life
you need to be worrying about. You get
what I mean? Fire stick
then on the internet arguing with some
[ __ ] with an IVA
that you don't even know, lad. Do you
get me? Trying to show off for YouTube.
You get me, bro? And this will always go
around in circles with these people, bro.
They'll never leave you alone, bro.
Trust me. until you make a new channel
and you get off of it. Trust, lad. Trust me.
100% they won't, bro. 100% they won't.
They're proper weirdos. They've got a
raging obsessing boner over me, bro. I
don't know how many times I tried to get
away from these people.
You get me?
[ __ ] knows how many times, bro. I can't
even tell you how many times.
Why do you think I traveled so much? um
feist it because of these people.
Because of these people, bro. Why? I I
don't know how long you've been watching
me, bro. If you ever saw the traveling
videos, but it was mainly because of
these people, bro.
I think it's weird. That's it. No.
This dating thing is depressing as well.
It's depressing, bro. Yep.
Yeah. But Terry kind of stopped his
[ __ ] He doesn't do what Timmy does. You understand, bro?
Do you know what I mean, bro? So, yeah,
so basically everything Timmy was saying
in in his video, everything Timmy was
saying in his video applies to him.
Applies to him, bro.
It applies to him. Everything applies to See
skin virgin. You get me, lad. You got to
play the bank. Baby.
Oh, some one night stand I had in
Manchester blocked me. Um, fire stick.
I found her number. I started messaging
her and it Yeah, bro. Mhm.
Yeah. Yeah. Whatever to me. Yeah. Yeah.
Yeah. Yeah, you're boring, lad. Wasn't
you going to sleep a couple of hours ago?
You [ __ ] little [ __ ] house.
I got you out fresh, mate.
I could beat you with one hand, lad.
You're the one that needs to go sleep,
mate. Not me. You jealous little bastard.
Everyone's going to laugh at you now
anyways. So, that's a good that's a good thing, bro.
That's a good thing.
Yeah. [ __ ] jealous little [ __ ]
Let's go over the facts. You're skinn.
You've got an IVA. You're ugly as [ __ ]
You're a virgin. These are all things
that you are. You know that,
brother. I don't give a [ __ ] if he's not
playing about a lot. I don't give a [ __ ]
He's going to see what happens to him
tomorrow. He's going to see what happens.
I'm going to mash his face up, bro. I'm
going to [ __ ] break his [ __ ] nose.
[ __ ] jealous little [ __ ] If you
think you're coming on people's doors
with another person, watch what happens
to you, bro. Just watch what happens to
you. Is it?
Yeah, bro. Just see what happens to you
tomorrow in it, bro. Make sure you go
live as well, [ __ ] [ __ ]
Little [ __ ] Little [ __ ]
I'm going to make sure you never ever
come back on this website and bother
anyone else ever again, bro. 100%. Yeah,
I will. 100% I will.
Jealous ass [ __ ] Little virgin. Blue noise.
Why do I complain about Why do I uh
Because I didn't dox your family. I told
you to keep my name out your [ __ ]
mouth several times.
I told you to keep my name out of your
mouth several times and you wouldn't do
it. And to be honest, I didn't even I Do
you know what the funny thing is? I
didn't even message [ __ ] Auntie Rose.
But I was going to. If you kept If you
kept mentioning my name, I was going to.
I told you. Keep my name out your mouth.
But I didn't anyways. But I don't give a
[ __ ] You said you're coming tomorrow.
So do what you said you're going to do.
Simple. No backing out now, [ __ ]
Simple. No backing out. I told you
several times. Don't mention my name.
Do not mention my [ __ ] name, bro, in
your stupid little self-projecting videos.
[ __ ] off. You're annoying, bro. I said,
"If you keep doing it, I'll message your
I'll message your family." That's what I said. Yeah.
Yeah. Cuz it's annoying. Stop mentioning
my [ __ ] name.
You know what I mean?
Yeah. But you muted the mic.
I didn't even message any of his family
members. That's the funny thing about
it. I told him that if he keeps
mentioning my name, I will. I said, "If
you keep mentioning my name from here on
out, I'm going to do it." I didn't even
do it anyways. I don't But again, I
don't give a [ __ ] if he's just big man.
I'm not trying to get out of anything.
If he's just big man, let him do what he
said he's going to do. Simple. That's
it, bro. I don't give a [ __ ] So, yeah.
Would be the first time, bro. Would it
be the first time? Oh, left.
I'm not backing down. I've told him if
he wants to come, he's more than welcome
to come. How am I backing down?
Backing down from what, bro? I said, if
you're going to do something, come and
do it. How am I backing down?
No, he's backing down, bro. He's the one
saying, "Oh, why are you messaging
family members?" Which he's the one
that's backing down, bro.
But I don't care, bro. Whatever happens
tomorrow, bro, I'm happy. Whether he
comes, whether he doesn't come,
whatever, bro. Whatever the result, I'm
happy, bro. Seriously. So, I can finally
go on to this new channel and leave
these little weirdos where they are.
Simple. So, whatever So, whatever
happens happens, bro.
Yeah, I did message I did message his
auntie Rose. So what? So
So what? I didn't. And I don't care
anyways. But if he comes tomorrow or
not, I don't give a [ __ ]
I really don't give a [ __ ] bro.
You really think I'm thinking about tomorrow, bro?
You really think that's on my mind?
You really actually You actually really
think that's on my mind, bro? No.
There's a million on different There's a
million and one different things on my
mind, bro. And that's not it.
Trust Trust me on that one, bro. Trust
me on that one.
Yeah. Well, then he can come then. Let him come.
Yeah. Let him come then.
Let him come what he wants.
I didn't I was going to message her, but
I didn't to be fair.
He's let you down a million times before.
He's let you down He's let you down a
million times before.
Yeah, bro. I'm proper scared. Yeah, I'm
The only thing I'm scared about, mate,
is the future.
Not losing to a [ __ ] in a fight, mate.
Yeah, big difference.
And it ain't nothing to do with tomorrow
any other day, lads. you know.
Okay, bro. Whatever.
Yeah. Okay, bro. Yeah. Yeah. I'm scared.
I'm terrified. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. I'm nervous.
We go to bed soon.
All right, Dusty. Do you reckon Monty
will be watching?
Do you think Monty will be watching?
Nah, Monty's off is he
UK side. Do you think Monty will be
watching or do you think he's off here? H.
Well, you think he'll be watching? Yeah.
kind of miss [ __ ] talking to
Christian is he bro
it was special then but it's over now
it was spe Oh UK son
hey listen bro it was special day but
it's over now
bro that's bango that's a banger about seriously. Yeah,
it was special day. Let's open now.
It's true though, is it, Dad?
It's true though, isn't it?
Hey, you know the thing is bro that if
this guy makes it bro if this guy
doesn't come tomorrow he's going to make
you lot look so stupid in it. Yeah.
You think it was [ __ ] lovey?
You can't love someone you just met,
bro. You know what I mean?
Nah, you can't love someone you just met, bro. You know
But Grezy was special then. But it's over now. Grezy.
To be fair, I get attacked quite easily.
Grievy. To be fair.
Don't know about you, bro, but I get
attacked quite easy,
which is not a good thing, but yeah.
These people are going to look so stupid
if he doesn't come tomorrow. in it. [ __ ] man.
[ __ ] up, bro. Yeah.
What are them army lads doing? Greasy.
Open the door. I got cash. What's What
business is that of yours? If I've got cash.
Yeah. [ __ ] hell, bro. Imagine
that though. Is it Greasy? Someone says
they're going to come smash your house
up. Yeah. And you're not worried about
that. You're more worried about if
you're going to get a reply back. That's
how you know you're in Solid 2D. Is it Greasy? Yeah.
So, what are you saying, Grezy? Like,
this is going to be the same thing that
Are you going to say this? Are you
saying that this is the same website you
can watch Robert the Bear on?
Is this the same site you can watch
Rbert the Bear on? What's happening tomorrow, Grezy?
Are you sure it's the same website?
No, I'm not. I'm not leaving the house,
bro. Unless Unless you're not, cuz I'm not leaving.
I'm not leaving, bro.
What? The bear in the big blue house, isn't it?
What? The the bear in a What? The bear
in the big blue house.
Good friends. Goodbye. Cuz now it's time to go.
Is that the one you're talking about?
Well, if he knocks on the door, I will.
I'm not. Unless he knocks on the door,
I'm not doing anything. Yeah. Simple as
that. Unless he rings the doorbell or he
knocks on the door, I'm not doing nothing. Yeah.
He does know this. Yeah, he does know
this. He does know this. I'm not
flapping it. I've already told you I'm
not wasting my time on jealous ass
people. They're not worth my time or
energy. But if he comes on the door,
then he's getting beat up. Simple as that.
It's as simple as that. It is as simple
as that. He started it. So that's it.
Let me see if I can see it on YouTube. One sec. Yeah.
I grieves the grievy. Grievy, grievy,
grievy. Go on Instagram. Go on Instagram, please.
Don't want it, Greasy. Go on.
Greasy, look at the mouth.
Greasy, look at the mouth, bro.
I will hear it knocking.
All right, Greasy. Hi. Greasy.
I agree. Look at the bear. Look at the
Bro, it's not going to happen. He's not going anywhere.
No. One second, bro. I'm not I don't
even know if my controller works. One sec.
We need to get ready, bro. We need to
get ready with the song, bro.
We need to get ready with the song, bro.
Where's my [ __ ] hunting remote?
Where's the remote? Oh, gosh darn it.
Where's the remote, man?
Oh, is it in here? my passport.
I don't use my passport anymore. I don't
really need it, bro.
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Where's the remote, bro?
Where's the remote, bro? This is what
I'm going to do tomorrow. Going to go [ __ ]
Yeah. I'm going to give you this. Looking
[ __ ] your [ __ ] face. You're going
to tear you [ __ ] Yeah.
[ __ ] your [ __ ] ear off, you can.
Yeah, that's what I'm going to [ __ ]
do. I'm going to be wearing I'm going to
be wearing the Spider-Man top as well.
Yeah. I'm going to be I'm I am going to
be wearing the Spider-Man [ __ ] top as well. Yeah. Look,
Spider-Man na only nons you lad.
He only launches you, lad. Okay, bro.
I love you all.
We love you all.
I know. I love you all.
Where's this [ __ ] remote, bro?
Where's this remote?
I don't know where the remote is, bro.
>> I don't know where this [ __ ] remote is, lad.
>> Bro, I don't want to listen to his
[ __ ] He's boring, bro. I'm going to
do this. I'm going to do that. You're
not doing nothing, man. Shut up.
You're boring, bro. Very boring.
No, I don't think it's in the bed. I
don't know where it is.
Some [ __ ] had it away. Greasy.
>> Yeah, you won £80. That's nice, lad.
I'm going to ask you tomorrow as well.
Why are you such a nonss lover?
I'm going to ask you tomorrow as well
why you're such a [ __ ] nonsense lover.
I want an explanation on [ __ ] video.
>> I don't know where it is, bro.
I don't know where it is, lad.
No, I don't know where it Oh, it's No,
it's downstairs. It is downstairs. Yeah.
Oh, no. It actually is downstairs. Yeah. One sec.
Don't tell me the [ __ ] telly's packed up.
Oh, here we go.
I haven't I haven't used my Xbox for ages. Oh [ __ ]
I just went in the room. Laney bro w bro
w bro w bro w bro w bro w bro w bro w
bro w bro woke up. I thought she thought
I was going to hit her. I think she
thinks I'm going to attack her when
she's sleeping or something.
Nah, bro. Peter belly don't do that. Franklin.
I don't have Franklin anymore. I didn't reby him. Um,
don't do this for months.
Yeah, she's paranoid. I think she thinks
I'm going to attack her in her sleep or something.
That's just sick, bro.
She woke up like straight away.
I'm on my little Xbox. Oh gosh. Right. I
want YouTube up. What?
Oh gosh. No, I want YouTube.
What is wrong with this [ __ ] thing, bro? Oh gosh. God bless. Oh gosh,
he's not coming. So no, she doesn't know
because he's not coming.
You lot are going to get ridiculed so
much tomorrow. You know when this guy
doesn't come yet, you're going to be so
you're going to look so stupid.
You are going to look so stupid. You know that.
So we could not connect to YouTube. Why not? Oh gosh.
What do you mean it can't connect to
YouTube, bro? What the [ __ ]
I want to watch the Oh gosh.
Why can't it connect?
Yeah. Yeah, whatever, lad. You're
boring. See you later.
Get a grip and get alive.
Settings. Are we even connect to the [ __ ] internet?
I want these people to leave me alone. Uh,
will these people ever leave me alone? Steven Howard.
Oh, I need to update the console, I think. Nah,
no, he doesn't.
My console's updating. Grezy.
He's doing it for all the females. What?
Getting knocked out. So, he's doing it
for all the females, yet he's going to
get knocked out and he's still going to
be a virgin.
Simps have never made sense to me.
Dusty, white knights and simps have
never made sense to me. So, you're a
virgin trying to look good for women.
You're going to get yourself hurt and
you're still going to be a virgin.
Can you please tell me what sense that makes?
There was some guy trying to be a s uh
yesterday. I said, "Fuck off, you little
farey little muggy cunt." And he tried
turning back, bro. He turned back and he
walked to me. I said, "Yeah, what? What?
Come on then." "Yeah, come on then." It
was by It was by the casino. Oh, I will
mistreat as many women as I like. Oh, I
will do what I want, whenever I want,
however I want, whenever I want.
Oh, I [ __ ] will. I'll do what I want
when I want, mate.
I'll do it in front of you tomorrow if
you want. [ __ ] s white knight. Jealous [ __ ]
Timmy's definitely jealous, bro.
You're telling me someone like, "Oh, I
[ __ ] will. I'll do it in front of
him. I'll do it in front of him and
smirk whilst I'm doing it." [ __ ] simp
little virgin [ __ ] Jealous bastard. I will.
Yeah. He could be angry all he wants.
The ugly little virgin. Yeah.
I have had a girlfriend. Try again, lad.
I have had a girlfriend. Try again.
And you don't even have a girlfriend
yourself. Stop the self projecting.
Okay, put it this way, Grezy. Yeah. How
long did it take Timmy to meet Monty for a fight?
How long did it take, bro?
Two months. I swear they had the the
same argument for two months. Was it a
month or was it two months? And they
lived in the same place.
And they lived in the same place.
And they lived in the same place, bro.
Do you remember?
You was around, bro. They were arguing
for like two months about the same [ __ ]
I'm going to be here. Oh, we're going to beat there.
Nah, he's not going.
But he kind of has to go because he's
never going to hear the last of it if he
doesn't. So, oh, I think the console's
updated now. Easy.
I don't like the fact LT is always
watching me as well. It's creepy. So,
I'm I'm trying to get away from a lot of
these people. Dusty. Nonstop, Timmy, Log,
LT. I'm trying to get away from all of
these people, bro.
All of these people.
You get me? It's not It's not just one
person. It's several. Several of these
people. Oh, [ __ ] They're spraying in my
face. It's several one of them, bro.
They're like a pack of wolves.
Like, one comes, then the other comes,
and the other comes, and the other
comes. They're like a pack of wolves.
I'm going to tell you one thing though.
Yeah, Grezy. On Thursday, when we go on
this channel, Thursday, Friday, bro, do
not tell me
about any of these people mentioning me.
I don't want to hear none of it. Yeah.
You understand me? I don't care what
they're saying, how they I don't care,
bro. Yeah. So, make sure you don't tell
me, please. I don't want to hear none of
it. No emails. I don't want to hear none of it.
No, seriously, I don't want to hear
anything any of it. Yeah.
I told you I'm going to start going back
out again in March. I don't want to hear
I don't want these people dragging me
down, bro. You get it?
You get me, bro? Yeah.
I'm not verifying my age, you silly goose.
I just want to go on YouTube. Oh, no. I
don't want any of your stuff. Leave me
alone. I just want to go on YouTube.
Right. Let's try again. Oh, yay.
Don't know. Don't care.
Dude, my opinion, Dusty,
they're all [ __ ] And why do you always
come back up, bro? Listen. Yeah, Dusty.
All the times I traveled. Yeah, being
real with me. Yeah, be real with me. All
the times I used to travel to meet
people, I was always by myself. Wasn't I
always by myself?
Wasn't I always by myself?
Was I always by myself, bro? I was
always by myself. Middlesbrough, Manchester,
I was I always went everywhere by myself, bro.
Timmy always comes with backup. He's a
[ __ ] bro. He's a [ __ ]
He is a natural [ __ ] bro. He always
comes with backup. I've never come with
backup. No backup, ever.
When I used to go up and down the
country. Oh, [ __ ] This is on now, bro.
Listen to this. Yeah.
You have time to sing a goodbye song.
Hey, this was really fun. We hoped you
like it, too.
Seems like we've just begun, but
suddenly we're through. Goodbye.
Good friends. Goodbye.
Cuz now it's time to go.
But hey, I say, well, that's okay cuz
you'll see you very soon. I know.
Very soon. I know.
Goodbye. Goodbye. Good friends. Goodbye.
The moon, the
big new house.
I might play Three Guys, One Hammer on the TV.
Nah, I wouldn't want to traumatize you poor [ __ ]
Nah, bro. I wouldn't want to I wouldn't
want to traumatize you poor [ __ ]
This can't be the same website.
A can't be the same website.
It is. It is. It is. It is the same website. Look
what Timmy has been saying. So [ __ ] Timmy.
I see Timmy. He's not surrounded. I do
miss a beat on his head in the conversation already
to let you all know Tim is only support
at this point.
>> See this has been going on for years.
Hasn't it? It's been going on. It's
actually been going on for years, isn't it? Yeah.
was not a game, Peter. I'm up 80 quid
tonight, just to let you know. Sleep.
>> No, bro. I don't need I don't need to
sleep. I'll go bed when I'm [ __ ] ready, mate.
>> Well, I want to play Franklin now, but I
can't play Franklin because I don't have
the game. We
If your If your subscription is currently twitting,
right, I want to I want to play G. I
want to play some Franklin,
right? Let me have a little look.
How much is it now? GTA 5. I need to
actually buy the game. But I ain't
played this for ages. Months. This Xbox. Oh.
Oh, I can't afford that. That's ridiculous.
$34.99. Is that how much it is?
I can't afford that, lad.
I can't afford that, bro. I'm broke. Sorry, man.
Yeah, I can't afford that, mate. I'm Skint, lad.
I've got Black Ops 2. I got Black Ops 2,
by the way.
I can't play online cuz I don't have the subscription.
No, I got Black Ops 2, lad.
Oh gosh. Wait, why are you saying that?
No, it's a 50 in.
It's a 50 in. Look.
Hey, it's a Samsung.
Can you play like campaign mode on this
[ __ ] No. No. Cuz it's a multiplayer, isn't it?
Yeah. I'm skin, bro. Can someone lend me
£35? I'm skin.
Yeah. This is a This is a 15 Samsung.
You said it's big enough, isn't it, Grezy?
>> Sorry to disappoint you, M. No damage
been done. Your city post has failed,
Mass. And I will be coming, Pet.
No, Peter, I'm being serious. I hope
you've warned Een. I hope you have
warned Eene, Peter.
>> No, no, Peter. here because I'll be
telling mommy all your internet actions
and she'll have she'll have a video out
and you'll have to stand on your own two
I know I've been watching in the
background and gambling all night
you know playing
barrels I'm up I lent my friend some
money I bought and you know what you
think this is a game it's not going to pay
ticket which is nonrefundable.
>> No one cares. Peter, you need to learn
your lesson. You watch me out the
window. That's fine. Get the police cuz
they need to know your actions.
>> Good night, Peter.
>> No one cares. Yeah, you're not going
anywhere. Shut up.
>> So, anyways, Greasy,
>> you think that's a Do you reckon that's
a good size TV?
Do you think this is a good size TV, bro?
You know, if he actually comes by
himself, I respect him, bro. If he
actually come If he actually comes by
himself, I rate it, bro. I rate it. But
he will never come anywhere by himself.
He's a [ __ ]
>> He's a [ __ ] >> PJ
four points, PJ. Four beers. That's all.
>> You can play what you want. Yesterday,
>> you can play what you want. I fear your
ass tomorrow, Peter. Game over.
I can't wait to own the living daylight.
Good night, Peter. I'm not going to do
nothing. Good night, Peter. You're not
going to do nothing. Shut up. There you
go, bro. Can you see properly? You're
not going to do nothing. Shut up.
You're not going to do nothing.
Yeah, exactly, bro. Yeah,
my mom knows about the people in this
community. These jealous ass people.
These jealous ass people. My mom knows
all about it. My mom watches everything,
bro. To be fair.
Yeah, he can be serious all he wants. I
don't give a [ __ ]
But will he turn up by himself? That's the question.
Nah, I'm good, bro. I don't need to I
don't need to enhance my rage for a [ __ ] [ __ ]
I don't need to enhance my uh range for a [ __ ]
All right. So, what do you think of the telegrams here?
I'll go to sleep when I'm ready, bro.
No, I'm good, bro. I'm not gambling. I'm
all right, bro. I'm good. Thank you, though. Yeah.
Yeah, bro. But here's the thing, Grezy.
Let's see if he Let's see if he comes by himself. Yeah, man.
I feel sorry for him, bro. I actually do
feel sorry for this guy, lad.
I feel I do actually feel sorry for him,
bro. I do feel sorry for him.
Yeah, I actually I actually feel sorry
for him, bro, to be fair. Like, he
actually thinks he's scaring people, but
you just you just pity him, bro. You
just pity him.
That's all you do is pity him.
Bless him, bro. He's so desperate to
lose his virginity. He has to try to
look good for YouTube. Bless him, bro.
You do have to laugh at these people.
Yeah, it's not going to happen, bro.
He won't be able to even kick me, bro.
I'm big, bro. I'm a big bastard, so it's
not going to happen. Yeah.
Oh, [ __ ] I should have told Kieran
about the other channel. [ __ ] Yeah.
You're going to tell I about my um
about my my internet activity. Is that
what he said? This guy's a he's a
weirdo, bro. Like, you actually have to
feel sorry for him. He actually thinks
he's scaring people.
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. [ __ ] [ __ ]
[ __ ] [ __ ] bro. Nope. Taller than that. Yeah.
How do we get on that now, bro? [ __ ]
[ __ ] in it.
Yeah, you know, bro. Yeah.
Imagine that. Trying to look good for
people on YouTube by trying to come on
someone's door. Imagine that, bro.
That's funny, bro. Is it? That is funny,
bro. It's funny as [ __ ] it. You know
what it is? It's where everyone hates
them. You see
where everybody hates this guy. Yeah.
Where everybody hates him, he uses my
name. Do you understand? He's been doing
it for years and years and years and
years. It's the same thing where people
use try to use people for clout.
It's the same where people try to use
people for clout. You get it? You see?
You get what I'm trying to say, bro?
You'll know tomorrow anyways. L.
You will know tomorrow.
that I can finally leave this jealous place forever.
Yeah, I can. Sorry. I can leave this
jealous place forever. That's if
Greavves doesn't start um doxing my
[ __ ] new channel.
Oh, [ __ ] bro. Never.
Um, never, lad.
You people are going to look so stupid
tomorrow when this come don't come. You
know that you're going to look so stupid.
Yeah, bro. Why can't Timmy come by
himself, Fruit King?
Why can't Timmy come by himself? Huh?
Why don't the dude turn up anywhere by
himself, bro? This is what I don't understand. Yeah.
Is this ever going to end on this community, Greavvesy?
Is it ever going to end all of this?
He's actually trying He's actually going
to try and come on someone's door to
look good for YouTube and he's just
going to get embarrassed
and all he's going to do is get
embarrassed. Do you know I'm going to be
up tomorrow? You do realize that?
He You do realize I'm going to be up tomorrow, bro.
Yeah, you do realize that. Yeah. Uh,
not at all, bro.
Just one of Peter Belly's punches will
be enough, lad.
Yeah. And I'll wrong some more women.
And I'll wrong some more [ __ ] women
as well in front of him. What? What? Who
are you? Who are you to try and tell me
who I can wrong? But I'm going to really
hurt this guy tomorrow, bro. I'm
seriously going to hurt this guy
tomorrow, bro. I'm not even joking. I'm
seriously seriously seriously going to
hurt this guy, bro.
Yeah, I'm going to hurt this guy badly, bro. Seriously. Really bad. Yeah.
Trust me, bro. He would that will teach
him to try to show off and look the big
man for YouTube.
Yeah, that would that will teach him to
try to show off and look the big man for
YouTube. Isn't that right, Mr. Bean? Yeah,
he is going to turn up with him.
He is going to turn up with him, bro.
He's not He's not turning up by himself.
If he turns up by himself, I'll rate it,
bro. I'll rate it. But it's he's not
ever he's not turning up anywhere by himself.
He's not turning up anywhere by himself.
I'm going to give him one big bang in
his face for mentioning my name. Another
bang for licking launch legs his ass.
I'll be ready for him tomorrow, bro.
Trust me, I'll be ready for that comp tomorrow.
Trust me, I don't care, bro. I'll be
ready for that comp.
Yeah. And you know what he's going to
do, Mr. B? Do you know what he's going
to tr do? He's going to say to Laney,
"Oh, I pulled it on myself when he's the
one that started it." Then he's going to
he's going to start backtracking. He's
going to start backtracking, bro. That's
what he's going to start doing. You know
it, bro. Ain't it? You know it. Oh, you
know, lad. You know,
you know exactly what's going to happen.
Is it, bro? You know exactly what's
going to happen. They're going to
reverse the psychology because that's
what these little jealous people do in
this community. Do you get me?
You knowing it, bro. You know. Yeah.
I'll run a woman tomorrow in front of
you if you like and I'll smile at you
whilst I'm doing it. [ __ ] little
white knight [ __ ]
Yeah, bro. Let's hope this all Let's
hope all this all talk this all of this
talking is not for nothing.
Yeah. Let's hope it's not all for nothing, bro.
Yeah. He's going to try and reverse the
psychology. That's what he's going to do, lad.
That's what most of the narcissist do on here, bro. Yeah. Yep.
Jealous ass [ __ ] on this community.
Yeah. Come on, bro. Let's get the anger
up. Let's get the anger up. Come on,
Timmy. Let's go, bro. Come on. Let's get
the anger up. Come on.
Come on, bro.
Let's have a talk. Let's have a talk.
>> I don't want to talk to you, mate. You
had your chance.
>> Are you Are you Are you coming tomorrow?
>> You know I'm coming tomorrow, Peter. Don't
>> Who are you coming with? And yes, I'm on
my own, Peter. I don't need to come with
anyone else. Peter, I will own you
myself, Peter. Right.
>> I'm going to use suggestions. Switch off
your live. Get your head down, Peter,
cuz I'm getting my head down in 20
minutes. No, no, no. Get your head down
because you'll see me at 9 on that train
to 10. I'm not playing. I gave you an
empty opportunity and you were scared.
He's keyboard. Now I'm going to
put his family over. No, no, no. You
have got your friends. If you come
anywhere, you are sick, mate. You lose
your reward. You understand me?
>> You're gonna do that. You could do
I'll use a weapon if I have to. I will
use a weapon if I have to, bro. Trust
me. I will use a weapon if I have to.
Trust me. I'm going to knock you the
[ __ ] out, bro. Just with one punch.
Yeah. You're going to try and look the
big man on YouTube. I'll put an end to
it, bro. I'll put an end to it. I will
put an end to it tomorrow, bro. Trust
me. Bring whoever you want. Yeah. Bring
whoever you want. I'm just going to give
you one bang and then another bang for
being a notch legs lover. Every little
thing, bro. Bang, bang, bang, bang. I'm
telling you, bro, 100%. Don't tell me I
need to get off here, bro. Just worry
about you coming tomorrow.
Just worry about you coming tomorrow so
I can knock you out for trying to look
the big man on YouTube. I'll show all
the women what happens to simps. I will
show I will actually show you Yeah. what
happens to white knights that try to
look good for women. And I'm going to
put it all over Tik Tok. Hey, this is
what I'm going to do to me as well.
Yeah, I'm going to put it all over Tik
Tok. I'm going to put it all over Tik
Tok. I'm going to bang you in your
mouth, give you a down cut, an uppercut,
slap you around the ear, that's what I'm
going to do. What happens to white
knights that try to look good for women?
Yeah. Take account like take take pay
attention to this. Anyone that goes to
bars and clubs, bars and clubs and bars
and clubs. Yeah. [ __ ] stupid little
[ __ ] [ __ ] bro.
Yeah. Come on, bro. Yeah. Come on. Simple, lad.
Simple, bro. All the times you mentioned
me in your video trying to rage bait me
and [ __ ] I've seen it all, bro. I've
seen everything you've tried doing. You
little range bait. Why don't you go for
nonslegs? You little You little ass
sticker. Tomorrow, when I'm done with
you, why don't you go for nonslegs?
That's a fair question, is it Grezy?
Instead of sucking his dick. Oh, he's
got all this money. He's got a couple of
quid, bro. When I'm done with you
tomorrow or when you don't show up, you
should start going for launch legs, you
should try different people, bro.
Yeah. Say that though. This guy's got a
lot of ass lickers, don't he, bro? Yeah.
He's got a lot of ass lickers, isn't it?
He's got a lot of ass lickers. So, what
I say about women, you're going to try
and come on my door and and show off.
Bro, I'm hitting this guy with a hammer.
I'm hammering this guy's face and trust
me, bro. If he comes, I'm going to
hammer his facing, bro. I can't lie. I
can't lie, bro. I'm going to hammer his
face in, bro. I'm I'm not even joking,
bro. I'm not even joking. I swear to
God, I keep it real, bro. I'm I'm going
to have to hammer the guy's facing, bro.
Seriously. I'm going I'm going to I'm
going to hammer him off for being a
little show off on YouTube. Yeah, I'm
Bro, I might have to do it, bro. I'm not
even lying, bro. I might just have to do
it, bro. I might just have to do it,
bro. I can't lie. Yeah.
Yeah. Just a No, just a little knock,
bro. Just a little knock. Just a little
knock, bro. Like nothing severe. Just
like a little knock, you know? Just like
you know, to get him over, bro. Just
just a little knock, bro. That's all,
you know, just like a little knock. You get me?
He thinks he's going to come on the door
and start showing off for women. This
guy's a mad man. This guy's a mad man,
bro. He's actually He's a mad man. I'm
telling you, he's a mad man.
You know, [ __ ] women. I'll [ __ ]
say, "Well, I want you cheeky little
[ __ ] I'll be wait I'll be waiting for
you all day tomorrow as well. I'll be
waiting for this [ __ ] all day tomorrow
as well." Why is it with him and LT
constantly stalking people, bro? This is
why I'm coming off after tomorrow, bro.
Whatever happens tomorrow happens, bro.
Yeah. What is it with these stalkers,
bro? Seriously, these jealous ass stalkers.
Yeah. Yeah. Will I really? Yeah. Yeah.
He's not locking anywhere.
He's not locking anywhere, bro.
Cuz that's annoying. The audacity. No,
that is annoying, bro. That is annoying,
bro. That is annoying.
That is annoying, bro. You can go back
to Birmingham and cry to your family
that you went on someone's door trying
to look good for women. What a loser,
bro. What a loser. What an absolute
[ __ ] attention-seeking little loser.
You know what? An attention seeking
little loser. Make sure you come. You're
the one who's been about for the last
four hours live. I've been laughing at
you in the background. Peter Peter
chance after chance, Peter. And you were
scared of some little [ __ ] keyboard
[ __ ] warriors. Well, guess what? It's
not going to happen tomorrow. Peter, you
need to learn to live in the real world.
And you need to learn that you can't go
around threatening families and you
can't do this and you will not do what
you want to do because I will make the
police turn up Peter and I'm going to
tell them about what you've been doing
and I'm going to show all the evidence
on the incel.
I think I think you go to a [ __ ]
autistic incel jail.
>> Stop leaving.
Peter, I'm going to make sure you're
never going to mention my name again.
You want to abuse women
as well. Give me a fat virgin. You can
say I've lost every fight. I don't care.
Peter, tomorrow is happening whe
you out. Trust me, bro. I'm not going to
stop until you're knocked out. Trust me,
I'm not going to stop until you're knocked out.
>> Yeah. And if you don't, I'll come back
with a weapon and I'll smack you in the
face with a weapon. [ __ ] it will
come. Talk about how you're going to
come on people's door. I swear to God,
Gregy, on my mom's life, I am I Bro,
I'll be live tomorrow, bro. On my mom's
life on my dead dad. I don't care, bro.
Yeah. This guy's not going to tell me
he's going to come on my door over women.
No way, bro. Trust me. I'm I'm going to
be live tomorrow, bro. Yeah. I haven't
even drunk today. I drunk yesterday,
bro. I'm going to be live, bro. Trust
me. Yeah. Trust me 100%.
Yeah, you're about you're going to do
your deed. I'm going to knock you out,
you [ __ ] IA little nonslegs loving
[ __ ] [ __ ] jealous bastard. And trust
me, the tone's going to get worse
tomorrow, bro. The tone's going to get
worse tomorrow. I don't give a [ __ ]
about No, there is no losing. You're not
going to come on my door or where I live
and try and tell me what's fair. You're
not going to come on my door and show
off and then try and tell me what's
fair. No, no, no. I don't give a [ __ ]
bro. Yeah, I will do what it takes. You
are not going to Yeah. come on my door
and tell me the rules where I live where
it doesn't matter who house it is and
try and tell me what the rules are.
Yeah. Simple. Yeah. You're not going to
come and show up for YouTube on my door
where I live and tell me what the rules
are. Yeah. Simple. There's no rules,
bro. There's no rules. It's as simple as
that. You want to show off on YouTube
for women, you will learn your lesson.
You'll learn your [ __ ] lesson. And
you want to show off for women, you'll
learn your lesson the hard way.
Yeah. And if that if that ain't the
complete opposite to golden, I don't
know what is. You want to come on my
door and show off for women, that will
just get me mad. You know I feel you
know how I feel about white knights.
Yeah. You know how I feel about little
showoffs that can't keep my name out
their [ __ ] mouth. Yeah. Stupid
jealous little [ __ ] And I'll say it to
you tomorrow, you I little virgin. Trust
me, the tone's going to get worse
tomorrow, bro. The tone's going to get
[ __ ] worse tomorrow. Trust me. Yeah. 100%.
100 fucking%, bro.
Yeah. Do you know what I'm saying?
Yeah. Your friend Timmy's going to be
getting knocked out tomorrow.
Trust me. Trust me, bro. [ __ ]
mentioning my name. Bang. Being a launch
legs leather, bang. Mention me on your
video, bang. Don't care, bro. Simply don't care.
want to try and show off for women. Oh,
there's consequences to your actions,
[ __ ] Trust me, I'll do a video before I
go to bed as well, bro. Trust me, bro. I
will. Trust me, I will see what happens
trying to show off for women on my door
tomorrow. See what happens, big man.
Just see what happens. I promise you as
well, I'll be live tomorrow. There's no
running away. There's no dead phones.
There's no nothing. I don't care. Yeah.
Simple as that. Simple as that. You
stupid [ __ ] [ __ ] You should keep my
name out your [ __ ] mouth. And then
guess what? Do you know when Elaine's Do
you know when Elaine Do you know when
Elaine's awake tomorrow? I'm going to
tell her everything. You won't keep my
name out, you [ __ ] and jealous mouth.
Though I've said I've had to message his
family just in case you tried to reverse
the psychology. Yeah. Just in case you
tried to reverse the psychology like you
always do, fatty jealous fat [ __ ] Yeah.
Do you get me, bro? Do you get me? Yeah.
Cuz when ladies are waiting going to
tell her that you couldn't keep my name
out your fat ugly mouth, virgin. Do you get me?
Do you get me, bro? Yeah. Everyone's
going to know everything. It's as simple as that.
Yeah. Simple as that. You're bringing
You are bringing trouble now. You are
bringing trouble now. Yeah. That's it.
You are bringing trouble and you're
trying to show off for women. Don't you
worry about what I've said about people.
Don't you worry what I've not said about
people, bro. Don't you worry. Mind your
own [ __ ] business, you ugly virgin.
What is it? Because I've had women and
you haven't? Is it because I've had
women and you haven't?
What is it? Cuz I've had women and
you're still a virgin. Is that where the
jealousy comes from? You [ __ ] stupid
[ __ ] You know, now are you telling me
that I'm golden people? Now are you
telling people that me that I'm golden people? Yeah. Simple. Yeah, bro.
[ __ ] little [ __ ] Yeah, bro.
about you're going to come on people's
door about what they said about women.
Are you mad, bro? Are you mad?
Please. Oh, please.
Yeah. Oh, [ __ ]
I'm going to explain this to Elaine
tomorrow as well, Grezy. I'm going to
explain this to Ela tomorrow
that this little [ __ ] show off has been
doing this for years, years and years
and years. I've got to knock him out.
Let me knock him out proper, bro. Yeah.
Let me knock him out proper.
Proper. Good and proper. Good and
proper. You want to keep pog of people
being jealous of people? You will see,
bro. You will see. You will [ __ ] see.
He doesn't understand. The guy's a
[ __ ] idiot, bro. He doesn't understand. Yeah.
You know what? It's a pity I don't have
one of them weight bars anymore, bro.
It's a pity. It's a pity I don't have
any of them weight bars anymore.
You know them weight bars, them dumbbell
bars. Whoa. They're the things that you
need, bro. They're the things that you need.
They're the [ __ ] They're the things
that you need, bro. Yeah.
They're the things that you need.
You know them weight bars, the dumbbell
bars. That's what you need, bro.
>> Just smack it on someone's back. Not
their head, cuz you'd probably [ __ ]
kill the poor [ __ ] but like their leg
or their back. That's what you need to
do. Just wound him, bro. Like even even
in the stomach. Yeah.
No, no, no. Dusty, he has started it and
he said that he's going to come on my
door. Stop reversing the psychology.
Stop reversing the psychology. He has
started this and I will finish it. It's
as simple as that. He started on me.
Yeah, he made a video on me. Did he not?
Did he not make a video on me self-projecting
trying to annoy me? Did he or did he
not? The video is still there. Yeah. I'm
about my channel, bro. I do my own
thing. This fat [ __ ] is bothering me.
Probably because he's jealous. Yeah. Has
he Did he not do a video bothering me?
Yes, he did. Yes, he did. Yes, he did.
Yeah. Yes, he did. Bro, it's not It's
not about it being Timmy Eldridge. It's
the cheek of it. It's the cheek of it.
Yeah. Do you understand? It's the cheek
of who does he think he is. It doesn't
matter who it is. Who does he think he
is? It's the cheek of it.
It's the cheek of it. You're cheeky.
You're not going to be cheeky and start
trying to tell me how we're going to play.
You started it. You mentioned my name.
You said that you are going to come to
me cuz I would have called you out. So,
you've started it. So, we'll make that
clear to Elaine as well. We'll make that
clear to Elaine as well tomorrow. Yeah,
we will make we will make it clear to
Elaine tomorrow. Uh who started it?
Yeah, just so like cuz he did start it
and I'll finish it. Yeah, 100%.
He started it, bro. He needs to learn.
He He can't be doing them things, bro.
Thinking that he's going to come on
people's daughter to try to look good
for women and won't leave people alone,
you know? He's a lot like these people.
This Timmy Elders, bro, do you not
understand? He's just a lot like these people. Yeah.
Yeah, he can go live on the train all he
wants. He can go live on the train all
he wants. No one's bothered. Yeah.
He's coming up. Didn't he even Didn't he
come on the door three years ago?
Didn't he come on the door three years ago?
Didn't this guy come on the door three years ago?
And this is what I'm saying. It's all Do
you not understand? It's all It's all
What's the word? It's all self projecting.
It's all self projecting with these
people, Mike. Like, you're going to come
on people's doors. You're going to come
on people's doors. [ __ ] off, bro.
Then he's trying to say that I'm the one
that started it. [ __ ] off.
You know what I mean? Yeah.
Yeah. This is what I mean with these
people in this community, Mike. They
never leave you alone, bro. They're
jealous as [ __ ] They never ever leave
you alone, bro.
I'm off on Thursday. If you want the If
you want the new channel, bro, then
you'll get the new You can get it, bro.
You can email me. I'm sure you got my
email. We're starting our own like
community, bro, after tomorrow. Well,
probably Friday to be fair, bro.
Like just like football bets and stuff.
Like we're trying to start our own
community to get away from these people.
You get like the self-p projecting
little weirdo stalkers
and [ __ ] bro. Like Yeah.
Yeah. You get me, bro. Cuz
this is going to keep happening and
happening and happening and happening
and happening. Do you understand?
This will continuously keep happening
with these people, bro. With the same
pattern another 8, nine years, it will
be the same thing with these people. Do
you get it?
Why do you think, bro? Why do you think
so? Why do you think so many people have left? Yeah.
You know what I'm saying, bro?
I don't know, bro.
Yeah, simple, bro.
all to try to show off for YouTube and
he's going to get battered. Does this
guy never learn? Three, four years
later. Does this guy never learn?
Does this guy never ever ever learn?
Really, bro? Does this guy actually never learn?
No, I don't think he does, bro. Does he? Nope.
Yeah, we'll see, bro. We'll see. He
ain't going nowhere, mate.
You are all going to look so stupid when
he doesn't show up tomorrow, bro. I did.
I won. Well, Timmy ran away.
Well, he actually ran away to be fair, but yeah.
And this is all to show off as well. You
know the thing is Mr. Bean, you know the
funniest thing about this? This is all
to show off on YouTube.
Do you understand? This is all to show
off on YouTube. Imagine the scenes on
that, Mr. B. That No, Tiger didn't win.
Tiger didn't win, bro. And Tiger would
even admit to you that he didn't win.
He didn't win the first, mate. I smashed
him to the floor, bro, when I got up
from the mattress. And I'm not talking
about that anyways. This is the past. He
didn't win. I smashed him on the floor,
bro. And you saw the past the past go in
his bus on his back. Anyways, I'm not
talking about that anyways. We're not
talking about that. So, yeah,
you people can keep living in the past.
Anyways, all you need to know is Timmy
Timmy ran away. That's all you need to
know. Yeah. Well, your eyes Well, you
need to get your eyes tested, mate, cuz
Tiger didn't win. Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Yep. He's an attention seeker. He's
trying to look good for YouTube, bro.
This is all for attention. Trying to be
the big man cuz he's jealous of me. Cuz
he was trying to draw me out. Draw me
out. Let him come tomorrow, bro. Let him
come. Cuz he's going to get hurt. He's
going to get himself really hurt, bro.
Yeah. Yeah. I'm shook. Okay, bro.
Whatever. Yeah. Okay. I'm good. Bro, you
know what's funny is you're you're not
you're he's not even going to come
tomorrow. So, you people are going to
look so stupid. Do you know I'm I I Bro,
if he doesn't come tomorrow, you people
are just going to look stupid.
Do you know what? Yeah. I just saw
Autumn Rose's thing. So I heard PJ
giving it the hard man saying he's going
to do Timmy and Ali saying he's not
meeting him. What an absolute spaz.
Timmy, if you do manage to get him out
of his house. Please give him a slap for
me. Oh, do you know what? I'm going to
tag you in a video where he gets beat up.
Yeah, I'm going to beat I'm going to
beat him up and I'm going to I'm going
to tag you in the video. I'm going to
tag you in a video.
Yeah. And I'll tag you in a video. How
about that one? [ __ ] stupid [ __ ] Yeah.
Trying to look good on YouTube. Hey, Mr.
B, he does this every time he does his
balls in. Yeah.
Every time he does his balls in, he does
this. Every time he does his balls in,
he does this. Am I lying, bro? This guy
was showing 80 pound earlier. Yeah,
he was showing 80 pound earlier, bro.
What the [ __ ] Yeah,
for some reason uh Mr. B, these people
in this community seem to love nonslegs.
Some people, the people on here seem to
love nonslegs, lad. They seem to really
really love nonslegs. I don't know if
you've noticed that. Me and Kieran was
talking about this yesterday, bro.
Me and Kieran was talking about this yesterday, bro.
Have you have you noticed that? Like
maybe maybe two people do it. Yeah,
maybe two people do it. Maybe two people
do it. But have you not Have you noticed that?
Have you noticed that, lad?
That's what I find very strange, bro.
I don't always talk about the [ __ ] I'm
just stating facts.
I'm stating facts. And that's how you
also notice jealousy because you notice
that no one will go for him. Just
probably because they're ugly like him.
Probably because they're ugly like him.
Yeah. Jealous of somebody that's got
less money than me. Has to date disabled
women. Yeah. Okay, bro. Go away. You Ly
Mong, go away you Ly Mong. I can't wait
until tomorrow so I can be done with you
people, bro. I can't wait tomorrow so I
can be done with you people. Seriously.
No, seriously. Seriously, so I can be
done with you jealous people. I can be
out of here, bro. I can't wait. I
literally can't wait to [ __ ] this guy up
tomorrow, bro. I want to get away from
you jealous ass people that won't leave
me alone. I don't know how many times
I've tried, bro, to get away from these people.
You know what I'm saying, bro? I don't
know how many times. The only person I
was subscribed to was Timmy. And the
[ __ ] draws me in again and again and
again. I'm going to give him one big
[ __ ] slap across his [ __ ] face
tomorrow. I swear to God, bro. You know
what? I'm just going to start with a
slap. That's what I'm going to do.
That's what I'm going to do. I swear to
God, bro. I'm just going to give him one
big slap across his face.
That's what I'm going to be doing. Oh,
I'm going live tomorrow. I'm going live
tomorrow. I'm going live. I am going
Yeah. You got someone stalking you on
here that claims they're not on YouTube.
Do you know what I'm saying?
You get me, bro?
Do you know what I'm saying? It's
stalking. It's just weirdness. Do you
not understand, Mr. B? It's weird. It's
weirdness and it's stalking. The amount
of people that I have got obsessed with
me on this community, bro. I tried to
get away from them time and time and
time again, bro. Yeah.
Nah, bro. I'm not doing any of that
stuff. No [ __ ] no, no [ __ ] like him is
coming knocking on someone's door, bro.
Trying to look good for women. It ain't happening.
He's going to know he's not going to try
and look good. He needs to learn a
lesson, bro. Like a proper proper
lesson. He didn't learn his lesson the
first time. And he started on me now.
And I'm going to tell as well. I'm going
to tell Laney everything. So you don't
try and [ __ ] stir. She knows about you
jealous people towards me. She knows all
about you jealous people. So, don't try
and sit there and say, "Now, this little
[ __ ] has been showing off on YouTube
now. I've got all the videos." Don't
even So, you can't try and So, you can't
try and um You can't try to reverse the psychology.
Yeah. So, you can't try and reverse the
psychology. No, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Yeah. No, no, no, no, no. Yeah. It don't
because it's because it's sing and he's
just using it as an excuse.
Because he's sing and he's just using it
as an excuse. He's using it as an excuse
to try to look good for YouTube. That's why.
Because he's doing it to show off for
YouTube. Cuz he doesn't live in a real
world. You see, this guy doesn't live in
a real world. Just like the last time.
He thinks he's going to come banging on
people's door like he did last and and
no one's going to go and no one's going
to do anything. Look at what happened
last time. Bro, I wasn't even living at
that address. Who was even living at
that address? I don't know if anyone did
live at the address. I can't even
remember, bro. No one was living at that
address. I was like, nah, no, no, no,
no. Like, you're not you're not I went
back on the train. Do you remember? Cuz
he's doing it to show off. He's doing it
to show off, bro. That's the reason he's
doing it to show off. And it's not even
just And it's not even just about women.
This guy will not leave me alone. Just
like the other people, bro. He tries to
draw me out. Draw me out. Draw me out.
Draw me out. And he will not leave me
alone. These [ __ ] people, bro.
Yeah. Do you understand what I'm saying?
Do you understand what I'm saying, bro?
Yeah. He's tried draw me out and
projecting the virgin, the projecting
[ __ ] I just want to knock him out.
Like, I do hope he does come tomorrow. I
do. And you know, even watching that
Monty stuff as well. Even watching that
Monty stuff as well was annoying me.
Yeah, it was annoying me, bro.
[ __ ] little trying to show off and
that, bro. Trying to look good for
women. What a loser, bro. Trying to
anger people cuz you've done your balls
in and your life [ __ ] Am I lying, Mr.
B? This is what these jealous people do
on here. Do you not understand?
Do you not understand, bro? Do you not understand?
That's what they do. Where they they try
to make you feel like them. You try to
get away from them, bro. They post so
many videos and you know like even
people not mentioning my name. Even you
know it's not even people mentioning my
name because people mention my name all
the time but it's what he's trying to do.
Virgin what he's trying to [ __ ] do.
Do you get it? Yeah. Do you get it, bro?
Like you you listen to it, man. You
listen to it. You listen to this [ __ ]
Do you get it, bro?
[ __ ] go for [ __ ] nons legs. Go for
[ __ ] rice, you [ __ ] fat, ugly
[ __ ] You get it, bro.
Go for [ __ ] I don't [ __ ] know,
bro. Who Who's on here, bro? You know
what I'm saying? Go for the five great
guys. Don't keep my name out your
[ __ ] mouth. I don't, bro. He's not
much taller than me, bro. Trust me. He's
not much taller than me. Trust me. I'm
going to put him in his place tomorrow
and show he's not going to show off on
this on this community anymore, bro. I
don't care who he brings. And bro, he's
not even much taller than me either. Yeah.
You know what I mean? That is just
annoying me. I can't wait till tomorrow,
bro. I can't wait till tomorrow so I can
give him one in his mouth, bro. I can't
wait. I'm going to smash the rest of his
teeth down his throat. Yeah. Yeah. 100%, bro.
Yeah. I'm acting shook. I'm acting
shook. Okay, bro. Okay, bro. Okay. He's
the one that didn't get in the taxi,
bro. Remember? He's the one that didn't
get in the taxi, right? Am I lying? Am I
lying? When he made me pay 200 pound
when he paid me made me and he did not
get in that taxi, he would not get in
it. But love no money, I ordered a taxi
from there to that address. Who's the
one that didn't get in that taxi, bro?
Despite saying that they were going to
get in that taxi, it weren't me. It
weren't me. Yeah, it was him. So
remember that, bro. Just remember that.
Playing all of them silly little games
in the pub. In, out, in, out, in, in,
out, in, out. Yeah.
You see it, bro? You see it? Yeah. You
Yeah, bro. He could do, bro. He's going
to get himself hurt. It's as simple as
that. He's going to get himself hurt.
It's as simple as that.
You know, trying to show off for YouTube
and try and come on people's mom's law,
bro. What does he think this is?
Simple. What does he think this is, lad?
Trying to show off. He's going to get
battered tomorrow, bro. Cuz I'm I'm
going to be in all day. I'm being in all
day, bro. Bro, we're not talking about
LT. We're talking about him. Yeah. We're
talking about [ __ ] him.
Yeah. Simple as that. We're not talking
about LT. We're talking about him. Yeah.
Oh, bro. But get here's the thing,
though. Here's the thing, Palace. When
has he listen? When has he ever turned
up by himself,
bro? Well, he's the one that said he
would get in it. Pendon, he's the one
that said that he would get in it. Yeah,
he's the one said that he would get in it.
The [ __ ] stupid virgin [ __ ] He's the
one that said he would get in it.
He said he would get in it before I
ordered it two times.
So, at the end of the day, that's that,
bro. He turns up with backup, bro. Yeah.
He has never turned up by himself, ever.
I have. I've always turned up by myself. Yeah.
I've always turned up by myself, bro.
I've always turned up by myself.
Always turn up by myself.
I'm going to [ __ ] knock him out
tomorrow, bro. I'm going to show I'm
going to show him this little show off
on YouTube trying to look good for women
because of his jealousy. I can't wait
tomorrow, bro. Honestly, I can't wait
I can't wait to show this jealous little
s figuring he's going to come on
people's door and then and then he says
and then you you only want fi you only
want fists. It's not going to be just
fists. I'm telling you right now it's
not going to be just fists. It's not
just going to be just fists. Yeah.
You're going to learn to keep my name
out you [ __ ] your mouth. You understand
me fat [ __ ] You understand me fat. So
I'm going to be live tomorrow when I
wake up as well.
Yeah. Because I've got no friends. Oh
that old self projecting chestnut lad.
That old self-p projecting chestnut. I
don't give a [ __ ] if it's cowardly. It's
cowardly. You coming on someone's door
trying to look good for women. You
coming on someone's door trying to look
good for women. You don't call the
shots, bro. Well, sorry. Sorry. Let's
Let's break it down. You're going to
come on someone's mom's door trying to
look good for women. You don't tell me
what's cowardly, bro. You don't tell me
what's cowardly, bro. You don't come on
someone's door thinking you're the man
and tell people how to call the shots.
You get it, bro? That doesn't happen in
any universe. That does not happen in
You do not come on someone's mom's door
trying to show off for women and try and
tell people what they can and can't use.
You've mentioned people. You've round
people up. You won't leave people alone
with your little gay videos. You
understand me, bro? You understand? Do you understand?
Do No, I did not call him too much.
Again, I'm explaining all this stuff to Laney tomorrow
that he will not leave me alone just
like these people. They will not leave
you alone. I've done how many times I've
tried getting away from them. You know,
if it's not one person stalking you,
it's another one stalking you. Yeah. So,
let him come. I'll break his [ __ ]
face and then he will go back to it will
go back to Birmingham and stay away.
Young, better looking people, stay away
from this community. They won't leave
you alone. Trust me, they will not leave
you alone. Anyone that's better looking
than these people, they won't leave you
alone. I should have said this to myself
years ago, bro. I should have left years
ago to get away from these people, bro.
Yeah. Years ago. So, it kind of was my
own fault to be fair. Yeah. No,
seriously, Mr. Be know it. It is though.
No, bro. Bro, but it is. It is. It is
with these people. It is. And you know
it, bro. It is. And you know it's
jealousy. You know deep down. You can't
even disagree with it, bro. Look at
Timmy, bro. He skintked. He's got a
gambling addiction. He went to rehab.
Look at the way he looks, bro. Look at
the way this clown looks. No wonder he
goes for you. No wonder. It's so
obvious, isn't it? Do you know what,
bro? I'm going to do a little video to
this guy, bro. Yeah. I'm going to do a
little video to this guy. Trust me, bro.
Early morning wakings, bro. He thinks
people are running away from him. No
one's running away, bro. No one's
running running away. Trust me. No one's
running anywhere, bro. Yeah. Trust me.
Trust me, bro. Yeah. Trust me.
I mistreat women as much. I'm going to,
you know, the first thing I'm going to
do, I'm just going to spit in his face.
That's the first thing I'm going to do.
Yeah. I don't give a [ __ ] I What about
all of the things that females have done
to me? I'll spit in his face, bro. I
will just spit straight in his face. I
will do what I want to females and I'll
spit in his face tomorrow. How about
that one? I will disrespect a female and
I'll spit in his face and I'll do it
great as well. Watch tomorrow, bro. Just
watch tomorrow. Just [ __ ] watch
tomorrow. I will spit in his face and
I'll spit in it great. Trust me, bro.
You'll see. You'll see. And I'll just
spit all over his face, bro. Trust me.
You You'll see tomorrow, bro. Trust me,
you will see tomorrow. I'm going to be
live tomorrow as well. I'm going to be
live tomorrow. Why does he care about
females? He's a virgin. The guy's a
[ __ ] ugly virgin. He's never been
with a woman.
He's never been with a woman. Time will
tell. Yeah, time will tell, mate. Yeah,
time will [ __ ] tell. Had enough of
this [ __ ] trying to show off for
YouTube. You understand, lad? No. No. It
wasn't women that rejected me. And and
and listen, bro, I've had more women
than you. Yeah.
Yeah, would I not? Well, we'll see
tomorrow, won't we? Come on, big man.
Come and knock on people's door trying
to look good for women. Come on. Come
on. Try to look good for women on
YouTube. Come on, bro. I swear to God,
this guy is going to get hurt, bro. I
swear to God, he's going to get himself
so hurt, bro. I'm telling you right now, lad. Yeah,
bro. He's he he's trying to look good
for women, but he's a virgin. No woman
wants him. Why is he Bro, how are you
going to travel, bro? all that way.
Yeah. For women when they don't even
want you. Imagine that. Imagine that.
Imagine that. They don't like you.
You're a virgin and you're trying to
look good. Seriously, bro. Yeah. You
will see the adrenaline. Yeah. Yeah.
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. You'll see the
adrenaline, bro. And it's going to stay
that way, too. It's going to stay that
way, too. Oh, we won't be getting no
women. They still won't [ __ ] him. That's
the thing with these white knights and these simps. Yeah,
that's the thing with these little white
knights and the simps. They don't like
them. Women don't like them and they
still defend them. You know what I mean?
What about all of the women that led me
on? What about all the women that played
games and you're going to come on my
door? Okay, bro. Okay, bro.
Okay, bro. Yeah.
You don't think I'm serious, do you,
Grezy? You don't think I'm serious, do you?
You don't think I'm serious, bro? Do
you? You actually don't think I'm
serious, do you? You don't think I'm You
think I'm joking, is it, bro? I'm
actually not joking, bro. I'm actually
being serious. Yeah, I'm actually being
serious, bro. So, you seem to forget
about a lot of stuff.
Yeah, you you
Yeah, tomorrow will tell 100%. I'll be
live tomorrow anyways. I'll be live
tomorrow anyways, bro. I'll be live
tomorrow anyways with this little
jealous [ __ ] I'll be live tomorrow.
Yeah, trust me. I'll be live tomorrow, bro. Yeah.
Yeah. Did he? That's nice for him, bro.
So, I'm not allowed to say stuff about
women, but women are allowed to say
stuff to me. Okay, bro. Well, no, it is
the same. But simps like you, Juggin,
white knight and simps like you that are
not normal people will just defend women
for the sake of defending women because
you're white knights. You think women
are angels. So, it is. But you simps are
not normal. So even when you're shown
what women do, you defend them because
you think they're going to sleep with
you. That's what you people do. That's
what you white knights do. Yeah. Yeah.
You you you with you little white
knights, whatever evidence you're
showing what a woman does, you defend
them thinking they're going to sleep
with you. Unfortunately, that's what
most of you people do nowadays. You
defend women to make them sleep, but
they don't like you. And no matter how
many times women hate you, women, you
will still defend them. You're not
normal, bro. And most of you people are
like this as well. You defend women that
do bad things thinking they're going to
[ __ ] you. It's embarrassing, bro. It's
embarrassing. Yes. Okay. Let's ask
Grievy then. Okay. Okay. Grievy. Let's
ask Griezy. What do you think about them
texts that I was showing you? Be it
Christian, is it? Be it all the ones in
the past because Greavvesy always tells
me when I'm wrong. I would say a fair
amount of them are leading people on.
What do you think?
I think a fair amount of them are
leading people on.
Give us your opinion, bro. Rey tells
disagrees with loads of the things.
Let's Let's hear it from someone who's
not a white knight simp. You know,
you're fil you're free to say whatever
you want. No one's going to get banned.
I would say, mate, pretty much that a
lot of these messages are in black and
white that someone's leading someone on,
but to you white knights and you simps,
you're scared of the truth. You will
never admit it.
Yeah, I lack life experience. Okay, bro.
I'm 28 and I've probably had and I'm 28
and I've probably had more life
experience than you. Yeah, it's as
simple as that.
But to these people, they're not greasy.
But to these people, they're not. These
women can't do wrong to these white
knights. You understand?
Oh, that's another excuse, Greavvesy.
Yeah. Oh, this was the excuse that they
were using. Someone needs to know you in
order to lead you on. They need to know
you. One second. Let me Let me quote
that again. They need to know you to
lead you on.
They need to know you to lead you on.
quotation mark. I'm not so sure I agree
with that, but each to their own, I
guess. You know,
yeah, I have had a girlfriend. Try
again, lad. I have had a girlfriend. And
a girlfriend is an individual woman.
We've been over this, Terry, multiple
times. I have had a girlfriend, and I've
had more women than you. And a
girlfriend is an individual woman, not
all women. [ __ ] So, you have no
argument. You have no points. I'm 28 and
I have had a girlfriend. Just like I've
shown I've got more money than you. But
with you biased people, you can't be
shown different. You've been shown
girlfriends. You've been shown money.
You still talk [ __ ] You're a waste of
everyone's time. You're literally a
waste of everyone's time.
A a proper relationship. Okay,
Greavvesy. What do you mean? I'm not
one. All women are the same. Yeah, all
women are the same. Bro, I'm not having
this conversation. You're not changing
my mind. Go away. Simple as that. I'll
ban you in a minute. [ __ ] off, white
night simp. [ __ ] off. [ __ ] your mom. Simple. Yeah.
You're saying that people don't want
relationships. Uh, Grezy, you saw the
messages between me and Christian, is
he? You literally saw the messages.
You saw the messages. Yeah.
You literally saw the messages, bro. You
saw every single bit of the messages.
Yeah, I do. And I'm battling you now.
See you later, [ __ ]
Bro, you literally saw the messages,
bro. The whole Well, we've been speaking
for a month and you're telling me that I
don't want a relationship.
Okay. What's What what what difference
does it make if I want a relationship or
I don't want a relationship? They're
[ __ ] They're not interested. Does does
it matter if I want sex, if I want a
relationship, if I want a friend? Does
Does it matter what I want?
You know, does it really matter what I want?
Does it really matter what I want?
But I'm not messing them about though.
But I'm not messing them about.
But I'm not messing them about because I
wasn't messing Christian Izzy about. She
messed me about.
But I'm not messing them about. She's
messed me about in the me in the messages. Yeah.
She's messed me about in them in the in the messages.
In the messages. Yeah. Yep.
Yeah. But I'm So, but she's messed me about.
Yeah, I know, Grezy. But she's messed me
about. She's played games with me. Does
it really matter what I want?
No, but I'm saying that you're saying
about me not wanting a relationship
because it doesn't make Oh, we're just
going. We're just having the same
conversation over and over again, bro.
But it's okay for them to mess me about.
But that's okay, isn't it? Yeah.
Okay. But wasn't I trying to see how
things went with Christian? Is he
okay? Fair enough. But wasn't I trying
to meet Christian Izzy fairly? So does
it matter what I do? Whatever you do is
wrong. So So what?
Whatever you do is wrong. So why why
does it matter? Huh?
Whatever you do is wrong. So why does it matter?
She messed me around, lad.
She played games with me.
She actually did. So what? That's pissed
It's pissed me off as well, bro. To be
honest, it's actually pissed me off to be honest.
That has actually pissed me off. Yeah.
Yeah. Well, it doesn't matter. It
doesn't matter, lad.
It doesn't matter. It doesn't matter to
be honest. She shouldn't have gave her a
number and keep messaging me.
I said I would meet her as a friend.
You know what I mean? But yeah,
and that's that, bro. Yeah,
about not a good frame frame of mind, lad. Yeah.
Well, you're not going to find the right
one, so why are we speaking hypothetically?
Yeah. If he knocks the door, rings the
doorbell. Hell yeah, bro. Yeah. Yeah.
Yeah. And then I'm bouncing on Thursday,
bro. And then I'm bouncing on Thursday.
Trying to show off for YouTube. What a
loser. He's going to He's going to learn
his lesson tomorrow. He's going to learn
his lesson tomorrow, bro. He's going to
[ __ ] learn his lesson tomorrow. Yeah. Yes. Yes.
Do you know what's going to happen? I'm
going to be waiting, bro, before it even
comes to that. I'll be waiting.
I'll be waiting, bro. You want to try
and look good for people for women on
YouTube. You're going to see what time
it is tomorrow, [ __ ] You're going to
see what time it is. You're going to see
what time it is. You're going to learn
to leave people alone on YouTube as
well, cuz enough people have tried
meeting you. Enough people enough people
have tried meeting you and you don't you
need to learn to leave people alone and
keep people's name out your mouth. I've
seen you do it multiple multiple times
as well. You jealous little [ __ ]
dick. And then don't go crying to Laney
trying to twist stories. Don't even try
it, bro. Don't even try it. You jealous
ass bastard. Yeah, you little jealous
[ __ ] I'll say it to your [ __ ] ugly
face tomorrow. Greavves. I'm deadly
serious, bro. I'm deadly deadly deadly
deadly serious. And he's not going to
reverse the psychology either. He's not
going to try and say people's brought
trouble to the door. Trust me, he's not.
He's not going to try and say that. This
little cunt's been showing off. I've got
his video as well. And I'm going to bash
his face in. I'm going to bash his face
in. It's as simple as that.
But I sound what? I sound what, bro?
Yeah, bro. Trust me, it's going to get
worse tomorrow as well,
bro. I don't give a [ __ ] This bastic is
not coming anywhere near my door, bro.
It's as simple as that. He's not coming
anywhere near my [ __ ] door.
No one did. No one's called him to the
door. No one's called him to the door.
No one's called him to the door. Stop
trying to reverse the psychology.
You mentioned my name. Yeah. You done a
video mentioning my name, [ __ ] You get me? Yeah.
You want to try and show off on YouTube,
I'll smash your face in. It's as simple as that.
Yeah. You don't leave me alone tomorrow
and you come anywhere near this
property, I'm going to batter the [ __ ]
out of you. And I don't care what I have
to use to do it. Believe you me, I don't
care. Believe you me, I just simply do
not care. Simple. So, you're best off
doing yourself a favor, bro. Or you're
going to get yourself seriously hurt.
So, which one is it? Yeah, I ordered him
a cab because he was keep saying that
I'm coming to London. I'm coming to
London. I'm coming to London. So, I
said, "Okay, I'll call you a cab." Cuz
you kept going on about it. Don't try to
reverse the psychology,
right? Don't try to reverse the
psychology, bro. Just Just have a pie
[ __ ] see London cuz you're going to
get yourself seriously hurt. I'm not
going anywhere tomorrow, bro. Trust me. Yeah,
simple, bro. I ain't going anywhere tomorrow, lad.
Trust me. So, there's going to be no
excuses. Just get yourself a pine. Enjoy
yourself, bro. Don't get yourself hurt,
bro. Trust me. Don't get yourself hurt,
Don't get yourself seriously hurt for
trying to show up on YouTube cuz we'll
be we'll be waiting for you all day
tomorrow. And don't try and tell Laney
Don't try and tell Laney that people
have brought trouble in the door. No.
No. No. No. No. No. The thing is, do you
know what? I've said I've said this to
Laney multiple times, Grezy. Yeah, I've
said this to Laney multiple multiple
times. Yeah, I'm not innocent. But these
people generally do start it. Yeah, I've
said this to Laney multiple times. They
start on me, bro. If you go on my live
stream, these spasticated [ __ ] like
Timmy, they start on me, bro. Yeah, they
do. They do. They do. Their jealousy
starts on me, bro. Yeah. And then that's what happens.
Trust me, he's just just just enjoy your
day tomorrow. Don't get yourself hurt,
bro. Trust me. Seriously, just just just
don't get yourself hurt, bro. Just don't
get yourself hurt. It's not worth it,
bro. You're going to get hurt. The women
are not going to sleep with you. Just
don't just just stop it, bro. You didn't
You didn't even You didn't even win last time.
Just get yourself a piper. I'm sure
you there's some lovely clubs I can
recommend you. You're not going anywhere near.
Yeah, I can't get a girlfriend. That's
self-reflecting, lad. Yeah, that's self-reflecting, brother.
Yeah, I'm going to sleep in a bit, but
I'm just going to make myself a tea.
[ __ ] I'll make myself a tea and then
um I need to do this video as well and
then I'm going to go to sleep, bro.
Ready for this [ __ ] tomorrow.
Yeah, he doesn't understand. I'm a big
[ __ ] bro. He doesn't. This guy doesn't understand.
He really doesn't understand, bro. Yeah.
Yeah. You'll see. Yeah. You'll see the main event. >> Yeah. Simple.
Yeah. Someone's getting hurt tomorrow.
And it ain't going to be me, lad.
And it ain't going to be me. Trust me.
Yeah, it ain't going to be [ __ ] me, lad. Yeah.
[ __ ] little [ __ ] trying to show
off women on YouTube
and and you're not going to say nothing
to lady's going to watch the video as
well. You can't keep my name out your
fat [ __ ] mouth. Yeah. And I think I I
think I told you to get into the cab
when you were trying to say that you're
coming to me. So, yeah, I did say that.
You stupid little [ __ ] blunt. I don't
know how many times you've been
mentioning my [ __ ] name.
Yeah, simple. You're going to try and
you're going to come to me and try to
look good for women on on my mom's star,
bro. Seriously, you didn't even do that
the last time when I weren't even living
with my [ __ ] mom.
You [ __ ] fat ugly bastard. Oh, bro.
I'm just gonna You know what I'm going
to do tomorrow, bro? Yeah. I'm just
going to do a Super Mario jump. I'm
rambling in his face, bro. Trust me.
I'm going to do a superhero jump. Bang
it straight in his face, bro. I swear to
God, one's going to be enough, bro. I
swear to God, one's going to be enough.
One's going to be enough, bro. Yeah,
one's going to be enough, man. One's
going to be enough. Just like a Super
Mario punch, bro. Yeah.
Trust me, bro. Just a Super Mario punch.
Bam. You know what I'm saying? Yeah.
I'm gonna knock him out. Yeah. Try and
say that to me tomorrow, bro.
Yeah. Try try and say that to me
tomorrow. I love it, bro. I love it.
Yeah. Try and say that to me tomorrow, big man.
Yeah. Trying to look good for women on
YouTube, you little loser. You [ __ ]
[ __ ] You called my name out, you
stupid jealous little [ __ ] Don't
[ __ ] start trying to play the victim.
No, you said that you're going to come.
You're a big man. Yeah. Okay, cool. Yeah,
simple, bro. You get me?
You [ __ ] jealous bastard. Going to
get out of your log. You [ __ ] stupid
little queer [ __ ]
And I'm also going to mention the video,
bro. No woman's going to sleep with you,
bro. Even if you defend them, don't get
yourself hurt. Don't get yourself
embarrassed. Seriously. Seriously. It's
not It's not worth it, bro. It's really
not worth it.
Yeah, that's fine, bro. He'll be getting
battered for all of the females tomorrow
then. He will be getting battered tomorrow.
He will be getting battered tomorrow for
all the females then, won't he? So,
he'll be looking even uglier.
So, he'll be he'll be looking even uglier.
Yeah, for all the He'll be looking worse
then for the females then, won't he?
Yeah. [ __ ] little [ __ ]
Don't try and don't try and reverse the
psychology tomorrow as well. Do not try
and reverse the psychology, you stupid
little [ __ ] Do not try to reverse the
psychology, you little virgin mug.
Don't I don't want this guy reversing
the psychology, bro.
Oh, I don't want this guy trying to
reverse the psychology. Yeah,
stupid little jealous little [ __ ] I
don't know how many times he's been
doing this now, bro. For [ __ ] how
many years, bro?
Yeah, like I said, bro, you want to go
London, you go London, bro. Whatever.
Like, you do what you want. But you
ain't coming, you are not coming here
running up your mouth. I'm telling you
that for nothing. You're not coming here
running up your mouth trying to look
good for women, bro. You're not coming
here period. Especially not to look good
for women, bro. That's even worse. Yeah.
Anyways, I need to go to bed soon
anyways, lad. I need you to do this
video and go to bed. Yeah.
Stop trying to show off a YouTuber. Yeah.
It's embarrassing, lad. You done it last
time and you didn't win. Yeah. Last time
you come, you was you ran away, bro.
Trying to look good for YouTube, you [ __ ] [ __ ]
Yeah. [ __ ] little loser. Fat [ __ ]
Simple as that.
Simple as that, bro. So, yeah, I'm not
going to have him I'm not going to have
him try and say that like
um that he's that whatever. No, no, no,
no, no, no. He's not going to try and
reverse the psychology, bro. He is not
going to try and reverse the psychology,
bro. That is not happening.
That is not [ __ ] happening.
Yeah. Sorry, bro. Like I admit it, I'm
not innocent. Um um Dusty and I never
pretend I am innocent, but you don't
even don't try to make it seem like
people have brought you to this store.
Your mouth has your mouth and not
leaving people alone. Am I lying, bro?
Am I [ __ ] lying?
So don't try and make it seem like
people have been bullying you and
they've asked you to come. Don't Don't
even try to Don't even try and say that,
bro. Don't even try to say that. You
ain't got no new nothing. You was upset
that you done your ballsing. Yeah. That
you done your [ __ ] balls in and
you're projecting your [ __ ] onto me. So
I thought, listen, bro, you're going to
keep me. You're going to keep mentioning
my name. I will message your family.
That's fair dudes. Yeah. You know what I'm saying?
Talking about fighting people, bro.
You're not a fighter. You're a [ __ ]
You know what I'm saying?
Haven't you got like anything other to
do with your life than getting going
meeting people for YouTube and getting
battered? Like you would have thought
after the fourth or fifth time. Yeah.
You know what I'm saying? You would have
thought after you've been beaten so many
times, you would just give it up.
I don't need to attract through birds on
YouTube, mate. I I don't need women on YouTube.
Yeah. I don't need women on YouTube. I'm
not a s like Lord J. I'm not a s like
Timmy. Do you understand? Yeah.
And the way I'm seeing it is it's cheeky
dusty. It's very very cheeky because
bro, people have got enough stress as it
is. And this come is it's saying that
he's going to come on my door over
women. No, bro. That's not happening. As
soon as I go out, bro, as soon as I as
soon as I literally wake up tomorrow,
I'm going live, bro. I'm going live as
soon as I wake up. Yeah. Like we got
this, that, this, that, and then we got
some little [ __ ] right? Trying to
look good for YouTube. Nah, bro. That
isn't that isn't happening, bro. That is
just not happening. Trust me, it's not happening, bro. Yeah.
I don't want her to change. I don't like
her. She's a fat ugly [ __ ]
I don't like her. She's a fat ugly [ __ ]
Yeah. I don't like her. She's a fat ugly [ __ ]
I don't want her to like me. I don't
want her to change her mind. She's a fat
ugly [ __ ] I don't want nothing to do
with anyone on here, bro. Every time I
try to leave, you little weirdos draw me
back in. I'm serious, bro. I'm [ __ ] serious.
You know what I'm saying, bro? I'm
deadly serious, bro. Yeah.
That's what you people do here, bro. You
get me? You're all like [ __ ] idiots. Yeah.
[ __ ] stupid little [ __ ] Don't
mention me in your little gay videos.
You [ __ ] stupid little [ __ ]
You know what I mean?
Then he will reverse the psychology. You
see what I'm saying? Then he's going to
then he's going to reverse the
psychology again. Yeah. Time and time
and time and time. And who are you, bro?
Like, who do you think you are?
You know what I mean? Yeah.
And this is what they do. These jealous
people, they start on people, then they
try to play the victim. You see what I mean? Yeah.
How many times did this [ __ ] keep
mentioning my name time and time and
time and time again and would not leave
me alone, bro? How many times did this
fat [ __ ] not keep my name out of his fat
virgin mouth? I don't know how many
times, bro. Yeah. Seriously, seriously.
Seriously, seriously. Seriously. Yeah.
And then the other one gets involved
like, have you got nothing better to do
with your life, bro? Like, have you
seriously got nothing better to do with
your life? Seriously. as someone that
claims they've got a life. You
understand, bro? Like, you know what I'm saying, bro?
This is like mental. And he's going to
get battered as well. He's going to get
battered. That's the thing about it. He
is going to get battered, bro. And I
don't care if he's got disabilities.
Yeah. Because his disabilities does not
stop someone keep mentioning my name
time and time and time and time again.
showing off on YouTube time and time and
time and time again when I've asked him
to keep my name out of your [ __ ] mouth.
Do you understand, bro? Do you get what
I'm saying? Like, yeah.
Just trying to show off. Like, you got a
life or something, bro? Like, you need
You know what I mean, bro? Think about
it, bro. Who are you to think you're
coming on people's door because they've
argued with some females, bro? Who do
you know what I'm saying?
Please. Do you know what I'm [ __ ] saying?
And I hope Laney watches the video as
well. So to make it seem like this guy
is making it seem like, bro, people have
have have started it, you know, cuz
obviously it doesn't look good on me,
does it? With this little [ __ ] Yeah,
he can be in the gym all he wants. I
don't give a [ __ ] I don't give a [ __ ]
Yeah, I don't give a [ __ ] where he's been, mate.
it doesn't matter if he's [ __ ] bro.
Keep my name out your mouth. Literally,
keep my name out your [ __ ] mouth.
It's not hard to do, bro. [ __ ] not
crippled. Crippled, not crippled. You get me?
Who are you to think that you're going
to come, bro? This guy. Yeah. He's the
one that's doing it. He's the one saying
that he's going to come on people's
doors, bro. He's the one trying to show
off. No one else. Stop reversing the
psychology, bro. You're the one bringing
this trouble. You're the one showing off
and not leaving people alone. And I will
make it clear as [ __ ] day. I will
make it clear as day, bro. You are the
one. You are the one showing off. I will
not leave people alone. I've got all the
evidence. Yeah, I've got all the
evidence, bro. Trust me. This will not
leave people alone. You know what I'm
saying, bro? Keeps trying to wind people
up. Doesn't matter how many times he
meets people. [ __ ] him, bro. There's no
rules in it. Tomorrow there's no rules. [ __ ] it.
All because of jealousy. It's [ __ ]
mad, bro. There's actual real life
problems going on in the world, bro.
Yeah. There's actual real life stress
that people have got to deal with. And
you got a [ __ ] trying to act the man on
YouTube over women. Like, bro, you're
telling me, bro, that's how you know the
guy's disabled? That's how you know the
guy is actually a [ __ ] [ __ ]
That there's actual like proper [ __ ]
like going on, bro. That people that
people actually need to do like you need
to do. And you're trying to think you're
going to start coming on people's doors.
This guy's a [ __ ] maniac, bro. I'm
telling you, a maniac.
You know what I'm saying, bro? He's
Someone has to be disabled to think that
way, bro. To think that way, bro.
They've got to be disabled to think that way.
Yeah, they've got to be, bro. And it's
jealousy as well. And And then you know
it is. You [ __ ] know it is. Anyways,
when I watch it, bro, when I put this
video up there. Yeah. Yeah. Laney's
going to see it, bro. That's all I want.
You know, I've got your video, bro. I've
got everything where you've started it
with me, you fat [ __ ] You've been doing
it for time now. Time and time and time again. Yeah,
you get me, bro. [ __ ] stupid little
prick. [ __ ] [ __ ] You know what I mean?
They will never leave you alone. I
should have listened to that guy, bro,
years ago. I should have listened to
him, bro. I really, really, really,
really should have listened to him.
Because you you say that people don't.
Yeah. Yeah. You know, you say that like
you don't listen to people, bro. Of
course I listened to I should have left
this [ __ ] long time ago with these
jealous ass people. Yeah. The only
person I was subscribed to was this [ __ ]
cuz of the gambling stuff. Like I was
still gambling. I don't know. I just
find it interesting, bro. Watching a
gambling vlog. Me. Me. Me. Me. Me. This
fat [ __ ] keep talking my [ __ ] name.
Me. Me. Me. Me. Do you understand, bro?
Yeah. Do you understand?
Do you get me, bro? PJ. The better
looking one. The one that ain't got a
gambling addiction like you. You fat
ugly bastard. The one who's better
looking than you. Come on. You can't
pull the will over my eyes time and time
again. Fatty. Don't know what you think
this is going to be tomorrow, bro. I
don't know what you think this is going
to be. But it's not going to be what you
think it is, bro. It's not going to be
what you think it is. Trust me on my on
my life. It's not going to be what you
think it is. Yeah. Simple.
Simple, bro. That's a That's a warning
as well. That's a warning, bro. you we
you know but I was sub to Monty as well.
Yeah. I was actually subbed to Monty as
well and they're the ones that are
bringing trouble. They are the ones that
are actually bringing trouble.
Yeah. We have our own channel. Yeah.
Talking about this, talking about that,
talking about this, talking about that,
talking about this, talking about that.
You get me, lad?
You don't know me. You don't know
anything about me, you fat [ __ ] Stop
using my [ __ ] name for [ __ ] clout.
And you know what, bro? Do you know
what? Even if I was [ __ ] scared,
I would still [ __ ] him up, bro. And I'm
not scared. I'm not scared of anyone.
But even if I was a little bit scared,
bro, I don't give a [ __ ] This guy needs
to learn, bro. He really really really
really really does need to learn. You
know the amount of times, right, where
where I watched that Monty Man thing.
Yeah. And he was pissing me off. Pissing
me off. Pissing me off. Oh, it drove me
[ __ ] mad, bro. And it And it wasn't
even me, but I didn't get involved
because it's not my name. They do
whatever they want. How long has this
guy been on here now doing this? You
know how long has this guy been on here
now doing this, lad? You know,
you get me, bro. Yeah, I'll save the
angle anyways. Don't worry, bro. It's
cool. I'll deal with a [ __ ] tomorrow. Yep.
They just do not know how to leave
people alone on this community lab.
Don't worry. I've got I've got I've got
loads and loads of fuel, bro. Don't you
worry about me. I've got loads and loads
and loads of fuel.
Trying to come on people's door because
you want to look good for YouTube,
bro. Please. Come on. Just Just rethink
it, bro, before you get yourself
seriously hurt. It's as simple as that,
bro. Just just rethink it before you get
yourself seriously hurt.
Think about it, bro. You left your mate
last time. You ran away. Last time the
[ __ ] ran away, bro. Are we forgetting
that? 3 years ago that this guy ran away.
Yeah. This [ __ ] fat [ __ ] ran away. You remember?
Didn't see him owning me, did you?
Didn't see him doing anything cuz he
ran, bro. The guy ran up the [ __ ]
road how many times? Yeah.
Stupid little [ __ ]
I don't give a [ __ ] If someone's coming
on my door, I'll protect I will protect
the property. It's as simple as that.
You know, it's as simple as that. Bro,
what are you trying to fight people for
anyways? Bro, you should do that in a
response video before you come tomorrow,
big man. You need to you what is it with
you trying to fight people on YouTube
and always getting battered, bro? How
many times is this going to happen? How
many people you going to meet? How many
times you going to act the big man?
Yeah. How many times you going to act
the big man to realize like, bro, what
are you really doing? Like seriously,
what the [ __ ] are you really really
really really doing? You know,
like how many times does it have to
happen? Like how many times does it have
to happen for you to get beaten up? What
are you trying to fight people for
YouTube, bro? You are [ __ ] No woman
is going to get with you. No woman's
going to sleep with you.
What the [ __ ] bro?
Well, fat, bro. You get me?
No, Timmy. Timmy is a jealous one.
Jealous bastard, bro. We could we could
safely say that about Timmy, bro. Come
on. Yeah, he's not going to be around
house kicking anyone.
Yeah. Well, that's your fault, bro. You
mentioned my name. Yeah, you mentioned
my name just like you do every time.
Never notch legs, no one else. You
mention my name. There's someone that
ain't got the gambling addiction,
someone that's younger than you, someone
that's better looking than you. You had
to mention my name again, [ __ ] Yeah.
Keep my name out of your [ __ ] mouth.
Yeah, at the end of the day, you keep my
name out your [ __ ] mouth, you fat
Shouldn't this guy be going rehab or
something for his gambling other than
trying to fight people on YouTube that
he doesn't know and he loses every
single fight? [ __ ] [ __ ] Yeah,
just go London tomorrow, bro. Have a
drink. Trust me, don't get yourself
hurt. It's not worth getting yourself
hurt, bro. and losing another fight.
Like seriously, seriously, it seriously isn't.
But I've got actual like real life
problems, bro. Like, not not like
problems like that, but real life stuff
I've got to do. Do you understand, bro?
Like, you get me, bro? Why do you think
I quit gambling and you got you thinking
that you're going to start knocking on
people's door to look good for YouTube?
Bro, you mad? You You need to get out of
life. And by all means, like I said, if
you want out the big man and come, do
what you want to do, bro. Do what you
want to do. I'm not asked, but just know
what's going to happen. It's as simple as that.
[ __ ] hell, bro.
Oh [ __ ] Live,
bro. You can't even play [ __ ]
campaign on this [ __ ]
No, but you get what I'm saying, bro.
There's actual like real life problems out there,
stuff and [ __ ] and you got this little
[ __ ] trying to good and bro you can't
fight. Like you cannot fight. None. You
cannot fight, bro. Yeah. Why are you on
YouTube trying to meet people that you
don't know? You can't fight, bro. You
It's been proven multiple times.
You know, it's as simple as that.
You came on the door three years ago
trying to show off. You got batted.
Well, you didn't get batted, but you ran
away. Let's tell the truth, bro. You ran
away. Yeah, you literally ran away.
he ran away, bro. He actually did. He
tried to hit me several times and he
couldn't hit me. Yeah,
several times. Several times. And he
mentioned my name several times, bro, as
well on that video. Yeah, he was trying
to get a reaction. He got the reaction
he wanted and now he's saying, "No, oh,
you don't miss these people's family.
Stop mentioning my name." As simple as
that. Stop trying to draw me out,
Virgin. I've had I've had enough of your
lip and enough of your mouth to last me
a lifetime, [ __ ] Yeah, you jealous ass
bastard. Try and do the next try and do
the next gambling addict, bro. Listen,
listen. Try to do try to do the next
gambling vlog without trying to mention
my name, you [ __ ] weirdo.
You get me?
You get me, lad?
Imagine that. Yeah. You got real life problems, bro.
There's actual real life stuff going on
in the world and we got some [ __ ]
that can't fight trying to get attention on YouTube.
Bro, he can go where he wants, but I'm
telling you right now, if he comes on
this door, that's it. I'm telling you,
bro, that is literally literally
literally literally literally literally
literally it. That's it, bro. Yeah, that
is generally generally generally it,
bro. Yeah. If you're not getting
attention on YouTube, bro, that's on
you, bro. You put some more gambling
videos up. You do whatever you want, but
you are not coming here, bro, making a
scene. You are not coming here making a
scene, you jealous fat bastard. And I
could tell I'll tell you that for
nothing now, bro. Yeah.
You know what I'm saying, Mr. Beo? Do
you understand what I'm saying, bro? You
understand what I'm saying? This guy has
got so many problems in his life, bro.
Yeah. And And he's still trying to meet
for a fight on YouTube to lose again.
What a loser, bro. What an absolute
loser. You You know what? You haven't
even took the [ __ ] video [ __ ] down,
bro. If he comes anywhere near the door
and then he knocks the door, he's
getting batted, bro. It's as simple as
that. He's getting battered
and then he's thinking he's going to show off
um on people's door.
You get me, bro? Like, what the [ __ ] do
you think this is, bro?
He ain't got no balls. If he had balls,
he'd turn up by himself. If he had
balls, he would turn up by himself,
which he never done. So, he ain't got no
balls. I've got more balls than him,
bro. Do you not remember the mad places
that I travel to by myself?
Do you not remember the the amount of
places I travel to by myself?
The guy ain't got no balls, bro. He will
never turn up anywhere by himself, ever.
He's a [ __ ] bro. Yeah.
Yeah, bro. He ain't got no balls, bro.
You'll see that tomorrow as well.
Yeah. Well, well, we'll see you tomorrow
then, won't we, bro? We'll see you
tomorrow then, won't we?
We'll see you tomorrow then, won't we, lad? Yeah.
We'll see you tomorrow then, won't we?
This guy likes trying to wind people up.
He likes trying to lick Nons's ass. To
be fair, a lot of people are there do it
to be honest. He likes trying to wind
people up when he does his ballsing. As
you can see, bro, when you when you when
you go on that channel, you get me, bro. Yeah, bro.
He is one jealous little [ __ ] bro.
You can't even deny the fact that he's
jealous, bro. The guy's life is
finished. It's over, bro. Yeah.
You know what I mean?
What are you going to tell Eene, bro?
What are you really, really, really,
really going to tell Eileen, bro? What
are you really going to tell Eileen that
you want to try and look good for people
on YouTube? Like, what what's the story,
bro? Like, when when I when I'm done
with you. Yeah. What are you really
going to tell Eene that you want to try
and look good for people on YouTube?
That you can't keep people's name out
your [ __ ] mouth. That you can't leave
people alone, fatty. When the attention
is on you, you jealous [ __ ] You know,
there's a reason for it, bro. There's a
reason. There's a reason for it.
Tell Eene all of this stuff, bro.
Yeah. Tell Eene all of this stuff.
Yeah. Tell Eene all of this stuff, bro.
You can tell Eileen, as you call her,
all of this stuff tomorrow. Yeah.
You know what I'm saying, bro?
I find it funny to be honest, bro. I
find it funny as [ __ ]
trying to fight someone on YouTube that
they don't know. I find it I find it comical, bro.
Does any of you people just laugh at it?
Does any of you people just look back
and just laugh at it?
Do you ever just like look back and just
laugh at it? And don't worry, Autumn
Rose darling, I will do a video for you
tomorrow. And what you think is going to
happen is not going to happen.
And what you think is going to happen is
definitely not going to happen.
You know what I mean, bro? So yeah,
anyways, I need to go to sleep. I need
to do this video. Go to sleep, bro.
I'm tired as [ __ ] man.
It's hot in it.
Yep. He's a white knight. He's a s. He's
an attention seeker
and he's bought it all on himself as
well. He's bought all it all on himself.
So I don't want to hear no excuses. I
don't want to hear no excuses. Oh, you
done this. No, no, no. You started
mentioning my name. Yeah, that's what
happened. You like you done with Monty
like you done with everyone else. Every
fight that's happened, he has started it
on this community, bro. Every fight this
fat [ __ ] has started it on this community.
Yeah, I'm pretty sure we started every
single fight on this community, lad. Yeah.
You know what I'm saying? Yeah. Well,
don't go on someone's door then. You've
got no reason to be even going on
someone's door in the first place. So,
if you don't want to affect Elaine, you
shouldn't even be going on people's doors.
Simple as that.
You you shouldn't even be going on
people's doors. You shouldn't even be
trying to meet people. You don't even
know me. Do you know what I'm saying?
You can't start changing the rules now.
You know, you can't start changing the
rules now. You mentioned my name.
Remember that? You done a video trying
to trying to annoy me. Yeah. Do you
understand? You were saying how you was
going to come to me, so I called you a
bluff with the cab. Yeah. It's as simple
as that, bro. Yeah. You're not going to
stop until you meet someone, you jealous
bastard. And you get attention on
YouTube. You're not going to stop. This
is what I mean. I don't know when to
stop. Yeah. I ordered him next last
week. Yeah. Why? Because he said he was
he wanted to come. I'm coming to London.
I'm coming to London. I'm coming to
London. I'm We heard it all, bro.
Everyone heard it. I'm coming to London.
I'm coming to London. I'm Cuz I would
have just said that for no reason.
I wouldn't have just said that for no
reason, bro. Yeah.
I'm coming to London. I'm coming to
London. I'm coming to London. Yeah.
You know what I'm saying?
So he he's this little [ __ ] started on
me. Yeah. When I clicked on his video,
generous ass people on YouTube will not
leave people alone. I don't know what I
don't know what to title the video as.
To be fair, I don't know what to title
the video as, bro. Yeah.
These jealous people just never stop.
They never ever ever ever stop. Never
ever ever ever ever ever stop. You
mention my name, [ __ ] You understand?
I'm not one of these people like Mr. B.
You mention my name, [ __ ] before you
start. You know what I'm saying? Oh,
he's gambling vlog. Do you remember the
gambling vlog video, bro? I clicked on a
video. Yeah. Watching this gambling
thing cuz I wanted to see what's up with
the gambling, bro. The guy mentioned me
and again and again and again and again.
And I said, "Listen, stop mentioning my
name. If you keep mentioning my name,"
and you can see what he was trying to do
as well. He's trying to draw me out,
right? Time and time and time and time
again, this fat jealous [ __ ] I said
to him, "Keep my name out your [ __ ]
mouth." I don't know how many times I
had to say. I said, "Listen, if you keep
mentioning my name again, I'm going to
message your family cuz this is the only
way this guy's going to learn to stop
trying to draw me out in his shit."
Yeah. And then he was like, "Oh, I'm
going to come to London. I'm going to
come to London cuz that would have been
him that said that. So, okay then. I'll
call you a cab right now then. Oh, I'll
accept it. I'd accept it. I'll accept
it. Ordered a cab twice. Didn't come in
the cab. Now he's saying he's coming on
people's doors. Bro, literally like you
watch the video. He mentioned my name
multiple multiple times. Yeah. He tried
to add me in with nonslegs again knowing
damn well what he was doing to try and
put me in a bad mood. You know, I was I
was in a good mood that day as well. Do
you know what I'm saying, bro?
Kim and Monty was the only people I was
sub to, bro. I'm I'm not sub to like and
it's the way he was doing it. It was the
way he was doing it, bro. Like, watch it
and you'll see what I mean. Keep my name
out my out out my Keep my name out your
mouth. You don't know what money I have.
You don't know when I gamble, [ __ ] If
you want to do your videos, you do your
videos and keep my name out your mouth.
If you ain't got anything nice to say,
bro, keep my name out your [ __ ]
mouth, you jealous bastard.
And I think that's fair, bro. Like to be
honest with you, I think that's fair.
You know what I mean? So don't go on
like people have started on you. No
one's put a gun to your head and start
making you mention people's name time
and time again. He's done it about four times, bro.
Keep my name out your [ __ ] mouth. I'm
sure you've heard me say that. Like, do
you know what I mean? with this fat,
jealous, farey [ __ ]
You know what I'm saying, bro? This is all madness.
Yeah, that's fine, bro. This is all mad.
Yeah, that's fine, bro. It's actually
embarrassing, to be honest, bro. I say
it's fine, but it's actually embarrassing.
You know what I mean? It's just jealousy
as well. That's the most that is the
most annoying thing about it is it's
just it's just jealousy. That's the
thing, bro. That's why I can't get my
head around it is it is jealousy.
That's the thing, bro. It is. It [ __ ]
well is. Look at the state of the [ __ ]
Look at the [ __ ] state of the fat
[ __ ] You understand, bro? Every time,
bro. Every year with this jealous [ __ ]
If it's not Monty, it's someone else. If
it's not this, it's someone else. I saw
the way they were moving, bro.
Over Natalie. And this. He's a jealous,
very, very jealous bastard. Trust me.
When it comes to money, anyone better
looking than him, anyone that ain't got
an addiction like him. Trust me, bro.
It's jealousy with these clowns.
Trust me, bro. Trust me.
Especially him as well, bro. He gets
jealous when someone shows 500, you know.
Yeah, it's not going to happen, bro. Yeah.
Yeah, that's fine, bro. He can show
tomorrow then, can't he?
And he can tell Laney the reason why
he's on people's doors and he can tell
people he trying to show off for women
on YouTube trying to show off, trying to
be the big man because Yeah. You I don't
know. You want to try the good big man
for women. Yeah. Embarrassing, bro. It's
so embarrassing. He It's embarrassing as
[ __ ] bro. You The more you think about
this community, the more embarrassing.
And the more it's jealousy as well.
That's the most annoying thing is, you
know, it's jealousy.
Yeah. It's all jealousy. That's the
thing about it as well. And it is. And
you know it is as well.
You know what I mean? Yeah.
I got these people that's got a raging
obsession over me, lad.
You know what I'm saying? I've got so
many people that's got a raging boner
over me, bro. It's [ __ ] weird, lad.
[ __ ] weirdo community, bro. Weirdo
community, lad. You know what I mean?
Trust me, I'm doing something tomorrow,
bro. Believe me, don't believe me. Trust
me. I'm going to bed in a minute and
we're going to see. Yeah,
You [ __ ] You're going to see
tomorrow, bro. You're going to see
tomorrow. And do you know what, bro?
Anyone would act exactly the same way as
well. Anyone would act exactly the same
way as well. You don't get it, bro.
Yeah. Trust me. We'll see you tomorrow.
But wake up. I'm going live as well,
bro. Don't you worry. No one's running
anywhere. Yeah. No one's running
anywhere, bro. Trust me.
Cuz I'm sick of this fat [ __ ] I've been
sick of this fat [ __ ] for a very long
time now, bro. No one's disability makes
them keep mentioning people's names.
Yeah. Do you understand, lad?
>> Oh, [ __ ]
>> Ray, do you get me? Yeah.
Trust me, Dusty. I'm serious, lad. I am
deadly serious, bro. I am deadly,
deadly, deadly, deadly, deadly serious,
you know. So, you've mentioned people's
names. I've asked you multiple times to
stop mentioning my name. And then you're
going to try and play the victim to
Laney when you get beat up. Yeah. Okay,
bro. Explain that to Laney when you're
beaten up. Yeah.
You know what I mean, bro? [ __ ]
stupid little [ __ ] [ __ ]
Do you know what I mean? Hey, Dusty,
know if you said something about
someone's kid, I I could understand it
more. If you like slang someone's
daughter off or
t Do you understand, bro? No, he didn't
call anyone out for a reason. This guy
kept mentioning my name. Yeah. He will
not keep my name out of his fat [ __ ]
mouth. Yeah. That's the reason why I
started cuz he will not keep me out of
his mouth. That's the reason. Yeah.
Let's go back to how it started. Yeah.
Yeah. That's the thing, bro. We always
need to go back to how it started. How
did all of these fights start? You said
come and I'll fight you. So, you got to
come out, bro. Bro, bro, he has started it. Yeah.
So, simple as that, bro. Simple.
Have you people got nothing better to do
with your lives?
Seriously, then coming on you. And I'm
not scared. Trust me, he will be getting
filled in tomorrow. I'm I'm wondering at
the same time. Have you got nothing
better to do with your lives? Seriously,
you not have like I don't know, bro.
Like financial stress, women stress,
work stress, family stress,
moving stress. You don't have anything
in your lives other than trying to fight
strangers on YouTube. Like I just want
to ask that, bro. No, like I just want
to add that in there, bro. Sorry. Maybe
someone can answer me. Someone Maybe
someone that's actually got brain power
can actually answer it, lad.
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Like, let let me just
let I just want to ask that at the same
time. Any anything going on or nothing or like
tell us tell us what's going on, bro?
Cuz he seems to have done this with
multiple different people now.
Same thing with LT. He's always wanted
to fight people. this person's always
wanted. Like, do you not do you not have
a [ __ ] life, bro?
Like, do you can't you just go and touch
grass or something? Like, can't you just
go and and and and go to a restaurant?
Like, is there have you got nothing
better to do in your life, bro?
Like, like, am I am I making sense?
Like, am I actually making sense? Do you
not have anything better to do?
And I mean it like go and touch grass or
something or like go to a bar by
yourself or something.
You know what I mean?
Do you actually like not have anything
better to do
than try to show off for people and
women on YouTube that are never going to
sleep with you?
I'll be mentioning that in that video as
well. I actually want I actually want a
response. You know that
I was out all day yesterday, bro. I told
you when it hits March, I'm [ __ ] You
know what I mean? Yeah.
It's just weird. I would just thought
like so many people have enough stress
in their life that they wouldn't want
to. I just wondering like people allowed
to wonder, you know, and not be scared.
I you know, you would think though. You
would actually think. You get me?
And you can't even fight people. Anyways,
I had loads of stresses this week. I had
that Christian Izzy thing
and oh, so much [ __ ] I had to do, bro.
You get me?
You get me, bro?
Yeah, he's a loser, bro. He's a loser.
He's a proper proper loser. He's going
to get hurt, bro. He's actually going to
get hurt, Dusty. Seriously,
these people just don't know when to
give it a break, do they, Dusty? They
really, really don't.
They really really do, bro.
You know what I mean?
Females that won't sleep with him. Did
he say before that he's come to Didn't
he say that he's come before to people's
doors over females? [ __ ] little s
right. But if he comes tomorrow, he's
getting battered anyways, bro. Simple as that.
He'll be getting battered tomorrow.
Yeah, trust me. He'll be getting
battered tomorrow, bro. [ __ ] that [ __ ]
You know what? I've actually got an
electric heater as well, actually, bro.
Trust me. Peter Belly's got a collection
of of lovely little things. Trust me. Yeah.
Yeah. He need Yeah. Literally, bro.
Literally, he doesn't seem to learn
this jealous fat [ __ ] Trust me, Dusty,
I'll be doing it tomorrow, bro. Trust
me. Yeah, trust me. I've had enough of
this little [ __ ] trying to show off for
YouTube. You know, he's the main he's
the main part of [ __ ] you know, um,
like I said, bro, you're coming on
someone's door. You don't call the
shots. You don't call the shots. It's as
simple as that.
Trust me, bro. You don't call the shots.
You're You're not going to tell me
you're coming to my where I live,
regardless who house it is, and try to
show off for women on YouTube, bro. You
don't call the shots. I am not losing.
It's as simple as that. Whatever it
takes, I'm not losing.
Whatever it takes, bro, I ain't losing,
bro. It doesn't matter what it takes.
Yeah. See, you [ __ ] [ __ ] Thinking
that you're going to come to another
city and start banging on people's door,
bro. Just keep that same energy
tomorrow. Yeah. Just keep that same energy tomorrow.
Yeah, [ __ ] jealous [ __ ]
Hopefully lady will see the video as
well. So you can't try and say that
people's brought it to their door.
You've done this with multiple different
people. You know, you done it you went
on you went on the door last time and no
one even knew you was coming. You
remember at Albert Square, no one knew
this [ __ ] was coming.
Do you remember when was it? Three, four
years ago. How many years ago was that, bro?
Three or four years a
more than the light's going to be on.
It's going to be more than the light,
lad. It's going to be more than the
light. Trust me. I'm going to go mad
tomorrow, bro. Trust me. And he's going
to learn to leave people alone, bro.
He's going to learn to leave people
alone. Trust me.
Yeah. So, you got a choice, bro. You
either go London,
just go about your day or you come and
you get seriously hurt. And you're not
call And you're not call You're not
calling the shots either.
You're not calling the shots either,
[ __ ] Don't think you're calling the
shots cuz you're not, you cheeky [ __ ]
[ __ ] You know, if I travel to someone's
door in another city, I ain't calling
the shots, bro. I I'd be expecting
anything and everything. Yeah.
What's the time? I need to end this live
stream in a bit, lads. Yeah.
Trying to say how people have done their
balls in, bro. got more money than you
will ever have, bro. You're sat on
YouTube flexing £80.
Self projecting your life
onto people as usual. Do you get me? Mama mia.
He'll do anything to show off for
YouTube, Clint. He's been doing it for
years. He's been doing it for years and
years and years trying to show off the
YouTube talking about people that he's
jealous of, bro. He's been doing it for
years and years and years and years and years,
years and years and years. He's done it
with me. He's done it with Monty. He's
done it with loads of different people,
bro. Loads of different people.
It's jealousy. It's jealousy with a fat
[ __ ] And trying to look good for women
on YouTube. That's all it is, bro.
Jealousy. And you can't try and tell me
Timmy ain't jealous of me, bro. You look
at Timmy and then look at me.
Look at Timmy, then look at me, bro.
Please. Come on. Come on now. Come on
now. It's not like the person is anonymous. Yeah.
And he will not leave me alone. Mike, he
keeps mentioning my name over and over
and over and over again. He's a jealous [ __ ]
I was watching his gambling video. I was
watching his gambling video and all he
keeps doing is talking about me. Me
me me me me me me me me me me me me me
me. Give it a rest, you jealous nonslegs
loving bastard. That's all I was
thinking, bro. But don't worry, he'll be
getting bad tomorrow anyways. Oh, he be
getting bad tomorrow. Let me do Let me
do this video, bro. Let me do this video. Yeah,
he's a jealous of He's a jealous
bastard, bro. Trust me. Right.
You got the chance now, bro, to to to to
leave it because you will be getting
hurt. Trust me. Just like just like last
time you ran away. You didn't win last
time. No one No one really ran, bro. You
went halfway up the street. Yeah.
You ran halfway up the street, bro. You
had to stop recording, you [ __ ]
[ __ ] Yeah, Mike. I made a new channel
anyways, bro, to get away from these people.
So on Thursday, we're all going on that channel, lad.
I don't want to be a part of this [ __ ]
anymore, bro. Because it just goes round
and round in circles with them.
So this is what happens, right? You go live.
Yeah. He can plan all he wants all
[ __ ] week. He can plan all he [ __ ]
wants all week.
What happens is you go live. This is
exactly what happens, mate. You go live,
someone starts [ __ ] with you, then you
go argue with them back, talk about
meeting, LT comes straight away, even
though he says he's left YouTube, then
you start arg and it's just the same
thing over and over again with these
weirdos, bro. It's the same thing with
these weirdos over and over and over
again. And they've been doing it for
years, bro, to be honest with you. And
now it's like marching out and I'm going
out and stuff. I'd rather not be
surrounded by these people. I don't want
anything to do with these people.
these negative ass people, lad. You know
what I'm saying? Like, people got enough
stress in their life. We don't want to
be communicating with these people, bro.
You get what I'm saying? That's why I
made a new like channel, lad. I've had
it for a while, but I just didn't tell
anyone about it, lad. You get it? Yeah.
still got three subs. That's perfect, lad. Yeah, man.
You get what I mean?
And then the same thing just happens
again and again. I'm a line dusty again
and again and again. I got LT stalking
me. I got Timmy [ __ ] talking. Like,
do you know what I'm saying, bro? Do you
not think it's just all weird?
Do you not think the whole thing is just
the same weird atmosphere?
You not get it, bro. Do you understand
what I mean?
No, I don't. No, no, no, no, no, no. If
he comes on the door, he's getting
battered. That's up to him, bro. If he
wants to come on the door, he's getting
battered. That's up to you. That is your
choice. If you want to show off for
YouTube and look good, you're getting battered.
It's as simple as that. You're getting
You're getting [ __ ] up. It's as simple
as that. Like you do what you want to
do, bro. Because we know what you're
going to do. You're going to try reverse
the psychology again and show Laney,
which is what you like, you you little
jealous people like doing. Yeah. Time
and time again. You if you go on the
door, which is up to you, you are
getting battered. And I'm not following
by I'm not following no rules. So that's
up to you, bro. You can do whatever you
want to do. But if you do and I hear any
knocks, any any doorbell rings, you're
getting it. Simple as that. you're
getting it. So, I mean, just think
twice, bro. You know, I know what I
would do. So, it's as simple as that.
And that's that, lad.
Well, no. Well, yes, I can. Well, yes, I
can. Who started talking about who? Who
started doing videos on who?
Who started doing videos on who?
Who started doing videos on who, lad? He
started doing videos mentioning me,
blowing me out. So there you go. Yeah,
that's what will work in court. Yeah.
Know what I mean?
So like the whole thing is, bro, he
started it regardless. So he started it
regardless. Yeah, he started it
So that's it. And that's what you people
always do and you'll always do on here.
Yeah. And that's it. You know,
and that's it, bro. You know,
no, it's not even that, bro. LT does the
same thing. Any excuse to start coming
on my road. It's weird. The whole thing
is weird, bro. You don't understand how
the whole thing is weird. LT does it.
Timmyy's trying to do it. It's like,
bro, have I got Are you obsessed with me
or something? Like, like, seriously.
Seriously. These people must be obsessed
with me or something, bro. You get me? So, yeah.
You know, a lot of you people here do this.
Okay. Okay, bro. Okay. Okay. Okay. Okay.
Who started talking about meeting first?
It was him. He started talking about meeting first. Yeah.
He started talking about meeting cuz
I've told him to keep my name out of his
mouth. I said, "Okay, if you really want
that, I'll order you a cab right now."
He didn't get in the cab. Oh, I'm coming
to London now. So, he started it. So,
it's as simple as that.
Yeah. So, that's it.
But what I'm saying now is, bro, if he
comes, he's getting battered. It's as
simple as that. Yeah.
He's getting battered. So that's what
I'm saying now. That
And that's that, bro.
It's never going to stop with you people
and ain't it, lad? Like, I'll leave I'll
leave you to it on Thursday, bro. I'll
leave you people to it on Thursday.
Trust me, I will. Yeah. Why are you even
mentioning people's names anyways, lad?
Yeah, I will, bro. 100%. 100%. Yeah. Simple.
100% I will.
You people really need you really You
people really are bored. But honestly,
bro, really really are bored. You just
don't know how to leave people alone, do you?
If it's not videos, you just don't know
how to leave people. And then you wonder
why we think you're jealous of people.
And then and then you and then you
wonder why we think that you're jealous.
This is what makes me laugh, bro. Yeah.
You always say, "Oh, what is there to be
jealous of? What?" And then you wonder
why we think that you people are
jealous. Look at what you're doing, bro.
Look at the videos that you're making.
Look at the stalking. Look at the
weirdness. And then you wonder why we
think that you're jealous. And then it's
apparently we we're having this ego,
bro. Come on, man. Come on. Seriously.
Seriously. Now. And you wonder why
people think that you are jealous? You
really want to know why? Okay. You want
to talk about GE? You want to talk about
um Kitty? Yeah, they get trolls. Yeah,
they get stalkers, but not as much as
me. Not as much as me, lad.
Not as much as me. And I can safely say
they do not get as many accounts
dedicated to them as they do me. But
then it's a shocker when we think that
you're jealous. Well, you're not [ __ ]
normal. Put it Put it that way, bro.
You're not normal.
You're not [ __ ] normal. Simple.
And that's that. You're not normal.
You're definitely definitely not normal,
lad. Wherever Wherever the [ __ ] you are,
Jealous ass people.
At least money man will be back, bro.
I've got more important things to be
doing to be honest with you, bro. I've
got more important things to be thinking
of. Not fighting a [ __ ] on YouTube
that's trying to look good for women.
But if he wants it, he'll get it, bro.
Simple as that.
If he wants it, I ain't backing down, bro.
And I need to say that way as well, just
so this guy can't try and [ __ ] try to
play the victim like he always does, you know?
You get me, bro? Anyways, I'm doing this
video now and I'm going bed. Yeah. ready
for tomorrow. I'll be live tomorrow anyways. Yeah.
And I will not miss a blink, bro,
because I'm not [ __ ] scared one
little bit. So, I'm going to do this
video and then I'm going to bounce to
bed, bro. Yeah.
And um yeah, bro. Stephen Pat's [ __ ]
anyways to be fair. But yeah, I'll be
back tomorrow anyways, bro. Didn't have
enough Streamyard anyways, so I'll be
back tomorrow. Yeah, lad.