Yep. Okay.
Ready as I'll ever be, matey. Ready as
I'll ever be. And I'm not scared one little bit.
How's about that one, bro? How's about
that one? I tried commenting on your
live stream, but you [ __ ] ended the
live stream, so I couldn't comment.
You [ __ ] little weirdo.
Oh, now it's back. It didn't let me comment.
One second, bro.
Yeah, bro. I tried to comment, but he
ended the live stream. The [ __ ] little [ __ ]
The [ __ ] little [ __ ] Yeah, [ __ ]
little [ __ ] Trying to look good for
YouTube. Well, he's going to be ended
today anyways, bro. He will be ended
today. 100% he will be ended today, bro.
Don't any of you worry about that.
Trying to be the big man on YouTube.
We'll see how that works out from today,
lads, cuz we're staying on it, bro. Just
as I said last night. Just as I said
last night, bro.
Come on, Timmy. Let me smash your face
in, please. Come on, bro. Don't let us
all down. Do not let us all down today.
Please do not let us all down today. Try
and show off your women in front of
YouTube. You'll be the first. See what
happens to you. Please see what happens
to you, big man. Please see what happens to you.
Yeah. No one's scared of you. You
[ __ ] fat [ __ ] You [ __ ] little
jealous little weasel. Yeah. It's the
truth, bro. It It's the [ __ ] truth. Little [ __ ]
Jealous [ __ ] I've been wait, bro. I've
been looking forward to this. I've
actually been looking forward to this,
bro. Actually, yeah. 100%.
[ __ ] jealous little fat [ __ ] He
knows I'm right as well, bro. I'm
looking forward to this, bro. I actually am.
Yeah, I actually am, bro. I really,
really am. 100%.
Yeah, [ __ ] fat jealous [ __ ]
bro. Let me message this person back on
Instagram. The [ __ ] is going on? Follow YouTube. [laughter]
[ __ ] mad. I'll be ready for this [ __ ]
today anyways, bro. And and here's the
thing. I don't need a drink. Here's the
thing. I don't need a drink, bro. That's
the difference. I don't need a drink. Yeah.
[ __ ] stupid [ __ ]
Jealous [ __ ] as well. I just had to make
that video and try in case you try
playing the mole high ground.
In case you wanted to try to play the
moral high ground and lie to Laney,
sorry I had to make that video, bro,
because you're not doing that. You're
not doing that, you fat [ __ ] Come on
that door today. You're going to see
what happens to you, you little [ __ ]
[ __ ] You're going to see what
happens. You're going to see what
happens. I'm going to make a I'm going
to make a Tik Tok video as well. I'm
going to do a video and put it on
TikTok, bro. 100%. Yeah.
I'm going to do a video and put it on
Tik Tok. What happens when you try to
look good for women? Extreme version.
Yeah, I'll show I'll show everyone, bro. Yeah, 100%.
[ __ ] that, bro. I don't need to drink nothing, bro.
Not even one little bit. When people
have to drink, that shows nerves, bro.
That shows nerves.
That shows [ __ ] nerves.
And that's why he's drinking. Cuz he's a
nervous little [ __ ] That's why. [ __ ]
He's a [ __ ] bro. He's a [ __ ] Watch
what happens to him today. [ __ ]
little [ __ ] Jealous bastard.
And that's why I got four thumbs up
because you know I'm right as well. You
know it's the truth. Exactly all I was
saying yesterday. Why these jealous ass
people go for you. You know it's the
truth, bro. As well
going to get even more hyped up when I
see that train video, bro. When I see
that train video.
Yeah. Is he really? That's nice, bro. I
don't He ain't going anywhere near this
house. I know that for a fact. He ain't
going anywhere near this house.
Yeah, he's not going anywhere near this
house. That's all I know, bro. I don't
know about any harvesters. I don't know
about I know he ain't going anywhere
near this house. As simple as that. No,
I'm telling you he's not going anywhere
near this house. And I'm completely
sober. I don't need to drink, bro. I'm
not I'm not a nervous wreck like him.
Ah, he would do. Yeah, he would do, bro.
Of course he would. Yeah, of course he
would, bro. He needs backup.
Of course he would. He needs backup.
Yeah, that doesn't surprise me, bro.
That's Timmy all over. He's been the
same for 15 years. I'm going to teach
him a lesson today. Good oldfashioned lesson, bro. >> [snorts]
>> Stop trying to show off for people on
YouTube, especially to people that you
don't know. I'm going to I'm going to
give him a good old lesson today, bro.
Don't you worry. Yeah, guys. Annoyed me
multiple multiple times. Will not keep
my name out of his [ __ ] jealous ass
mouth. He wants it. I'll give it to him, bro. Simple.
He's asking you to come with him because
he's a [ __ ] This is what he does. This
is what he does, bro. He needs backup.
He does this every time, bro. He's a
[ __ ] He's a [ __ ] little [ __ ] bro.
Of course he would, bro. Of course he
would ask you for backup. The jealous
little [ __ ] Little [ __ ] IA bastard.
Cuz he can't fight his own battles. This
is what I'm saying. He can't fight his own battles.
Yeah. Well, he's not coming anyways,
bro. So, yeah.
He ain't coming out. He ain't coming anyways, mate.
So, no one's letting anyone down from my side, bro.
Yeah, [ __ ] stupid little [ __ ] trying
to show up for YouTube. He's such an
He's such a little jealous attention
seeker. You know that as well, bro. No,
I had plenty of sleep, bro. Plenty of
sleep. Slept fine. Not scared one little bit.
Not scared one little bit like probably
you are, lad. Not even one little bit.
Slept fine. Had a good couple of hours.
I'm fine, bro. He seemed like he didn't
sleep well, though. Yeah.
Yeah. This bastard,
bro. As soon as I see him on that train,
it's going to get worse and worse and
worse. This rage, I'm telling you, bro.
Yeah. Worse and worse and worse and
worse. I'm going to splatter his face.
I'm going to do the noise and splatter
his face as well, bro. Yeah.
Trying to show up for YouTube women.
Keep PJ out your mouth, you obsessed
[ __ ] He's getting it today, bro. Trust
me, he's getting it today. I don't know
who he thinks he's he's saying he's
going to come on people's doors. I don't
know who he thinks he is, bro. I don't
know who this fat [ __ ] thinks he is, lad.
I'm just going to get a glass and
splatter all over his face. That's what
I'm going to do, bro. I'm just going to
get a glass and splatter all over his
face for all the times he's mentioned me
on YouTube, bro. Trust me, it's going to
get dirty, bro. Trust me, it's going to
get dirty. This cunt's going to know to
leave people alone like the rest of the
people on here. I'm going to get a glass
and bang it over his face, bro. Trust
me, I'm not play I'm not playing fair.
I'm not playing fair, bro. There's no
fair. I'm not playing fair, lad.
Trust me, I'm not playing fair at all.
Not at all. At all. No one hide or made
excuses in the first place. Yeah.
Simple. Yeah. Free already. Yeah.
I'm going to teach him to stop showing
off YouTube. I got a nice big glass,
bro. in that middle, bro. Don't you
worry. I got a nice Because I do need
weapons. Because I do need weapons.
Because I do need weapons. You don't
call the shots. Like I've said multiple
times, you don't call the shots. You
come on my door, I'm going to glass you
on your face trying to look good for
YouTube. Simple as that.
Yeah. Simple as that, bro. You come on
people's door YouTube trying to look
good for women. I I'll break you and
I'll break your face. That's literally
what I said yesterday. I'll break you
and I'll break your face. You don't
think I'm serious, do you? You're going
to leave people alone, bro. I don't give
a [ __ ] I I don't need to, but I'm going
to. I don't need to, but I'm going to.
Yeah, you're going to learn to leave
people alone, you jealous [ __ ] Same as
this jealous Joe F. You're going to
learn today, bro. You're really, really,
really, really, really going to learn.
Trust me, you're really, really, really,
really, really going to learn, bro.
You're really, really, really going to
learn. Trust me. Yeah. Trying to look
good for YouTube, you jealous [ __ ] And
then think you're going to And then you
think you're going to call the shots,
bro. I'm going to I'm just going to
glass over his face. I swear to God,
bro. Yeah, that's what I'm going to do.
Just one big glass across his face. Then
maybe he'll learn, bro. No. If you're
coming on If you're knocking on my door
and you're coming on my door. Yeah. If
you're coming on my door, you're
harassing me. Yeah. You're harassing me.
Yeah. You're coming on my door harassing
me. I will do what I want. Simple as
that. I will do what I want. You come on
my door, I'm glassing you in your face.
I'm telling you what's happening, bro.
So, I'm just telling you know. I'm just
letting you know what's happening. I
will give you one big glass across your
fat face. One for the [ __ ] one for
the notch legs ass licking and then the
other for keep mentioning my name. Yeah.
Yeah. I'm not going to do a thing. Well,
you'll see that. You'll see about that,
won't you, lad? Yeah. I literally don't
care. Yeah. I literally don't give a
[ __ ] I literally don't care, bro. I
literally don't care. Simple as that. I
Teach you a lesson for showing off on
YouTube, you jealous bastard. It's
simple that you you you'll get You'll
get taught a lesson, won't you? You'll
get taught a lesson then, won't you? Yeah.
You dead little [ __ ] Yeah, bro. Got
some lovely sleep, bro. Feel good, man.
Yeah, got some lovely sleep. This guy is
so jealous of me. He's another one. This
Timmy's another one. He's so jealous of
me. Why do you think he mentions my name
over and over and over and over and over
again? Just let this guy please come
today, bro. I hope this is not [ __ ]
because I'm in a mood. I'm in the mood,
bro. I'm in the [ __ ] mood. You're
going to knock on people's door and show
off. Oh, bro, you're getting spat in
your face. Simple as that. And now now
don't start saying, "Oh, there's no
weapons. There's no weapons. There's no
weapons." Bro, there's going to be
weapons. You start knocking. There's
going to be weapons. That's going to
That's going to be your wakeup call,
bro. That's going to be your [ __ ]
wakeup call. Do you know what? I don't
even have a bottle of piss to be I don't
even have a bottle to piss in to be fair.
Yeah, I don't even have a bottle to piss
in to be honest with you.
Yeah, no one cares, Joe. I can't wait to
leave you jealous people. I can't wait
today so I can get away from you jealous
people. Oh, I can't wait until Thursday.
These I can these jealous people will
leave me alone. I can't wait, bro.
I can't wait. I can get away from these
jealous ass gay people. And I'll say it
in the video as well. They're so jealous
of people. It's unbelievable. And
everyone says the same thing, bro.
Everyone says the same thing. It is such
jealousy on this community. Like, it
actually stinks. It actually is, bro.
Yeah, it's actually is. It actually stinks. Yeah,
it's as simple as that. It's such
jealousy. And you know it is as well.
You know it is. It's jealousy. Hardcore
jealousy. Anyone that's better than
them, better looking, admiral women,
it's such jealousy, bro. It's jealousy.
That's the worst thing about it. It's
jealousy with these fat [ __ ] these
ugly ass people on YouTube. It's the
truth. You know, I'll do a video about
this before I [ __ ] off on my um on my
other channel now, which is going to be
my main, bro. I'm going to talk all
about these people, bro. All about you
little jealous lowife people that ain't
got no life. I'm going to talk about it, bro. Yeah.
Yeah. It's the truth.
The jealousy, the pe the amount of times
it is such jealousy. I've never known
such jealousy in my life.
I've never known such jealous ass [ __ ]
in my life.
No, you're not fighting for a cause.
You're fighting to try to look good for
YouTube. You was the one mentioning my
name. No, that's not a cause. You was
the one mentioning my name.
You was the one mentioning my name,
[ __ ] That's the cause. Cuz you're a
jealous ass bastard. Yeah, which I've
explained on the video about four or
five times. Oh, trust me. Listen, Dr.
Echo, the day that you can show your
face, then I'll keep saying it's
jealousy. Same with Same with a lot of
you people until you come on here. Yeah.
and you show your faces, you're jealous
ass [ __ ] It's as simple as that. How
about that one? We're gonna do this now.
Yeah. Until you show what you've got and
you show your face, it's confirmed
jealousy. And if you do not prove
otherwise, then that's it, bro. There's
no there's there's nothing. Do you get it, bro?
Yeah. Exactly, bro. He's just trying to
show off for YouTube. He's just trying
to show off.
That's what Yeah, exactly, bro. This fat
[ __ ] is just trying to show off. Yeah,
he's just trying to show off our
attention. How many times has he done
this, bro? But he will get what he wants
today anyways. He'll get what he wants
today anyways. Jealous ass [ __ ] Yeah.
Yeah. Okay. I'm deluded, bro. Okay, I'm
deluded. I've already explained it
multiple times, bro. Okay, I'm deluded,
lad. Bro, he can be on any Guinness he
wants. I don't give a [ __ ] what Guinness
he's on. I'm completely sober.
Uh, I've already done it. More money
than you, better looking, better life.
I've already shown it, lad. I've already shown it. Yeah.
One second. Let's see what I got. I
think I got a nice glass downstairs to
splatter over his face. I have I have to
warm it up first.
I'd have to warm it up first.
Let me just splat I'm just going to
splatter over his face. Jen [ __ ] Yeah.
One second. Let me see.
>> Yeah. Got a lovely glass here.
There we go. Let's see if it's strong enough.
Yeah, that's going straight over his
face. So, as soon as I see soon as I see
London, bang him over his face with that
glass. He's going to stop being jealous
of people in 2026. I'm just going to
bang it over his face and he's coming
and he's coming on my property. This
[ __ ] fat [ __ ] is coming on my property.
Yeah. Do you understand? Trying to look
good for women on YouTube. He's going to
see what goes over his face today, bro.
I'm deadly serious, bro. I'm deadly
deadly serious. I'm not going nowhere,
bro. I am not going nowhere. Yeah,
simple. I'm just going to bang it over
his face. I'm warning you. I'm warning
you. I am warning you now. So, it's You
know what I'm saying? It's up to you. I
don't give a [ __ ] bro. You're just
being warned in it. Yeah.
No, I don't give a [ __ ]
I don't give a [ __ ] Leave people alone.
Jealous ass fat [ __ ] You're going to
learn to leave people alone. You come on
my door. You come on my property. I'm
recording it as well. And you see what will happen.
And you'll see what will happen.
You will see what will happen, bro.
Yeah. You will see what will happen. I
don't give a [ __ ] It's going over your
face. Simple as that.
Yeah. You want to try and let the big
man for YouTube, big man. Come on. Put
your money where your mouth is now. I'm
sober, bro. No drinking for me, bro. I'm
bad. I'm bad enough sober. No drinking
for me. No drinking for me. Yeah.
Lady's right here now. Do you want me to sell lady? Yeah.
[ __ ] stupid little show off. Little
[ __ ] Little [ __ ] [ __ ] trying to
look good for YouTube and then and then
you're going to try and call the shots.
No. No. No. No. No. No. No. No. No. No.
So that's a no to the camera then. Yeah.
That's a no to the camera.
That's a no to the camera then then. Yeah,
that's a no to the camera. Exactly.
That's what I [ __ ] thought, bro. Yeah. Yeah. Anyways,
you get me, lad? >> Yeah.
>> Yeah, bro. Like I said, I'm waiting,
bro. I'll be waiting all day, bro. I'll
be waiting all day.
Yeah. Jealous little [ __ ] [ __ ] on YouTube.
Jealous little [ __ ] on YouTube. Do you
want me to Do you want me Do you
actually want me to add J? All right,
bro. Do you want me to add jealousy in
the video as well when I make this
example video? Do you want me to do it?
Yeah. Oh, I [ __ ] have. I I [ __ ]
have, Lavong. I [ __ ] have, Lyong. Oh,
I [ __ ] well have.
I [ __ ] have you, Larry Mong.
I [ __ ] have you, [ __ ] Ly Mong. Yeah,
that's what we call you. We call you the Lavong
and people like you. That's what we call
you, bro. We call you the Lavry Mongs, lad.
Yeah, we call you We We call you We call
you the Lavongs, lad.
We call you the Lavs, bro. Yeah.
Yeah, you are all Mongs. Yeah, you
definitely are all Mongs. 100% you are.
Yeah. Well, Lav Lavy Mongs. Yeah, you ain't blocked.
You ain't blocked at all. Yeah. Batman. Batman.
Can you imagine, bro? Could you actually
imagine me drinking?
I'm I'm worse. I'm bad enough sober.
I can't believe the amount of jealous
ass people in this community.
This jealousy is unreal. They say that
they're not, but they can't show their
faces. They can't show anything they've
got. So, I mean, they can keep saying
that they're not jealous whilst talking
about people on YouTube every day, but
it's so obvious that they are jealous,
bro. It's so obvious that they're
[ __ ] that they are jealous. It's
obvious, bro. The amount of people that
I've got obsessed with me on this
community is unreal, bro.
It's like gay territory, bro.
It's actually like gay territory. Do you
get me, bro?
Yeah. It's narcissism. is jealousy.
Should have got off when I had the
chance, bro. Generally, they say,
"What's they got to be jealous of?" Bro,
most of these people don't even leave the house.
Most of these people don't even leave
the [ __ ] house, bro.
Yeah. They don't even leave the house, bro.
Most of them don't. They just sit online
all day doing talking rubbish. Yeah.
Yeah. Don't worry. We're ready today,
Grezy. Don't you worry, lad. We're ready, bro.
100% ready. I'm ready anyways. Ready as
I'll ever be, bro. I know exactly what I'm doing. Yep.
No drinking for me, bro. I'm bad enough
sober. I don't need to drink. Yeah, man.
There's not going to be no fight, bro. I
don't know why you think there's going
to be a fight.
It's Bro, Fruit King, he's trying to get
attention on YouTube. Do you not understand?
Do you not understand? It's all jealousy
and attention seeking. Do you not understand?
It's all jealousy and attention seeking.
That's all the vibe you get, bro. Why?
Why does that surprise you?
Does that really surprise you, bro?
Does that really surprise you with this
jealous [ __ ] [ __ ] hell. He's been on
it for years now, bro. Years and years and years.
So that should to be fair
that shouldn't surprise you.
He's he's traveling 150 miles to get his
head smashed in.
To get his [ __ ] head smashed in.
That's what he's going to be. That's
what he's doing. Freaking He's traveling
150 mi to get his head smashed in. Yeah.
Yeah. to get his [ __ ] jealous head smashed him.
No one called him out, bro. No one
called him out. He started on me, bro. I
sound scared. Would I be live on YouTube
if I'm scared? Would I be live on
YouTube if I was scared, bro? No, I
wouldn't. And no, he started it with me.
[ __ ] which you should know if you
watch all of these videos. He started on
me. Yeah. And I will finish it today.
It's as simple as that. Just like most
of you people. I'm for me. Probably cuz
I'm younger than jealous. probably cuz
I'm younger and better looking than you
people. I mean, there's a there's there
there's a reason for it. You come from
me. You mentioned my name. You
understand, [ __ ] Don't try and reverse
the psychology, bro. The video is still
there. Don't try to play the whole high
ground. Don't even try play that [ __ ]
Yeah. You started mentioning my name,
licking Launch Legs's ass, trying to
draw me out. So, you'll get what you
want today. Simple as that. Simple.
Turn about all you cool people. Well,
[ __ ] off, bro. You should watch the
whole thing before making judgments. You
might learn something. Yeah.
That's it, bro.
I'm scared, bro. I'm not scared of no one.
He's definitely definitely definitely
definitely jealous. Definitely. Just
like a lot of the people on here. And we
know what Timmy looks like as well. We
know what Timmy is. So, how can you even
say that? You can't call it speculating.
It doesn't matter if he's got someone
with him. I already know what I'm doing.
I already know what I'm doing anyways,
bro. Them glasses are going straight in
people's faces. So, I mean, I've already
got I've already got this planned. I'm
going to get them glasses and bam, bam,
bam, bam, bam. That's all I'm going to
do, bro. Yeah. If he comes, he knocks on
the door. That's what's happening, bro.
Yeah. No one cares, bro. He's a weak
little [ __ ] Cuz I've actually met
people for fights. Unlike you.
Yeah. Unlike you. Yeah. Unlike you.
Yeah. I've actually met people for
fights unlike you. Yeah. So, you know
what I'm saying? The guy's a weak and it
doesn't matter, bro. I mean, I'm not
fighting fair anyways, so I I I won't
know. The glass is going straight to his
head, bro. Straight to his head.
Trust me, it's going straight to his head, bro.
It's going straight to his head, bro. 100%.
Yeah, [snorts] man.
I don't give a [ __ ]
Yeah, I don't give a [ __ ] bro.
>> No, no, no, no. I'm scared of prison.
[ __ ] off, bro. You're scared of talking,
you little gay leads. [ __ ] Yorkshire
[ __ ] You're scared of [ __ ] talking.
You're scared of talking, you [ __ ]
little gay boy. You little gay [ __ ] with
a 300 pound phone. You poverty ridden
bastard. You poverty gay eyed moy
poverty Joe. Scared of talking. You're
scared of talking, bro. And you're
talking about people being scared of
prison. You can't even talk, you jealous
[ __ ] [ __ ] ugly ass hands. You can't
even talk, [ __ ] [ __ ] Yeah, you
can't even talk. Let's bring up the word
scared. You can't even talk. Talk. Half
of you people don't even come in the
panel and talk. [ __ ] little [ __ ] Yeah. [sighs]
Yeah. That's nice, bro.
That's nice, bro. Do you want a medal?
Do you want a medal? Do you want a si silver?
Do you want a silver, gold, or bronze
medal for that, bro? Yeah.
[ __ ] retards. [ __ ] retards.
Anyways, Joe, why are you scared of
talking on a panel anyways? Cuz you know
you're a [ __ ] You know you sound
like a [ __ ]
just like your boyfriend nonss. Yeah.
[ __ ] little weasel. You [ __ ]
jealous ass weasel. You're another one
that can't get me out of your head.
You're [ __ ] little jealous [ __ ] Bro,
you don't call the shots, bro. Like I
told you, you you do not call the shots.
You do not call the shots.
You do not call the shots. You're you
you have no you have no say in what
happens. Do you understand? What happens
happens. You don't have no say. You
don't have a say in the matter, bro. No
one's obsessed with that virgin. I'm not
the one with channels dedicated to
someone else like him. Lavy Mong. Dr.
Echo. Lavy Mong. I'm not the one with a
channel obsessed with someone else. Get
that through your head. Lavy Mong. You
[ __ ] you're another one who sucks
LJ's dick, little [ __ ] Which a lot of
people in this community do as well. I'm
not the one with a channel dedicated to
another man, lad. Never have been, never
will be. No, I fell asleep, bro.
Yeah, he's going to boot my dog out, is
he? Is he really? Is he really?
Is he really, bro? Yeah. I love that
energy. I love that talk, bro. Stop
calling me Pete, you [ __ ] little weirdo.
Yeah, stupid little jealous [ __ ] This
is all jealousy as well. Do you know
that, Cory? This is all jealousy.
This, Do you know the thing is this is
all jealousy. And it's been that way for
years, bro, with these people. That's
the maddest thing about these little
jealous [ __ ] who've got no life on
YouTube. Yeah. Yeah,
bro. Make it work. I'm going to be I'm
going to be I'm going to be putting in work, bro.
I'm going to be putting in work.
No, no one's getting anyone in trouble.
You're the one coming on people's doors
trying to show off. You want me to tell
Laney as well? You Hey, Grievy. Do you
want me to tell Laney?
All right, Grezy, do you want me to tell
Laney before it happens? Like, so no one
tries to [ __ ] stuff. I don't know if
she's watched the video. Do you want me
to tell Laney?
Do you want me to tell Laney?
just in case they tried to [ __ ] stir and
stuff. Yeah, I think I'm going to say
it, bro. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
No, I haven't. No. No. This guy is
trying to Yeah, I'm going to tell him actually. Anyways, yeah.
Mom, did you watch my video um earlier?
This stupid little fat [ __ ] on YouTube
is trying to show off trying to say he's
going to come on the door today. No
one's asked him. He has not This [ __ ]
has not left me alone, Mom. Over and
over, I told this [ __ ] "Keep my name
out of his mouth time and time again."
>> Yeah. No. Give me that. Have you got a
hammer? Have you got a hammer?
>> Yeah. You don't have a hammer? I'll just
use the glass then. You don't have a
hammer. I would just hammered his face
in. Yeah. And this [ __ ] will not leave
me alone. I've asked them multiple times
to leave me alone. They will not leave
me alone. These fat jealous these fat
jealous. No, no, no. I will answer the
door and I'm going to put a glass
through his head. That's what I'm going
to be doing. Putting a glass through his
head just in case they try and say to
you, "Oh, people's speaking trouble to
your door." Bro, they will not leave me
alone on this, bro. Mom, mom, I swear to
God, they will not leave me alone over
and over again with their jealousy. I
don't know how many times I've tried to
get away from these people. So, when you
see a glass in someone's head today, you
will know why. Yeah.
Yeah. It's jealousy. I've asked them,
"Leave me alone, you jealous fat cunt."
I've asked them multiple multiple times,
you know. I can show you all the videos.
>> They are jealous of me. They won't leave
me alone. You've seen all the videos.
Why are they so jealous of me? I've
tried to get away from these people,
bro. I have tried to get away from these
people how many times now? Moms,
>> how many? Oh, no. How many times have I
tried to get away from these jealous ass people?
>> And And they will not stop. So, bro,
just let them get in their face today.
Let them get in their face today. Yeah,
it's jealousy. It's so jealousy, Mom.
Over people they don't know. It's jeal I
know. I know. I know. Like, there were
actual things going on in the world,
actual life stresses that not someone
trying to look good for YouTube because
they're jealous of you. Do you get me?
Do you get me? So, no. Cuz what they're
going to try and do is they're going to
try to play them all high growth. Oh,
words brought trouble. Oh, no. No, no.
They started it. The video was right
there where they will not stop
mentioning my name. They will not stop
mentioning my name. It is such jealousy
and it's been this way for a long time
with these people. Yeah.
Just leave me alone. WHY WOULD THEY
leave me alone?
>> [ __ ] me.
>> They just will not leave me alone. I'm
telling you, Mom. They will not leave me
alone, bro. Do they want to [ __ ] me? Are
they jealous? They got They say these
people, they say they're not jealous,
bro, but they've got to be. They've got
to be, Mom.
You understand? They have got to be.
I'm going to put the glass next to that.
I'm going to get that glass put next to
the door and bang it over his face when
he knocks. You understand? He's going to
learn, bro. He's going to learn. He's
going to learn today.
You know what I mean? This is what they
do. They try to draw you out. They try
to draw you out. These people, it's
jealousy. That long tail is watching
every day. Another one that's jealous of
me that will not leave me alone. Another
jealous person that will not leave
people alone. You get it? I'm about to
make a new channel, bro.
and and and have a couple of people from
the sector to go on that. I want to get
away from these people. They will not
leave me alone. It's weird. It is weird.
You know, I said this a couple of days
ago. It's weird with these jealous people.
You know what I'm saying, bro? It's
every day with these jealous people.
It's weird, bro.
>> You understand? >> Yeah.
Yeah. 100%. 100%, bro. 100%. >> Yeah.
I said multiple times, stop mentioning
my name. Stop mentioning my name. Stop
mentioning my name. I don't know how
many times I have to ask this fat [ __ ]
to stop mentioning my name. Do you understand?
And now they try to reverse the
psychology. It's jealousy. You see, this
is what these narcissistic people do. Do
you not understand? This is what these
narcissistic people do.
Yeah. All cuz they're jealous of you.
All it's all jealousy, you know. It's
all jealousy with these people, you
know. Yeah. After today, I will after
when I make an example out this [ __ ] I
will do, bro.
Yeah. Yeah. And they're bringing it.
They're bringing it and they don't even
know you. They don't even know you. Do
you get it?
Yeah. Exactly. Because it's it's
jealousy. They want to It's all jealousy
with these people. You know these
people, bro. You know what these You
know these people, bro. Do you get it?
Yeah. Do you understand, lad?
They're jealous of people that they
don't even know. They say they're not,
bro. Listen, listen. Listen to me, bro.
How many times How many times do you go
on that Lord Jay's? How many people them
show their faces? How many people them
talk? Tell me, bro.
>> None of them. Why do you think that is?
Cuz they're fat and ugly bastards. They
ain't even got a life, bro. Do you understand?
Do you know what I mean? Jealousy every
time. PJ PJ. How many times do these
people mention my name, bro?
>> They're so It's like the deep down
jealousy, bro. Yeah.
>> Obsession and jealousy, bro. And they're
all like it as well. They all like it as
well, bro. Trust me, they are. Trust me,
they are, bro.
>> What they're trying to do is they're
trying to show off. So, you kick me out
of the house. That's what they're trying
to do. This is jealousy with these.
They're very bitter, bitter, jealous
people. Do you understand? What they're
trying to do, right? They're trying to
make it seem like I brought the trouble,
so you kick me out. Do you understand?
>> Yeah. It's jealousy. Do you not
understand with these little fat,
narcissistic, ugly ass people? You know,
and do you know what I've noticed with
these jealous people are? Every time you
start doing stuff with your life, they
start on you again. They do it again.
They try to draw you out again and again
and again. You understand, bro? Again
and again and again. That's what they want.
>> No, just leave me alone. Why is so hard
to leave someone alone? Leave someone
alone. Why is so hard? It's nothing.
I don't want to.
>> You understand?
What they're doing is they're trying to
reverse the psychology. So you chuck me
out. So they piss the names off. So I'm
homeless. They want me to feel like
them, alone, ugly. Do you understand
with these ugly people in this community?
That's what they do, bro. It's jealousy
and it's a horrible drug.
>> You know,
you get me, bro.
You get me? Every time. It's weird. It's
weird. You know, why do you think I
don't really go on that much? I wasn't
on there much day before yesterday, day
before that. Why do you think that? Why
do you think that? And when I was, I was
trying to get other people on the other
channel. Do you get me?
>> That's what they want. And they want the
neighbors to start complaining.
So they get me chucked out so I'm ugly
like them cuz they got no family. You
saw what they done over Christmas. These
jealous people, you saw what they done
will not leave people alone. How many
times have I said the same thing, bro?
You know, and it's not a simple trying
to wind people up on the internet. They
are obsessed. They're not even windups,
bro. They are obsessed. Do you get it? Yeah.
They're weirdos, bro. You got so many
things going on in the world. This,
that, this. The amount of [ __ ] I've had
to deal with the past couple of days.
And you got people jealous of you
showing up for YouTube. What the [ __ ]
Freaking, bro. Like he didn't even win
the first time.
Do you get me, bro?
Just jealousy, jealousy, jealousy. I
advise anyone there that's younger than
them, better looking than them, do not
go on this community. They will be
jealous of you. They won't leave you
alone. Like, it's been happening for
years with these people. Years and years
and years and years and years with them.
Do you get me? Cuz
you know what I do when I actually do
get this whole channel? I'm going to
move. I'm going to move out of this
house. Huh? I don't want any any of
these [ __ ] weirdos know where I live. Mom,
you get it?
You know what I mean, bro?
And that's it.
So you So if the neighbors work, you can
explain to them what I've just explained
to you. Yeah.
You can explain to them what I'm
explaining to you with this little
jealous [ __ ] on YouTube. You can watch
both the videos. You can literally
watch. They do not leave you alone. You
do not understand with this disabled
community. They don't leave you alone, bro.
Or maybe five maybe
same time yesterday perhaps. >> Yeah.
>> I thought maybe midnight to be fair,
bro. I thought midnight to be fair. You
know what I mean?
>> You understand, lad? Like that's what I
mean. So what they're trying to do is
they're trying to say that I've caused
it. So you you um you start chucking me
out to get it. It's jealousy with these
people. They got no family, no looks,
nothing going for themselves. A a
gambling addiction. This is why they go
for you constantly. Do you not see the
patterns with these people?
Do you not see the patterns with these people?
>> It is.
>> And they're the ones bringing the
trouble. No one's bringing it. They're
bringing it. This is what these
narcissists do. They're bringing it all
themselves cuz you're younger and you're
better looking than them. This is what
happens on this community. Yeah.
Do you get me?
>> I'm sick of these people, bro. Sick of them.
Yeah. Someone should show P uh show Ela
where PJ called it to the door. No, no,
no, no, no, no, no. Right, this [ __ ]
kept mentioning me time and time. Please
leave me alone. Stop mentioning my name
about your fat ugly mouth. I don't know
how many times I told him, stop
mentioning my name. I said, if you don't
me stop mentioning my name, I'm going to
message your family. Oh, I'm coming. I'm dead.
I'm dead. I'm coming.
I said, okay, I'll order you the taxi.
Come outside the door then because they
are starting on me. Yeah, me. They're
not going to reverse the psychology. Me.
Me me me me me me me me me me me me me
me me me me me me me me me me me me me
me me with these jealous ass people.
Don't worry, I've got that glass ready
anyway or when the [ __ ] comes. Yeah,
I've got a big glass ready for that [ __ ]
when he comes anyways. One second. Let
me put it out here, bro. Yeah, don't you
worry about that, bro. Got a big lovely glass
ready to go over the cunt's face. Let me
just let me just nip that in a little
hiding spot. Don't you worry about that. Yeah.
So don't be crying today when there's
blood everywhere and you can explain why
this people will not leave you alone in
this community. Yeah,
>> you can explain it. You can explain it.
>> You know what I'm saying?
How many times I've asked these people
to leave me alone, Mom? Huh? You understand?
So, he's going to be getting a glass
through his [ __ ] head today. Trust
me, the glass is right there. Leave it
exactly where it is. Leave it exactly
where it is, bro. cuz he's getting it
straight through his forehead. I'm not
[ __ ] about, bro. I'm not [ __ ]
about, bro. I swear to God, I'm not
[ __ ] about. But I just gave you the
heads up because you know what these
little narcissists do? They're
narcissistic. Very narcissistic. Do you
get it? Yeah. Very narcissistic.
Jealous ass people. Yeah.
You know what I'm saying, bro?
Very, very narcissistic.
That's what they are. They're very, very
narcissistic. No, it doesn't matter,
bro. Anyways, that glass is staying
exactly where it is, bro.
It's staying exactly where it is, bro.
Exactly where it is. Yeah,
it's staying exactly where it is. Yeah.
Anyways, I'll be back in a bit. Anyways,