videos and everything. I got the videos
and everything, bro. I literally just
come back now. Was I inside the house?
>> I swear to God, I was not inside that
house, bro. Tell him to come back now,
bro. He's He's going to make you go. No.
No. Tell this guy to come back, bro.
>> Doesn't matter. Tell this guy come back,
bro. Tell this guy. Let him go. Go
somewhere in Roford. Even just somewhere
in Ronford. Don't let him go, bro. I've
just come back in the cab. Yeah, I can
prove it. I've got all the videos and everything. Yeah.
Just tell the Tell him to come. I'll pay
for his taxi fair. I'll pay for his taxi
>> No, no, no. Tell him to come back, bro.
Was I in? I literally wasn't a boozer. I
just come back now, bro. I literally
just come back now. I've literally just
come back in on my mom's life, bro. On
my mom's life. I just come back, bro. On
my I swear to God, I wasn't here, but
I've just come back on the cab. I can
prove my bank statements and everything.
Yeah, I was in the boozer. I thought,
"Fuck it. I'll ignore this guy." Yeah,
whatever. Tell him to come back, bro.
Oh, I'll meet him anywhere. Tell him to
come back, bro. I'm here, bro. I'm
waiting. I'm waiting. I've just I've
just literally paid £20 for a taxi. Tell
him to come back. Tell him to come back.
Tell him to come back, bro. I'm here,
bro. He's here. Like, simple. And there
was a black taxi, bro. I opened the
door, bro. There was no one in there. I
opened the door. There was no one in
there, bro. Literally, look, I've just
come back, bro. I'm I'm pissed. I've
been drinking all day, bro. You think I
was in that house? No. No. I wasn't in
that house, bro. Listen, Timmy, wherever
you are now, I'll go to you, bro. If
you're in the town or whatever, I'll go
to you, bro. Wherever you are, even if
you don't want to come back, I'll go to
you right now, bro. It's not a problem.
It's not a problem. I've seen this come
back, bro. I'm pissed. I've been in the
Guinness. Come on. Come on, bro. Come
on. Come on, Timmy. Come on, Timmy. Come
on, bro. There was a black. There was a
cab, bro. I swear to God, I opened the
door, bro. I said, "Get out here." And I
open the cab. He was not there. Come on,
Timmy. Bro, come on. Come on. Come on.
Even wherever you are, bro. We know
you're not in Birmingham, but I'll come
to you wherever. Yeah. Simple, simple,
simple. Come on, bro. Come on. You went so fast.
I don't know, bro. Was I there? Was I
there? No, I wasn't. Was I there? No, I
wasn't. Was I there? No, I wasn't.
Timmy, come back. Come back. I'll pay
your taxi. I'll pay your taxi, bro.
Look, I got my card right on me now. Come back.
Yeah, I'll pay your taxi, bro. Come on.
Come, bro. It took me 10 minutes to
[ __ ] get here cuz you know what I was
doing, Greavves? I was trying to calm it
down to see like, oh, if this guy wants
to start, if he wants to start, if he
wants to stop. Yeah. If he wants to
start, if he wants to start, if he wants
to start, you get me? But I thought, oh,
let me try and calm it down. And as soon
as he starts Oh, no. [ __ ] that, bro. I
got the first cut back. No, no, no, no,
no. [ __ ] that. Call me started showing
me videos and that. Yeah, Timmy, where
are you, bro? Come on. Come on. Come on.
Come on. Yeah, I got owned, bro. He was
there for 5 seconds. I wasn't even
there. You [ __ ] stupid [ __ ] You
want me to show you the cab
transactions? You [ __ ] stupid [ __ ]
Timmy, come back. Come back. Come back,
Timmy. Come back. Come back. Yeah, it
doesn't matter if I knew he was coming.
He's full of [ __ ] Doesn't matter, bro.
Come back then. Simple. Come back then.
I'll pay your taxi. Come back. Or tell
me where you are. Simple. You either
tell me where you are.
Come, Timmy. Come. I will pay for your
taxi. I will transfer you £50, bro. It's
not a problem. It's not a problem, bro.
Just do not go back. Just do not go
back. Oh, doesn't know me another
chance. All right. Mom.
I told I told you I told you I was
coming. Why didn't you not tell him I
was coming, bro? I was in a black taxi.
I told you I was coming.
>> I didn't know that.
I text you saying that I was coming.
Yeah. To tell him to wait. You understand?
>> You understand? No. No. No. [ __ ] the
police. No. No. No. [ __ ] bro. [ __ ] all
that, bro. The [ __ ] all the police, bro.
Why you calling the police? [ __ ] this
little [ __ ] Well, I'll catch I'll
catch I'll go run for then. I'll go run
for then. It's as simple as that.
>> Yeah. Yeah, that's fine. I'll go run for
then. Yeah. Yeah. I'll [ __ ] make
noise wherever he is then. Tell him to
go live. Tell him to go live. Tell him
to go live in the pub. Whatever. I'll go
live in the pub. I'm gonna [ __ ] you. I'm
gonna [ __ ] him up, bro. Don't let Don't
let this guy go back to Birmingham, bro.
Whatever. Do not let this guy back go to
Birmingham, bro. Just tell me. Let me
know where he is. Yeah.
Yeah. Listen, bro. Listen. Do you know
what I'm trying to say? You know what
I'm saying, bro? Let Let me Tell him to
tell me where he [ __ ] is. Tell him to
tell me where he is. Do you know why I
was ignoring him? Do you know why I was
ignoring him? To diffuse the situation.
Not cuz anyone's scared of him. Not
because anyone's scared of I wasn't even
in the house.
I'm not in the house, bro. I'm not in
the house. I'm not in the house. I
wasn't in the house at all. Can you
swear I was not in the house. I've got
my coat on, bro. I've been drinking.
[ __ ] them, bro. Just leave a minute.
Yeah. Just let him come back, bro. We'll
have a conversation. Come. We'll have a
conversation. Come on. Come on. Come on.
Come on, bro. Come on. Come on. Don't go
back. Wherever you are, just let me
know. Don't come back.
You okay with Tell them to Okay. What
pub are you in then? Let me know what
pub you're in then. Simple as that.
Yeah, I ran away. I wasn't even in the
house, you [ __ ] [ __ ] Whatever,
bro. Listen. Listen. He's still here in
it. He's still He's still in the area.
Yeah, he's still in the area, bro. Come on,
bro. Listen, I'm plugging my phone here.
I'm going to I'm going to wait for
updates from this guy. I'll wait for
updates, bro. Yeah. I'll wait for
updates. It's as simple as that. Yeah.
Come on to me. I'll send you the money,
bro. I'm drunk myself. I'm drunk myself,
bro. I'll give you the money, brother.
I'll tell him to let me know where he
is. Yeah. Simple. Simple, bro. Stop
pussyfooting and tell me where you are,
lad. Tell me where you are. Just bro
listen listen just come back we'll have
a chat. Come come come come come come
come come come come come come come come
come come come back bro bro bro bro bro
bro bro bro bro bro bro bro bro bro bro
bro bro bro bro bro just come back yeah simple
I was ignoring you to get away from you
jealous people. Yeah the moon and stars
in Ridford. Is he actually Bro, tell him
to come on here and show me where he is
and I'm getting an Uber and I'm getting
an Uber. Tell him to come on here and
tell me where he is even if he's
charging his phone. Come on. Yeah, come
on. Come on. Come on.
Come on, bro. Simple. Come on then. Come
on then. Let me put a link up. Let me
put the link up.
One second. Let me put the link up, bro.
One sec. No, no, no. [ __ ] that, bro. I
got that I got in that first cab. I got
on that first cab, bro. I got in that
first cab as soon as I saw him coming. I
got in that first cab, bro. I was not
even in I've been drinking, bro. I was
drinking, bro. Look, I wasn't even
inside the house, bro. You know I don't
drink inside, bro. No, no, no, no. [ __ ]
that, bro. [ __ ] that, bro. One second.
One second. Let me Let me restart this,
bro. Let me restart this. One second. In 1 second.