I'm at the pub. Where are you, Timmy?
Come on, lad.
Miss you by a [ __ ] airbrush breath,
mate. Come on to me. Come on. Come on,
big man. Come on to me. I'm at the pub.
Come on. Just got to come right now,
lad. Don't hear no excuses. Come on.
Come on, you little [ __ ] Come on. I
don't want to hear no excuses now. You
little [ __ ] There's a lot of Timmy
El's look alikes here to be honest with
you, lad. There's a lot of Timmy
lookalikes here to be honest, lad. Yeah.
Yeah. You said you said you was in this
pub. I missed you by hair's breath, bro.
Come come. You're still in London. Come
on. Come on. Come on. You said you're
here. Come on. Bro, you was at the door
for 3 minutes. Do you want me to put the
video up, bro? You want me to put the
video up? Yeah. You want me to put the
video up, lad? Yeah. Where I was on my
way back home, bro. Please. I'm going to
do it, lad. I'm going to do it 100%.
Come on to me, you little [ __ ] Come
on. Come on. Come on. Come on. Come on.
Where is he? Where is he? Come on.
Where is this little [ __ ] Come on.
So many people that look like Timmy.
>> Where is he, bro?
He's a [ __ ] bro. Everyone told me to
come here. He's a [ __ ] bro. He is a
[ __ ] He is a [ __ ]
>> He is a [ __ ] You know, bro, he was at
the door for 3 minutes and I wasn't even
in the house. I'm going to put the video
back up anyways, lad. I'm going to put
the video back up anyways.
I'm going to put the video back up
anyways, lad. Not a problem. I'll put
the videos up, lad. I'll put the videos
up. I will put the videos up, bro.
I will put the videos up. Yeah, I was on
my way back home. You [ __ ] little
[ __ ] No one was even in the house, you [ __ ] Yeah,
[ __ ] little [ __ ] He is an absolute
[ __ ] lad. Why leave the house in the
I've already explained it. Anyways, bro,
like that's it, is it? He's still in
London. He knows where I am. Come. He
knows where I am. Come. He went there
for 3 minutes. I told I messaged my mom
legitimately to tell him to stay there.
I said, "Tell this guy to stay here."
And she didn't. She didn't. I said,
"Tell him to stay on that door." Would
do it. Literally would not do it. R
would not stay on that door.
>> Yeah, I'm good. >> Yeah.
>> Ask me to leave, please.
>> Why? No reason for that.
>> A bit disruptive. I'm not
>> I'm standing I'm standing here.
>> You're pacing up and down the phone. So,
>> yeah, I'm on the phone to someone. Yeah.
>> But it is a problem cuz they're telling
someone to go. >> Okay.
>> So, it is a problem then. So it is a
problem. Make up your mind then isn't
it? It's like if it's a is it a problem
or is it not a problem
>> at the minute? Yes. It's a problem.
>> Okay. And and it's an establishment
where where you drink, right? You're not
authority. You're not police. You can't
tell people what they can and can't do.
You know what I'm saying?
>> You can do. Yeah.
>> Yeah. But I don't have to. I'm saying
>> not technically. No, but I should bring
the police when I come.
>> So you being drunk in in an
establishment when there's alcohol
>> saying that you're drunk to Okay. So
what's the crime? Trespassing is not
it's a civil matter.
>> Yeah. So what they going to me for? Not
not reason. But you can't get nic trespassing.
>> Yes, you can.
>> No, you can't. It's a simple matter,
mate. I know the law, bro. Yeah. Yeah.
>> So, yeah. [ __ ] bro. [ __ ] idiot.
He's gone now. Yeah.
>> Everyone told me to go there and now
he's not here.
>> [ __ ] idiot. Owned again. Yeah. Shut
up, Joe. He didn't owe no one, bro. He
didn't owe no one. Anyways, I'm around
this area anyways. I'm still using their
Wi-Fi. Come on, lad. Come on.
Come on, lad. Where are you, you [ __ ]
[ __ ] You told me he was at this
pub. You literally told me he was at
this pub. You legitimately told me he
was at this pub.
Retards. Absolute retards. You literally
told me, bro, that they were that they
were at this pub.
That's what you literally told me. No,
it wasn't two hours ago, bro. It wasn't
even an hour ago, lad. And I'm still
here anyways. I'm still in the area. So what? Yeah,
he's a [ __ ] little [ __ ] He's an
absolute little [ __ ] [ __ ]
What a [ __ ] lad. What a [ __ ]
Absolute [ __ ] So many pimpers looking
like ST as well, bro.
Yeah, bro. I wasn't even in the house,
lad. I wasn't even in the house,
brother. I wasn't even in the house.
I'll show you the video when I was in
the cab. I'll show you the video when I
was in the taxi, lad. It's all good,
bro. Don't worry. It's all good, bro.
It's all good cuz I'll show the video
when I'm in the taxi.
Yeah. Why was your mom waiting for me
when you went home? I told my mom to
wait for him to stay there. He wouldn't
do it. He wouldn't do it. He wouldn't do
it. Yeah, of course I was watching these
live, bro. That's why I went back.
Simple. But where were you now? You're
nowhere now, are you? You're nowhere
now, are you? You're nowhere now, are
Yeah, he must have went just straight back, bro.
Yeah, he must have just went straight back, lad.
Yeah, it must have went straight back.
He was there for 3 minutes, bro. The guy
was legitimately there for 3 minutes.
He was literally there for 3 minutes,
bro. [ __ ] idiot, man. 3 minutes. Three minutes.
Jesus Christ, bro. 3 minutes. He was
there for 3 minutes. Where was he now anyways?
I don't care what you feel for. I don't
really care. I don't really give a [ __ ]
I've got the video to show I wasn't
there. So, yeah. I mean, I've got I've
got the video to show I wasn't there.
I've got the video to show that I wasn't there,
you know. Hey, bro. Echo, you're the m.
You people are the ugly munters. You are
the You are the online monties, mate.
You are the biggest monties of YouTube.
You are the biggest ugly monties of all
time, bro. Yeah. You are the biggest
mters of all time.
So, he's not here then? No.
So, he's not here then? No. So, he's not
here. Yeah. And then he ran away and he
won't meet me. Yeah. And he ran away and
he won't meet me. And he ran away and
now he won't meet me. Even though you
told me to come here. [ __ ] [ __ ] bro. [ __ ] retards.
[ __ ] absolute retards, lad. Absolute
[ __ ] bro. Yeah.
I wasn't in the house, you [ __ ] Yeah.
So, he's not coming, huh?
Waste of time. Waste of money. Yeah.
Yeah, he bullied my mom when I wasn't
there and he ran away after the but the
the neighbor told him to [ __ ] off. The
[ __ ] little fanny, bro. The little
fanny. The absolute little fanny, bro.
The absolute little fanny. Yeah. You
didn't win nothing, mate. Nothing.
He's not here.
My babies told him to [ __ ] off, bro. My
mom told me. Yeah.
[ __ ] stupid little [ __ ] [ __ ] bro.
So, he's not coming now. So, he's not
coming now. Yeah. You people are the
Monties. You're talking about
yourselves. You are the ugly monted
little virgins. Yeah, you are the
alltime YouTube virgins. I'll do videos
on you people anyways, but it's not it's
not it's not a problem. Yeah. Yeah, man.
Yeah. You people are the moners.
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. And didn't he say that
he was going to run in the door and kick
the door down? Yeah, bro. Yeah. Yeah.
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Okay. So, he's not
coming now then. Okay. Okay, bro. Okay.
Okay. Okay. So, he's not coming then.
Okay. There you go. Done. Done, lad.
Absolutely finished. Done.
So, it's finished then. Yeah.
Yeah. So, it's [ __ ] Yeah.
[ __ ] stupid palm, bro. Link.
>> There we go. Hello.
You let him bully. You're mad at the door.
>> There you go. Exactly. You're nowhere to
be seen, so shut up. Yeah. So shut up.
You told me to go to a pub. No one's
here. You told me to go to a pub, but no
one's here. No one's here. No one's
there. No one's here. No one's here. No
Bro, you ain't about that life, Timmy.
You're not about that life. I even
offered to pay for your taxi back as
well. You're a little fanny, bro. You're
a little fanny. You ain't about nothing.
Look how fast you ran back. your [ __ ]
little ugly little buddies. Anyways, I'm
gone anyways. I'll see you all later, [ __ ]