You know, I just wanted to say something. Yeah. One sec.
I think people fell asleep yesterday, so
they didn't get to hear it.
People fell asleep yesterday, so they
didn't get to hear it, bro.
Oh, [ __ ] One sec, bro.
Like about 1:00 in the morning. Yeah.
That's why people didn't hear it to be fair.
Oh, thank you. Yeah, man.
I was I was live at like 12:31
yesterday, so you wouldn't really hear it, bro.
But yeah, bro. [ __ ]
yeah, I was just basically saying, yeah,
that [ __ ] um
I was just basically saying that these
people already had their excuses already.
So, the best thing happened to be
honest. Yeah, cuz they were just going
to make excuses anyways. Simple.
What's going on, bro? Yeah, simple, bro.
Yeah, you should have went on L's
yesterday. Um, Ki, bro, they already had
their little excuses ready if Timmy got
battered or if Timmy got faced. They're
so predictable, bro. Hey, bro. You know
this this community, bro? Yeah. With
these with these [ __ ] disabled,
jealous ass people, they're so predictable.
They're so predictable, bro. Like, it's
it's you can you can just tell what
they're going to do. Mentally obsessed,
jealous people. I already I already knew
the excuse, bro. I swear. I already knew
the excuses that were going to come. I I
already knew it, bro. I already [ __ ]
knew it. No, I didn't. I just I just
read the comments, bro, to see what [ __ ]
that they were talking. And yeah, they
make they were going to come out. They
were going to make excuses anyways, bro.
That's what I'm saying. You can't
remember these little virgins on this community, bro.
You know, you should know this anyways,
bro. I I knew this anyways with the
money thing, the women thing. They talk
[ __ ] Even with the fight things, they
talk [ __ ] lad.
Yeah, bro. Basically. Yeah.
Proper, man. Proper.
Yeah. And then people, bro, you know,
you know the people that watch him, bro.
Yeah. They're the biggest [ __ ]
spastics ever. They're just sat there.
Yeah. Drinking 99 P kinds of beers, bro,
every day cuz they got nothing in life.
They're sat there with a 99p green piss
color piss kind of beer, bro. With no
life talking about other people. These
are the people you're dealing with on
this community, bro.
You know that cheap beer. They That's
what they do, bro. They sit in all day
drinking cheap shitty ass beer cuz they
got nothing in life. Nothing to live
for. No family, nothing. No money,
nothing. That's why they on here
chatting [ __ ] about people every day.
Bro, we got nothing to be jealous of
when these people are [ __ ] old men
with a 99 p can of beer in their hand,
bro. Yeah. Nothing to be jealous of.
Yeah. When was the last time you people
left your houses? [laughter]
Do you know what I'm saying, bro? I I
don't know, bro. He got bullied by the
neighbor, then he ran into the field.
You should have heard that on his live
stream. That neighbor called him a nons,
bro. And he ran into a field. [ __ ]
little [ __ ] Yeah,
he's a little [ __ ] bro. He's an
absolute [ __ ] bro. He really, really,
really, really is.
Yeah, he he ran into a The neighbor
called him a nons. He said, "Fuck off
your nons." Cuz he was trying to call me
a nons. And then he was making noise and
the neighbor told him to [ __ ] off your
nons. That's funny, bro. >> [gasps]
>> And he was still around the area when I
went live as well. He must have been
about a minute or two minutes away.
He's a [ __ ] [ __ ] He is He is a
[ __ ] absolute [ __ ] And guess
what, bro? No. No neighbors ever called
me a nons,
you know. No, I'm not doing anything,
Dustin. I'm not doing anything. I'm just
I'm just stating the fact. Rewind what I
said, bro. Rewind what I said. Hey, do
you know another thing, bro? Yeah.
Oh, do you know another thing, bro? Um,
what was it?
>> Yeah. So, no one on the No, no neighbors
ever called me a notch, bro.
Yeah, he come to my house when I wasn't
in, bro. And when I pulled up, he was
hiding in a field. Yeah, he was hiding
in a field. Yeah, he came to my house
when I was not there, which I've already
provided the evidence that I wasn't even
there. You told me to go to a pub. I
went to the pub. He wasn't there. So I
can mouth off all I want. And another
thing is Dusty, why does it matter
whether I was there, I wasn't there, my
mom won, my mom lost, I won, I lost.
These people is always going to come out
with excuses. Was Wasn't you on Lar's yesterday?
Bro, wasn't you Wasn't you on Lar's yesterday?
Didn't you see the excuses that they
were making when I was when I was
running up the road? Oh, well, you're
fast enough to go for Timmy, but not
London Taylor. That's exactly what they
would have said if I battered him.
That's exactly what they would have said
if I batted him, bro. You can't win with them.
You cannot win with them, bro. You
literally cannot win with them cuz even
if he got battered or whatever, they
would always make excuses.
Okay, bro. I'm not about it. Okay. Okay.
[ __ ] you. Say whatever you want, bro.
Say whatever you want. Say whatever you
want, bro. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. I'm not
about it. Okay. That's why I went
running up the road calling his name and
then when he was still in the area, he
wouldn't come back or tell me where he
was. I went into the city center, he was
gone. Where was he, bro? He didn't go to
Marley Bone in that short space of time, lad.
Yeah. And that's it, bro. Like, but
yeah, they would have still made excuses anyways.
They would have still made excuses anyways.
They would have made excuses anyways,
bro. They would have said that you're
hitting a [ __ ] and you won't meet
London Taylor. That's exactly what they
would say. Bet on it, bro. Bet money on
it. No, you can't win. That's what I'm
saying. You cannot win with them.
Regardless of the result,
regardless of the result, you will not
win with them. This is what I'm trying
to say to them. Regardless of what happens,
when he had already left, why he should
have already left? Cuz his taxi was
there. Why had he already left? If he
stayed there a reasonable amount amount
of time, he wouldn't have left. Anyways,
we'll just go around and around in
circles. Anyways, bro, I'm done with
this conversation. All I'm saying is
that you people are always going to make
excuses. Whether I won, whether I lost.
They're always going to make excuses,
bro. People like Joseph [ __ ] Farra
with his little 200lb poverty phone.
People like that's always going to make
excuses. I'm telling you that now. It
just so you know. Just so you know. I'm
telling you that now. I'm telling you
that now. Yes.
All right, Joe. No, no, no, no, no, no,
no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no,
no. I saw your comment. I'm glad my mom
done that. I'm glad my mom called the
police because you people was just going
to come out with excuses like you
already did. I'm glad. I'm proud of her
for not being proud for not being
scared. I'm proud of her, bro, because
all you was going to do is say you're
hitting a [ __ ] and and you're scared
of London Taylor. I'm happy cuz I knew
the excuses coming with you, you
povertyridden [ __ ] fake pension cub.
I'm glad that happened and and the
neighbor bullied him out the area. I'm
glad. I'm happy because I knew that
these excuses was going to come and come
and come and I was right. I was right.
So I'm glad the neighbor done my work
and bullied him out that area. I'm
[ __ ] glad. I'm I'm grow I'm proud cuz
all you're going to do is make excuses.
Joseph [ __ ] Ferrar. You're just going
to make excuses just like you do with
the virginity thing. Just like you do
with the money.
Yeah. I'm glad. I'm proud. I'm happy.
You know, I'm happy, bro. I'm [ __ ] happy, lad.
Uh, yes, they did. Bully him. The
neighbor [ __ ] him out the area. Oh,
yes, they did. Oh, yes, they did. Oh, it
was absolutely at all. Then the the
neighbor called him a nons and he went
running in the field, mate. He bunkked
the cab and everything. Oh yes he did at
all. Why do you think he ran out of the
area? Oh yes he did. The neighbor told
him to [ __ ] off you nons. Had he done
what he was told? Oh yes they did. Oh
yes they [ __ ] well did. Poverty eye
Joe with a 200lb phone. Oh yes they did.
And if and if and if he stayed live you
would have heard it as well.
Uh I did do something. I went back and
he ran away. I absolutely did do
something. I went back and he ran away.
Yes. Well I did. I went back and he ran
away. Anyways, end the conversation now
cuz you're just going to keep twisting
things. I ran up the road and he ran
away. He must have heard me calling him. Yeah, simple.
Simple. I absolutely did something. I
went running up the road and [ __ ]
made him go back to Birmingham. I
[ __ ] made him go back to Birmingham.
I went to the pub running up my [ __ ]
mouth. Oh, I [ __ ] did do something
just like the neighbor did. I [ __ ]
did do something. I [ __ ] ran that
[ __ ] out that [ __ ] close. I [ __ ]
absolutely did something. Oh, I
absolutely did something. But listen,
this is what I'm saying, Cory. Listen to
me, bro. Yeah. If you went on Lord Jay's
yesterday, you would have saw the
excuses that they were making. They knew
I did something. Otherwise, they
wouldn't say, "Oh, well, you forced off
to go back to Timmy." Why would they be
saying that, bro, if they didn't think
that if they think that this guy beat
me? Why would they think if this guy Why
would they say that if they thought this
guy beat me?
You understand what I'm trying to say?
They wouldn't say that if they thought
this guy beat me. You get what I'm
trying to say? They they know it deep
down in their heads. People like, "Bro,
listen. Listen. People with jealous
Joseph Raw, [ __ ] ugly [ __ ] You can't
win with them. You cannot win with these
ugly people. You should have known with
the virginity thing." Oh, don't say
that. He's got a girlfriend, bro. Don't
call him a burden. But then it's okay
for people to call me a virgin. You're
not going to win with biased people.
Trust me. The the result would have been
the same, bro. Trust me. I done what I
had to do and that's it. Simple. You're
not going to win with ugly obsessed
biased people like Joseph [ __ ] Ferrar
Dodge. You're not going to win with
them. You can show a million pound. You
can show you're better looking than
them. They still talk [ __ ]
You understand what I'm saying, lad?
Yeah. You can you cannot win with
jealous people. You're wasting your
time, lad. It's a w complete waste of time.
So, there's no point, bro. Simple as
that. They were always going to make
excuses. They were always going to make
excuses. They were always going to bring
up London Taylor. That was the That's
all they needed to do to bring up London
Taylor. They're so predictable, bro.
They're so predictable. And they can sit
there with their 99p green pound of beer
saying, "I'm not jealous." As a
middle-aged man, bro, as a middle-aged
man. Yeah. They can sit there and say,
"I'm not jealous. I'm not jealous."
whilst they're drinking a 99p [ __ ]
beer with no life, with nothing at their
age, bro. They can say that, bro.
You know what I'm saying? They can say
that all they want, bro. Whilst they're
sat on YouTube talking about men every
day cuz they got nothing. And we laugh
at them. People like you, Joe. Yeah. We
laugh at you. Ugly old men sat on
YouTube. I laugh at you. I get so many
giggles out of you. I get so many
giggles. It's unbelievable, bro.
I get so many giggles, shits and giggles
that I [ __ ] myself out of you people.
Guess what? I'm still here. And I'm
still here, bro. And I'm still here. You
can't get rid of the [ __ ] I get so
many shits and giggles out of you more
than you'll ever get out of me, bro. And
I love it, lad.
And I [ __ ] love it. And I absolutely
cuz we know deep down this is this is
this is jealousy. All right, Fire Stick.
You know, they already had this excuse
ready for this Timmy, by the way. Right.
This guy, these people already had
excuses. You know what they were trying
to say in LJ yesterday? Right. When I
went back for him, listen, listen,
listen, listen, listen, listen. When I
went back for him, bro, when I went back
for him, do you know the excuses that
they were making? Oh, uh, yeah, you're
fast enough to go for Tibby. You're fast
enough to go for Tibby, but you won't go
for, uh, LT. I told you, you can't win
with jealous people. I told you, bro.
You can't win with them. If I knocked
this [ __ ] out yesterday, the other day
and I bumped into him and he didn't run
out the close. Oh, you're going for the
weaker target, you're not going to win
with jealous people. Jealous people you
won't win with. Trust me. Biased jealous
people you will not win with, lad. Trust
me, bro. You should have saw it. I don't
know if you watched the channel, but
they they already had their little excuses.
They already had their little man-made
excuses made up. So, there's no point,
bro. They've already had their man-made
biased excuses already made up in the
factory. So there's no point, bro.
There's no point with them. Obviously,
people that hated Timmy would have loved
it. Obviously, people that hated Timmy
would have loved it. Yeah. Fire stick.
People that hated Timmy would have loved
it. But there would have been too many.
There's so many biased people. There's
so many biased people. What these people
want? Yeah. Do you know what these
people want on their Fire Stick? Yeah.
I'll tell you what these people want.
People like Joseph Ra, the absolute
[ __ ] with a 200 pound phone, the
little gay boy who can't talk. He wants
London Taylor to beat the [ __ ] out of me
because he can't do it. Because he can't
do it. He's scared of everyone. He will
never do anything. So what he wants, he
wants the perfect excuse. Trust me, I
know this stuff, bro. He wants the
perfect excuse along with noddlegs, the
jealous gay boys. They want someone to
do me and dirty cuz they can never do
it. That's what they want, bro. That and
it's never ever ever going to happen.
And we're going to keep continually
coming on here and we're going to keep
coming and laughing. It's as simple as
that because what they want is never
going to happen. What these people want
is never going to happen, lad.
But yeah, Fire Stick, they are biased,
lad. Yeah. And everyone saw I ran up the
like just ignore these jealous ass
middle-aged people. That's what I'm
doing now, bro. These middle-aged ugly
people, nothing to live for. They can
say what they want, bro. We all saw me
running up that road. We We all saw I
tried to meet him several times. So
that's it, bro. They can keep making
excuses, bro. 99% of the people in this
community are fat, ugly, irrelevant
people. You, your opinion doesn't even
matter. Your opinion does not even
matter, bro. Yeah. Most of you people
are fat and ugly ass people. No, nothing
to live for. I don't care who's who you
think's right or wrong. It's as simple
as that. 99% of you people are fat and
ugly. Nothing to live for in your lives.
I don't care what you think. I'll just
continue having laughs about you. I will
have shits and giggles and keep [ __ ]
myself laughing at you people every day.
How you're old, how you're butt, how
you're ugly. Like I laugh at you every
day. I'll do it every day, bro. I'll
come on here and laugh at you. Oh, Porky
Pete. Bro, you people are obese. I'm
much better looking than you people.
Much in shape than you people. You
people talk about yourselves with your
little 99p cans of beers cuz you're skinnier [laughter]
than you people, mate. All right,
listen. Like I've said multiple times,
Fire Stick, that there's a reason why
these people don't come on camera, and I
prove it every day. Cuz of their looks.
They're ashamed of what they look like.
Cuz of the bullying that they've got at
school, bro. They sat there with a 99
can be big cans of beer. [ __ ] ugly as
[ __ ] Straight on this app when they
wake up. They're jealous. They got
nothing to live for, bro. These people
haven't even got a mother. These people
don't even have a mum that loves them,
bro. They're just fat, ugly ass fat
people with no girlfriend, no mother, no
money, no life. And bro, do you know
what? They could take all of that back
if they just had a life, bro. But they
don't have a life. They're fat, ugly,
bitter, defeated people. It's the truth,
isn't it, lad? That's it. Fat, ugly,
bitter, defeated people. Oh, I liked
your comment as well, Fruit King. Nobody
was scared of that [ __ ] Yeah, nobody
was scared of that [ __ ] He should have
been in that taxi. That taxi was waiting
for him, bro. Yeah, that taxi was
waiting for him. Yeah, it's as simple as
that. Yeah. No one was scared of that
[ __ ] fat [ __ ] They told me to go to
the pub, bro. They told me to go back to
the pub. I went to the pub, bro. No one
was there. What the [ __ ]
Next to his cab, so he went. Tim said he
got a bus.
Yeah, but he must have been waiting for
the bus longer than 5 minutes. Buses
don't come one every two minutes. You
get what I'm saying, bro?
That's it, lad. My mom didn't get
abused. My mom laughed at him. Anyways,
you're not going to [ __ ] stir, bro.
You're not going to [ __ ] stir. You ugly
people. We know what you are now. You
ugly people sat on YouTube every day. We
know what you are, bro. You're not going
to bother me, bro. You can you can say
all of this stuff. You're not going to
make me feel like you ugly, hopeless, [snorts]
lifeless people feel. Don't even waste
your time, lad. Simple. Yeah.
Yeah. Simple as that. Uh, bro, you're
talking about yourselves anyways. You
get kicked now. Anyways, you little self-reflector. So, yeah.
You're a little self-reflector. And this
is what happens, Fire Stick, with these
people. Yeah. Anyone that's better
looking than them, they don't like.
Anyone that's got more than them, they
don't like, bro. This is what I mean.
This is how this community has always
been, bro. How do you think this whole
thing started, lad? anyone that's better
looking than them, they don't like it
because their lives are over. Unlike
unlike other communities, bro, where
they talk about religion, where they
talk about other stuff, um these people
are fat, ugly, and lifeless. They got
nothing in their lives. Nothing, bro.
Absolutely nothing in their lives. You
understand what I'm saying? Just an app
and a 99p can kind of be with their fat,
ugly selves every day. That's all they got, bro.
And that's that, bro. So, yeah. And and
they also had excuses coming. Bro, if
you if you went on large age, you would
have saw the excuses coming. Fruit King,
you should have saw the Did you see that
Joe F making excuses? He said, "Oh, I'm
fast enough to go back for Timmy, but
not LT." See, I told you, bro. I told
you what it was with these jealous
people. I told you, bro. That's what
they said. And then they even But then
apparently they're saying that I'm
better. But then apparently they're
saying that Timmy beat me. So which one
was it then? Did he beat me or did I go
for him? Make up your mind. So, they're
always going to have these excuses, bro.
They're always going to have these
excuses. They go for you cuz they're
jealous ass people. Yeah.
Yeah. Pretty much stick. Yeah. Not
everyone on here is Not everyone on here
is jealous. I'm not saying everyone on
here is jealous. Not everyone, bro. But
a lot of them are. And you can tell,
bro, by the way they act, the how biased
they are, the way they talk about
people. It's clear as day jealousy. When
these people are on their deathbed, bro,
I think they're going to well, they
would regret [ __ ] talking about me
all that time, bro. Do you get it?
Apparently your mom No, she wasn't at
all. My mom wasn't scared at all. O,
bro, fire stick. The neighbor The
neighbor told him to [ __ ] off. The
neighbor said, "Fuck off, you nons."
Yeah, exactly. No, exactly. You're
biased. This is what I'm saying. You
can't win with jealous people like you
and your gay boyfriend noddlegs. You
know, you and your gay boyfriend
noddlegs, you can't win. Even when you
get shown more money, you talk [ __ ]
Shown more women, you talk [ __ ] Beat at
the money, you talk [ __ ] That's why no
one waste their time on you poverty
weasels. You skit little weasels. That's
why no one waste their time on you
little weasels. You know, no one wastes
their time on weasels like you who make
up an excuse every time. So, you're
telling me that I need to fight Timmy?
Then you've got to Bro, just sort your
jealousy out, bro. Go get Listen, listen
listen listen, bro. Get your money up.
Get a better phone. Stop stalking men
online. Go suck off your boyfriend nlegs
and you'll be in a better place, lad.
You never stopped anyone's sublet money.
That's not going to work, lad. And this
is what I mean. This is every day with
these people. Fire stick. They got no
girlfriend. They got no life. They got
no money. And it proves it. Every time
you come on here, it proves that they
are jealous. And this is why I do this,
bro. Their jealousy proves it. They can
sit there and deny it all they want,
bro. Tell me one of these people that
come on cameras and talk about and show
themselves. They can't do it cuz they're
ugly, fat, ugly people. And they know
it, bro. You can call them it every day,
bro. They will not show themselves. They
will hide away. They will not show their
ugly faces with their 99p beer because
they're wasters in life, bro. Because
they're fat, ugly wasters with nothing
but an app. That's what they are, bro.
You get it, lads?
Ugly, [ __ ] hopeless. [ __ ] half of
them are probably virgins on this
community as well. Did anyone ever
mention that, bro? No.
So, yeah, lad.
And the whole you can tell, right? The
whole the whole this goes you know how
this whole thing comes about bro right
the whole you know how the whole thing
comes about like in the first place and
all of that stuff by stick you just know
it's jealousy you just know just the way
they act you just know it is jealousy
cuz these people are old ugly no woman
no nothing no life I shouldn't even say
no woman cuz that doesn't really mean
anything they haven't even got a life
bro I shouldn't even say they've got no
no that doesn't they have got literally
no life. They probably ain't left their
house in probably years, bro. Some of
these people, you understand? It's It's bad, bro.
They're going for you cuz they're
jealous. It's so obvious. Look how many
people in this community, right, or
organ stick, you got non legs. Non legs.
Nonss. Now, how many people brings up
non legs? How many people brings up
rice? How many people bring up Oh god,
bro. Like, there's so many people. Isn't
it funny how they go for the younger and
better looking? What's the odds of that,
bro? What What is the odds of that? That
they go for someone that's younger and
better looking than them? How they're
constantly on here trying to drag you
down to feel how they feel? Do you not
understand, bro? There's so many wrongs
on here, lad. And no one ever says
anything. Timmy sucks his dick. Joth
sucks his dick. I can't call him a
virgin without people defending him. So,
do you understand what I'm trying to say
to you, bro? I tried to call this guy a
virgin. Oh, don't say that about him.
He's got a girlfriend. Don't say that
about him. But, bro, you got people on
their channels. Do you not understand,
lad? Do you understand? Do you No, no,
no, no, no, no, no, no. You people go
for what? Why you do? It's cuz it's
jealousy, right? What people have said
years and years and years ago, it
doesn't matter. You do it because you
are jealous. I've got something in life
that you want. better looking, more
money than you. I don't have a 300 pound
phone like you cuz I'm not skinn like
you. You do it because you are jealous.
And the sooner you admit that to
yourself, the better you can get on with
your life, bro. You can get you can go
to cancel, right? Yeah. Oh, and that's
another thing, bro. Yeah. Oh, that's
another thing on his post. That's
another thing on his post. Yeah. People
were saying he was saying about how I
didn't meet this person. I didn't meet
that person. This might be Fire Stick
before Fire Stick's time. Bro, I went
around this guy's area putting up
posters and make him scared to leave the
house. I had this guy scared to leave
the house for [ __ ] god knows how many
days. He stopped going to events. He
went running to the police. I actually
put up hostess, bro, which is worse than
what anyone has ever done to me. And he
still comes online telling people who
shade it. No, no, he is he is the
ultimate coward. And I done it three
times. I tried to meet the [ __ ] three
two times, then the final time. Then the
final time. Then the final time, bro.
Um, then the final time. Um, I put up posters.
What the [ __ ] £1,000. But no data.
There is data. You just have to use
Wi-Fi and there's Wi-Fi everywhere. And
this and this phone right here. And
believe it or not, right, this phone,
this phone right here, this phone right
here is worth more than um Joseph Ra's
phone, even if it's even being blocked.
Yeah, it is. This phone is probably worth about
Yeah. A couple hundred pound,
you know. This phone is worth uh a
couple hundred pound now. It's been
blocked. It's still worth Yeah, it is.
It is. Go look up phones if you don't
believe me, bro. Yeah, it might be
blocked. But the thing is, bro, when you
go out in London, there's Wi-Fi
everywhere. There's Wi-Fi everywhere,
bro. There's Wi-Fi literally everywhere
in London. So, you you just Yeah. But
the phone's worth more than Joseph
[ __ ] Fra's phone. Even it being
blocked. If you don't believe me, look
it up. So a blocked phone is worth more
than your phone that ain't blocked. Yeah.
Oh, well, you can use it as a phone if
you got Wi-Fi. I just explained Oh, are
you a [ __ ] I've just explained it to
you. You can.
Yes, you [ __ ] did stop going places.
And this is what I'm trying to say. Yes,
you [ __ ] did stop going to [ __ ]
places cuz the post is you little
[ __ ] How many times did you go
running to the police? Oh, I'm not a
fighter. I'm not a fighter. And then you
come back on here talking about Timmy.
Bro, guess what? Do you know the
difference between me and Timmy? Let me
tell you the difference between the me
and Timmy situation, right? I was
probably less than a minute away from
bumping into that [ __ ] Yeah. I tried to
[ __ ] I tried to um I tried to um what
was the word? I tried to then meet him
after. I tried to I I was seconds away
from bumping into this [ __ ] I don't
know how I missed him, but I missed him.
You was never going to bump into me ever
in any of these events that you tried
calling people out on when I went to
your little virgin gay little India area
full of virgins like yourself. You would
have never bumped into me.
You would have never ever ever ever
bumped into me. Never. And you made sure
of that. You made sure you was never
ever ever ever ever going to bump into anyone.
You're the biggest coward on here. Like
you are you are the biggest biggest
coward on here. I don't think there's
anything worse than you, lad. Oh, would
have I really? Yeah. Oh, would have I
really? Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Oh,
really? Yeah. Would have.
Like that's what I'm saying, bro. You
need to sort your [ __ ] out, lad.
Yeah, you need to sort your [ __ ] out, bro.
No, he's worse. No, no, no. But he's
worse though, Dusty.
Yeah. And he he's worse. He's No, no,
he's actually worse, lad. Cuz what he
does, bro, is he actually he he doesn't
stop going on about people all day,
every day, all day, every day. But he
will never ever meet anyone. See, with
this Tibby thing, it just come about
past week with this London Taylor thing.
He comes on if I ever bring his name up.
But this guy, right, this is worse
because he's got a channel dedicated
to someone that he's never ever going to
meet. And he's been doing it for years,
every day for years, and he will never
meet anyone. He will never say anything
to anyone's face. So people like that,
bro, should just not People like that
shouldn't [ __ ] stir.
Uh he wasn't screaming in my mom's uh he
wasn't screaming in my mom's face
firstly. Uh and secondly, she wasn't scared. No. So yeah,
you will never meet anyone, lad. You
will never meet anyone. You will never
ever ever ever meet anyone. That little coward.
He will keep saying that he didn't stop
going to events. It's You can say all of
that stuff now. It's easy to say all of
that stuff now. You know, I can say that
stuff about people that's beat me. Oh,
well, you just smashed my windows. Oh,
well, you just broke into my house. I
Anyone can say that, bro. Here's the
thing. Here's the thing, Dusty. Anybody
can say that, right? Anyone can say that
stuff 3 years later. Anyone can act the
big man 3 years later. You understand?
Anyone could do that. But let's really
Let's put it to this. Right. Let's
really put it to this. Let's put it to
this. Right. Let's put it to this. You
come off of YouTube for two weeks.
Everyone saw you come off of YouTube for
two weeks when those posters were put
out. I'm not even deflecting. I'm just
stating you can come back on here two
three and three three and a half years
later and pretend it didn't affect you. Simple.
So yeah, I wouldn't have done anything differently. Simple. So
like I said, lad, you would have made
excuses anyways. You would have made
excuses. You would have tried to get
London Taylor involved. It's so obvious.
You people are predictable. You people
are predictable. You're so predictable.
Oh, you heard that? Yeah. Yeah. The
neighbor bullied him, bro. The neighbor
said, "Fuck off, you nons." And he went
running into a field. Yeah. Uh I don't
know which neighbor it was, but I know
it was a neighbor.
Yeah. My mom told me that anyway. So,
you must have heard it. Yeah.
He didn't make anyone. And like I said,
at the end of the day, it all comes to
jealousy with you people. That's why
there's there's there's no point
reacting to you. You already had your little excuses.
Okay. Okay. Okay. Put it this way.
Dusty, right? What do you think would
have happened? Right. Okay. Let me ask
you this question. Okay. W. So, what do
you reckon would have happened if I beat
the [ __ ] out of him on Well, come Wednesday.
What do you What do you think would have happened?
What do you think? I can tell you
exactly what would have happened.
I can tell you exactly what would have happened
in exactly the way it would have
happened as well. You can't win with
jealous ass people.
You can't win with jealous ass people, lad.
But I'd ask you, bro. I didn't, bro. He
started it. Oh, I'm not going over this
again, bro. I've already been over this
over and over and over again, lad. He He
is the one that started it.
Why exactly do you mean? So, you're
asking me So, you're asking me what do I
think you people are jealous of? Is that
what you're asking?
I've already explained it to you
multiple times. I'm already losing brain
cells already on this community, bro.
They're making me lose brain cells already.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no. They
would have said that you're hitting a
[ __ ] It would be my first W.
Wait, what? One second. Let me let me
let me scroll up. One second. One
second. One second. It would be my first W.
Uh, what are you people jealous of? The
fact I'm younger, better looking, got
more money, better life, more family,
more friends, and you people are sat on
YouTube, maybe there nothing to live
for. Does that answer your question?
Wait one second, Wister. That would have
been my That would have been my first W.
My very first W in six years. Really?
My first W. This is what I mean. You
can't win with these people. You can't
win with jealous people. That's what I'm
trying to say. You can't win with them.
You can't win with people that are
obsessed and jealous of you. You can't
win. And like I said, like I've said as
well, please, can you stop asking people
what are are you jealous of? Show your
faces. Stop hiding. I've asked this
multiple multiple times. If you people
are not jealous, show your faces. Show
us your looks. And then it will prove
what I'm saying. Show us your body, fat
and ugly. Bro, if you're not going to do
that, if you're not going to do that,
stop hiding and asking the same
question. You people are pissheads.
You're middle-aged. Yeah. I have got
more money than you. I've got more
friends than you. I've already had a
girlfriend and I've had more women than
you. And you people and what you people
are is [ __ ] pissads with no friends.
No girlfriends. Sat on YouTube every day
calling people that you don't know. Look
at you people. [ __ ] no friends with a
can of beer in your hand. No life.
Anxietyridden. You can't even leave your
house. No girlfriend. Look at you
people. Take a closer look to home.
Little spastics on YouTube, right?
That's been on here for 15 years
drinking your life away. You ugly fat
people. Look at yourselves and then look
at me, bro. Better looking than you will
ever be, bro. I've had many, many birds.
More birds than you, ugly boy. You've
never ever ever been, you've never had a
woman. Not any of you people in this
community has ever shown you with a
woman cuz you ain't got one. You're too
ugly. That's why you try to bring people
down, bro. That's what it is with you
little alcoholic people. You're fat,
ugly, you're lifeless. A dead person has
got more of a life than you, bro. Do you
know the people in this community? I
would say a dead a dead person in a
coffin has got more of a life than you.
[ __ ] little wastes with your little
can of beers. That's it, bro. That's it.
That's it, lad. You I reckon a dead
person has got a better life than these
people. That's how sad it is. That is
literally how sad it is. That is
literally literally how sad that they're
so lifeless that that the a dead
person's got more life than these little clowns.
Yeah, of course he is, Chico. Of course
he is, Chico. Of course he is. And
there's a lot of people like that on
here, bro. There's a lot of people like
that on here. There's a lot of people
like that on here, bro.
Yeah. Slug bullied my mom. Really? It
does make complete sense. It does make
complete sense. You people won't show your looks.
No, I'm No, no, no. I'm not angry. I'm
tell Okay. Okay. If I'm telling if if
you're telling the truth, then why won't
you come on here and show us what you look like?
Why won't you people show your looks? Is
it because you're ugly? See, I would I
would show myself. If I was if I was
talking down about people, I'd have no
problem showing my face. But you ugly
people just can't do that. You ugly
people just can't do that cuz it shows
what you're ashamed of. Your looks.
There's a reason. Listen. Listen.
Everything happens for a reason. Yeah. I
don't know if some people believe that
saying, but there's a reason why you
people sit on here every day for 15
years. There's a reason for it. Cuz
you're lifeless. You got nothing.
There's a reason. There's a reason why
you people sit on here talking about
people you don't know. Cuz you're bully
victims. You're utter bully victims.
Right. You probably You are probably
right. Yeah. Listen. Listen, bro. You
probably have been bullied so much in
your life. You've got PTSD, anxiety.
You're absolute bully victims. Like
everything happens for a reason. You
know that. And the fact that you're on
here every day talking about men, right?
Yeah. Everything. Every you understand lad? Yeah.
Yeah. Owned you, bro. You people own
yourselves. You little losers. Listen.
Listen. You people own yourselves.
Little [ __ ] sat online every day
talking about people you don't know.
Bro, life has been owned you. You're
your bro. Listen. You are actually right
society's rejects. You are society's
rejects. So you don't you don't even fit
into society, bro. You don't even fit
into society. your actual society's
rejects. That's how like irrelevant you
people actually are.
And yeah, that's it, lad. Anyways, yeah,
an intel that's had more women than you
and better than being a middle-aged
[ __ ] loser. I could never imagine
being so much of a loser. I have to come
on YouTube every day recording men and
stalking men that are better than me. I
could never be that loser. Some people
have middle-aged piss heads like you,
you ain't got no shame coming on here
talking about people every day. You got
No, you No, I'm not talking about
myself. I'm talking about you people.
And I'm going to put the link up as
well. So, if anyone wants to show their
face or come on here and talk, I'm more
than happy to be proven wrong, lad.
I'm more than happy to be proven wrong
with you jealous people.
You're 23. Oh, really? Come on. Come on
and show us what you look like.
We've done enough running and raving for
one day. Anyways, let's see what you
people look like. Come on. The link's
up. No one's banned.
Come on, let's see, bro. Let let let let
let let let let let let let let let let
let let let let let let let let the
truth come out today on this Friday
morning. Come on.
So with me, right, if I was on any kind
of community, right, if I was on any
kind of community,
someone trying to come in and not show
their face and try to porn bomb me, you
get kicked. See me me, right? If I was
on on a sector, right, talking about
people's this, people's that, people's
this, people's that, people's this,
people's that, people's this, people's
that, people's this, people's that,
people's this, people's that, people's
this, people's that. Okay, whatever.
Fine. Okay, so show what you look like.
I would show what I look like. I could
come on and at least talk to people. Why
can't any of you people do that? You've
been on this community for long enough
now. You've been on this community now
for long enough. So, can you just come
on here and show what you look like?
Come on, bro. Come on. I'm waiting for
someone to to to uh to get doxed um and
not be ugly as [ __ ] I'm waiting for
somebody to show their faces and not be
ugly as [ __ ] I am waiting on the day
and and you can't prove me wrong. So,
I'm right. I'm right about a lot of
these people in this community.
Not one of these people look normal. Not
one of these people have got like like I
said multiple times, I hate saying it
cuz it sounds horrible, bro. But if I
look like some of these people, I'd kill
myself. It's their lives are over. Timmy
over, LJ over,
launch legs over. A lot of these people,
their lives are over, bro. Their lives
are finished. It's over. Done. Done and dusted. Rice finished.
Like a lot of these people, their lives
are finished. So, is it any wonder they
go for you? It doesn't take Albert
Einstein from Germany to to know the
reasons why these people do what they do
every day. It is jealousy.
It is jealousy. It's a hard pill to
swallow. I know cuz it's such a horrible
word, but it generally generally is.
Think about it, Cory. Who's the one
who's the one that comes and and and
starts talking about who?
Who's the one that was trying? Who was
the one? Who's the one that comes on
here starting on who? You get me?
Who's the one that comes on here
starting on who, lad?
That's all I'm saying, lad. That's all I'm saying. Yeah. Hi.
>> Yeah. I'm just saying. I'm just saying.
Do you know Do you know was going to
make excuses as well? Um, you know,
never going to make excuses again. You
know what I'm saying? Yeah.
>> I know. They always make excuse. And he
got Isn't that true with the neighbor?
What did the neighbor tell him to? [ __ ]
off, you n he went running, didn't he?
>> Exactly. Yeah. >> Yeah.
>> Yeah. Cool. I just
>> Yeah. This is what happens. This is what
happens when you're better looking than
these people. This is where all of this
All of this comes from. All of this. And
do you know what, Mom? Yeah. I'll tell
you the truth. Listen. Right. Forget
forget the house for a second. Right.
I would go, Listen, get this house for a
second. Leave this house. I would go to
Birmingham today and knock him out. But
do you know what's going to happen? I
can tell you exactly what's going to
happen. Oh, you hit this bad dick and
the jealousy comes again. Do you? And I
know exactly what's going to happen.
>> I know. No, this is exactly what's happened.
>> Do you understand?
>> Yeah, I am leaving it. But I'm saying if
I went that is exactly what would
happen. Am I lying?
>> Yeah. It's as simple as that. Yeah.
It's exactly as that, bro. Yeah.
Yeah. It's exactly as that. This is what
happens when you're better looking than
these people. It's been going on for
years, bro. Years and years and years
and years and years with these people.
They don't like anyone better, bro. I
chuck the link up. Yeah. I chuck the
link up. I don't have the money to go. I
don't I don't have the money. Okay, bro.
Yeah. Okay. I don't have the money.
Yeah. Yeah. Cool. Yeah. That's funny,
bro. Yeah. Like, this is what I'm trying
to say, bro. Yeah.
Yeah. This is what happens when you're
better looking than these people. They
don't like it. This is what happened
when you got more money than these
little piss heads. They don't like it.
I don't have the money to go to Bro,
that's funny, bro. Don't make me laugh.
Please do not make me laugh. Please do
not make me laugh. You need They need to
get Bro, you need to get off that cheap
ass beer, bro. It's doing something to
your brain. It's actually that that beer
is doing something to your brain, lad.
That that 99 p beer is doing something
to your brain, lad.
Laney, throw him out. He allowed you to
be. Oh, bro. You're not going to try and
split a family up, bro, just cuz you've
got no family, bro. You're not going to
make people like you ugly [ __ ] with no
mom. You're not going to do that, bro.
You're not going to do that. You're not
going to make people feel like you, you
little piss head. You 99 P be little
waster. Take a day off of YouTube, bro.
Take a day off. Just one. Do you know
what? Right. Let me I'll give you this challenge, right?
Take one day off of YouTube. Just one
day. Just one whole day.
Just Just not a week, not two weeks.
Just take a Let's just see how you do
without a day of coming and self
projected. Let's see if it's Let's see
if it's too much for you. Come on.
You know, let's see if you can do it.
What? It's true though. Yeah, I will.
Yeah, I will. I'm just I'm just stating
facts. I'm not starting anything. I'm
just stating facts.
Yeah, it's true to be honest with you.
Yeah. Did you not go in Law J yesterday
and see the excuses that they were going
to make up even if you beat him up?
They've always got excuses. No, but I'm
saying cuz you I assumed you went on it.
You know, they're always going to have
excuses, isn't it?
Oh, by the way, I've got two SIM cards,
by the way. So, you um you calling is
not going to go through cuz uh yeah,
I've got two SIM cards, lad. So, you're
wasting your time and your credit
calling me, you [ __ ] stalking bastards.
And that's that in it, bro.
That's it, isn't it? [clears throat]
That's that is it. D.
See, unlike football, you can't predict
football. You see what happens in
football, you can't predict. With these
people, you can predict everything they
do, all the excuses that they have. Um,
Worster, you said that would have been
my first W yesterday. How How do you
work that one out, lad?
Yeah. Anyways, you're going to get a
kick now anyways, you little weasel.
Um, so you said that that was going to
be my first W yesterday.
My first W.
Still notice no one's comment on the
panel want to show what they look like.
Shocker. [snorts] Um, my first W.
My first W in six years. Really? And
that's why people don't waste their time
on people like you, lad.
You're new on here. Well, guess what?
You can suck my dick because you know
all the W's that I've took. Again,
biasistness. Again, this is exactly my
whole point. This is exactly my whole
point with you biased people. I don't
need to name you stuff that you already
know about. And this is what I mean,
bro. There's no point. Um,
there's no point with these people.
Like, there's literally no point with
these [ __ ] people. Um,
there's no point with these people, bro. is [ __ ]
being told to leave the internet. Yeah,
like I said, bro, I put the link up.
Come on in here and show your faces. If
you're not jealous, fair enough. I'm
wrong. I admit when I'm wrong, but you
people can never come on here and show
your faces or even talk. So, that's
because you're ugly as [ __ ] jealous.
You people are jealous. If you weren't
jealous, you wouldn't be on here hating
on people you don't know every day. Yeah. Yeah.
Yeah, bro. Okay. Okay. Just come on the
panel and just show what you look like.
It's as simple as that. It's not a hard
thing to do. You claim that you're not
jealous. I've explained to you how you
are jealous. Then you ask the same
question again. Okay. Bro, listen. You
got to understand, bro. This sounds
ridiculous. Um, Cory. Yeah. This sounds
really ridiculous. This sounds really
ridiculous. But listen to this, lad. I'm
better looking. I've got a I've got a
nice voice. I've got more family than
them. I've got more money than them.
I've got more of a life than them. I'm
more confident in everything, bro. It's
not even just looks, it's everything.
You are better than these people in
every single way. Bro, why do you think
when Timmy's done his balls in here,
he's trying to draw me out and no one
else? Why do you think he's trying to
draw me out of everyone else? Cuz he
knows I'm not the gambling gambling
addict. He knows I'm not the ugly one.
You understand, lad? You get what I'm
saying, bro? It comes to jealousy with
these people. You know, like I said, a
dead person's got more of a life than
these people in this community. A nice a
nice voice, better looks, had more
women, don't have a 300 pound phone like
you. Don't have to show fake pensions
like you. Like my life is way better
than yours. But again, that's not like
the thing is even if even even the thing
is Cory, even if you're deemed as as a
loser in society, you're better than
these people cuz these people are
rejects to society. Why do you think
they're on YouTube every day typing
away? Cuz they got nothing. They've got
nothing. Why do you think they're on
here every day typing about men being
this, other men being that? Because
they've got nothing to live for. They're
lifeless. They might as well be on a
coma. They might as well be in a coma,
these people. They might as well be in a
coma, bro. Like, they've got nothing in
life. They've got nothing to live for.
You know, it's not co anymore. It's not
co anymore. It's not a month of winter
anymore. It's been going on for years
with these people. Years and years and
years and years and years.
So, and what they do on here is [ __ ]
lad. It is the case. Why am I on it? To
talk to Grezy and to clear up your
excuses. To tell everybody the excuses.
To tell everybody the excuses that you
was going to make. Bro, who have I had a
W against? Oh, bro. You already know all
the W's I've had. I'm not listing it again. Right.
If I'm projecting, bro, like I said,
come on camera and show your faces.
I'll put the link out there. If I'm
projecting, okay, I'm projecting. I
don't mind being proven wrong.
That's fine, bro. I don't mind being
proven wrong. That's good, bro. I don't
mind being proven wrong. Come on here
and show your face.
Come on here and show yourselves then.
If I'm projecting, show us who you are.
Show us what you got. Okay, fine. I'm
giving you the chance, but you can't do
that. You continuously hide. Then
there'll be about 50 60 people watching
law J's will not join a panel will not
show their faces will not talk in a
panel. I think that pretty much proves my point.
Like their anxiety is so bad, bro. Yeah,
their anxiety is so bad that they can't
even talk on a [ __ ] panel.
Well, there the links work. There you
go. Like that's it, bro. Like just come
show us what you look like, bro. Show us
what you got. Show us all these things
that you've got. You know, it's about time now.
That's that, bro.
And would I would I kill myself over
looks? Not really. If I was average or
slightly below average, no. Even if I
was ginger. Okay, let me let me put like
this. Oh, you you made a good point
about the looks. If I was ginger,
if I was ginger and I wasn't ugly, I
wouldn't kill myself. If I was short, I
wouldn't kill myself. I wouldn't kill
myself if I was a ginger and I looked
normal. If I look like [ __ ] Timmy
Eldridge and [ __ ] Lord J, I would
kill myself. Yeah, that's the that's the
that's the difference. That's the big
difference, bro. That is the big difference.
That is the big big big big big big difference.
So, no, if I was if I was just normal
looking in any way, what these people
are not, I wouldn't kill myself.
That's it, lad.
I'm not obsessed with looks. I'm just
stating that these people are so ugly.
You don't even see people like that in public. So, yeah.
You see what I'm saying? You don't see
how hard can it be doing this, Cory? You
don't see unworthy clot doing this, lad.
You don't see any of these people doing
any stuff like this. Do you not find
that a bit weird?
You don't see Jake the Snake doing this.
Why is that, bro? Cuz these people are
not jealous of anything. They don't have
to be jealous of anything.
The only people that do this are people
that are below you. These are the only
people that do this, lad.
If I look like Timmy, I would kill
myself. Yes. And I'm sure a lot of
people would. Well, I would want to be
alive looking like Timmy.
Being a [ __ ] like Timmy, looking like
Timmy. No, bro. [ __ ] that. And it's not
even that. There's so many issues that
he has as well. Yes. If I was him in
these situation, I would kill him. I
would kill myself. [clears throat]
And L J and and and and the thing with L
J as well, I couldn't even I wouldn't
even be able to take my glasses off.
Imagine L J when he takes his glasses
off. Why does none of these people look
normal on this community?
Why does none of these people in this
community look normal?
community look normal? I find that to be
I find that to be very suspect. You get me?
Don't know. They don't care. Yeah.
It should be the other way around if you
wasn't jealous, lad. They are jealous.
They're jealous as [ __ ] lad. [snorts]
They can't go out and approach women.
Doesn't matter if they if the women
don't meet them. They can't go out and
do what I do.
I'm oddlooking, bro. That's self-reflecting, bro.
I'm literally the best looking on this
community. Better looking than you.
Better looking than launch legs. Better
looking than LJ. You want to talk about
people being oddlooking? Okay, I can
tell you one. Have you seen your
boyfriend, Lord J?
Have Have you seen your boyfriend, Lord
J? You want to talk about oddlooking?
The word oddlooking.
Someone that's got four eyes. [ __ ]
someone that's half blind with a ginger
beard who's bold. Yeah, I think you'll
find that's oddlooking, lad. Not me. Not
somebody that's got brown hair and a
beard. No. No. I think you'll find your
boyfriend Lord Jay is the is the
weirdest looking fellow on here along
with Timmy. Yeah, that's nice. Okay,
that's fine. Joe, why don't you show us
what you look like? That's nice, bro.
That's cute. But guess what? I bet
you're uglier. I bet you look worse than me. [laughter]
And this is where you'd always win with
these people because you can you can you
can start this argument, right? But
you're not going to make me feel like
you. I know I'm better looking than you.
I've had more women than you. And we
know that even if you do have a misses,
bro, and even if you do have a misses,
bro, I bet you she's fat and ugly. It
proves my point. The fact I've had more
women than you, your virgin boyfriends
legs, it proves that I'm better looking.
You can come on here, write your
comments whilst being uglier than me.
You can say what you want. I don't have
a massive nose, mate. My nose is
completely normal. But I know one thing.
You will never show your face. And
there's a reason for that. I know that
you will never show your face, you
skinny, crackhead looking bastard. And
there's a reason for that. I know that
much that you could never show your face
and tell me how you're better looking
than me. I can do it to you, but you
can't do it to me. I know that much that
an ugly northern skinny [ __ ] with an
ugly face like you can't show your face
and say nothing. You probably look like
rice. I would bet my money on to be
honest with you. If I was to put money
on it, I would say this [ __ ] looks like rice,
you know, ugly, like non-slegs. Bro,
there's nothing wrong with my nose. I'm
better looking than you and all of the
people in this community. Go by the
experiences. Had more women than you
people, more friends than you people. I
am way better looking than you people
will ever be. And that's part of your
jealousy. This is part of your jealousy.
If I'm lying, bro. Embarrass me right
now. Embarrass me so badly that I have
to end this live stream. I'll put the
link up again. Show us your perfect
good-looking face that's better than me.
You can't do it, bro. You can't do it.
And that's where you always beat these
people. It's what Singings always used
to say as well.
I've got my teeth, lad. I've got my
hair. I've got my beard. You people are
[ __ ] stinking, bro. On this
community. You people are stinking, lad.
I'll show myself right now if you want.
Should be fine. I need to go to the
barbers to be honest. Now look, bro.
What's your excuse?
One second, bro. Now you're trying to
change the subject. One second, bro. I
need to get myself a [ __ ] haircut,
bro. I'm starting to look a bit like Bin Laden.
I need a little trim. One second. So,
you're saying all of this, right?
Oh, [ __ ] So, I need to wipe that lens a bit.
Right. [clears throat] So, you're saying
all of this [ __ ]
I'm showing my face. You can't show your
faces. I'll be the first one to show my
face. Here's my face. Nothing wrong with
my nose. Nose is not big at all. So, and
I'm and I'm not shaved, bro. I need to
go to the barbers and everything. So,
I'm I'm giving you I'm giving you like
chances to show that you're better
looking than me.
Come on. Haven't been to the barbers in
almost [ __ ] weeks. Probably almost a
month. No, bro. Like, you've got you've
got one over me. You've literally got
one over me. You got all this money. You
look after yourself. Okay, come on here
and show what you look like.
You know, nothing wrong with my nose,
bro. There's nothing wrong with my nose
at all. My nose is not big. My beard is
not patchy. I'm definitely not balding.
Yeah, my hairline might not be as fresh
as it used to be cuz [ __ ] that's what
happens as you get older and whatever.
But look, there we go. So, if I can show
myself like this, why can't you people show yourselves?
Why can't you people show yourselves?
>> Well, that's me
back years old. Back to
>> Exactly what I thought, bro. Exactly
what I thought. Exactly what I thought,
bro. Yeah. Exactly. Listen, Joe, come on
the panel and show us what you look
like, bro. Stop. Stop talking [ __ ] I'm
showing my face. This person showing
their face. Come on up. What's your problem?
Come on. Let's go.
What are you waiting for, bro? What are
you waiting for? Come on. Yeah.
Come on. I let anyone up.
What you'll find Joseph for all lad is
I'm better looking than you. I'm better
looking than your boyfriend nons legs
and I'm better looking than LJ. No
matter what you try to say I look like
and no no no no no like you I'm better
looking than you bro. It's as simple as
that. You don't show your faces for a
reason. And you and it's a smart move.
You not showing your faces. You know
it's a smart move as well.
You know it's a smart move as well
because you're ugly as [ __ ] So you keep
that you keep that to yourselves. You
keep your ugliness to yourselves. You
hide it away. You understand, bro? You understand? Yeah.
Look, I'll even show you me wearing a
pink t-shirt if you want. See what you
little losers. See, the thing is, right,
with people like you, Joe, you
non-slegs, you pair of ugly losers,
right? Is you talk [ __ ] about people,
right? One second. These are spraying my
armpits. We talk [ __ ] about the way
people look. And your whole goal, right,
and with you people in this community,
right, your whole goal, right, is to
basically make people feel insecure. Or
a better word, make people feel like you.
Oh, [ __ ] Make people feel like you,
lad. Yeah. Yeah. But guess what? The
only people that are not showing their
faces are you people.
The only people that not are not showing
this is my lovely little t-shirt. The
only people that not are not showing
their faces are you people.
So it actually backfires on you because
you're trying to make people feel
insecure whilst you can't show your
faces. There you go. Look, I'm not
covering up my nose. I'm not covering up
my whole face because I'm not insecure
and the [ __ ] that you say. The [ __ ] that
you say. No. Like I said, bro, you come
come in here. Show your face. Show us
what you look like. Prove to me that
you're not ugly and I'll show you
anything you want. I'll show you my dick
if you want. I'll show you my dick if
you want. Yeah, bro. I'll show you my
dick if you want. I'll show you my
stomach, my dick, my ass, my [ __ ] Just
come on here and show your face. Simple.
Yo, another one. Red start up. You can
come in as well. Let me put the link up.
Sorry, I know there's sometimes there's
there's problems with these links. I'll
put the link up. Anyone's welcome to
join and show their faces. It shouldn't
be that hard.
It shouldn't be that hard to come on
here and show your faces. You got a lot
to talk about other people. And look, I
I need to go to the barbers, bro.
What are you waiting for, Joseph? What
are you waiting for? Come on, show us
your face. Show us what you look like.
Red Star, Joseph Ferrar. [ __ ]
just show your faces, bro. It's not hard
to show your face. No one gets doxed.
Bomb never got docked. What are you waiting for?
What are you waiting for, lad?
What are you waiting for? Come on the
camera. Okay, join the hangouts, right,
and talk and and I'll show you my
stomach. How about that one? I've showed
you my face. I've showed you me wearing
a pink t-shirt. I'm I'm trying to help
you. I'm trying to build your confidence
up. You know what I'm saying?
You can never do it, bro. And that's
where I'll always win with you people.
This is where you always lose. This is
where you always come into a dead end
because you can talk the talk but you
can't walk the walk. You understand? You
can talk about the way people look and
ret but you hide. You literally hide. I
need a bra, bro. You can say what you
want, bro. You're a skinny little
crackhead looking bastard. I need a bra.
Do I really? Nah, bro. I think what
you'll find is that that is muscles. So,
you're not coming then. Yeah.
So, you're not coming. Oh, also Kobe add
J in there as well. You need to add L J
on there as well.
You also need to add L J into that as well, lad.
To be fair, I do need to go to the gym.
But bro, listen, I'm not I'm not like
[ __ ] I I sound like an insane launch.
Really? That's nice, bro. You must be
talking about yourself. Takes one to no
one, lad. Takes one to no one. Yeah,
that's fine, bro. Okay. Okay. Oh my god,
bro. Listen, we've heard your words
right over and over again now. You're
this, you're that, you're this, you're
that, whatever. Okay. Okay. So, come on
here and show what you look like then.
Come on here and show what you look
like. If you're not even better looking
than a [ __ ] someone with a terrorist
beard and [ __ ] their hair growing by
their ears, then I don't really think
you can talk about people. Really, to be
honest, in my opinion, if you if you're
not even better looking than this, a mug
like this right now, then bro, like
you're definitely not going to be better
looking than me when I had my haircut.
Yeah, he's the worst, Dusty. He's the
worst. He is actually the worst.
Yeah. Not showing my full body. I
thought you said showing people's full
body was gay. Bro, stop trying to twist
[ __ ] Just come on here and show your
face. What are you scared of? You are
the insecure ones. Yeah. Nothing wrong
with my nose. Nothing wrong with my
beard. Nothing wrong with my face. You
people are the ones that are insecure
about your looks. That's why you talk
about looks all the time cuz you are the
ones that are insecure. Think about like
this, bro. Yeah. You you you people in
this community have been coming on here
now for 4 years, right? Four to 5 years,
maybe maybe calling people this, calling
people that. I'm still showing my face.
I'm not hiding up any part of my body.
You people are the ones that don't show
your faces. So, it proves it proves I'm right, bro.
You don't show your faces for a [ __ ]
reason. And there's 95% of you people
that don't do it. There's 95% of you
people that don't talk on here. What the
[ __ ] you know,
and you know it's because of your looks.
You're ashamed of what you look like.
Just admit it, lad. It's fine. You know,
that's what I mean. Like, it's not even
like what you people are. It's not even
what you people are. It's what you do
and you try to make other people feel
the way that you do. That's what it is.
You try to make people feel the way that
you do. That's what it is, lad. With
with you with you people, lad.
And you're not coming in large, you get
kicked. Simp. This is only for people
that want to show their faces. Why have
you gone quiet now, bro? Like, if you
want to be a waster, then be a waster,
bro. I'm not going to have an opinion on
you being a waster. If you want to drink
your little 99 ps of beer every day cuz
you're skin, that's fine, bro. I won't I
won't bother with you. But then it's
when you get cheeky and then you start
thinking you can talk about other
people, then that's where the cheat
comes into it. You're very very cheeky
because then you start talking about
people, right? Then you start talking
about people that are better than you.
This is what I don't understand. This is
where the thing doesn't make no sense.
Own your situation, bro. Own the
situation that you're in.
Don't start trying to bring other people
down to your level, lad, cuz that's not
going to help your [ __ ] situation, is it?
You can call me all the names under the
sun today, bro. I'd still go out and I'd
still be able to to to meet women today.
No matter what you'd say, you can put
all sorts of [ __ ] in my head. I won't be
scared to show my face. I wouldn't
question my looks. You don't believe me
when I tell you that years and years and
years and years and years and years and
years and years and years that you
people, right, you don't believe me when
I told you for years and years and
years, you people never made me feel
windy about my looks.
You never made me ever feel insecure
about my looks. Ever. You never ever
ever did. You might like to talk over
people, but look, like I said,
show my face. Show my face. Show my
face. Show my face. Show my face. See,
you can't. You people can't do it.
You people can't do it, bro. You people
can't show yourselves. You people are
bored. You people are middle-aged. You
people most of you people probably look
like L J. It's self- projecting.
Absolutely self-p projecting, bro.
That's why you can't show yourselves.
And you know it. That's exactly why you
people can't show yourselves like I can.
Yeah. Simple. Why don't you come in the
panel and show your face, Ryan?
Why don't you come on here and show your face, Ryan?
Joe, we're still waiting for you to join the panel.
Everyone's waiting for you to join the
panel and show us what a good-look man looks like.
Yeah, that's what I thought, lad. That's
exactly what I thought, lad.
It's clear I'm receding. Oh, really,
bro? That's nice. Why don't you come
online and show show us what you you
know the fact, right? You know another
thing, right? Yeah. Let me just let me
just make this clear. The more you keep
talking about me, the more it shows
jealousy. the more it shows that you're
trying to deflect from your ugliness.
The more you go on about me, right, the
more you don't show your faces, it shows
that you people are jealous and ugly.
The more you do it, the more it proves
it slowly but surely. You people, I've
gave you the chance to come on here and
show your faces, but you can't do it.
You change the subject and you can't do
it. Why is that?
Simple, lad. Because you people want
people to make people feel like you,
life's rejects, virgins, ugly, fat, and
it's not going to work, bro. You what
you're trying to do is not going to work.
It's really just not going to work, bro.
It's really, really just not going to
work. Do you not understand? Like when
people [ __ ] tell you this [ __ ]
with your little 99p cans of beer in
your [ __ ] hands drinking because
you're [ __ ] skinn as [ __ ] Sat on
this. Why else are you sat on here every
day? all day, every day. Come on, tell
us, bro. Get it in your head, bro. As
much as you want to convince yourself
that I'm bored like you people, I'm
never I will never be bored like you
people already are. You can keep telling
people that they're receding, it's self
projection. See, what is with you
people? You love to have hair. You would
love to have hair, but you don't have
hair. And that's another jealousy that
comes into it because you people are
bored. Already bored. Not balding,
you're bored. So that's why you try to
tell people that, oh um they got no hair
because you people have got no hair. You
people are ugly. You people are fat. You
people ain't got no confidence. It's the
truth. Is it? Tell me I'm lying, bro.
Furthermore, come on the panel and tell
me I'm lying. You know I'm right, lad.
You know I'm right. You're just
alcoholic skin little wasters trying to
bully people, but you've already been
bullied all your lives. That's all you
people are. That's literally all you
people are on this community. That's all
you people are in this community, lad.
Yeah. Like I said, okay, come on the
panel and show us what you look like.
Come on the panel and show us what you
look like. If you're not scared, join
the link. The link's there. Come on. The
link's there, lad.
The link's there, lad.
The link's there.
You know what I'm saying? The link's
[ __ ] there. So, yeah.
Yeah. Let's see what you look like.
Let's see your face. [snorts] Anyways,
I'm not going to answer any of your
questions until you join the link and
you put your cameras on. That's it. I'm
not answering any of your questions. If
you if you want to ask me a question,
you can come to the panel and ask me a
question. If you want a question,
you can you can you can come on here and
ask me the question on the panel before
even showing your face. I'll put the
link up again. This is the fifth time
I've put the link up. Right,
this is the fifth time now I've put the link up.
There we go.
There you go. That's the fifth time. If
you've got any questions to ask me, bro,
you can join the panel.
Like I [snorts] said, bro, the link's
right there. If you've got anything to
say, you can join a panel. [snorts]
You can join a panel, lad.
There you go.
You're biging yourself up. You're trying
to big yourself up. Okay, come on the
panel then, bro. It's not hard.
You know what I'm saying? It's not hard to do.
Yeah. Yeah. Like are you going to join
the link or you just going to keep typing boring?
Are you going to join the link or you
just going to keep typing, lad?
>> Yeah. Are you going to join the link?
You got 10 seconds or I'm blocking you,
lad. You know, when I do a video about
you people, this is all another thing
I'm going to bring up. The amount of
times you put you get the link up and
you will not show your faces, which pro
which proves my point about you being
[ __ ] ugly as [ __ ] on this community.
1 2 3 4 5 6 7 8
Come on. Nine
and you're banned. See you later.
You're banned. See you later, lad.
Simple as that. You had [ __ ] god
knows how many chances to join a link
and you get banned. Simple, bro. It's
not hard. You just get kicked.
You get kicked.
Not one of you could have joined a panel
and show your faces. That is that is
insane, bro. Not one of you people on
this on this community that calls other
people can actually back up what you
look like. That is a madness to me, bro.
To me, that's so mad.
That is so mad to me, bro.
It just proves that you are jealous ass
[ __ ] on this community, bro. It just
proves it even more.
Proper weirdos on this community, lad.
as I'm going anyway since no one's
joining the panel. So yeah, in a bit. Peace.