Why the [ __ ] don't this guy go warm, bro?
[ __ ] hell, lad.
Steen, now we should be on round about
this time, lad.
I don't know whether to put Thursday on
this channel or the other channel cuz
shit's going to go down, lad. Shit's
going to go down.
[ __ ] is going down, lad. Trust me. They
know this channel or the main channel.
Maybe the main one. Depends
because obviously there's biased people
on here in it. So I don't want them
making excuses. So it might be the main
channel. It's going to be one of the channels.
I had a walk, bro. I walked about four
miles, lad. Had some chicken. I'm going
to cook this steak later, bro. There's
going to be a madness on Thursday, bro.
Yeah. Just come out the shower. You
better. You wanted content, you little
[ __ ] You're going to get some content
on Thursday. You're going to get some
content on Thursday, bro.
Yeah, I went for a walk, bro. I was
sending people like voice notes and [ __ ]
about this country and what it's like
and [ __ ] like
Yeah. gay people thinking they could
tell you what to do and [ __ ] Yeah. I
was messaging people and that, bro.
Trust me. [ __ ] is going down, bro. On
Thursday, you watch. 100%. We're in it
now. When you're in it, UK asylum,
you're in it. We get it, bro. Yeah.
Shit's going down on Thursday, lad. Trust.
The madness is going to be happening.
We're going to make sure there's more
people out this time. So, we'll pick a Thursday. Yeah.
Evil [ __ ] women. Yeah. You'll see
what happens on Thursday, mate. You'll
see what happens on Thursday.
Trust me, you will see what will happen.
Going out with a bang lad. Then it's
Thailand, mate. Then it is Thailand. I'm
not going down without a fight, bro.
Then it's Thailand.
Simple. Then it's Thailand, bro. Simple
as that. I made up my mind, bro. Deadly Trust.
Trust me. Trust me. Trust me. I'm not
going down without a fight, Grezy. Trust me, lad.
Yeah. I'm not going down without a
fight. You will see what happens on
Thursday, mate. I've had enough of this
to last me a lifetime. Yeah.
[ __ ] evil little [ __ ]
Watch, bro. Watch.
Yeah, I was mad enough on Monday, bro.
You should have saw how many people I
was sending, bro. Watch what happens, bro. Watch.
That gay guy better be in as well, bro.
That gay guy better be in. And if not,
then anyone who anyone who wants to back
chat and be a cunt's getting it. Simple,
bro. And it's all going to be recorded.
It's all going to be recorded. Yeah.
Yeah. I know, bro. Is it? I know. Well,
maybe if men was as evil as women, then
maybe maybe I'd make more an effort into men. Maybe, lad.
They're getting it, lad. They're getting
it on Thursday. Don't worry. Like, I
ain't forgot about nothing, bro. I went
for a long walk, had a shower, bro.
Thursday's going down, bro. Trust me.
Thursday is going to drop down, bro.
Trust me. [ __ ] this, bro. I've had
enough of this [ __ ] to last me a
lifetime. Hopefully that gay guy's there.
And I don't know whether to put on this
channel, Grevy. I'll put it on another channel.
Um, it's going to get bad, bro. Really
bad. Trust me.
Yeah. No one stuck it on my mom. Laney
wasn't even scared of Timmy, so he
didn't stick on anyone. I've already
explained this multiple times. Anyways,
we're not talking about this. You can
keep repeating and bringing up the same
old [ __ ] That's on you, lad. Laney
didn't even flinch a blink. Yeah. And
that's that. We're not going over the
same thing over again anyways. Just look
forward to just look just looking Just
look forward to Thursday.
Just look forward to Thursday, lads. No,
I'm still going out Thursday, Dr. Eka.
I'm still doing a madness. I'm still
doing a madness on Thursday, bro.
And I'm not going to calm down. Trust
me. When I'm in one of these moods, I'm
not going to calm down. Yeah. I want to
[ __ ] you over. I want to make you feel
like [ __ ] I want to make you feel like
low. I want to make the gay man feel
like low. Oh, bro. Trust me. I'm not
going to calm down, bro. Trust me. When
I was in these moods before, it took me
two weeks to calm down. A whole two
weeks to calm down. And that's when I
had given up. So, bro, I ain't going to
calm down in 4 days. Trust me, I know
what I'm like, bro. I know my temper.
So, th Thursday's happening, bro.
Thursday is happening.
Do the countdown, bro. Do the countdown,
bro. No, not going after gays, but if
that gay manager's there, I'm going to
tell him about himself. I already told
him about last time, but I'll do it to
the extreme this time.
I'm th the whole part of Thursday is
taking things to the extreme which I
hadn't well I have done it before but I
mean like I didn't do it all the time.
It's taking [ __ ] to the extreme lad.
It's taking stuff to the extreme which
is what I didn't do every time I went
out before. Even though I defended
myself every time. I don't think I ever
defended myself. I [ __ ] did. And
that's it, bro.
I'm going to bother every woman. I'm
gonna try and collect numbers to [ __ ]
one of them over. Trust me, I'm gonna be
a nasty little [ __ ] on Thursday. Yeah,
I'm gonna be a nasty dirty awkward [ __ ]
on Thursday. I hope you like that. Um I
hope you like that, Grezy. I'm going to
be a dirty dirty dirty dirty awkward
little [ __ ] How about that one for you,
bro? Yeah, I'll show you dirty, bro.
I'll show you dirty. Trust me. And we're
going to we're going to do it all day as
bro. We're going to do it all day.
I'll go in that same place they told me
that I can't go in as well. I'll say,
"Fuck off, you gay [ __ ] You don't tell
me what to do in my own country, you
faggot." That's what I'm And that's what
I'm going to say this time. I'm going to
say, "Fuck off, you little [ __ ] You
little grinder dick sucking little
faggot." Watch what happens on Thursday,
bro. If I'm ready, bro. Count down the
days, lad. If it was Wednesday today or
Thursday or Friday or Saturday today, I
would have went I would have went out
today, bro. We don't want it peaceful.
We want it booming, bro. Trust me. First
Thursday Thursdays are booming, lad. Yeah.
Simple, lad. And I'm going to and I'm
going to make sure one of these people
meet me again so I can [ __ ] their life
up. Like how they try [ __ ] my life
up. Yeah. Have you ever heard that,
Grezy? One person [ __ ] your life up,
you [ __ ] their lives up.
You know, I'm not [ __ ] about, bro.
I'm not playing about, bro. Trust me,
I'm not. Trust me, I'm not.
Trust me, I'm not lad.
Yeah, it's going to end on Thursday,
bro. Yeah, we end with a bang. Yeah, not [ __ ] around.
Sorry to say, lad. Sorry to say.
This has been going on far too long now, lad. Yeah. Really?
Oh, [ __ ] off Jimmy, man.
Yeah. On Thursday. Yeah, lad. On
Yeah. Bullied. Yeah. Yeah. Okay, bro.
Yeah. Be out on Thursdays, lads. So, Thursday.
Oh, I'll be doing madness. Lotty. I'll
be doing madness, lad. I've had it up to
here with it with these women. these
[ __ ] gay people trying to tell you
what you can do. Oh, I'll be doing the
most stupidest things. I'll be doing the
most stupidest things, lad. And you're
going to watch me do it as well.
Content for the fans, bro. Get the [ __ ]
in there. You want the content? You'll
get You'll get your little content on
Thursday. You'll get your little content. Yeah.
on Thailand. We need to focus on leaving
after this. Yeah.
So, you get your little video, bro. You
get your little madness.
It will be a madness, bro. Trust me, it
will be. And I will intentionally make
it a madness if anyone gets in my way.
Yeah, it's as simple as that, bro.
And obviously, we need to approach
people to try to get people's numbers so
they can meet us so we can [ __ ] them over.
You know what? I might even try and go
on an instant date and then just leave
the person with the bill. Trust me, bro.
I might I if I could try and get an
instant date and say they want to go for
us, I can just leave them with the bill.
Trust me, it's going to be dirty, bro.
It's going to be dirty. Trust me,
Greavvesy. It's going to be dirty, lad.
Just like how they've done me dirty over
years, years and years and years. Bit of
payback, taste of your own medicine.
You're going to get a bit of taste of
your own medicine, [ __ ] You're going to
get a taste of your own medicine, mate.
You know that person who I left in
waxies greasy they're so lucky they
didn't meet me that day cuz I would have
left them with about£500 bill lad.
Yeah well I won't need good luck cuz I
mate I will find someone mate. Trust me
I will find someone. Yeah I will. Trust
me I will. Yeah.
Never hit by my mommy smokey. I'm not
talking about it again, lad. I've
already explained it. I've already
explained it. I've already explained it.
Yeah. All of this leading on all of this
[ __ ] You're going to know about it
Thursday, bro. You're going to know
about it Thursday, bro. You're going to
know about it Thursday. Yeah. Countdown
the days. Count down the days, lad. You know,
you will see. Don't you worry about
smokey me. The video is going to be
there, lad. You don't need to worry, bro.
You're going to see the video, Smokeoky, lad.
Yeah. Okay, whatever. I've already
explained it. Don't you worry about
that, bro. Just worry about what's
happening on Thursday as well. Just
worry about what's happening on Thursday, bro.
Why not today? Because it's a Sunday and
I don't go out Sundays and I always go
and it's never Saturdays. I don't go out
Saturdays. I go out Thursdays, mate.
Yeah, I went out last Monday. I caused a
madness. What are you talking about, you
[ __ ] I always go out Thursdays. Not
going to go out today, am I? It's
Sunday. It's [ __ ] I will be out
Thursday. Don't you worry about that. Yeah.
Yeah. Simple, bro.
Okay. Yeah. Whatever, Smokey. Whatever,
lad. Did I Did I fold with the bouncer,
Smokey? Did I fold with the two guys and
the two women? Did I fold with Terry?
No, I didn't, lad. No, I didn't. I've
stuck it on plenty of people, but you're
biased, so you ignore it. Again,
selective memory. That's all I need to say, bro.
Selective memory. That's all I got to say. Yeah.
Yeah. Okay. My word means nothing. Good
for you, lad.
Good for you, bro. I'm not asked what
you think, bro. I'm not asked what you think.
Like honestly, I'm not asked what you think, bro.
I'm not asked what you think.
You can think what you like, lad.
It's just the day I like going out. I
just like going out on Thursdays, lad.
Uh I've just always gone out on Thursdays.
It's just the day, lad. Thursdays are
the one, bro.
Oh yeah, it's not you, is it? You hide it.
Yeah, I'm going to [ __ ] them over, bro.
I'm going to [ __ ] I'm going to [ __ ]
their life up, bro. If one of them meets
me, lad. Trust me. Trust me. Yeah, I'll
be doing posters as well, lad. Don't you
worry about that.
Yeah, don't you worry. I'll be doing an
absolute madness. These women need to
learn smoky bit. [ __ ]
No posters, dusty. Definitely posters.
I'll show you crazy. Yeah. You accuse me
of being crazy, so I'll show you crazy.
Nah. Nah, lad. I'm going to try to get
one of them to meet me and then I'm just
going to rob them. Rob them. Use them.
Bro, trust me. Something's going to go
down, bro. Something's going to go down.
They're going to learn, bro. They're
going to learn, lad.
No, you're not. You're not coming in and
you get banned, lad. See you later.
See you later. Self projector. We don't
have self projectors on this channel.
Um, so yeah, that's what's happening.
Trust me, I'm being serious, Dusty.
Okay, Dusty, think about it like this,
right? You remember when I was trying to
get that one to meet me in the
restaurant and she weren't having none
of it and I stood up in waxies? Bro, you
don't even know what I was going to do, do you?
The one I tried meeting in the
restaurant and they weren't I said,
"Let's go for a steak. Come on. Well, I
was going to D and dash him, bro.
I was going to D and dash him. They got
lucky, bro. They got lucky. They they
they they they they they meet me, bro. Trust.
These women are going to learn, lad.
They're going to learn.
They're going to [ __ ] absolute learn
to stop being [ __ ] their life,
you know? And that's it. That's what I'm
here to do, bro. I'm here to do I'm on
on a mission and that's it.
They are [ __ ] little [ __ ] They can
have me on CCTV all they want. Uncle
Andy, I'm going to go into the same
place that manages in. I'm going to say,
"Fuck off, you [ __ ] [ __ ] tell me
what to do, lad.
[ __ ] tell me what to do, you little
dick sucking [ __ ] cunt." They can have
that on [ __ ] CCTV as well.
They can have that on CCTV as well. Yeah.
No, I didn't hear that to be fair.
I don't follow these idiots.
I don't follow these little idiots on YouTube.
Nah, bro. Cuz I don't need to be
sectioned. That's years and years of
dealing with their [ __ ] That's
enough to make anyone like that. It can
make the most laidback person like that.
Yeah, I'm going to do it. Do you want me
to do it? Do you want me to do it, lad?
You want me to do it? No more Tik Tok for you.
What? Like the little cat? Like the
little cat in it. A
>> yeah, bro. Watch. There's going to be
madness on Thursday. I want to try and
get an instant date with someone so I
can die and dash them.
I want to make them how feel how they
No, no, no, no. I'm going to go in that
premises because I can. And no gay guy
is going to tell me. And this time, no
gay guy. Well, he didn't tell me the
first place. I told him about himself.
But I'm not moving. So unless you call
the police, you little gay boy. I'm not
moving. It's all right for you to suck
dick on Grinder. It's all right for you
to [ __ ] do your little gay pride. So,
I'll do what I want. Understand, [ __ ]
So, [ __ ] back to where you come from,
Kent, and bring your attitude with you,
you [ __ ] little gay grinder [ __ ] [ __ ] Yeah.
Life's hard enough without a [ __ ]
[ __ ] trying to tell you what you can
do in your own country. You understand?
Yeah. Trust me, it's going to it's going
to go down, bro. It's going to it's
going to all of these years and years of
this [ __ ] years and years and
years, shit's going to go down, lad.
Yeah. Trust me, there will be a diamond
and dash. Trust me, lads. Trust me, it's
happening, bro. It is happening.
It is happening, bro.
Don't tell me where to go, you [ __ ]
gay [ __ ] You know what I mean?
Stop going on Grinder. I don't like you
on Grinder, but you don't see me talking
about it. You don't see me talking about
it, do you, Grezy? You don't see me
talking You don't see me telling you you
can't go on Grinder. You don't see me
telling you you can't do your little gay
pride. How about you give me your number
and I'll come cop you. Every time you're
in a gay bar, every time you go to a gay
bar, I'll come with you and I'll cop you
and I'll tell everyone that you're a
nons. How about that one? How about
everywhere you go, I'll come with you
and I and I'll be and I will cramp your
style like the cramps twins. Since you
want to try and embarrass me, let me
embarrass you. Give me Give me the same
option. Did you know this guy's a 30 knots? Yeah.
Yeah, that's what I said. Bro, listen.
Let me cramp your style. Let me cramp
your style. Come on.
Never come for eating in my life, lad.
Not you people.
Uh, what? Ooh, a s. Ew.
Ew. A s, everybody. A s. Ew.
Y. Y. A s.
Ew. A s.
Well, that's not possible, lad, cuz
you're not going to know who they are
and what they look like. So, uh, yeah,
that's that's not going to work.
But you're a simp lad.
[ __ ] simp white light [ __ ]
Yeah, you simp white light [ __ ] [ __ ]
Is that right, lad?
coming Thursday. Oh, really? Is he, bro?
Well, then he'll see me then only if he comes Thursday. Oh, really?
Oh, really, bro? Where's that?
What the [ __ ]
Nah, definitely definitely not, bro. Yeah.
So, what you want me to say that to the
gay manager, Greavvesy?
You want me to say that to the gay
manager? You want me to own the little [ __ ]
I'll embarrass him in front of all of
the um the colleagues if you want me to,
lad. Not a problem.
You know, and I will do it as well, bro.
I will do it. You've seen what I've done.
You know what I mean?
But I'm not going to talk about no
fighting or anything
cuz I know you people on here don't like that. But
yeah, but I'm I'm going to go into the
same environment. Yeah, but I'm going to
go into the same environment. So if he tells me
about like I'm I'm going to tell him straight, lad.
You know what I'm saying?
Yeah, we're not talking about Timmy
anymore, lads. So, you can keep bringing
up and we're just going to keep ignoring
it. We're not talking about that.
You can You're talking to yourself, lad.
That's all you're doing is talking to yourself.
Yeah. Okay, bro. Yeah. Yeah. Okay, bro.
Don't worry about that. Just worry about
who I'll be sticking it on Thursday.
Just worry about who I'll be sticking on Thursday. Thursday, lad.
Don't worry about that. Don't worry
about that. Any
bouncers trying to get involved or tried
to put their hands on me, they're
getting it. Simple. Doesn't matter who
they are. Yeah. It doesn't matter who
And I'm not moving either, lad. I'm not moving either.
So, I'm not moving either. I'll be
awkward, bro. Trust me. I'll be an awkward [ __ ]
I'll be sticking on these women, lads.
Don't you worry.
>> Yeah, I'll get hurt badly. No, I [ __ ]
won't, Belly. No, I won't. No, I won't,
mate. No, I [ __ ] will not get hurt badly.
Sorry, belly. No, I [ __ ] won't. No, I
[ __ ] won't, mate. Trust me, I've had
it with loads of bounces in the past,
lad. No, I [ __ ] won't.
No, I [ __ ] won't, mate.
Trust me. No, I won't, lad.
I don't care if they're solid. I'll use
a weapon, bro. I've got a glass in my
hand. I've got a glass in my hand, bro.
Yeah, remember that, Greavves. I've got
a glass in my hand. They can be solid
all they want. I've got a glass in my
hand. Don't forget, I'm the one with the
glass in my hand.
I'm the one with nothing to lose. So, I
mean, I don't give a [ __ ] what they are.
They'll get smashed in their face. It's
as simple as that.
Trust me, I don't give a [ __ ] You put
your hands on me, you're getting smashed
in your face. It's as simple as that.
Oh, yeah. What could go wrong, bro?
Well, it's been fine so far, Dr. Eko.
All these years of traveling, I've never
had any issues before.
If a bouncer tries to get in my face and
he tries to put his hands on me, he's
getting it. Yes.
Yes. Yes. Yes.
You should have saw that [ __ ] Polish
one, bro. He thought he was a [ __ ] bro.
Oh my god.
Yeah, he thought he was the man, but he
wasn't. And you know what? Even if one
beats me, I'll go to the shop. I'll buy
loads of glass bottles and just start
throwing it at them.
Just start throwing it at them, bro. So,
even if one say bigger than me and beats
me, I would just start throwing bottles
at them, bro.
like from a distance. Trust me, bro. I'm
not in no mood. Trust me, I'm in no no mood, lad.
Yeah. You know, you'll find a way to
win. You know, if you can't if you can't
win fist to fish, you'll find a way to
win. Trust me. Yeah. Yeah. It'll just be
like bam bam bam bam bam bam bam. Just
throwing it like smacking them in the
face with it, bro. Yeah.
You want to be a [ __ ] I'll be a [ __ ]
lad. It doesn't matter in any way.
And you could do that. Anyone that that
tells you not, yeah, is is [ __ ] If
about to beat you or he chucks you on
the floor or somehow he beats you, even
if you do it the cowardly way, beat them
the cowardly way, bro. Simple as that,
bro. Just as long as they don't get the
last laugh. Yeah, they're cowards.
They're [ __ ] They jump people. [ __ ]
him in it. Yeah.
Trust me, bro. Trust me.
Yeah, if I get punched in the face, I'll
go back. It's simple as that. If I If I
get punched in the face, I'll go back.
Then I'll go back. Obviously, bro, I
might not win. I'm not saying I will
win, but I will win in the end. I will
win in the end, lad. Trust me. You don't
know the amount of bounces that I have
stuck at a pro. You don't know. You
really don't know. People that weren't
even in uniform, I said, "I'm not moving
and you're not moving me." Trust me,
that's You have no idea, lad. Trust me,
you have no idea, lad.
Ones that were trying to, you know what I mean?
Yeah. I Yeah. I I swear you people
forget the amount of men I've stuck it
on and you've tried twisting it and making excuses.
That's crazy. Bouncer, the people that
were sat down.
Yeah, you you seem to forgot forget a
lot of stuff as well. You bias [ __ ]
If a bouncer tries to embarrass me in
front of people, you're going to know
what time it is, lad. You're going to
know what time it is. I'll get them
glass bottles and start smacking it at
them, throwing it. Throw, throw, throw,
throw, throw, throw, throw. They're not
even going to be able to move, lad.
If a bouncer thinks that they're going
to try and imbalance me in front of
women, I will smack them and I'll smack
their face. You're going to see on
Thursday as well, bro.
I will smack them and I'll smack their
face. Simple as that. Nah, DH10, bro.
I'm going out Thursday, lad. I'm doing a madness.
I'm doing a madness on Thursday, bro.
Are you guys forgetting about the
bouncers that I stuck it on and the guys
that I stuck it on in front of their
women. Talk about selective memory, huh?
Talk about selective memory card, huh?
Bro, I've already done it before and
I've proven it multiple times. I've also
stuck it on women in front of men in the
natural environment. You people seem to
have got selective memory, lad.
Like you're Bro, the thing is Yeah. You
know, like the thing is, lads, you're
talking to me, bro.
Yeah. Just a bad experiences with women and [ __ ]
And that Christian Izzy [ __ ] me over,
bro. Proper proper [ __ ] me over. So, I'm
trying to find out near about where she
lives as well, lad. I'm going to be I'm
going to be doing posters of her as
well. [ __ ] that, bro. No, [ __ ] that.
[ __ ] Yeah, I stuck on a Listen, lad.
Listen, listen. That's not what
happened, brother. Yeah, that's not what
happened. Everybody saw the video and
that's not what happened. You can keep
twisting it and keep lying to yourself.
Brother, that's not what happened. Go
and watch the video properly. Yeah, it's
not like nonslegs that's never met
anyone. Brother, brother, that's not
what happened. That is not what happened, bro.
That is not what happened, mate. I told
them to [ __ ] off back to Newcastle in
front of their woman. I called them a
[ __ ] I said, "My trainers are worth
more than your whole outfit, ugly." And
they didn't even stand up. That's not
what happened. Go rewatch the video
again, lad. You need to rewatch it
again, brother. That's not what
happened. So, what I'm saying is what
whatever happens Thursday, um, Grezy,
people are just going to be biased, lad.
Yeah. Do you understand? They're just
going to be biased.
Um, it's the women's [ __ ] UK asylum.
The Christian Izzy, the women's [ __ ]
all of it, lad. All of it. Not Not I
don't need to prove myself to any of
these people here. I got told to go
away. H, that's not what happened. Keep
telling yourself that, lad. Listen.
Listen, Nick. You keep telling yourself
that. Listen, bro. You keep telling
yourself that. Keep lying to yourself.
If that's what makes you feel better,
you keep telling yourself that. If that
helps you sleep at night that they made
me run away, keep telling yourself that.
If it makes you feel better, keep
telling yourself that.
Yeah. So, um, no, there's no way.
There's no way. Unless Christian Izzy
meets me and apologizes to me, which is
never going to happen. Uh, no. DH10.
They haven't. I went out Monday, bro. I
got three numbers. None of them replied,
but I'm not asked about that anyways
because that's just to be expected.
Listen, like I said, lad, you keep
telling yourself that happened. If it
makes you feel better and it makes you
sleep at night better, you keep telling
yourself that. I got owned, okay? You
keep telling yourself that, lad.
Everyone saw the video. Everyone knows
what happened. But again, keep telling
yourself that. I'm all for people to
feel better, lad. Anyone that feels
better, you know, that's that's good. I
feel better. That's good, lad. If you
feel better about that, then keep
telling yourself that, lad. I got owned.
Yeah. Okay. You keep telling yourself
that. That's not what the video shows
though. In your head, that's what it
shows. But the video shows me sticking
on men in front of their girlfriends and
they didn't do nothing. Me telling a man
to suck his mom. He didn't do anything.
Yeah. Yeah. No, I am angry. Dent, I am
angry, lad. I'm angry with women time
and time again. The bad experiences time
and time again. The fact that this is
still 2026. I'm not dealing with it no
more. And I'm going to put up posters
all around the churches in that area,
lad. I know where the [ __ ] lives. The
[ __ ] lives in England. Trust me, mate. I
will do a madness. Trust me, I will do a
madness, lad. Yeah, that's it. That's
the end of the road, lad. Yeah, that's
the end of the road, bro. And I'm going
Thailand after this. And that's me, bro.
So, I'm going out with a bang.
So, I wasn't far behind Ant-Man, to be fair, lad.
That's it. Yeah, [ __ ] it. I don't care,
bro. Look at Bro, look at the posters
that I done at Nlegs. Look at the
posters that I done at N with Nlegs.
Look at the posters I done, lad.
Look at the posters that I done.
Yeah. With nonslegs. Look what I did. It
was on a train [ __ ] everywhere, bro.
Yeah. Okay, bro. You keep telling
yourself that, lad. Like I said, if it
helps you sleep at night better, then
keep telling yourself that, bro. I don't
care. The posters was on the train, the
pub, everything, mate. This [ __ ] left
YouTube for two weeks, but people will
pretend that never happened again.
Selective memory, bro. A lot of people
on here have got selective memory. I've
had enough of it. DH10, bro. Like, I'm
not even a psychopath, bro. I swear to
God, I'm a calm person, but [ __ ] this,
bro. I'm not I'm not having this no more, lads.
Leading me on playing games, false hope,
all of that [ __ ]
DH10 talking to someone for a month only
for them to [ __ ] you over. No, [ __ ]
that, bro. [ __ ] that. I said, "Oh, meet
me now then." I said, "Meet me now. If
you want an apology, meet me now." Oh,
I'm crazy on this, that. [ __ ] off, mate.
[ __ ] off, you [ __ ] Yeah. I hope I
[ __ ] bump into you on [ __ ] Thursday.
Yeah. Yeah. I'm I'm I'm I'm hoping, bro.
this is going to stop. This is going to stop, lad.
Yeah, this has got to stop, lad. I'm
telling you right now, bro. Yeah.
The same reason why you're still a virgin.
Um, I'm going to do loads of things. I'm
going to try to get as many women on
dates. I'm going to [ __ ] them over, run
away with not paying the bill. I'm going
to be I'm I'm going to try and get as
many numbers as possible. I'm going to
try lead people on, make them feel like
[ __ ] like they do to me. I'm going to
tell this game manager about himself if
he thinks he's going to try and tell me
where I can and can't go. Like, it's
madness is happening. Any white knight
wants to get involved, he's being told
about himself. It's happening. And
madness happens all the time when I go
out, bro. And I just go out to go out.
This time, bro, it's a different story, lad. Yeah.
I will be a nasty nasty little [ __ ]
Trust me. Yeah. a nasty nasty little
[ __ ] And they've had it coming, bro.
That's what happens when you take
people's kindness for weakness, lad. And
it should go viral all over top Tik Tok as well.
Yeah. You know what I'm saying, bro?
So, you'll see what happen, lad. You'll
see what happen.
I don't even like this Christian, is he,
bro? He's a bit too young for me
anyways. But it's the point. It's not
That's not the point. That's not the point, lad.
Yeah. That's not the point. I don't
care. I don't give a [ __ ]
Yeah. I've had enough of these [ __ ] bro.
Nah, lad. Nah, you know what it is,
DH10. I've had enough bad experiences to
last me a [ __ ] lifetime, bro. And
there's no way I've spoken to someone
for a month for them to disappear, lad.
Yeah. Yeah. No way, mate. No [ __ ] way
is that happening.
No [ __ ] way is that happening, mate.
Not a [ __ ] chance. Yeah. DH10.
Imagine that, bro. A whole waste of time
speaking for a [ __ ] month. All the
other [ __ ] that they've done as
well, lad. No, no, no, no, no. [ __ ]
that, bro. Absolutely [ __ ] that, bro.
Yeah. Cuz when you're in it, you're in it, bro.
When you're in it, you're in it. Do you
get me, Dreamsy? Yeah.
I don't give a [ __ ] lad. I will [ __ ] a
couple of people's lives up like they
[ __ ] my life up. What do you want me
to do, DH10? What do you want me to do?
Carry on as normal. Keep getting bad
experiences? Keep getting my time
wasted? Keep being made to feel like
[ __ ] Is that going to get somewhere? Is
that going to get someone somewhere?
Is that going to Is that going to get
you somewhere? Keep being shhat on all
your life, having gay people telling
you, "No, no, no, no, no, no."
You know what I'm saying, bro? Nah, no, no, no. Yeah.
You know what I'm saying, bro? No, I
ain't being careful. I'm not being
careful at all, mate.
I'm going Thailand, lad. I'm going
Thailand. See you later, Fatty Thompson.
Fatty Thompson virgin. See you later, lad.
Yeah, I am going to Thailand. But why
should I have to Why should I have to
DH10? You get my point, lad?
You You You get my point? Why should I have to?
I shouldn't be able I shouldn't go into
a premises and have some day [ __ ] try
and tell me what I can and can't do. I
shouldn't have to speak to someone for a
whole month only for them to [ __ ] me
over. I don't need [ __ ] this [ __ ]
bad vibes, bro. Why do you think I don't
go out drinking?
Why do you think I rarely go out
drinking, lad? For these exact reasons. Yeah.
I don't know who you are, bro, but Yeah.
Like that's that's that is it.
And you know what? I've sent voice notes
to a couple of my my friends telling
this, telling them this, explaining
this. Tell me something, bro. Tell me
something. I want one of these people.
Yeah. Who I sent voice notes to
explaining this situation to tell me
something. They can't they can't even
argue with it, bro. There's nothing they can say.
You get me, bro? There's nothing they can say.
There's nothing they can say, lad.
No, I'm not, bro. Why should I have to
be made to feel like [ __ ] because of
these women, lads? Why should I though?
Why should I? DH10, why should I? And
you know the thing is, do you know how
bad it is now, DH10? You can't even go
to a premises now and try to speak to
someone without a gay jealous manager
telling you, "Oh, you got to leave. Oh,
you got to leave. Oh, you got to leave.
You get me?
It's bad, bro. It's bad vibes, lad."
Nah, bro. I won't feel better because
when I gave up dating, I was in this
mood for two weeks, lad. I was in these
mood. I was in this mood, DH10, for
about 2 weeks, bro. When I gave up for
about 3 months. Yeah, you don't know. I
was going mad in my head for like two
weeks, bro. Mad in my head. Mad in my
head. Mad in my head. Mad in my head,
bro. Two weeks. Every day. All day.
Every day for two weeks. Do you remember
when I was going to the dentist?
Yeah. When I was following up with the
dentist appointments, it kind of calmed
me down. But every morning. Every
morning, bro. From the time I woke up to
the time I went to bed, I won't be fine
Thursday, bro. Trust me.
No, I will wait till Thursday, bro. I'm
going to be in the same mood, lad. I'm
going to be in the same mood. Don't you
worry, bro. Already done a mad this
Monday. Trust me there. I'm going out
Thursday, bro. Count on it. Bet.
Bet, lad. Bet.
You know what I mean, bro? Trust me.
Nah, there's no such thing as trying to
RDH10. What's your opinion on this woman
leading me on for a month and then being
a [ __ ] What do What do you think of
that, bro? What do you think of that?
What do you want people to do? Go on
dating apps that don't work.
Did I go out Thursdays? I've already
explained this. I go out Thursdays.
Bad vibes, bro. Bad vibes. UK is bad
vibes, bro. There's Instagram res on
that, you know.
Yeah, 100%. Well, a woman. Yeah, that
woman. Yeah. Yeah, that woman. Yeah, I'm
putting up posters. I'm pulling up
posters, lad. Thursday pip day. Nope.
I've got plenty of money, bro. I can go
out right now if I want to.
Nah, none of them are decent. Some are
decent. Some are decent, mate. They're
all [ __ ] evil little [ __ ] And
you're going to see that on Thursday as
well when I go out, bro. Not one of them
[ __ ] little [ __ ] are decent. Don't
you even dare come on my channel, bro,
and try to tell me some birds are
decent, bro. Don't you even dare try and
say that. They are all little evil
[ __ ] That's what they are, bro.
Not one of them little [ __ ] are decent.
How dare you even [ __ ] say that, bro?
And don't forget, I've met more women
than most of the people most most people
in the world.
Yeah, bro. They are all [ __ ] They are
all [ __ ] lad.
Um, like I said, bro, if you saw my text
messages and you saw my approaches, you
would see the common divinator. It's
them. If you watch my approaches, if you
you would see it's them. The common
demonita is them because then as soon as
when people leave the country, they
don't get these problems. The common
demonita is them. When I'm speaking to
someone for a month and they're leading
me on, it is definitely definitely them,
which is why I recorded all of my
approaches, which is why I recorded all
of my messages to prove that the problem
was them all along. And it's there on my
phone. You can't argue with it. The
problem is women. It is them. The
problem is them in these westernized
countries. Yeah, it is them. The problem
is them. Yeah.
That's who the [ __ ] common
denominator is. Yeah. That's who the
common denominator is. It's them [ __ ]
It's [ __ ] them [ __ ] I mean, I've
shown you enough approaches. I've shown
you enough messages. I can show you the
messages with this Christian Izzy if you want, lad.
And I'm telling you, you can't tell me
nothing. I'm telling you, you can't tell
me nothing. I can scroll up right now,
lad. Yeah, right now. 5th of 6th of February.
What's the date today? [ __ ] hell,
bro. That's over a month ago. I can put
all these messages up. You still talk
[ __ ] bro. You still talk [ __ ] lad. Yeah.
Yeah. I'm saying, lad.
Nah, mate. Listen, DH10. Come to London,
lad. You'll be surprised. Come to
London. You'd be surprised, lad. I mean,
I don't know how. Have you not watched
my videos? Have you not watched my
videos? Have you not watched my messages
and stuff? I mean, I'm surprised you'd
think that, lad.
They're all single. Most of them are
single, lad. Most of them are single.
They're just [ __ ] They just waste
people's time. That's all they do. None
of them are decent.
None of these [ __ ] are decent. None of
them. Not one of them are decent. That's
why I'm getting revenge on Thursday.
Bro, don't you worry. I'm getting my
revenge. I'm getting my revenge. Don't
you worry about that, lad.
If I knew where this [ __ ] stupid [ __ ]
lived, I'd brick her window in, bro. I'd
put a brick through that window. A
female's window. I'll brick the window,
bro. I swear to God, I'll brick it.
Trust me, I would. Like their exact
address. Like their exact address. I
would I would put a brick through their window, bro.
Trust me, I would put a brick through their window.
Yeah, trust me. I don't [ __ ] them out
when it comes to stuff like this, bro. Yeah.
Yeah. Well, don't get your hopes up,
lad. Don't get your hopes up. That's up
to you, bro. I know what I'm doing. I
know what I need to do. This is real
life, lad. This ain't YouTube. This is real life.
This is real life, lad. This isn't
YouTube, Dusty. This is real life. You
understand? This is real life. There's a big difference.
Nope. Even the average ones think
they're better than everyone. DH10.
Even average women think they're better
than everyone. I was speaking to this
person for one month. Oh, they're going
to meet. They're going to meet. They're
going to meet. I only go for
supermodels. No, I do not. There's no
such thing as supermodels in this
country. Most of the women are average
or below average. So, I don't know how
that's possible. Saying that we were
going to meet and then they don't meet you.
A whole month of talking DH10. All that
time, all that [ __ ] for nothing,
lad. [ __ ] them, bro. Absolutely [ __ ]
them, lad. I've still got their number
as well. Watch. [ __ ] stupid little
Yeah. Watch. Watch, bro. Watch. Watch. Just watch.
Yeah. It's happened loads of times.
DH10. They do it to make people feel
[ __ ] bro. They DH10. They do it to make
people feel [ __ ] cuz they're evil, lad.
They're [ __ ] evil. That's why they do
it because they're evil, bro.
Evil, lad. You can watch my video if you
want, bro. It's the last one I made.
Doesn't matter what we spoke about.
Loads of different things. And you're
not going to try and put the blame on to
me either, lad. Because if you're trying
to find something, you're not going to find it.
Yeah. You're not going to find it. All
of this DH10 is to try to make people
feel like [ __ ] They are evil. I'm so
certified they're evil [ __ ] I've got
all the evidence, all the proof to
suggest they're all bad people. They're
all evil. Not even Jesus can tell me
different, lads. Not even Jesus Christ
can tell me different. There are no good
ones. They're all bad. And I say that
with my head, bro. I don't Bro, you
don't need to meet more people. You have
met more women than anyone in the world
to know what they're like. It doesn't
matter what anyone says. It doesn't
matter what anyone. It doesn't matter, bro.
No. No. No. No. There's no coming on too
strong [ __ ] No. No. No. No. No. No. No.
No. No. No. No. No. No. No. No. No. No.
[ __ ] madness, bro.
I hate them both the same.
Yep. And I think they're just [ __ ]
DH10. They they they love leading people
on. They're evil, lad. They're [ __ ] evil, bro.
They're evil [ __ ] I mean, I'm not
dating, bro. This was from last month. I
went out last month cuz I was like I had
some stress and stuff with um with some
guy, bro. So, I just went out drinking
and I thought, "Oh, let me do a couple
approaches. Look, I'm in the same
problem. I'm in the same predicament.
You understand? Um, bro, I I I give it
up as well. That was the first time in
Oh, [ __ ] That was the first time in 3 months.
That was the first time I went out in 3 months, lad.
So yeah, I don't I don't approach I
don't [ __ ] with any women because I know
they're all the same DH10. I know that
they are literally all bad people.
Nah, bro. I don't I honestly honestly
don't, lad. The only reason DH10 I was
entertaining this person is because they
seemed all right and I was out anyway.
So I thought, okay, well, like it's a
new year, 2026, you know, whatever. And
they're all the same. No, I generally
don't. They are all evil them, bro.
They're all the same.
You don't know how many problems they've
caused me over the years.
You know, I had anxiety a week ago. I
couldn't sleep. They're evil. These
women are very evil people. Trust me.
But very nasty, nasty, evil, horrible people.
I'm I'm don't be serious like that. I'm
not even saying that to rage, bro. I
seriously I'm not, bro. I seriously am not.
I didn't I didn't approach for 3 months.
I didn't care. I didn't got no date. I
was done with it, bro. Because I know
what they're like. They are the same. So
why don't But obviously if you're out
drinking, it's 2026. Oh well, let's see.
You know, same old [ __ ] bro. Same old
It's all negative. You just need to
leave this country. That's as simple as
that, bro. Like, well, you I mean me,
bro. But yeah, only one in the same situation.
No, they use age as an excuse. DH10.
They also make excuses.
They're not interested. Oh, you're too
young for me. They're [ __ ] as well,
lad. Unless they're in their 60s, lad.
They're [ __ ] as well.
They're all [ __ ] Young, old, whatever.
They're all [ __ ] It's as simple as
that, bro. I prove that enough with the
amount of women I've met. They're all [ __ ]
They're all nasty little [ __ ] that
don't care about anyone's feelings
because most of them are narcissists. Yeah. So,
that's that, bro.
[ __ ] nuts, lad.
Yeah. They don't care about anyone's
feelings where you wouldn't block
someone. They just go someone.
They would. That's the difference. They
would do it because they got no They're
narcissistic, horrible people. You
understand? They're narcissistic, evil, horrible people.
Yeah. I just messaged the bouncer
telling him about what happened the
other day. He said, "That's insane,
bro." I said, "Yeah."
Yeah. I'm I'm going out Thursday, lad.
I'm going out Thursday, Annie. Don't you
worry, lad. Uh in the end, she blocked me. Yeah.
Yeah. Cuz you cuz she was trying to play victim. Yeah.
I don't go out to Oh, bro. I don't go
out to meet women. You I just explained
this to you, lad. I just explained this
to you, bro.
No, they didn't block me straight away.
What they were doing is they were trying
to play victim and started crying when I
asked them to meet me and stuff and I
said, "Oh, you're never going to find
anyone as good as me." And then they
started like [ __ ] playing victim and
all [ __ ] like that, bro.
Um, so weren't they just they didn't
randomly just block me? No.
No. What it was was I said no. I asked
them basically what I said to them was
oh you want to meet and that cuz after
exams oh I'll let you know I was like oh
what do you mean you'll let me know like
you said that we was going to meet
what's going on like let's just meet up
and then it just ma madness started just
madness started then I got pissed and
then I started messaging them
pretty much bro yeah
so I hate these women. I hate them with a passion.
No, it doesn't happen every time I get a
number, bro. I don't get led on every
time. I don't get led on every time.
Sometimes I just don't respond.
Mad, is it mad?
Yeah. Good. We hate each other, don't
we? Yeah, we hate each other. They're
[ __ ] evil. Little [ __ ]
Says I'm crazy. I'm scary for saying,
"Oh, let's meet up." That's scary, lad.
Yeah, that's scary, isn't it? Yeah.
[ __ ] [ __ ] I hate him, bro.
Yeah. Shout out to all the women that
get that has miscarriages. Shout out to
all the women that get cheated on. Big
up, lad. This is a That's going to be a
day to remember.
Big up all the miscarriage victims.
Bring up all the [ __ ] that's got
cheated on. Big up yourselves.
Absolutely lovely. You deserve it.
[ __ ] absolutely deserve it for all
the [ __ ] you put men through. Poor men.
Poor [ __ ] men, lad. you know, poor
poor men that they lead on and play
games with. [ __ ] him. I got no I got no
sympathy for the [ __ ] And that's that
simple. I've got no sympathy for them
little [ __ ] wankers.
And that's it, is it? [ __ ] they ain't
got no sympathy for us when they're
leading people on.
They've got no sympathy for us when
they're leading people on. Do they um Grezy?
Yeah. Well, well, don't Well, when I go
into the premises on Thursday, don't
come up to me and tell me I need to
leave then. Yeah. Don't come up to me
and tell me I need to leave and then I
won't tell you about yourself. How about
that one? Cuz I don't start on innocent
people, bro. Okay, fine. Just don't come
up to me, bro.
I don't think it's funny. I'm glad I'm
You know what? I'm happy that you're
laughing, but cuz I'm [ __ ] not, mate.
I'm not laughing.
It does happen to most men, mate.
There's plenty of men that living in
Thailand now. There's plenty of men that
can't find girlfriends. Oh, it happens
to most men, lad. And there's plenty of
And there's plenty plenty plenty of
examples. Oh, it definitely happens to
loads of men, lad.
It definitely happens to most men. Trust
me, I see it every day on Instagram. Oh,
trust me, it does. Oh, you've seen the
facts. Like I said, I'm not proving
myself to bias people.
It's as simple as that, lad. It's as
simple as that. I I'm glad you find it
funny, DH10, because I don't. Yeah.
Yeah, I mean I got like I said spill
spirit it right. I mean I got led on for
a month lad. So I mean I mean I I spoke
to someone every day for a month and
they led me on.
So I mean I've approached people in bars
and clubs. I mean
how many excuses are you going to make
lad? They're [ __ ] As simple as that.
They're just [ __ ] That's it. They're [ __ ] [ __ ]
I'm just going to be going out Thursday
and I'm going to be doing what I need to do. So, yeah.
Um, not for a very very Not really,
DH10. Not really, lad. Uh-uh.
If I ever got with someone, it always
ended badly. Not really, bro. No.
There's been so many bad experiences I
can't even remember that the No, not
really, lads. Not really.
To be honest, they're so little. They're
not even worth talking about.
Nah. And this Christian is pissed me
off, lad. And what they do, DH10, is
they lead you on to make you feel like [ __ ]
That's what they do. I was getting, like
I told you, I was getting bad anxiety,
bro, last week. Really bad. I've I've
only just kind of got over it. Um like
uh like um like well I hooked up with
them and then they ghosted in the end
and basically didn't um didn't give closure
um or tried to [ __ ] me over in some way.
So no really have I really had good
experiences? Not really, lad. No, to be
honest with you, not really.
It was mostly all just a slap in the
face. one way or the other, it was
always a slap in the face or a kick in
the teeth if it was worse. So, it's
always been pretty It's always been
pretty bad, lad.
Nah, it's over now. It's the way it is,
lad. It's the way it is in 2026.
It's never going to change, lad. That's
why I don't go out.
That's the reason why I don't go out,
cuz it never changes. They're all the same.
That's why I don't [ __ ] with it, bro. You know,
Ant-Man used to be out every week, but
not me, cuz there's no point me doing
anything. They're all the same. Every
time you give people the benefit of the
doubt, DH10, they [ __ ] you over again.
They [ __ ] you over again. Yeah.
It's like walking up to heaven with a
staircase, right? And then a kangaroo
kicks you in your face right back down
to hell again. It's always the same thing, lad.
It's always the same thing with them.
Yeah. Years ago they did. Yeah. Couple times.
The thing is, DH said, it's what I was
saying to these dudes earlier. If I
approach someone and they don't want to
talk, I don't care. If somebody says
that they got a boyfriend, I don't care.
You know, if someone says whatever, as
long as they don't get rude, bro, I
don't give a [ __ ] But when someone
leads me on now, oh, [ __ ] that, bro.
That should be illegal. That should be
illegal. Posters, people going on the
door and everything. And I stick by what
I say, bro, 3 years later. And I stand
by what I say. It's what I'm blew in the
face. [ __ ] that [ __ ] bro. [ __ ] them.
They deserve every bad thing that
happens to them. Just the same as if I
was to do it, you know?
That's why I got away from this [ __ ]
bro. This is why I gave up, lad.
They won't, lad. Bro, Greavves, are you
forgetting that I've gone to the gym
before? Are you forgetting that I've
lived by myself? Whatever you do, they
will never change. You can go gym, you
can get more money. They will always be
the same [ __ ] Doesn't matter what you
are. What doesn't matter what you do to
yourself, what you change, they will
always be the same [ __ ] forever and
always. It's written in the Bible, lad.
You know. Yeah. Cuz it is a lie most of
the time. So, and I get over it. Yeah.
That's an opinion. They do lie. When
they say they got a boyfriend, nine
times out of 10 they're seven times out
of 10 they're lying. Yeah. They are
lying. Yeah. So, people can have an
opinion if someone's lying.
because they are lying. What are people
not allowed an opinion? They're full of [ __ ]
It doesn't matter if people get married
and have children. There's loads of
lonely people out there. There's single
people out there. There's virgins out
there, lads. You know, there's there's
reasons why people have met people. They
might have got lucky through school.
They might have got lucky on a dating
app that them people are not me, lad. I
don't compare myself to other people
just like I don't compare myself to
virgins just like I don't care I I don't
compare myself to people that's never
kissed a woman. I don't pay attention to
other people in different positions that
got lucky cuz it's not going to change my situation.
They're not going to change my situation.
You know, I'm the same. I'm born alone.
I'll die alone. I don't care who's
better or who's worse. It's not going to
change my situation.
Simple. There's no point thinking about
others because it's not going to change
your situation. I've done what I've had
to do and that's it.
No, bro. No one cares about this Autumn
Rose, bro. She's up. She's up nons's
ass, lad. I don't give a [ __ ] what she
rates me. I don't care. She's a fat ugly
[ __ ] who uses filters.
But yeah, self Greavvesy. What I'm
saying is self-improvement. You're
supposed to do self-improvement. I'm not
knocking self-improvement, but you're
not going to get a woman. You You'd be
better off being a crackhead. If you was
a crackhead, you'd have more chance of
meeting someone, lad.
You You would Whatever you do, you're
going to be in the same situation. Until
you leave this country, you are going to
be in the same situation. It is as
simple as that. You can go like with in
regards to that, it will always be the
same. Always and forever.
Yeah. You're talking about yourselves,
lad. See you later. Your situation will
never change no matter what you do. And
that's not me being negative. Rezy,
don't forget you're old. You're older
than me and I've done more than you.
I've been to so many different places.
I've made so many different friends.
I've approached so many different women.
It will not change. Even if you done the
same thing for 3 years, you're still
going to get [ __ ] around with by
women. Nothing is changing and nothing
is happening. It's as simple as that.
And that's what people need to get in
their head, lad, and then move on with
their life. That's it.
Then that's it, bro. It will never ever
ever Bro, I was going in the old house.
I was working in the old house. No, no,
no changes. No difference. They're
[ __ ] They'll always be [ __ ]
Yeah, simple. Yeah, I laugh at you as
well, you fat, ugly [ __ ]
I laugh at you as well, you fat, ugly
filter using [ __ ] I laugh at you as
well. Guess what? You can never show
yourself without filters, [ __ ] I can.
You can never show yourself without filters, [ __ ]
How about that? Bey loves that. It's the
truth though, is it?
So yeah, I was just talking to my mate,
security guy. And
I don't want you, you fat ugly [ __ ] I
don't want you, you fat [ __ ] Why don't
you come on here right now without
filters? Why don't you come on here
right now without filters?
Come on here right now without filters.
I can do it. I'm not overweight like
you. You're a fat [ __ ] Come on. Why
don't you come on here right now without filters?
Go and have a [ __ ] wank with your you
shitty little [ __ ] [ __ ] You
probably got AIDS, bro. You probably got
[ __ ] AIDS. You [ __ ] stupid little
[ __ ] Nah, no, no, no. You thought I was
going to go and get beaten up.
You thought Timmy was going to beat me
up, mate? Yeah,
you you was waiting for it, weren't you,
mate? You was waiting for it. It would
never happen, mate. It was never going
to happen. Bless you. You thought I was
going to get beaten up. Yeah. Yeah.
Yeah. Yeah. Ah, bro. That's That was
never going to happen under any
circumstances. I'm still here. Yeah. I'm
still here for Grievy. I'm never
leaving. I'm not moving, lad.
Yeah, I'm on it for life now. Simple.
Yeah. No one ran out the house, lad.
Everyone saw what happened, mate. No one
ran out the house. No one ran out the
house, mate. He was the one that ran
away when I was live in the pub that
everyone told me to go to. Yeah.
hiding behind my elderly mom when I
wasn't even in the house. Oh, yeah.
Yeah. Okay, bro. Yeah, yeah, yeah. Okay.
Who do you reckon would have won that
fight, Grezy? Me or Timmy? Go on. Well,
who's your who's your money on?
Who's who's your money on? Go on.
>> If you was going to put your money on
it, lad. If I caught up with that [ __ ]
Ah, you know, bro, is it? You [ __ ] know, lad.
You [ __ ] know, mate. Ain't it? You
know, in it, Grezy. Don't even try to
lie. You know,
I was going to [ __ ] knock him out. I
swear to God, bro. I was I was [ __ ]
running up that road and I was going to
knock him out. Trust me, bro. I swear to
God I was. Yeah. You told me to go to
the [ __ ] pub. I'm looking for a
[ __ ] [ __ ] I'm looking for a
[ __ ] [ __ ] bro. That ain't there.
Reezy, I'm going to knock him out.
Yeah, it's true though, isn't it? Yeah,
it is true. I was just going to give him
one I was going to give him one bang in
his [ __ ] face. Bro, he won't he won't
going to get up. I'm telling you. Yeah.
Yeah. Just one swing, bro. Trust me. My
knuckles are hard as [ __ ] bro. Yeah.
Trust me. I'm going to knock him out.
Remember that? Remember that? Who said?
Who said that? Grezy, who said that?
Do you remember the video? Wednesday.
You know that. You [ __ ] know, lad. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
They were laughing at you, mocking you.
Trust me. I'm going to keep thinking
about that, lad. I'm going to keep
thinking about that. Yeah.
Nothing. We're going on a madness
Thursday, lad. We're going We're going
for a drink Thursday. Stephen Howard.
No, I'm not going out attacking anyone,
mate. I'm ruining people's lives for all
the shitty experiences they've gave me
over the years. Bro, I hope I bump into
this Christian. Izzy, bro. Elen and
Central is not even that far, you know.
Oh, mate. It will be a madness, bro.
It will create a scene, Greavesy. It
will create It will It will It will
literally It will create a scene.
Yeah, it will create a scene, lad. Yeah.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
They've led me on enough times, DH10,
lad. They've they've they've led me on a
[ __ ] with me enough times, lad.
No, I ain't calm down, mate. I'm not
going to calm down. And I'm not going to
calm down either. Yeah, my my pit, bro.
You don't even know how I get money. You
don't know how much money I get. You
don't know how much money I have.
Listen, you keep telling yourself that
autumn. You don't know how much money
people have. You can keep thinking
people are skin. You can keep thinking,
you know, when people get money, that's
on you, man. You know. Yeah.
Yeah, I told a bouncer about this. She
said, "That's insane, bro." I told him everything,
I told him everything, bro. Little [ __ ]
Yeah, man. A lot of women are going to be [ __ ] Yeah.
Will I, lad? Will I really? I bet you I
won't. I bet you I won't, lad. Yeah.
Timmy saying he's coming Thursday, is
he? Mate, no one's getting in my way, lad.
No one's getting in my way, lad. No
one's getting in my way on Thursday.
Trust me, no one's getting in my way.
Okay with you, Greavvesy boss.
Okay with you, boss.
Obviously have to run it by you first,
lad. Okay with you, boss.
And then we need to do the posters as
well, lad. We need to do the posters as well.
I'm sick of these women, bro. I'm sick
of these women [ __ ] I'm sick of them,
lad. I'm sick of them, bro.
Yeah. Pit Thursday. I didn't know I got
money Thursday, lad.
I'm overweight, bro. Talking about
yourselves, lad. I'm not even
overweight. Again, self projecting.
We're just going to stick on women and
managers and people if they try to get
involved. Stephen Albert basically. Yeah.
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Okay, bro. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Okay.
And I'm going to be putting up posters
of Christian Izzy as well.
Bro, again, yourself. We're just going
to ban these little self projectors yet.
We don't have self-reflectors on my channel. Yeah,
posters are [ __ ] going up, mate.
Did you like Did you like Did you like
the last poster videos, Grezy? Did you
like the last posters?
Did you like the last posters?
Did you like the last ones, lad? You
didn't believe me, did you? You didn't
believe me, did you, lad?
No, he definitely was, lad.
Yeah. No, no, no, no, no, no. I'm not
leaving anyone alone. I'm not leaving
anyone alone, lad. I'm not leaving anyone alone. 100%.
100%. Steven Howard. Yeah. Listen.
Listen. You can come on Thursday, can't
you? You [ __ ] [ __ ] And this time,
don't run away because you know, you're
lucky you ran away, you know, cuz I was
going to knock, mate. I was going to
knock you out, mate. You're lucky you
ran away, you know. You're lucky you ran
away and you ran out the area when I was
live in the pub. You was going to get
knocked the [ __ ] out and you know you
was as well. You know you was. What's
this about you being in a chat saying
that you're coming Thursday? Come on
then. Come on. Thursday. I'll be out in
I'll be out in London, bro. You don't
need to go. You You don't need to go in
anyone's door. I'll be out and about.
I'll be out and about, lad. Yeah.
And I will knock you out. Yeah.
We I'm going to knock him out. I swear
to God I'm going to knock him out.
What? Yeah. I heard you said that you're
coming Thursday. Yeah. Oh, yeah. Yeah.
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Really?
Yeah. Yeah. I'm going to knock him out. Yeah. Really?
But no, I'm not leaving her alone,
Leslie. I'm not leaving her alone. The
more you tell me to do it, the more I'm
going to do it. The more you tell me not
to do it, the more I'm going to do it.
And I'm going to send it to her on the
new phone. I'm going to send it to her
on the new phone. Greasy, of like all
the posters and that
okay with you, boss.
Okay with you, boss.
Is that okay with you, boss? Obviously
I have to run it by you first, lad.
Yeah, I have to run it by you first, lad.
Oh, I put him in the internet cuff.
No, the internet cuff, lad. Up the road.
Yeah. Yeah. You want to lead me on for a
month, [ __ ] do you? Yeah. I'm going to
make sure people know exactly what
you're about, lad. I'm going to know.
I'm going to make sure people know
exactly what you're about. You little
leading on little [ __ ]
Yeah. You never hiding under the bed
when I was outside. Yeah. You keep
telling yourself that, lad. Her face and
everything, bro. Her face and
everything. Everything, lad. I've got
her face. I know what she looks like. I
got her pictures.
You want to do it bad or you I gave you
the chance the other day. Do you want to
do it or do you want to do it bad? Yeah.
It's as simple as that. Yeah.
Don't even like this person, but still
it doesn't matter. Last. Yeah.
Or do you want to do it really bad? Do
you want to do it really bad? I'll do it
bad. I'll do it bad.
Yeah. I'll do it really bad, lad.
You want to be start being a [ __ ] Yeah.
And start giving people attitude, do
you, [ __ ] Yeah. Yeah. So, we we will
see who's the first one that's going to
be going to police.
No, I agree. You don't know what she looks like.
He doesn't even know her name.
He don't know her name or nothing. He
only know what she sounds like.
He doesn't know anything.
I don't give a [ __ ] if she's only look
young. I don't care. She's 22. She's old
enough. I don't care.
You know, all of these things that these
exes have done to you in the past. What
I'm going to be doing is worse. What I'm
doing is going to be worse. So, it's
going to be something to add to your
collection. Meet someone on a night out.
People plast up posters all over you,
mate. You know what I'm saying?
All on the same website. You can watch Elmo on.
N all over Elen. She lives in the Elen
area. There you go. I gave you I gave
you some clues, lad. Straight to Elen,
bro. It's not a problem, man. It's not a
problem. It's not a problem.
I'll show you delusional. I'll show you
crazy. I'll show you an attitude, [ __ ]
You want to see crazy? I'll show you crazy [ __ ]
Yeah, this is what you need to do. Uh,
this is what you need to do, Greavvesy,
when I'm saying this stuff. Oh,
everybody knows that you're a crazy
[ __ ] You need to say you need to say
that like periodically. Nah, not the
Central Line, bro. Elizabeth line. The
Elizabeth line goes straight to Elen,
lad. You don't even need to change.
You don't even need to change, lad.
You It's straight Elizabeth line, dusty.
It's straight straight Lizzy line. One train, lad.
One train, bro.
I don't give a [ __ ] if they're 22. I
You know what's so mad is actually it
was actually all right at first,
but she wanted to start being a [ __ ]
Then the Westinity started. Reezy. Then
the Then the Westinity started.
Then the Westinity started, lad. after a month.
Well, they can do what they want, lad.
They can do what they want, lad. They
can do what they want. Yeah.
But that's not in your in your 2026
books. Really? Yeah. That's not in your 2026 books.
You want to see some of these messages, lad?
I will knock you out. Trust me, bro. Any
anyone that wants to get involved, I'm
going to knock them out, bro. I'm going
to show I'm going to show everyone where
I am on Thursday. Yeah.
How about generally? I'm quite scared of
you. Yeah. Cuz you don't like the truth. [ __ ] hell. We see.
They're a [ __ ] kid to me, lad. 22 is
a kid to me, bro. Yeah.
No, I don't let people out, mate. I'm not desperate.
So they did they did they delete my
number before Grevy?
Uh well no cuz they led me on and played games. Yeah.
Yeah. Yeah. Because they led me on and
played games. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
Yeah. Cuz they led me on and played
games. Make sure you add that bit,
Leslie. Make sure you add that bit, lad.
Because when you're saying that
someone's a young When you're saying
that someone doesn't want to date
someone, that's somebody that walks
away. That's someone that says they've
got a boyfriend. That's not somebody
that sits there. That's not someone that
sits there for a month and starts
leading people on. So, big difference.
Yeah, big difference, lad. Big
difference. I think you'll find
big difference. Nope. Wasn't allegedly.
It was led on. Not allegedly. It was led
on. Nothing alleged about it, mate.
Mate, the only M is you, lad. The only m
you, bro. You people don't show
yourselves. The only ugly people, you
people in this community, lad. You You
people in this community has not even
been seen with a woman.
Like you people are the actual muners.
The real life muners. You've never even
been with a woman, lad. Uh, no. It's not
my opinion. It's facts. It's messages.
So, it's facts. Having an opinion is
saying God exists and then someone else
saying God doesn't exist. Uh, it's not
an opinion. It's facts in black and
white like Tom and Jerry in black and
white. You remember like Tom and Jerry
when it was black and white years ago?
Uh evidence is not an opinion. It's a
fact. That's the difference between
opinions and facts.
You know, lad, you know Steven Howard,
you know the drill, lad. I'm never going
to stop. I'll never leave them alone.
You know what I'm like, bro. I You know
what I'm like. I will never leave them
alone. I will never ever ever ever ever
leave them alone. Never ever ever ever ever.
Poor girl. Defending the women just cuz
they're a woman. Loser.
Defending women again. Loser.
Oh. Anything to defend women. You loser.
He's another one that thinks women can't
do no wrong. What a [ __ ] loser.
Another s. Another white knight.
Probably another virgin as well, lad.
Because it tends to be virgins that do
that. Oh, poor girl. Yeah, they don't
lead people on. Yeah, poor women.
They're so innocent. Oh, I'm going to
cry. Women are so perfect and so
innocent. They can't lead people on. Oh,
poor girl. Poor women. They're so
innocent. Give me a tissue. Give me Give
me I'm going to cry. I'm going to cry,
lad. Give me a tissue. All women are
innocent just for having a [ __ ] in
between their legs. Give me a tissue,
mate. Cry me a [ __ ] river, lad. Cry
me a [ __ ] river.
Cry me a river. That's so sad. Having a
[ __ ] in between your legs makes you poor
all of a sudden, mate. Oh, Jesus Christ.
Oh, [ __ ] hell. Crying, lad.
[ __ ] hell. Oh, cuz they got a cut in
between their legs.
No substance, no nothing. Just straight
to defending the one with a fatty
between their legs. Isn't that right,
Grezy? Just because they've got a fatty
in between their legs. Just because
they've got a smelly [ __ ] in between
their legs. Oh, poor girl. Poor women.
They're so innocent. Oh, yeah. Right, man. Yeah.
Bless. Bless them, lad. Oh, bless.
So, Greg, you know what you're talking
about, lad? You know when you're saying
about people being angels,
right? Women being angels and stuff.
This is what these people are doing.
That's what these people are doing.
Yeah. Calling someone a virgin. Yeah.
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
One second. I need to go downstairs.
Defending women just cuz they're women.
What losers? They're doing the same I
agree with you. They're doing the same
thing as what you were saying.
thinking women are angels. They're doing
the same defending women tactics again.
They're doing the same loser [ __ ] lads.
Defending women for being women. No
substance, not interested in the story.
They're doing the same thing as what you
was talking about. Yeah, lad.
was complaining about, lad. Defending women.
Yeah. No women would ever want you
either. You're a virgin, lad.
Yeah. Same to you, lad. No woman would
ever want you.
[ __ ] sick. [ __ ] white man.
>> Yeah, they'll never want you either. You
[ __ ] virgin m.
Just like you, you mter. Little spazp pants.
Well, tell tell Well, tell that to these people, Greasy.
Don't tell me that, lads. Tell these
people. They're the ones saying, "Oh,
poor girl. They couldn't possibly do
anything wrong. Poor girl."
Did you hear what they were saying? That
they were offended. them just cuz
they're women. [ __ ] little simps.
Little white knights.
Yeah, little white knights.
Poor girl. Poor women.
Poor girl. Poor women. They can't do nothing wrong.
Yeah, you're calling me a virgin even
though I proved they had sex, lad.
Yeah, you're you're calling someone a
virgin that's proved they've had sex. I
think you'll find that you're on a m and
[ __ ] you and [ __ ] your ugly kids as
well. If you do have kids, they're ugly as [ __ ]
If you do have kids, I bet they're as
ugly and munish as you. I bet I bet your
kids are more of a mun than you. Your m
kids. No wonder why you're so bitter.
Your kids are the actual bunters. You
see bunters every day, which are your
kids. Yeah. They probably get bullied
for being a buna. The brist of the ba.
So, you're another one. I told you
multiple times. I'll show you the
messages. You don't want to see the
messages. You're not interested.
We get it. You're not interested. You
>> cuz you cuz you because you made a statement, right? >> Right.
And I'm cuz I want to show you why I
feel the way I do and show you the
messages, but you keep ignoring it. So
if someone keeps So I will show you
everything that you want and it seems
that you're just defending them for
being a woman,
>> right? Okay.
>> Okay. But I But you're saying something
and I'm trying to show you it, but you
keep talking over you me. Yeah.
>> You keep talking over me. You're another
one. So does someone So does Okay. So
does someone have to do anything bad?