Sorry about that, bro. I got a bit heated. Yep. Sorry, man.
Don't even think that steak was cooked properly.
We're back to how we was two months ago.
Two months. About two months ago now.
So yeah, it got heated, lads. Sorry
about that. Had to end the live stream.
Sorry about that. Yep. Yeah. What's the
Mr. G respond back. Nah, he never Yeah.
>> Yeah, bro.
Yeah, I was just arguing
about to end the live stream, bro.
Yeah. Can you hear me?
Don't know, bro. Yep.
Just had some steak.
I'll probably be in bed all day
tomorrow. I didn't brush my teeth today,
bro. I noticed I didn't brush my teeth.
I think we're back to being depressed
again, lads. Damn. Bit like 2 months
ago, ain't it? Back to how we were 2
months ago. That sucks, bro. That took
so long to get out of that, you know,
bro. Couple weeks and now we're just
slipping back into it again.
Sad, sad, sad, sad, sad.
You know, I wish I wish I could laugh,
bro. But like, you can't even laugh at
it. It's that sad, lad. You can't even
laugh at it.
Sad, sad, sad, sad, sad. This is exactly
why I got away from this. Tried to get
away from this [ __ ] you know. Yep. Yeah, that's that.
Yeah, I don't know how I didn't brush my
teeth today. What the [ __ ]
That's mad. Where's Bust my teeth, bro?
What the [ __ ]
Sad life in it. Sad sad sad life. Yeah.
Can you hear me or can you not hear me? Yeah.
I was trying to explain it to Laney. She wouldn't listen.
Um, I told her I had bad experiences.
She just didn't listen. Um, she said she
listened, but she didn't. I said, "I can
show you the proof." Weren't interested.
So, yeah. I mean, for [ __ ] sake, bro.
It's It's mad.
It's like you against the world, you
know? Even when you got evidence of what
they've done, people still people still
dismiss it. And I don't know how that's
possible, but that's what they're like.
That's what people are like, you know?
how they can ignore.
Oh, look. I'm banned on Instagram now
for seven days.
How did that work?
Banned from messaging for 7 days.
Oh well, I don't have anything to say to
any [ __ ] anyways. So,
she was just basically making excuses for them.
Bit like what people do on here. bit
like what people do on Reddit. So just
that's the way it is. People just make
excuses for them.
Tell them multiple times. They led me
on. I've been going through it for
years. I sent it to Ant-Man. I said,
"Well, at least Ant-Man's mom
understood. And Ant-Man's not been
through half the [ __ ] I have." And she
just wouldn't understand. She wouldn't
she wouldn't get it.
So bit like most people, they don't understand it.
Sad, sad, sad, lad.
They just they just make up stuff, isn't it?
They just make up stuff.
Yep. They just make up stuff.
I'll show you.
>> No, I can't give examples. run. I'm too tired.
That's not good, is it?
That's not good, eh?
You'll never change, lad. never change.
You just go backwards in this country.
That's what happens. You just go
backwards in this country. I don't know
if anyone else feels the same way, but you know,
you just go backwards in this country
with women, with people, with weather.
That's all that happens. You just get
[ __ ] over. That's all that ever
happens. And that's all that will ever happen.
So, you know what I said to my mom as
well? I said, "You can say that I'm
this. You can say that I'm that." And I
said, "But guess what? I'm not a
narcissist like these women." Couldn't
say nothing. Couldn't say a damn thing.
I said, "At least I don't block people
and and and leave people blocked and
stuff like I could never do that to
anyone." Couldn't say anything.
nothing at all that the truth. Yeah.
What people do make me mad. Even if I
don't like the person, doesn't matter. I
don't like what people do, lad. Simple as that.
You got to understand that all of these things are
collapsing the faces. Do you not understand?
All of these things that happen, it's
just another slap in the face.
It's like being kicked to the ground,
right? Trying to get back up and then
someone keeps kicking you and kicking
you and kicking you until you eventually
die. That's that's what it, you know,
that's that's the analogy I can use.
You get me, bro. That's the only analogy
I can use.
I was going to stand this [ __ ] up, but
they blocked me cuz I was talking about
someone else, someone I met from Tinder.
I was just going to I could have [ __ ]
them over, good and proper, but I was
talking about someone else and [ __ ] So,
they literally they blocked me.
N just fed up and depressed. I think I'm
going to stay in bed all day tomorrow.
I think we're going to be back to that
again, lad. 10 steps forward and 24
steps back. Good old England.
It will always be the same here.
Just as I know.
Just as you know, lad.
It will always be the same here. It's
depressing as [ __ ] bro. I want out of
this shitty country.
Seriously, I actually do, lad.
Yeah. Tomorrow is going to be exactly
the same as today. Nothing's changing in
this country. Nothing's getting better.
Nothing ever has and nothing ever will.
It's end of story, bro.
Tomorrow's a new day in the same country
with the same women, the same people,
with the same [ __ ]
Well, it does. Well, to be fair, it does get worse.
So, to be honest with you, I say it
doesn't change, but it gets worse. But
[ __ ] Do you know what I mean, lad?
Yeah. A new week with the same
experiences. New week. I mean, how many
different years has there been? And it's
been the same [ __ ] every year.
It's been the same [ __ ] every year.
How does Ant-Man's mom understand? But
my mom don't understand when I've been
through way more [ __ ] than he has. I
don't understand that one. But hey ho.
Nah. Never, lad. Nah. All I'm thinking
about now is revenge. See, because I've
been [ __ ] over again, rap boy. All I
think about is revenge. That's what I'm
like, bro. I was like this a couple of
months ago for like two weeks. And then
I gave And then I done it for like two
weeks. Every day I was getting these
mood swings. Then they went away. Then it went,
"Oh, for myself, lad. For all the [ __ ]
they've done to me over the years, you know. So yeah,
I don't know, man.
Yeah. What is tomorrow? Yeah, it's Monday tomorrow.
Yeah, same old [ __ ] next week as well.
Always be the same here. Always be the
Yeah, two weeks I was like this for,
bro. Whole two weeks. Like two months ago.
Don't care that I probably go to sleep
at like 6:00 in the morning.
Yeah. When the birds come out singing
just like the good old days, eh?
You don't need to know that, lads. You
don't need to know that.
Yeah. This is We're just You're just
going around in circles, lad. In this
country, you're just going to go around in circles.
That's all that's happening here.
Bad experiences feel like [ __ ] Bad
experiences feel like [ __ ] This is all
that's ever going to happen is always
going to be the same error.
It's been proven many times. Many, many,
So yeah, I'll be in bed tomorrow doing nothing.
Same old [ __ ]
You live, you get bad experiences, you die. Done.
I can. I can. I can and I will. I can
I can. Trust me. And you can watch me do
it. I will, lad. I will. I can blame the
entire countries when most people are
[ __ ] I've worked in this country.
I know what people are like. I know what
women are like. So, I mean, I can when
I've experienced more than him. When
I've got more experience than that said
friend, and I'm agreeing with him. I
definitely can. The country is [ __ ] The country shambles.
You got gay people telling you, trying
to tell you what you can and can't do.
You got women that are [ __ ] You got
[ __ ] the weather that is [ __ ] You
got to wait around for [ __ ]
everything. You got [ __ ] homeless
people on the street that's from this
country. Oh, I'll keep on blaming the
country. Definitely. Definitely keep on
blaming the country.
Definitely love I will love I'll keep
blaming good old England cuz that's what
it is. It's a [ __ ] [ __ ] [ __ ] country.
Everything's a negative here.
Everything's just a negative here.
Everything's a slap in the face here. Yeah.
Everything's a slap in the face and it
gets worse every year as well.
[ __ ] that up, bro.
So yeah, that's the way it is, man.
Oh, you're not coming into me. You're
[ __ ] lad. See you later.
You don't have spastics on the channel,
lad. It's Timmy that's trying to join. [ __ ] off.
Yeah. The only reason I haven't gone to
Birmingham is because my mom said, "Oh,
don't go. Don't go. I don't want the
fighting and that." That's another thing
she brought up. She said, "Oh, you can't
you can't go for a man." I said, "How
many men have I gone for?" I said, "I
literally would would go to Birmingham
and you didn't want me going. I
literally told you I'd go and smash the
[ __ ] out of him. You didn't want me go.
Now he's trying to use it against me.
You know what I'm saying? Like now he's
trying to use the [ __ ] thing against me.
You're not coming in, lad. You do your
own little videos. I'm not arguing with
a [ __ ] bro. See you later, lad. Yep.
She wasn't understanding the thing with the women.
Even though I explained it multiple
times, I offered to show her messages on
my phone. She just weren't interested.
So, people like that can't be helped.
They got their way of thinking and
that's that, lad.
They want to think that they're
innocent. Let them think that, lad. I
know my experiences.
I know what they're like.
And that's it.
I know the way it's always going to be here.
Oh, wow. Is that Sig?
One second. And I think I found that on Facebook.
Let me have a little look. Is that
Oh, it is. [ __ ] hell.
Why is that just popped up? That's weird.
Living in London.
Yeah, that's good, lad.
I've quit life. So, He's
quit YouTube. I've quit life. So yeah. Yeah. Okay.
Yeah, I've quit live, lad. [ __ ] that.
I'm back to where I was two months ago.
looking at some people on uh Facebook headache, bro.
Funny how Antman's mom understands when
he hasn't really been through that much.
Well, he has, but obviously not as much as me.
Pisses me off, lad. You know it used to as well.
Yeah, I found Sig on Facebook.
That's weird cuz I don't have Sig's number.
It popped up. That's weird. New Zealand.
Definitely you, mate. That's weird.
Why did that come up?
Don't know. Don't care.
Timmy lost. Timmy lost 400 lb in that
machine in it.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah,
yeah, yeah. dead.
Lane was trying to talk [ __ ] about the
Timmy thing as well. Said, "Oh, well,
you don't do it to a man." I said,
"Mate, firstly, I went back. Second of
all, I went to the pub that I was told
to go to." Then I said, "Oh, okay. I'll
go to Birmingham." Then you didn't want
me to go to Birmingham.
So, which one is it?
Can't have two sides of a coin, mate.
You know what I mean?
She's going a lot away. That sig, man.
What the [ __ ]
[ __ ] hell, man. Yeah, that's mad.
as I know lad she was sticking up for
women as well
even though I offered to show her the
messages and mash just weren't interested.
So people like that can't be can't be helped
which is why which to be fair is why
that's why I used to say like you can't
um complain about this stuff because
they're always just going to defend
women no matter what they've done and stuff.
That's why I always said like there's no
point saying anything because they're
always just going to make excuses for
them no matter what they do. And no, no,
no. You know, you know,
they would always make excuses for the
shitty things that they do.
That's why I always said like there's no
point ever saying anything about it cuz
you're never going to get fair advice.
You're never going to get a fair answer
cuz obviously the the Yeah.
So that's that.
And then they'll somehow find a way to
put the blame onto you.
Happens every time, lad.
No, I don't want people to tell me anything.
I mean, you've been shown evidence of
what they've done and you still argue. I
mean, that's the kind of people we're
dealing with. People that argue with
black and white leading on, black and
white being [ __ ] Even some of my
approaches, I think I've approached
people and they've been [ __ ] before.
So, you're showing all this evidence and
then you still deny it. Like, how is
that even possible, bro? It's like going
to court. Yeah. Pleading not guilty to
murdering someone and expecting not to
get convicted, bro. Evidence is is
evidence, but you still counteract it
and try to make up stuff and add on
things that aren't there. It's in
denial, lad. It truly is in denial. It
really is in denial. You know, when
you're shown something
and then you're still trying to deny it,
like you're delusional, bro. How do you
not see that? How do you not know that? You know,
this is why I got away from the dating
thing. This is why I stopped going out.
This is one of the reasons why I stopped this [ __ ] you know. But no, it's madness.
It's depressing as well. It's depressing
what they do. You don't even need to
like them, bro.
They still do these things. People make
excuses for them.
[ __ ] hell, bro.
I hate him, bro. I hate him.
That's an ant as well.
No. Showing showing my mom women that
have led me on. Big difference. No. No.
No. No. No. Women that have led me on
and played games. Again, listen. You can
try to mix it and twist things all you
want, but evidence is evidence of what
they've done. No, no, no. From women
that have led me on and wasted my time
and gave me false hope. Big difference.
Yeah. There's a there's a fine line.
There's a fine black line. Yeah. No, no,
no. Women that have led me on and play
games. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
Which which explaining does which Yeah.
Which is what they have done. So yeah,
you need to add that bit in there as
well, lad, cuz that's a that's a big thing.
Led people on and make people feel like
[ __ ] That's another one with a couple
of them. You need to add them things on
there as well, lad. Cuz the messages
don't lie. The messages don't lie.
The messages don't lie, lad.
Evil, evil, evil bastards.
You know what I said to my mom as well?
If I could turn back time, bro, when I
had that house, I would have moved to
another country and just lived off that
lived off that money from the house or
um I would have just I would have went
out drinking. Honestly, if I could turn
back if I could turn back time, that's
what I would do.
I would have never spoke to any of them [ __ ]
Add what you want, but trust me, I've
never met what I've never met someone
your age doing. Well, they [ __ ] do.
There's plenty of women that do that,
lads. I've got the messages.
No, I'm talking generally, pending. No,
I'm talking generally, bro. It's not one
person. It's not two people. It's
generally the whole the whole thing,
lad. It's what's happened in the past
and what will happen in the future with
various different people.
It's not one person, lad. It's loads of different things.
Oh, well, well, she wasn't listening.
Well, my mom wasn't listening. So, what
did you want me to do? I tried to
explain to her the same thing over and
over again. She wouldn't listen. I said,
"Okay, do you want me to show you my messages?"
She wouldn't have it. So, then just shush then.
Then, shush. If you're not going to read
what they've done, then stop it. Simple.
Yeah, I would have done a lot of things
different if I could turn back time lap
time. Turn back time, lad. I already
lost two years to one [ __ ] Two years of my life,
you know, because all because of this
dating [ __ ] Two years I'm never going
to get back. You know,
I would have done things a lot
different, bro. Trust me. I would have
got out of it a I would have got out of
it ASAP, lad.
After about 3 to four months of trying,
I would have left. I would have got the
[ __ ] out of this country. That's what I
would have done
when I was 23, 24.
That's what I would have done, lad.
Not these nasty, nasty, horrible women.
I would have just left. I would have got
the [ __ ] out of here. simple.
You know, there's no there's no life in
England. There's nothing for you in
There's nothing here, lad.
So, we need to make a plan and get out
of it, lad, or we're just going to be in
the same boat forever.
And that's that. Sadly, that's it. Yeah. Do That's that.
See, the thing is it's not even about
people's age, you know, being 22, 23,
being young, cuz they will like it. I
mean, you get 37 year olds that will
[ __ ] like it, you know? I had
[ __ ] I had I had I had Jane message
me now. I'm thinking, bro, and this
[ __ ] in her 40s and she's messaged me
over YouTube. Well up, man. [ __ ]
hell. They never change. No matter how
old they are, they never change.
All the same, lad. All the [ __ ] same. So,
yeah, this [ __ ] messaged me over
YouTube. I just ignore the I just ignore the emails.
Sick of the emails.
I'm sick of the Oh [ __ ]
Yeah, this is someone that's 40 odd and
they never stop their [ __ ] They never
I will hunt. There's that
[ __ ] [ __ ] Then you got gay
people telling you what you can and well
trying to tell you what you can and
can't do. What country is this, bro?
What [ __ ] old country is this really?
It's [ __ ] March. It's [ __ ] raining.
Got people leaving their own people on
the street. What the [ __ ] is this country, bro?
Takes the whole enjoyment out of going
out, I reckon.
It takes the whole enjoyment out of going out.
Things got really fat.
What the [ __ ] happened, man?
Jesus Christ. He's fat as [ __ ] man.
That is mad, bro. I don't know why she's
popping up on my Facebook. I don't have her number. That's weird. Oh gosh.
Oh, no. No, no, no, no.
This is still making community post.
Don't know how someone like that can
make community post on me, bro. But
world's gone mad. How someone that's ran
away from me multiple times can make.
And then you see people in the comments
going along with it like, "This guy
didn't get run out of the area by me
three times." I mean, what I done to
Launch Legs was worse than what Timmy
done to me. Timmy only acted the big man
on the door for like a minute and then
ran away and I tried to meet him. Tried
to catch him and then I tried to meet
him when this little [ __ ]
got ran out of the area for three times.
Three times I ran this car out of his
area. Then I pull up posters and then
you're coming on here like the big man mad.
That's crazy, bro. And then people just
go along with it. How does that make sense?
That don't make no sense, lad.
Telling me I wouldn't dare fight any
man. Did your Did your Did your
boyfriend fight me when I was in his
area three times putting up posters?
You went to You resorted to running to
the police. No, no, no, no, mate. Mate,
listen. Listen. I put up posters in
Nonsex's area and I had him off of
YouTube for two weeks. Adam stopped
going to that event for a very long
time. Timmy never stopped me leaving
stop me leaving the house. Timmy didn't
stop me going on YouTube.
No, no, that was that was definitely
worse, mate. He probably had to walk
different ways because he knew he was
probably going to get battered. So, you
had all this stuff done to you. You
didn't do anything and you're and you're
trying to call other people cowards.
How is that possible, bro? The biggest
coward on YouTube
is is is trying to to call me a [ __ ]
[ __ ] you people need your head
examining, lads. You really do. You got
something wrong with you, man.
That is I don't know what to say, bro.
I went to the cunt's area three times. I
put up posters all over the area. Had
him running off of YouTube for two
weeks. And he's acting the big man,
trying to say I would never fight any man.
What the [ __ ] Where was you when I was
live in your area twice? Where was you
when I was live doing [ __ ] posters?
What the [ __ ] lad? You're mad.
Cowards don't have no shame, lad.
Cowards don't have no shame.
And you made sure you was never going to
bump into me. You made sure you was
never ever going to bump into me ever. I
was about to bump into Timmy. We must
have missed each other by seconds. Then
I tried to meet him again where they
told me he was. So, I made active
efforts to try to catch the [ __ ] before
he went back home. You never done nothing.
You literally done nothing but call the
police. I don't know why my mom called
the police. I don't know why. I never
asked her to. Maybe just to get the
[ __ ] out the [ __ ] I don't know why she did.
I couldn't tell you. But I never called
the police. You called the police on me
when I put a postage in your area, mate.
And you've been trying to annoy people
for years and years and years. You are
the ultimate coward ever. Like you would
never ever meet anyone ever. No. No one.
You would never meet anyone.
>> Yeah. Well, it's funny how Launch Legs
didn't try to meet me after I put up
posters of him. Is it? But I don't see
you on e channel cuz you're biased. I
don't see you on e channel. Yeah.
Yeah, and I've already fought Timmy
before as well. And I've actually fought
Timmy before as well. This cunt's never
fought me. So, he's got to be the
biggest coward ever. Then he's trying to
talk about me not meeting people.
Little virgin. The little virgin that
dates disabled women.
[ __ ] little virgin. How many times
did you go crying to the police? You
skin. Well, I might just do a video on
this [ __ ] in it. Cuz you just get
addicted to these people's stupidity. Like,
I might just say, "Come and meet me
tomorrow. I'll beat you up and then I'll
go Birmingham if you want." I mean, we
could do that if you want since you're
making so many community post. I'll I'll
smash the [ __ ] out of you and I'll go
Birmingham tomorrow. No, no, no, no, no.
But he does community post on people and
he harasses people and he harasses women
that people have been with. So mate,
it's fair game. You've got a channel,
you've got channel dedicated to people.
You've got a channel harassing people.
So it's fair game, lad.
Simple. Where were you when people are
putting up posters in your area? You're
not saying anything to anyone's face.
You're not doing or saying anything to anyone's face.
It's like right now if I started if I
started going around being racist
and then somebody wanted to meet me or
come in the door, I can't turn around
and say, "Oh, well, no. No, lad.
You're a coward, mate. You've been
making community posts on people for
years and you will never meet anyone
ever. You will make sure no meat ever happens,
but then you'll go running to the police
like a coward." Like, and this is what I
mean. Like you can't talk about no one,
bro. Like absolutely no one. Like I've
already fought to me. I fought a few
people in this community.
You know, you make sure you never get caught.
You make sure you never ever get caught.
No matter what, no matter what the
circumstances are, you make sure you
never get caught. And that's it.
Biggest coward [ __ ] ever.
No, no, no. Nons is the biggest coward on here,
man. You're the one that got rejected by
Britney. That's why you got to date
disabled women, lad. But I don't care
about all of that. I'm just saying that
you can't talk about anyone. Um,
calling people that trying to call
people Elliot Rogers when, bro, I've had
more women than you and I've never been
with a disabled girl. What does that
make you then? You must be the proper incel.
having to date disabled women because
you can't get anything normal. You must
be the proper incel then. You must be
one of the first incelss to be met. Do
you know what I mean? I mean, look at
all the people that you've been with.
Like, you can't talk about anyone.
You know, you can't you can't talk about
no one, bro.
You can't even try and [ __ ] stir. Like,
keep doing what you do, lad. That's
fine, man. You can keep making community
posts. Don't try and [ __ ] stir, though.
Like, I've not been to your shitty area
three times live and had you running
every time. Like, bro, come on now.
Let's Let's not be silly now. Come on.
You know, let's really really really not
be silly now, lad.
It's because it's ridiculous. You know,
LJ can say stuff, LT can say stuff,
other people can say stuff, but a coward
virgin like you can't say nothing. You
You can't talk about anyone, lad.
You have never tried. You have never put
yourself in danger.
Um like I have multiple times I put
myself in danger when I didn't even know
what the person looked like. Yeah.
And I [ __ ] have, mate, with the bomb
with Terry. I didn't know what these
people look like. This was back before I
gave a [ __ ] but I before I knew what it
was on this community. I put myself in
so many mad situations, but you people
have got selective memory. Where was you
ever trying to meet me? Never.
And London Taylor can say, "Oh, I've
said stuff to him in the past." But
listen, you have got a channel dedicated
to stalking someone and you will never
say anything to anyone's face.
Never, never, ever, ever, ever say
anything to anyone's face.
You just show your ugly face on YouTube
making community posts trying to talk
about other people. You ugly [ __ ]
Any Rogers, when you're the one with the
disabled girl, lad, I've been with way
more women than you. just cuz I speak my
mind and I don't simp over women. I'm
going to do a video on this kind anyways, lad.
And if he wants to meet, I'll meet him
tomorrow and I'll go Birmingham tomorrow.
I'll go Birmingham tomorrow if you want.
If you meet me, I'll go Birmingham
tomorrow and everyone can get involved.
Like, it's simple as that, bro. Like,
you need to stop this, bro. You're the
one that got run out your own area. It's
very easy to say stuff after. Yeah, it's
very easy to say stuff after,
you know. It's very easy to say stuff
after it happened.
My money is in on entrepreneurs day.
Nope. I've already got plenty of money, lad.
You don't know what I have and you don't
know what I don't have.
One second, bro. My friend sent me a voice message.
One second. I'm just listening to this
voice message. One sec.
Women bully me. All him. Trust me. The
only one that gets bullied is women.
I've made them change their number. I've
messaged their family. I've shouted in
their face. I bullied one in the park.
Oh, trust me. No woman bullies me, lad.
No woman bullies me, lad. Trust me. The
only thing I' they've ever done is got
bullied by me, lad. Trust me. Trust me.
No [ __ ] stupid c woman bullies me,
mate. Trust me. Never has. Never would.
I bullied one Monday as well. I bullied
one Monday as well. Told her [ __ ] off
and let's come outside. [ __ ] her pants,
bro. Anyways, I'll be right back, dude. Yo, listen. Autumn,
I've been with more women than your
[ __ ] stupid nonsle's [ __ ]
boyfriend. You do realize that, ain't
it? You're a manta, Autumn. You're a
manta, lad. Do you do you you you use
you used filters and you're still ugly
about how about that on filters supposed
to like cover up uglinesses. You're ugly
as [ __ ] bro. You look like a [ __ ]
DeWolf, mate. You're ugly as [ __ ] How
are you trying to talk about anyone
else, mate? [ __ ] me. You're an ugly
[ __ ] And I'm not even just saying that.
Use filters and you're still fat. You're
still Listen, show yourself without
filters. I can do it. Why can't you do
it? That's all I'm asking. Just show
yourself without filters. The only
people that say you're attractive are
these losers of this community when half
of them are [ __ ] virgins. Yeah. Half
of them are [ __ ] virgins on this
community. They're the only people that
say you're not ugly. And that's not even
me trying to be nasty. Like you are an absolute m.
You're an absolute you are an absolute m. Yeah.
You can't even get a man in real life.
Why do you think you're on here trying
to get attention from men?
the truth. What I'm saying, I'm not even
being nasty, bro.
It's the truth.
That's it. So, yo, [ __ ] just show
yourself without filters and then come
back in it. That's all I can say, lad.
Then talk about the way people look.
I may be a M, but you could never, bro.
I don't want you. I don't want to get
this. I don't want to get this, mate.
[ __ ] off. I don't want to get this. I I
don't want no part of you, mate.
[ __ ] fat become, mate. Yeah.
>> No [ __ ] no woman on YouTube's my
type. Do you think I care about any
woman on YouTube, lads? I When people
have got a life outside of YouTube, this
stuff doesn't matter to them. People
like L J and that they ain't got a life
out of YouTube. They don't go out and
meet people. They can't approach people.
That's why they give you attention.
These people that are giving you
attention, W people that don't even
leave the house.
And your [ __ ] little boyfriend nons
keep talking [ __ ] when he's the biggest
runaway man ever.
That's funny, lad. You know, these
people are so stupid. It's hard to
ignore them sometimes.
No one could ever put posters up of me,
lad. I would have been in Birmingham
that same day, mate. If anyone put up
posters of me, Yeah. like when the whole
Trino thing was going on, I didn't know
where they were, bro. So, you let a man
come to your area, put up posters of
you, and you done nothing? Are you
crazy, lad? Are you Yeah, he's got a
disabled girlfriend. Yeah, I don't
You're right. I don't want a disabled
girlfriend and I will never have a
disabled girlfriend because I don't go
for spastics cuz I'm not an ugly [ __ ]
like him. I'm not an ugly disabled [ __ ]
Yeah. Calling people a virgin that's
proved they've had sex, lad, it's boring
now, lad. It's boring. Calling people a
virgin that's proved they've had sex. It
just makes you look like the virgin.
Same as Timmy, bro. Like when you're
doing stuff like that, you're just
putting yourself on Timmy's level.
You're just you're you know, you're
putting yourself on Timmy's level when
you're doing that and it's just making
you look like a virgin. Doesn't bother
me. Like I'm just telling you what it
makes you look like cuz the thing is,
bro, is like the only people that that
still say that are actual virgins
themselves. So you're just making
yourself look like Timmy when you're
saying that. No offense, but you you actually are.
Calling someone like me a virgin. It
just proves that you're the virgin.
It's I'm just saying, bro. Trying to
give a bit of advice. It makes you look
silly. Silly Billy. It makes you look
really silly. You know that.
Everyone knows I bang more women than
anyone on this community, lad. I've
shown more women than anyone on this community.
So why are you going to call people a virgin?
That doesn't make sense, bro. It really
makes no sense.
And do you know another thing I'm going
to tell you as well? You know, when you
do stuff like this, this is why people
don't show you money anymore. This is
why people don't do certain things anymore.
This is why people don't do certain things anymore.
I'm just giving you the heads up
cuz look at what you're doing. You know
what I mean? [ __ ] hell, man.
Just silly. All it is is silly, lad.
Just silly as [ __ ] lad. You're calling
someone like me a virgin. How does that
even make sense?
You need to grow up, man. A lot of you
people in this community have got a lot
of growing up to do. You know that
you're older than me, man. [ __ ] You got
a lot going up to do you people in this community, lad.
Yeah. Someone made up posted on me, man.
I would have I would have caught them
that same day. I think anyone would.
Even if someone's not about anything,
you know, you done nothing but come off
YouTube for 2 weeks. Anyone can act the
hard man after it's all done. You
understand? After all these things are
well and done, you can easily act the
odd man. Oh, you didn't make me do this.
Oh, you didn't make me do that. That's
like me saying the same [ __ ] to someone
that breaks into my house two years
later. Anyone can do this.
Why can't you get a woman, Leslie? Why
can't you get a woman? Same thing to
you, self projector.
That's the same thing to you. Why can't
you get a woman? You should ask yourself
that question. Oh, [ __ ] Shut up.
Yeah. So, you need to ask yourself that question,
you know. You need to ask yourself,
yeah, but I'm doing something with my
life. I'm leaving. That's the thing. I'm
getting out of here. So,
you know, I'm doing I'm doing something
with you people who sit on YouTube for
15 years calling people what you are
yourselves every day.
Unless you're going to meet anyone
yourself, you need to stop calling
people a coward, lad. You made about
four or five posts.
Yeah. Okay, bro. Yeah, I'm a virgin, lad. Okay.
Yeah. Okay, bro. Interesting enough,
>> No. No, no, no, no, no, no, no.
You people in your 40s still on YouTube.
That's a madness, man.
That's what you call a [ __ ] madness.
answer because you are the M lads.
You're talking about yourself. Anyways,
we're not going to react to your little
self-reflecting comments. Anyways,
they're self-reflecting comments.
I want to know why you make community
posts trying to egg people on to fight
and stuff like that's I want an answer.
I want to actually read a community
post, bro. I think it'd be interesting. You know,
you know what I mean, lad.
I've got a new channel.
I want you to like write a community
post and just like answer it to me. I'd
love to know, you know.
No, I'm going to do a video actually.
It's round about time, but I actually I
actually want some like responses on
this community post. 1 second.