Uh-uh.
Let's see who's on YouTube first thing
in the morning, eh? Let's see.
Maybe it will stay to zero. The number
will stay to zero. Who knows? With a better luck.
Today is the day for nothing, bro. I
mean, it's Monday.
New week, same old, same country. I
mean, what what are you expecting?
You people, man. Like you really you
really got to get your um you really got
to get your brains tested.
How you think anything is ever going to
change in this country is beyond me,
lad. Like you got to be you got to be
trolling at this point.
Nothing happens and nothing changes.
That's my slogan. Nothing happens and nothing changes.
That's my little saying. Everyone's got
their own little saying, but that's mine
anyways cuz it's the truth, lad.
Stop leading Stop leading people to
false hope. It's the same as It's like
It's the same as leading a horse to
water, but then the the the horse is not
getting the water. Poor [ __ ]
The horse is starving. You keep leading
him, leading them closer to the water
only for the water to get ped down the
sink. [ __ ] Poor [ __ ]
Do you get me? Shouldn't give people
false hope. It will never change here.
The only thing that will happen here is
life will just get worse that in in
this, you know,
it's only down from now, lad. That's
that. That's what people need to
realize, man. It's okay. You know, we
can take it. We're adults. You know,
nothing will ever change ever.
That's that. It will never change and
you know it. So that's that.
There's nothing less to There's nothing
less to say.
It could be 2 weeks, 3 weeks, four
years. It will always be the same.
Not suddenly going to change, is it?
Come on, lad. Let's Let's look at Look
at the odds. It's never going to change.
I'm leaving soon anyways, bro. So it's
not a problem at all. [ __ ] this.
been dealing with this [ __ ] for too long
now, lad. [ __ ] that. So
yeah, I'll be out this depressing country.
What's that, man?
Nothing will ever change. Nothing will
ever happen. So I don't know why people
say that. They're kind of cool, you
know, giving people false hope. You
know, people in this community,
people are not different. Women are no
It's just annoying talking about it. I
don't even like talking about it. It's
annoying, bro. It's like such an energy
um zap. It actually is. It's depressing.
It really really is. But anyways, I
don't know. I don't know. Social
experiment on Reddit last night. I said
about, "Oh, u I'm beginning to hate all
women. People had a big problem with
it." Then I said, "Oh, I hate" And then
I pretended to be a woman saying I hate
men. No one cared. And if that does not
tell you what it's all about, I I don't
know what will.
That tells you everything you need to
know. It's a gender thing. It always has
been a gender thing. It's not an
individual thing. It's not a personality
thing. It's a gender thing.
That's what I'm saying. It's all to do
with it's a gender thing. And the sooner
you get that in your head um the quicker
you you know you can move on. It is gender
not individual it's genders see biasness
sexism whatever you call it you Huh?
Don't think the way I do. Pimp Smoker.
I'm really surprised cuz it's the
correct way to think.
It's the correct way to think cuz I'm
completely unbiased. It's the correct
way to think. And all these people that
think different or virgins are people
that's not been with many women. So, I'm
surprised there's not more people like
me in the world, you know, to be honest with you,
cuz the way I'm thinking is correct.
I've I've been there, done it, won the t-shirt.
I mean, [ __ ] I'm surprised so many
people in denial
about it. I'm surprised, you know.
I am surprised, you know. I would have
thought there would have been more
people like me, you know. But no,
they got no problems with women hating
men, do they Greavves? No.
They got no problems with women hating men.
They got no problem with that.
You actually have people try and message you
and and and feel sorry for you. That's
mad, isn't it? Yeah.
What makes me laugh is people that say
they're not all the same. That makes me laugh, lad.
That makes that makes me really really
laugh. Yeah. is when they try to tell
someone like me that women aren't all the same. Really, bro?
Well, I disagree. I've got I've got
evidence. Bear in mind, I've got
experiences and evidence to back up
everything I say. This is what people
are failing to realize.
When I'm saying this stuff, I've got the
evidence to back it up.
That's what I'm trying to say. This is
what these people fail to realize.
You know, of course they're all the
same, bro. It's so obvious they're all
the same. I don't know how many more you
need to keep meeting until the generaliz
until the generalization is warranted.
How many more do you have to keep meeting?
I was thinking about this earlier when I
woke up. I'm thinking, okay, so how many
more people do you need to meet until
the generalization is warranted?
When can you start generalizing?
Like how many how many more do you need
to meet? I mean, if years and years of
meeting and traveling and meeting
different women is is not enough, then
what is like I think that's a fair point
to be fair. You know,
how many more bad experiences do you need? That's that.
All right, I just think that's valid to be fair.
Yeah, they are biased.
They got no problem with women hating
men. Uh but they got a big problem with
men hating women. Yeah.
Like I said, double standards. So
yeah, you can never ask for advice.
Never ask for advice from anyone.
and all they're going to do is twist
things and dismiss your struggles.
That's what they love doing. I sent some
people Instagram messages yesterday
about dating and the way it is in this
country. They didn't even respond back.
What could they say?
What could they say? It's the truth. So, yeah,
it's the truth. None of them are good.
Do you see my video on nonslegs? Uh, pip smoker.
That was That was true, lad. That was actually true.
Yeah, they are biased.
Why are you Why are you going to have
hope when there is no hope? That's just
going to make you feel worse.
You You're having hope, but there's
literally no hope. So, why wouldn't that
just make someone feel worse instead of
accepting their situation and moving on?
Why aren't people told to accept their
situation and move on?
Why Why are they told that there's hope
when there's no hope? There is literally
I can't think of any less hope than now.
But they still think there is. They
still think one day you're going to go
out and people are all of a sudden going
to be different. How?
In what way?
Like I said, if they if they ban
smartphones, then um yeah, there's a chance.
You know what I'm saying? Yeah.
I'm just curious about it to be honest.
How could it possibly change? Um and
it's been going on for years and it's
only and it's continuously getting worse as well.
That's fine, lad. Like there's other
things you can do in life, you know?
You're never going to meet anyone.
People just need to be honest about it.
You will never ever meet anyone ever.
You have to be cool to be kind, bro.
Like that's it. I don't know what the
problem is, you know? Why don't people
admit it on Reddit, Grezy?
Instead of leading it's like leading a
horse to water and then the and and then
and then the the horse not getting water.
keeps being being pulled to false hope
only for the water to be poured down the
drain. There is no hope. People are
[ __ ] You can't even drink in places properly now.
So, I mean like
why do they think it's going to change?
I have no idea.
That's one thing you will know will
never change. You could gamble, you
might win. Uh you could come across some
money. There's so many things that could
happen, but that will never change cuz
they will never change.
Once you've met one, you've met them
all. Simple as that. Once you've met one
woman, you've basically met all of them.
None of them are good. None of them are different.
Whether they meet you, whether they
don't beat you, it's as simple as that.
They they are all the same. Doesn't
matter what what they are literally all
the same. That's that.
I probably met more women than your dad.
I probably met more women than your mom.
That's how bad it is. Like anyone's parents
probably, bro. I [ __ ] met a lot I met
a lot of people. So that's that.
Like I said, good luck to you, Greasy.
Good luck to you. You're going to need it.
Good luck to you. I love to hear when
you start dating and I want to hear your experiences.
I love it, bro. I love to I'd love to
hear other people's experiences, bro.
It's funny. I love it, bro.
Yeah. You'll go out one day and people
will be different all of a sudden.
I got I got more I think there's more of
a chance of pigs flying generally. Feel
like Yeah. there's more chance of a pig
flying over a chimney.
It's like do It's like doing the lottery. Yeah.
And then thinking the next time you do
the lottery, you're going to win. Now,
most people that you know in in the
world don't win the lottery. Most people
that you know do the lottery don't win
the lottery. Friends, friends of
friends, cousins, they don't win the
lottery. So, if they do the lottery,
they're not expecting to win. Same thing
with this. This is like lottery odds now. Um,
so why do you think why do you think
people all of a sudden it will be different?
I love to know the way of people's
thinking. I love to get to the I love to
get to the bottom of it.
So you got people that are [ __ ] you
got that don't work, you got women that
leave people on. You get people that
suck you out of places if you try to
speak to people. So where is this hope?
Because I must be I must be missing something.
My brain must not be working properly or
something because I don't see any sort
of hope. I don't see no light at the end
of the tunnel. Um
despite people keep saying that there is mad Pauly. So yeah,
that's all I wanted to say really. Yeah.
I have some chicken say. I think I'm
saving money. So yeah,
that's what I'm doing, mate. Saving. Saving money.
We just get like a couple of pieces of
chicken. Love it. Lad,
listen. Lavy bomb. Go back to Go back to
Go back to LJ's channel.
And I'm not your mate either.
Well, anyways, since you're here, I've
got a question. Dr. Echo.
Why is it that when I um
I was on Reddit and I said that I uh I
said I hated women and people had a big
problem with it. Then I was I I
pretended to be a woman and I started
hating men and people didn't really care.
Tells you everything you need to know, don't it?
I didn't get told to go to therapy. I
didn't get called a fem cell. If
anything, I had people feeling sorry for
me. Tells you all you need to know, don't it?
Don't know about you, but that tells me
all all you need to know that it's a
gender thing. It's not an individual
thing. It's double standards.
You know what I'm saying? Same person, different gender.
Mad how that works, is it?
Mad how that works.
Yeah, that's mad how that works, isn't it?
So many in denial people, bro.
Evil bastards. That's what they are.
And I'm not in a bad mood today either,
bro. I just say how I see it. It's
facts, is it? Yeah.
They got no problem with [ __ ] women hating men.
Why is that? Why are women allowed to
hate men but men are not allowed to hate
women after bad experiences?
Why is that? Bit rude, isn't it?
Isn't it greasy? Bit rude.
Bit biased, isn't it?
So yeah, anyone you can't take advice
from anyone sadly
cuz everyone everyone's just biased. So,
well, most people are. Maybe like 10% of
people aren't, but most people are.
No, sometimes I I I just think stuff to
myself, you know, man. Like, I just wake
up and I'm not even in a bad mood. I was
just thinking to myself, you know, you
think out loud and how I I was just
saying to myself, how many more women do
you have to keep meeting until you until
the warrant the the generaliz
the generalization is warranted. How
many more do you have to keep meeting?
You've met him for years and years and
years. None of them are good. Uh you've
had so many bad experiences, but you're
not allowed to generalize. Okay, fair
enough. So, how many more do you have to
keep meeting until I can start generalizing? Another
2,000, another 3,000. How many more is
someone supposed to keep meeting?
Like, like, tell me, like, I'm generally
curious here. How many more do you How
many more bad experiences do you have to keep having?
And I think that's a good question, bro.
And and I want the answer, you know,
UK asylum. I'm generally curious. I want
the answer, lad.
I'm being deadly serious. How many more
bad experiences do you need to keep having? You know,
enough to kill you or what? Like, I
don't understand. Is do do you need Do
you need one that's really bad to give
you a panic attack to then kill you?
Like, I I I don't understand. But I'm
being serious. I'm not trolling. I'm
being deadly serious
cuz it does make you wonder these
things, you know.
No, I think you need better experiences.
That's what I think. I think you need better experiences.
That's what I reckon. I reckon you need
better experiences. Me?
Yeah, I reckon you need better
experiences. Me, lad.
that that'll do the trick, but that's
never going to happen. But yeah, so but
yeah, like so what I'm trying to say is
how many do you need to keep meeting?
I don't understand how many more do you
have to keep meeting till you realize
they're all the same.
You know what I mean? People
telling you it's going to change is like
leading a is like leading um is like
leading a horse to water and then and
then putting the water down the drain.
So then the the the the basically giving
the horse false hope basically. Yeah.
No, no. Like I said, uh it's bad
experiences cuz they led me on. We've
been over this many times, Dr. Eko.
We're not going over this again. It was
bad experiences cuz they led me on and
play games. That's what made it the bad experiences.
Yeah, but UK Asylum, I get what you're
saying. I get what you're saying, but
the thing is
the future's going to be exactly the same.
The future's not going to be no different.
That's that's what I'm trying to say.
Yeah, you can accept the past. I was
saying this to Ley yesterday as well. I
said, you know, even if we forgot the
past and we left the past where it is.
Okay, we can do that. But the future is
going to be exactly the same. Cuz with
dating, you can predict the future. You
know exactly what's going to happen.
With gambling, you don't. With other
things, you don't.
No, no, no. Uh, saying that you're going
to meet somebody and speaking to
somebody for a month is leading somebody
on. You know it and I know it. And if if
a man if a woman was doing it to a if a
man was doing it to a woman, you would
call it leading on. This is where the
double standards are coming into it. Again,
I've repeatedly shown you messages where
I've been led on as I have repeatedly
shown you. Yeah. I have done more than
I've done more than told. I've actually
shown and you're still denying it. How
are you denying black and white
evidence, bro? Like, get your You need
to seriously seriously Okay. Okay. Put
this This is This is the analogy I used
yesterday, right? If you if you if you
murdered someone, right? Say you you
murdered someone, right? And you went to
court, they got CCTV and everything,
would you plead guilty or would you
plead not guilty? I'm asking I'm asking
this question. Because me, I would I
would never murder someone to begin
with. I would plead guilty because the
evidence is is out there. So, I know
there's a good chance I'm going to get
out at some point in my life. It's like
going to court and pleading not guilty
when there's literally CCTV evidence of
what you've done.
Bro, you're going to you're going to get
more time in prison by doing that. How
can you plead not guilty when there's
when there's evidence?
It's like pleading not guilty when you
when when it's on camera. You killing
someone. That doesn't even make sense.
And you have seen messages. Of course
you've seen messages. You've been you've
been on my channel for a very long time.
Of course you've seen the messages.
Everyone's seen the messages.
It was when that whole Ricky Minton was
going on. You know what I'm saying?
So yeah, you're just going to keep
getting bad experiences. Anyways, so you
know, even even if you forgot the past,
the future's going to be the same cuz
it's always going to be the same here.
It's as simple as that. So,
it's never going to change. So, I don't
know why people think it will. It will
never change ever.
So, uh yeah, stop stop stop leading a
horse to water and then putting the
water down the drain, lad.
That's the only way I can put it. You know,
it's gotten worse here. It's gotten
worse here, you know.
It's not going to change. Never going to
You're just going to keep getting bad
experiences in the future. That's all
you're always going to get. That's it. Uhuh.
Bad bad people.
That's what they are. Bad bad people.
None of them are different. Simple.
What's going on here then? Oh, here we go. Yeah. So,
yeah. How many more um people do you
have to keep meeting
until you can say, "Oh, they're kind of
all the [ __ ] same."
I mean, how like how many more
1,000, 2,000, 5,000. How many more does
someone have to keep meeting? How many
more years do people have to keep doing
this? Because you say that they're
generalizing when in my opinion the
generalizing the generalization is
warranted. And if it's not warranted,
how many more do you have to keep
meeting? I think that's a fair question.
I think that's fair me. But some people
don't, you know,
none of them more different. They're all
the same. They all play the same games.
They all lead people in the same way.
They all have the same attitude. Even if
they're not leading people on, how many
more times you got to keep doing it? You know,
until we can just say it because it's
the truth, you know? I'm wondering, lad.
I'm really wondering. So yeah,
to a woman as well, if women was
generalizing all men and they've met
like as many men as I uh I've met women,
I'd say, "Yeah, you can you can you can
hate men if you want." I'd be like,
"Yeah, you can hate men."
I'll be like, "Yeah, you can hate men
100%." Yeah, 100%. I got no problem with that.
I would I would say that they could hate
men if they wanted to.
If they met loads and loads and loads of
people and they were out approaching,
I'd say, "Yeah, you can hate men all you want."
You get my point, though, Grezy.
So, yeah. any. Yeah.
But yeah, how many how many what I what
I want to know uh Dusty is how many more
women do you have to keep meeting until
the generalization is warranted?
I'm actually not in a bad mood today.
I'm actually like you you think these
stuff to yourself? Like they say that
you can't generalize all women even
though you've met [ __ ] god knows how
many in how many years. Okay. So, how
many more until I can generalize?
5, 10, 15, 20, go out every day, every week,
you know, how many more bad experiences
do you have to keep getting?
I'm I'm just asking. Maybe someone can answer it.
If you're out in a bar and talk to a
woman for a few hours, does that count
as a woman you've met? 100%. 100% it does. 100%.
And it doesn't even need to be hours. It
could be 10 minutes. 100 million%. 100%.
Yeah. That is a woman that you've met.
Yes. Yes. You don't need to be in a
relationship with someone to know them.
This is what I mean. You get somebody
right that will be in a relationship and
they think they know all about women
when no I've met more women than they
have. You know, and a relationship with
a woman is one woman. That's not
multiple women. I have met multiple
multiple women. And yes, if you speak to
someone for five or 10 minutes, you've
met them. You know their name. They know
your name. You get in conversation. You
speak to them. You know them. You don't
know them, but you've met them. Yeah. Of
course you have. Of course you have met
them. Well, what else would you call it?
No, I'm still going, bro. I'm still I'm
still going 100%.
So, yeah. But how many women do you have
to keep dealing with? How many women do
you have to keep meeting? I'm I'm curious.
I'm I'm curious. I'm actually curious.
I sent it to Ant-Man about me and my mom
and he says, "Oh yeah, but she's not
going to understand." But he says, "Oh,
the way that they're defending them, he
can't understand the way that these
people defend them."
He says, "Oh, your mom's not going to
understand because it was different and
that like they can't help you." But then
at the same time, he says, "I know. I
agree with you that they that they that
they um that they don't empathize
um even though you've had bad
experiences and [ __ ] Like that's that's
the bit he didn't get, which I don't get
as well. I don't understand it myself,
but they just love defending women.
Dusty, I was on Reddit last night. I was
saying about how I hated women. People
had a big problem with it, mad problems
with it. Then I said that I was a woman
that hated men and no one cared. No one battled.
So, um, that tells you all you need to
know, I reckon.
I'm just going out and doing the madness. Yeah.
Yeah, that that's what happened last
night on Reddit. Uh,
greasy. Uh, Dusty,
anyone gets in my way? Yeah, I will.
What? Why is this not working? One second.
Trying to message someone.
Why is that not working?
Yeah, they they don't they don't protect
women in front of me, mate.
They don't they don't protect. Yeah,
they might do it to someone else, but
they don't protect women in front of me, mate.
I need to change my attitude again. Uh
it's not my attitude. I'm going by my
experiences with women that I've got
that I've got proof of. In order for the
attitude to change, the experiences with
women need to change. The experiences
need to change before the attitude
because your attitude is based on your
life experiences. You need better
experiences with women. Otherwise, your
attitude will never change and it's
never going to change. So, it's as
simple as that. You need better
experiences with them and it's never
going to happen. So, you're never going
to change. It's as simple as that. They
need to change. Their attitude need to
change, but they're not. Oh, trust me,
they will. Dusty, dusty, dusty, dusty,
dusty, dusty. Trust me, they will allow
it. Trust me, bro. They will allow it
cuz I'll glass them in their face. Trust
me, they will. They will. cuz I would
just if they knew what was good for
them, they would cuz I would glass them
in their face. So, it's as simple as
that. They would. No one's No one would
look good for a woman in front of me.
Oh, they would allow it cuz I'd glass
them in their face. Trust me. Trust me,
they would. Anyways, we're not talking
about any of that stuff anyways, bro.
Cuz I'm not trying to be put in a bad
mood again. Um, but yeah, we're going to
move on from that now because we will
see what happens on Thursday, won't we?
So, we're going to we're going to stop
talking about that kind of stuff. Yeah.
And this is exactly what I'm trying to
say. You know,
we're going to stop talking about that
stuff as well, cuz it's all talking for
no reason, bro. So, l
Why is it not letting me message this person?
[ __ ] that's weird, lad.
No, Thursday's not going to be all talk.
I'm just not talking about it until it
happens. It's simple as that. I wasted
enough energy yesterday, bro.
But yeah, I love how they don't have no
problems with women hating men. Huh?
I love how they've got no problems with
women hating men. That tells you all you
need to know.
That tells you all you need to know.
But I'm not talking about I'm not
talking about this, bro.
Yeah, exactly. I'm not talking about it.
Like, I've already put enough white
knights in their fa put them in their
place enough times, lad. Why are we
still talking about this?
If anyone gets involved Thursday, then
they're getting they're going to see
what happens. We don't need to talk
about it. Why are we still talking about it? Yeah, good.
See what I mean, Greasy? They've got no
problem with women hating men.
They've got no problems with women
hating men, do they? [ __ ] biased
Yeah, you keep telling yourself that,
Shotty lad. You keep telling yourself that.
We're not going to get into these
pointless arguments anyways. I'm going
to do what I'm doing on Thursday and
that's it. You can keep writing what you
want. You can keep twisting the
narrative. You can keep making stuff up.
I'm not interested, lad. You're not
going to get a reaction. So, you're
wasting your time.
You keep defending women and you will
always be a virgin. It's as simple as
that. Like, that's all I've got to say.
That's all I've really got to say to
these people, Greavesy. Like, they can
live their life the way they want. If
they want to keep defending women,
they'll always be virgins. So let them
just let them keep seeing where sing and
white lighting gets them all their life.
Nothing but being a virgin and still
being a virgin. So I don't care about
these people, lad, to be honest. Yeah.
Yeah. Simple as that. So
yeah, of course. Yeah. Of course you
have, lad. Yeah. Yeah. Of course you
have, lad. Of course you have. Yeah. If
you had relationships, you wouldn't be
on here white nighting women. But okay,
anyone can say anything behind a
keyboard, bro. A 10-year-old can do it.
A 10-year-old can say they're a
millionaire. But the fact that you're
winging women, it shows you've never
been with one. The only people that do
this are people that don't get women.
Never been with a woman or they just
don't get women. It's just it's just
obvious. The people that do that are
people that don't get women.
The people that defend them like
nonslegs. He don't get women. He's with
a [ __ ] that don't give him sex. Same
thing with LJ. He simps. We've never
seen LJ with a woman. The only people
that do this sing and white nighting are
people that don't get women.
And they think by doing this it's going
to um it's going to get them a woman,
but it's not going to get them a woman.
So that's why they do it basically. Sad
really cuz how long is it going to take
them to learn?
So anyways, let me try and message this person. on Reddit. So yeah,
there loads of simps on here, bro. He's
not the only one. Uh Nons is a S as well.
Why is he not letting me message his mother?
We've already been over this, lad.
Anyways, things that you're bringing up
that I've already repeated, I'm not
going to I'm not going to dive into it again.
Simple as that.
Yeah, it's as simple as that.
Let me message this person on [ __ ] Reddit, bro.
That's [ __ ] weird.
Maybe it's a capital I. I don't know.
That's [ __ ] bro.
So yeah, you keep defending the women
and you see where that gets you in life,
lad. When you're 90 in your deathbed and
never been with a woman, all that defending,
that's on you, lad. That's your life. If
you want to live your life like that,
that's on you, mate. Simple as that.
Horrible bastards. evil bastards.
Not all women are the same. They [ __ ]
well are all the same, lad. But again,
you keep telling yourself that, lad. I
already know the truth. So you you know,
you you keep telling yourself they're
not all the same. That's on you, lad.
I know they're all the same.
They are definitely definitely
definitely all the same. And I see it
when it's not even me approaching them
as well. They have so many similarities
with people, Dusty, that are not the
same. So many similarities.
Yeah, I begged her to talk. No one
begged her to talk. I said, "Meet me and
let's talk." That's what I said. Didn't
beg anyone to talk. Big difference. It
was someone I was speaking to. But yeah,
like I said, Dusty, they've got a They
do a lot of the same stuff to other
people as well that for people that
aren't the same. Let's just put it this
way. I'd be very concerned if a man
acted the same way as me, even one of
them. So, the fact that you got loads of
these women acting the same way, even to
other people, but they're not the same,
maybe, bro. But the chances of that is
very slim. No man's the same as me. No
man would ever act the same as me. I'd
be very surprised if one did because I'm
different. I'm an individual. Do you
understand? That's what you call a different person.
Do you understand? I'm a different
person. None of these women are
different in any way.
And I've seen it with my own eyes when
people have approached them even when I
haven't been [ __ ] going out. So they
do and act. And of course they're the
same. They all watch the same [ __ ] Tik
Tok, Instagram, everyone's the same now.
That's that. Like they are the same.
You've seen it with your own eyes. They
do the same stuff. They act the same
way. The same things that men never do.
So of course they're the same. They're
exactly the same. All of them are the
same. I've got no reason to lie. I've
had sex. I've been with women. I've got
no reason to lie.
I've got no reason to lie at all. I
wouldn't say if I didn't believe it.
Nah, it's not it's not it's not shaping.
No, no, not even. I just don't like
people being I just don't like people
leading me on.
I just don't like people leading me on.
And I don't understand how people can
keep making excuses for these women. Uh,
it's just something that I wonder
how people defend people that are worse
than men. I just don't understand it.
And if I don't understand something,
I'll say I don't understand it. I just
do not understand how people defend these women
when they're horrible ass people. I just
don't understand how people do it.
I just don't and I will never
understand. I know I will never get an
answer to it, but you just wonder these
things sometimes. You know,
people don't have a problem with women
hating men that they've got no problem
with hating men.
Women that hate men, they they don't get
called for it. So why should we get
called for calling them all the same
based on our bad experiences? Why should
we get called for it? They don't get
called for it. Everyone feels sorry for
them. So why should we get called for
it? This is where your argument is
always going to fall flat on its ass
because it is a gender thing. This is
where your argument will always get
thrown flat on its ass because of the
because of the because of the double standards.
Oh, I'm leaving, rat boy. I'm out of
here. I'm gone. I'm leaving. Simple as
that. That's that's the long-term solution.
I'm leaving. I'm getting out of here.
That's it. I mean, yeah.
So, I'm just going to leave, bro, and
start a new life somewhere. I think
that's the only thing now I can I can do
cuz nothing's ever going to change in this country.
You know, you speak to someone, you get
led on for a month. [ __ ] all that, bro.
That was the final straw. [ __ ] that, lad.
[ __ ] that, lad. [ __ ] that, lad. No, no,
no. [ __ ] that, bro.
Do you remember all of these people, Rat
Boy, that was saying that you need to
speak to them longer? You need to speak
to them longer. And then when you speak
to them longer, they lead you on anyways. Like
they're horrible, horrible bastards. And
I'm not, bro, I'm not biased either, rat
boy. I've been with women. I've had sex.
So it's not even like I'm a virgin or
anything like that. I'm telling I'm
speaking facts. I will never say
anything if I didn't believe it.
If I didn't believe it, lad.
No, no, no, no, no, no. does work out,
but they do what they do on purpose. No,
no, no, no, no, rap boy. They do what
they do on purpose. You know, there's a
reason why things don't work out.
There's always a reason why things don't
work out. And they do it on purpose to
make people feel like [ __ ] And I
believe it now, bro. And I've got no
reason to lie. Why would I lie, bro? I
don't I don't even care about lust. I
don't care about sex. Why would I need
to lie, bro? If I didn't believe it, why
would I say it? I believe they are evil.
I believe it. If I didn't believe it, I
wouldn't say it, bro. Honestly, I would
not say it. If I didn't believe
something, I wouldn't say it. Do you get me?
The experiences prove what they're
about. Do you understand? Like, it's
what what what can anyone say really?
Like, what can anyone say? They can't
say anything. They are all evil. They're
all the same. I was having this
question. I was having this question. I
was having this argument with Laney um
yesterday uh yesterday, rat boy, and I
said, "Listen, you can say whatever you
want about me, but I don't block people
and leave people without closure." I
could never do that, bro. I could never
do that. I could never ever ever do
that. But they can do it cuz they're evil.
They will do it cuz they're evil little
[ __ ] with no feelings. I couldn't do
it, bro. I generally don't think I could
do it. I don't think I have the heart to
do it. They do it casually. They're evil
people. I don't know how many more
people you have to keep meeting.
That's my thing. I don't know how many
more women you have to keep meeting
before you can generalize. You've
already met thousands. [ __ ] sake. You
know, but who knows, man. Who who you
know what I'm saying?
They're horrible, nasty people.
And that's it. And that's what I said to
Laney basically and she couldn't say anything back.
Yeah. And they're evil to you as well,
cuz you don't get women yourself, lad.
And they're evil to a lot of men. And
they're evil to you. Don't pretend that
you're not in the same boat, lad, cuz
you are. You people that white knight
and s women, they don't like you. They
hate you. Which is which is the whole
confusion as why you would defend
someone that hates you. They don't like
you, bro. No, I know what you're saying,
rat boy. No, no, I know what you're
saying, bro. But I've you know what
pisses me off, bro? The thing is, yeah,
is that I had I had anxiety for like a
week and I never get anxiety all because
of this dating thing and t
you know, women are all evil. I've been
saying it for years, evil, evil, evil.
And the thing is, rat boy, every time
I've gone out, there's been a reason why
I've gone out every 3 months. Someone's
pissed me off. Oh, I need to just get
out of the house. And every time you
give them the benefit of the doubt, they
all turn out to be the same. Every
single woman you come across is the
same. People can say something in your
ear. Yeah. It's like devil advocate. Oh,
women are not the same, bro. You go out,
they're the same again. The same again.
The same again. And this has been going
on for years and years and years. So the
question is, when can people say
something without being questioned? Oh,
they're not all like that. They're not
all like that. Well, they evidently are
all like that. You understand? They
evidently [ __ ] are. And the last time
I went out, bro, I had already given up
with the dating [ __ ]
Yeah. It's called a fulfilling prop.
Yeah. But it isn't called that when
people have shown you evidence. When
someone has shown you evidence, that's
the fine line. See these people, rat
boy, I've shown them women leading me
on, women doing this, women doing that,
and all they do is keep making excuses.
Even when you show what women have done,
they still make excuses.
Like that's the funny thing about it
though. You can't women them. You will
show women leading you on and then
they'll be like, "Nope, no, no." They
will not have any bad things said about
women. Men can be hated. Men can be
[ __ ] But a woman leading someone on,
no, no, no. I won't have that. No, no.
She didn't lead you on. Uh uh. She
changed her mind. Like, you can't win
with them, bro. You literally cannot win
with them. They will not have any bad
things said about women. This is this is
this is the point I'm trying to make.
And when someone takes it upon
themselves to prove what they've done
and they're still denying it, that's the
point where they become in denial. This
is in denial. Yeah. See, the thing is,
Grezy, do you know what people on Reddit
always ask me? Why are you recording
your approaches? One second. One second.
No, no, no. Why are you recording your
approaches? Why are you recording your
approaches? Why are you recording it?
They always had a big problem with
people. Um, they always had a big
problem with people recording approaches
because the reason why I started
documenting this is to spread awareness.
Women aren't innocent. They isn't easy.
Women are bad people. And if people
didn't believe it, then I thought by
showing it, it would it would make them
at least understand a bit more. But they
seem to still ignore things that they're
shown, which is very scary to be honest
with you. You know,
you know, they've been shown multiple
multiple women doing me wrong and they
still make excuses. That's scary, bro.
That's very very very scary.
You know, that's very very scary. You
could show a woman strangling a baby and
they'll be like, "Nope, nope. The baby
had a bad personality. There's evil
babies out there and there's a reason
why she's killed that baby." You'll
never win with biased white knights. And
most people are are like this nowadays
as well. This is the scary thing about
it. They'd be like, "Nope, nope, nope.
The baby failed. the baby tripped. They
could they could be showing a woman
throttling a baby and they'd still make excuses.
It's [ __ ] madness, bro. Like, you got
to you got to laugh at it. It is funny.
They will never have any and you know
what? It's not even bad things said
about them, Griezy. It's they will not
hold them accountable for anything.
Listen, Grievy, they will not hold them
accountable for anything. It's not even
bad words. Okay, they these people,
right, would rather Okay, put let's use
this analogy. They would rather kill
themselves than hold a woman
accountabable for anything. I think
that's the better way to put it. They
will never ever hold a woman accountable
for anything. I think that's the better
way to put it. A woman lead you on, they
make excuses. A woman [ __ ] you over,
they make excuses. They will do anything
in their power to take that
accountability away from from any woman.
And it could be simply as someone
leading you on.
That's that's that. Yeah. They've got
Yeah. Yeah. Bro, you're saying that
you're saying you're saying that like
you're saying that you haven't had all
of these bad experiences, but bro, I've
watched enough kick streamers. I've
watched enough people approaching women
and it's not a walk in the park for them
either. It's not a walk in the park for
them either. I watched like Ed Matthews.
I watched HS. I watch all these people
and I've seen them go and approach women
and to be honest with you, their
experiences are not much different than mine.
So yeah, okay, maybe not everyone has
these experiences, but let's just say
half of the people do and half of the
people are going to be you people, but
you will sit there and keep defending
women. Like, let's be real right now.
You ain't got women surrounded but
around you like a porn star. You haven't
got women you're [ __ ] every day.
You're not you're not like banging women
every day. So what I can't understand
how you could justify defending them the
way you do. This is what I'm trying to say.
So let's just say this if 50% on the
Abanese experience is 50% is maybe it's
more but let's just call it 50%. Bro,
I've seen it when I've g when I've given
up on the dating app. It was it's pissed
me off watching it. So you can't make it
out like I'm the only one that's getting
it because it's [ __ ] It's [ __ ] bro.
[ __ ] I was watching Ed Matthews. I
don't watch him anymore. This guy was
like, "Oh, England's [ __ ] The women are
stuck up. We need to go back to
America." No, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Like, bro, [ __ ] I've seen other
people do it as well. They've had like
people be rude
cuz it's the women. Do you understand?
Yeah. I've seen that stuff before, Grezy.
But yeah, they just won't hold him
accountable for anything.
They just won't hold them accountable
for anything. I don't know why.
And even if they murder someone, they
get less time. There's been times where
people have planned murders and they've
got they've got they only got
manslaughter. They only got manslaughter. Grievesy.
All they got was manslaughter.
when they obviously [ __ ] plan to kill
the person and they also get lesser
sentences as well. Even if they do kill
someone and they get convicted of
murder, they still get they get they get
a lesser sentence.
That's why whenever I was renting them
rooms before, I said, "Uh, it's double
price for you cuz you're a woman." I
always used to say, "Oh yeah, it's going
to be double for you. If you want to be
in this household, the prices is going
to be double for all of the leading on
um and all the [ __ ] and that. Um you
know what I'm trying to say,
you know, so it's going to be double. So
if it's 300, it's 600. So yeah, that's
that's where we're at basically.
And that's it. And then obviously they
[ __ ] off. So yeah,
that's victim. [ __ ] don't affect my
life at all. Why would I feel the same
about them? No, you shouldn't. You
shouldn't. You shouldn't. You shouldn't.
But they you shouldn't be making excuses
for them either when they proven to be
wrong. When they're proven to do [ __ ]
shitty things. You shouldn't. But at the
same time, you shouldn't be making
excuses for them like you do.
So why are you making excuses for them?
No, you shouldn't care. I'm not asking
you to care, but you shouldn't make
excuses for them either.
[ __ ] sake. I can't find this person now, man.
It's like I don't really care. Christian
Izzy, bro, she led me the [ __ ] on. It is
what it is, bro. Like
She led me on. That's it. It is what it
is. Just accept it, bro. It is what it
But the worst thing about these women,
Griezy, is like what what I was saying
to Laney, is how they could never give
closure. They can block people and just
get on with their lives. I couldn't do
that, bro. If I done someone wrong or
done something like I couldn't do it me
like what USA is done and other people
have done it in the past. I I don't
know. She didn't ghost. No, she didn't
ghost. She just blocked cuz I said, "Oh,
I was drunk. I said, "Oh, let's meet up
and that in it. Let's have a talk in it.
Let's get to the bottom of this
problem." You know? And then yeah, they
just they sent me like [ __ ] 20
messages. They deleted most of them and
then just blocked me.
But they can these people I'm talking
generally anyone that you come that you
can come across in the future Grezy is
that they will they will [ __ ] people
they will [ __ ] people over bro and they won't care.
They will literally just just go with
their lives. They don't care, bro. They
literally don't care. That's that is
sad, bro. And it really if you think
about it if you was to do the same
thing. Yeah. Yeah, I sent her some voice
notes drunk basically just saying that
to be honest.
Then she deleted all of the messages and
that. But she was playing games before
that anyways. She was playing games
before that. Anyways,
bro, I wasn't falling in love at all.
I was just happy to speak to someone.
See, at my age, Greavves, you you stop
caring about sex. I don't care about
lust. I don't care about sex. I don't
care about anything. Uh, what did I say?
Literally just um, oh yeah, you said
that you want an apology where okay,
let's meet up then.
Let me come to your area and let's have
a talk. Literally just that.
That's literally all I said. It was four
voice notes of the same thing. I just
said, "Oh, well, let's talk then." Is
it? That's literally all I said, bro.
Literally all I said. Didn't say
anything bad at all. though.
Yeah, she said I'm She said I'm actually scary.
How is that scary, bro? How the [ __ ] is
that scary? You think that's scary?
She's like, you're you're actually
scary. Am I actually really? No, I'm not.
But it doesn't matter. That's just
that's just victimizing yourself, isn't
it? That's just a form of victimizing yourself.
She was victimiz she sent me like so
many messages then she deleted it, bro.
And then all the only one that popped up
was, "Oh, you're actually scary." She
dodged the bullet even though she was
the one leading me on and playing games.
But she dodged the bullet and not me.
Not sure I agree with that one, but hey ho.
So someone that was leading me on
playing games with me, giving me false
hope, being a [ __ ] to me is the one that
dodged the bullet. H strange. Well, if
she dodged the bullet, bro, I' I'd
dodged the [ __ ] nuclear.
So, how about that one? See, this is
taking the woman's side again. This is
exactly what we're talking about, Grezy.
This is taking the woman's side.
This is the whole point of what I'm
talking about with the double standards.
It's okay for them to lead you on. It's
okay for them to play games. It's okay
uh be a [ __ ] Um but you you're not
allowed to um Yeah, I accept that. I
accept that, Grezy. Yeah, you can say we
both have issues. Okay, fair enough. But
it's not a one-sided thing. So don't
make it sound like a one-sided thing.
That's not scary saying that you you
want to meet someone. What the [ __ ] bro?
But it's all victimizing anyways. It's
all victimizing yourself.
It's a form of victimizing yourself. You
know what I mean?
Nope. Don't care about a relationship,
lad. Don't give a [ __ ] about any of that
Yeah. She told me she's got severe anxiety.
She gave it on to me, bro.
She gave it on to me, bro. I'm [ __ ]
like I was last week, bro. Bear in mind,
I never get anxiety. Don't really get
anything, bro. I couldn't sleep. I
couldn't do nothing, bro. What the [ __ ]
I tried drinking and the next day I felt
worse. Yeah. She said that she got
severe anxiety and [ __ ]
She was crying. She was crying on on the
voice notes. All cuz I said, "Do you
know why she was crying?" Because I
said, "Oh, you're not going to ever find
anyone like as good as me." And I didn't
mean like good-looking or as good. I
meant like someone that's not going to
cheat and stuff.
That's what I meant. And that's what I
meant, man. I didn't mean like as
obviously I didn't mean to sound rude,
but it's the truth. Like, I'm not being
nasty when I was saying it. It's the
truth, bro. And I wasn't being rude when
I was saying it. Um,
I wasn't being rude. I was talking
facts, bro. Like, I actually wasn't
trying to be rude or trying to
manipulate anyone. I was. And she's
like, "Oh, how can you say that?" Me.
And she started crying. I'm like, "You
got you've got issues.
You got issues."
But yeah, I wasn't rude or nasty at all.
any of the messages cuz I felt sorry for
them you know cuz what they were saying
about their ex and stuff. So
it's quite but even though I knew that
you know they bring it on themselves
they go for these people they know what
these people are like but I thought you
know maybe I don't know bro is in it you
don't like to hear stuff like that you know but yeah
but I didn't mean it to be like a
narcissist. I was speaking facts cuz it
is the facts
like that. I wasn't trying to be like
trying to manipulate anyone. I was being real lad. You know
damage kids screw loose.
She says I love my little quiet life.
You've got problems.
Then you put you g you put your [ __ ]
anxiety onto me.
Yeah, it is still happening.
Everybody knows that you're a crazy [ __ ]
See people like Lord Jay, they would
deny Oh, I've never had anxiety. I've
never had anxiety. Well, you have cuz if
you saw yourself in that pub the other
day, mate, if that ain't anxiety, I
don't know what the what what what it
is. If that ain't [ __ ] anxiety,
if that's not anxiety, I don't know what
is, mate. You've definitely got anxiety, lad.
You definitely got anxiety.
I had it the other day. What's What's
wrong with that, bro? Why can't you
admit it in it?
laughing at you. Mocking you. Greasy.
Laughing at you. Mocking you.
I had it. No, I had it before Wednesday
and it was nothing to do with Timmy. It
was nothing to do with Timmy. I'm not
scared of Timmy. Had nothing to do with
any of that stuff. I had it Monday, Sunday, Saturday.
Yeah. And it was nothing to do with
Timmy, mate. It was to do with this
whole like thing.
Yeah, laughing at you. Mocking you.
Mocking you. Bro, that just makes me
want to go Birmingham. You know that,
bro. That just keeps playing in my head.
So, what you're saying, Greavves, is
them Birmingham [ __ ] were laughing at us.
Them Birmingham [ __ ] were laugh. Did
you see my video on nonsakes? Oh, Dusty.
Dusty, bro. You can't even deny that,
You can't even deny that thing with what
I'm saying about Nod legs.
You know it's facts, bro.
That is [ __ ] facts, lad. And you know
it as well, bro. I know you watch that
video. That's That is true. That is
true. That is actually true, bro.
So, I'm going to put up posters around
you in your area. That is mad. That is
worse than what's Timmy done. That is
worse than what LT has done. It's worse
than what a lot of people have done,
bro. You know, like that is insane. That
is insane, bro.
Jesus Christ. Jesus Christ, bro. And
then Laney was trying to Laney was
trying to bring it up. Oh, well, you
don't fight a man. I said, I literally
said to you, I wanted to go to
Birmingham the other day. You said, "Oh,
don't go. Don't go. Don't go." So, when
when when someone's trying to go
somewhere, you're not letting them go.
So, it's kind of like and bro, it wasn't
an L at all because I tried meeting him
and we're not getting into that again
anyways. And I'm not and I'm not going
to Birmingham for that exact reason cuz
it just goes around in circles with
these people. It's the same thing. We I
was talking to Monty about this the
other day. I said if he does any videos
on you, ignore it. If you do, if he does any videos
or anything, do not respond because if
you if you meet them, right, it's going
to go around in circles again.
this is what's going to happen. It's
literally going to go around in circles
again and you're not going to learn from
your mistakes. So, just don't respond to
it. Don't try meeting anyone. Do not do
nothing. You know, if someone catches
you like then they catch you in it like
just don't get into it with any of these
people. I was talking to Monty Man about
this the other day. Seriously, don't. As
funny as it is to watch, it's like look
how many times have you met him, he
still goes around in circles.
So, you're best off just not doing
anything. No, I didn't take the L at all
cuz it's not an L and I don't need to
prove myself either.
So, you really think I couldn't go to
Birmingham today and not that come out?
I could do, but what am I I'm not going
to get paid for it. All I'm going to do
is waste my time, waste my money. It's
going to go around in circles again.
It's going to cause that's all that happens.
I didn't take the L. I never took the L
at all. I never took the L. But I'm just
saying, yeah, that's it. Like, don't
meet anyone on on here.
I could go today. It would be no
problem. I've got the money, but it's
I've got, you know, like and that's it.
I've got tenants that live there. I know
people that live in Birmingham, but it's
just going to go around in circles. So,
if you ignore it, then it's that's it.
That's the best way to be honest. And I
had, to be honest with you, I've got I
had better things to be dealing with.
To be honest,
you know what I'm saying? I was dealing
with this [ __ ] Christian Izzy whil
trying to deal with this. Like, bro, I
had real life [ __ ] to actually deal with.
You know what I'm saying? Like, is Yeah.
Like, that's it. Like, so you don't need to
unless someone paid me, which I'm not
going to accept money from no one. I've
got my own money. But if someone paid
you, then yeah. Okay. That's a different
story. That's the only way you can
justify kind of meeting these people in
here now if someone paid you money.
Don't know, bro. Probably. Yeah.
Now, if someone gave me5 600 pound right
now, I'd do it 100%.
I would do it 100%.
But I wouldn't accept money from people
cuz I got my own money. But that's what
I'm trying to say is that's the only way
it'd be worth someone's while. This is
what I'm trying to say to you.
Cuz what if someone gives you £500? What
what you what I'm saying, bro? Like you
got £500, you're going to go there. So
you're going to either way you had
nothing to do. If it goes around in
circles, you ignore it. You got £500.
You might spend 250 of it, you know, but
you know, it doesn't matter. You you you
I'd go out and approach people and [ __ ]
with people, bro. If you know, if
someone gives me that, but yeah, I'm not
doing it. I've done it so many times
with Bomb Greavesy. The amount of money
I wasted on that [ __ ] going to
Manchester. Oh my god. And it just went
round in circles again.
Oh my [ __ ] god. Twice it was I went.
Wasted so much money the first day.
Then the second time I went. But he Do
you know what? I can't even I can't even
bad mouth bomb. You know, he actually
got me laid. If he didn't wind me up.
Yeah. If he didn't wind me up that sec
that second time, I wouldn't have went
there when Ed Sheeran was playing on
that good Friday. I wouldn't have got
laid if it wasn't for him. So, I mean,
yeah, he actually got me laid. So, yeah.
But the point I'm trying to make is
there's been other people as well like
um you know, you you would always go
around in circles.
So, if Timmy wants to be a [ __ ] and
talks about meeting, then let him, bro.
You know, that's it.
This isn't real life, bro. You know, at
the end of the day, lad. Like, you got
other problems you got to be dealing with.
And that's the only reason I had anxiety
cuz this dating thing. There was no
other reason. It wasn't even that video
I watched. I don't think
it was kind of sick to watch. But I mean
like I don't even think it was that. >> So
and then obviously Dusty, you know, LT
would have got involved as well.
So that's what I'm saying. and it would
just go around in circles. That's what I mean.
But obviously if if he put posters up
about me then no, I would go to
Birmingham then. Do you understand? No,
I would. If someone if if he put posters
up about me or something like that or
like he hit my mom or something like
that then I would. No, you would have to
then like that's what I'm trying to say.
Or even the posters. No, I would, bro. I
would I would that's not even a joke. I
could have got someone killed. So launch
legs lets people pull up posters about
him and he never got me back once
despite knowing where I lived. I lived
by myself and he could have got me back
in a cowardly way as well. Posters he
could have done the windows in but he
never. So how are you going to let
someone put up posters about you, right? And
allow it to happen and then try to [ __ ]
sto other people's fights. That is mad,
bro. That to me is crazy.
That's what you call someone that's got
no shame, lad.
Dusty, that's what you call someone
that's got no shame. Okay, look, LT,
right? Listen. Okay, he might have broke
into the house, whatever. Yeah, but
think about it. Yeah, he broke into the house.
Yeah, no one got hurt. I was still
making money from that house. Yeah,
whatever. Okay. It was more easier to
move on from. Even I don't think the
neighbors Well, they must have knew, but
you just carry on as normal, is it? Cuz
you don't want to lose the house. Fine.
That's one thing. But when someone put
someone's put up posters of you all
around the area, bro, by the by the
train station, you get you get hurt,
bro. Seriously. Seriously, you could get
hurt. And at the end of the day, the
neighbors around here, they know me.
They know I'm not a [ __ ] dump. So, I
mean, people can write what they want,
but they know me in it. Like, so, but if
you go around other areas, other areas
might not know me. So, I could be
walking down the street, someone could
beat the [ __ ] out of me,
you know, and that and launch legs let
that happen. That's mad, bro. That is on
par with the LT thing. That is bad. What
the [ __ ] And then you're trying to [ __ ]
stir fights between people. No, I don't
argue with any neighbors. No.
No, I don't argue with any of them, bro.
They don't say anything to me.
All you got to do All you got to do All
you got to do All you got to do is take
one look at me, bro, and you would know
I'm not a nons. Do you understand? Like
there's there's there's like people can
say whatever, but all you got to do is
is take one look at someone, bro, and
you would you would know. You get it?
Yeah. It doesn't look good obviously.
Yeah. But what I'm saying is they know
deep down I'm not a nons. That's what
I'm trying to say. They know deep down
that I'm not a pedophile. So, do you see
what I'm trying to say?
Yeah. Of course he would say that, bro.
Of course he would say. Of course, he
would say that the posters were only up
a few hours,
but I done worse to him, Dusty, than
anyone's ever done to me. And yeah,
okay, breaking in someone else's some
breaking in someone else's breaking
someone's breaking into someone's
house's house is bad. Yes, it is bad. No
one's saying it's not bad, but bro, like
that is that is just as bad, if not worse.
So the the fact that you let that happen
and you never tried to get anyone back
once, it shows the kind of coward you are. Really,
that is like it's not Go on and keep
doing your um go on keep go on and keep
doing your obsessed videos. Keep doing
your little obsessed videos.
That's fine, man. You can do your
obsessed community posts. Yeah, that's
fine, man. Don't try to [ __ ] stir fights
when you have never met anyone on here
and you will never meet anyone. I've
tried to meet people. Bomb. I've got a
history of meeting people. So, at least
I've backed up 40% of my talk. He will
never meet anyone, Dusty. Never. Never.
Ever. Ever. Ever. Ever. Never. And he
could have beat me as well. Nonsense
could have beat me. No one. Who's Who's
to say that he he could have beat me
for? What? Am I a professional boxer?
No. Do I go to the gym? No. When was the
last time I had a fight? Can't even
remember. So, I mean, you can't even say
about weaker targets either. You're just
all biased on it, is it? It's the
simplest. You're all biased. I don't
even know why we're wasting our time on
why we even waste our time. It's just
all biasness anyways.
And you'll know that from the comments,
but yeah. Yeah, whatever. So, yeah.
Not really, bro. No.
Do you know why, Rat Boy? Because
there's actual like there's actual worse
things going on in the world.
There's worse things going on in the world.
There's serial killers. There's [ __ ]
all sorts of [ __ ] So, not really, lad. No, not really.
Nah, bro. I used to go on that um best
go. You see a lot of sick [ __ ] on there.
See a lot of a lot of sick [ __ ]
So, not really, bro. No,
no one ever started talking about this
stuff until they come in this community
as well. Me and Monty was talking about
this back when we was on PlayStation.
No one ever spoke about
um like children and [ __ ] No one ever
spoke about that. It was It was only
until we come on here.
It was only until we come on here. Do
you understand? So that tells you all
you need to know. No. No.
What do I need to go on the dark web web for, bro?
It would never happen though, Dusty. It
would never happen.
It would never happen. It's never
happened in the past and it would never happen now.
cuz they wouldn't Google my name.
It wouldn't happen. So, and they don't
even know my name anyways. So, yeah,
it would never happen.
Imagine. You don't Yeah, you don't need
to imagine because it would never happen
cuz a they don't know my name and b they
wouldn't look me up. So, it would never
happen. It's never happened before. It
would never happen now. So, it would
never ever happen. So,
has it ruined my life? Nope. Definitely
definitely not ruin my life. No. Yeah.
Nope. Not at all. I haven't lost my kids
over it. I haven't It's called
inconveniences. Yeah. It's caused
inconveniences, but it's not ruined my life.
It's just caused inconveniences
time and time again. But no, it's not
ruined my life at all. Not really.
Well, we'll cross that bridge when we
come to it, isn't it?
It has in most aspects. Not at all.
I don't have kids that's been took away.
I've not lost money because of these
people. These people haven't ruined my
life. They tried to, but they haven't.
People that have tried to say they got
my money stopped. They've never got my
money stopped ever. Not one of these
people. And trust me, you'd know about
it if it happened. Oh, that's another
thing. If anyone got my money stopped,
that's that's another way I would do stuff.
Nope. I didn't get locked up at all. You
know what the police done? They they
they they they picked me up. One second.
One second. They picked me up with my
mom, interviewed me. I was there for
like half an hour and then they let me
go. They dropped us back as well. The
police dropped us back.
The police The police dropped us back
home the first time. Yeah, bro. So, I
mean, I'll take it. No. Didn't get
locked up at all. Didn't even get put in
the cell. So, what I don't understand
Can I Can I ask you a question now?
Right. Now, can I ask you a question?
like all of you people that watching
this cuz I'm generally curious now,
right? So, you know how you said that I
took an L against Timmy and well, I
didn't face him or whatever. Okay, so
why are none of you people on Nex's
channel calling him a coward for the
fact that I put up posters of him and he
didn't do a damn thing about it? Can I
understand why we don't see any of you
um on his channel asking that question?
Just just curious. Um bit bit biased,
isn't it? Where is he? Cuz you're
talking about people not doing stuff and
whatever. Well, how you going to let a
man put up posters around you all around
your area and you don't do a damn thing about it?
That's a good question. You know, I'd
love that question to be answered. Um,
and because you tried saying I was a
[ __ ] that's why I needed my mom. So,
we're not changing the subject. I
thought I'd just bring that up
cuz you all got your little agenda on
here. And that's another reason why you
shouldn't meet anyone for fights as well
cuz people have got their own agenda on
here. So they'll make up stuff that's not there. So yeah,
stick on a bouncer, they make excuses.
Stick it on two guys in front of their
girlfriends, they make excuses. Stick it
on women in Weather Spoons, they make
excuses. [ __ ] turn up to bomb, they
make like the list goes on and on and on
and on and on.
You're just bas It's just a biased
audience to begin with. And the fact it
goes around in circles even if he was to
meet any of these people. So
I mean the only way I could justify it
bro is if I went to Birmingham and I won
money to pay for the whole thing and I
could lose money and then have lost even
more money. It's not worth it. So that's
long legs on. It doesn't matter if he
mate listen listen listen. Uncle uncle
uncle he has spent years and years and
years bowed mouthing me on his channel.
It doesn't matter if he's calling people
out or he's not calling people out. He's
tried to get my money stopped. He's
badmouththed me a million times. He's
put my mom all over YouTube. Just
because you don't physically call
someone out, right, that doesn't make it
any better. It's like me, right, coming
on here now being racist, saying, "Oh,
black people's this, black people's
that." Uh uh uh uh. But I'm not calling
them out, so they can't do anything to
me. It doesn't work like that, bro. The
world doesn't work like that. Just
because you're not physically calling
someone out, it doesn't mean that you
you you got you got energy on the
internet. Yeah. Every day as well. Every
single day. All day. Every day. I don't.
So it's like it doesn't matter, bro. If
if they're calling people out or not.
Like you're you're trying to [ __ ] with
people. You're trying to [ __ ] with
people in real life. So simple as that.
Say something to their face. Simple as
that. And if you're not going to do that
despite someone putting up posters about
you, you're a coward. Simple as that,
bro. Like the thing is with me and Rick,
yeah, we might have took us We might
have took some L's. Yeah, me and Rick I
don't even like this Ricks guy. Me and
Ricks might have took some L's, bro. But
guess what? We've backed up a lot of our
talk and we put oursel in situations
where these things could happen.
Do you understand? Where that [ __ ] never has,
you know, we've actually put ourselves
in [ __ ] danger god knows how many
times. This little virgin has never. So,
you know, you can't It's just weird to
me. It's weird.
I couldn't be obsessed with someone
every day and then they come and then me
not and then I just couldn't do that,
bro. Posters is ridiculous.
It doesn't matter though. I've met
people. I've tried to meet people.
Nonsense hasn't dusty despite taking the
biggest L on it. Posters. Posters.
Someone someone putting up posters of
you. Like, that's crazy.
posters, actual posters, and you didn't
do anything to get me back. That's
crazy, bro. That is mental.
Well, again, this is what I'm saying.
This is the bias list again, lad.
Because if anyone else calls the police
on people, you'd call them a grass. So,
he didn't. And I'm not going to call
either. And this is exactly what I mean
with a bias list. You people say that
you don't like grasses. Oh, you don't
like people that inform the police. But
now you're saying someone's got one
over. Like, bro, you're biased. This is
why people don't entertain you. This is
this is exactly why I'm I'm trying to
explain to you why people don't
entertain you with these things anymore.
The money game, the meeting people, cuz
you're all biased. That's why no one
waste their time. I specifically told
Monty the other day, do not waste your
time. Let this guy do videos on you.
Like, it's the same thing as what you're
doing now. You people are saying that
you don't like grasses, police
informants, yet you're trying to big
somebody up that's called the police.
You're biased. That's why you're not
worth anyone's time. That's what I'm
This is what I'm saying. This is the
whole point I'm trying to make. You
know, with this nons legs, you seem to
love him for whatever reason. He could
be the biggest coward, the biggest [ __ ]
house, and you people still love him.
It's crazy. Like, it's stuff that me and
Kierin will never understand.
So, you must really love pedophiles.
Like, that's what that's what makes me
start thinking that you people must love
pedos. You must do. Like you you call
people pedos enough time on this
community, but you must really love
pedos. Biging up police informants,
biging up cowards. You really must love
the pedos. So like you you you shouldn't
really start calling people things that
you love in future. You know that. You
really really shouldn't lad. Bro, you
don't hate people that you don't know.
How can you hate people that you don't know?
Bro, listen. This guy is allowed to [ __ ]
stir fights. No one talks about the
posters. No one talks about when I've
gone to the cunt's area three times and
he's not shown up. Where's all of that gone?
You know, where's all of that gone, lad?
Where's all of that, bro?
I'm not allowed to call him a virgin.
Every time I call him a virgin, I get
sick. But he's allowed to call me a
virgin. Make that make sense.
So that's it.
That's it, bro.
Yep, pretty much.
Yeah, there are. Yeah, there are there
are people that do.
I mean, I said it's the same thing with
LT. I couldn't understand why LT was
backing him up when LT's had problems
with him in in the past. Cowardliness,
grassing. It It amazed me how he would
defend him every time I'd call him a
virgin. But every time he called me a
virgin, he didn't say anything. That was weird.
um since we were both a victim of their
bias list. That was weird. That thing
went on for ages. It just doesn't make sense.
That just did not make any sense whatsoever.
So that you let him call me a virgin,
but yet you don't like the guy, but
every time I call him a virgin, you got
something to say about this girlfriend.
Biasist. So yeah, I just didn't
understand that. Even though I provided
more evidence that I weren't a virgin, but okay.
Never made any sense. It doesn't make no
sense. The people on here don't make no
sense. That's that in it. So, yeah. So, um
Oh, well, that's that is it. M don't know.
He still tries to call me a virgin even
though I got his channel banned with
that porn video. Interesting.
Strange people are strange and people
are strange, aren't they, lad?
Yeah, they're very strange, these people
in here, aren't they, lad? They are strange characters.
Strange characters. Strange characters. M
goods damage goods damage goods
both damage goods I'm not a dam I'm not
damaged goods lads. [ __ ] hell, man.
Yeah, with that Christian Izzy, I was
scared. I was like, I hope she doesn't [ __ ] um
find my name or whatever. If she finds
my name like 3 4 months down the line,
it's not going to be as bad. But um
yeah, you don't want them finding your
name straight away, bro, and looking you up.
It's all right after a while. Well, it's
not all right, but you know, it's it's
um you get what I mean? Oh yeah. Yeah.
See, if you met someone for three or
four months, right, and you continuedly
meeting someone and you continuously met
someone and then they looked up your name,
they would like probably meet you again.
Whereas, if they haven't already met you
and then they saw all of this stuff,
then obviously they wouldn't. You get me? Uh uh.
Does that make sense?
Right. I need to go. We now major anxiety.
That's no laughing matter. You know that
that's no laughing about her.
It's quite serious, bro.
I'm doing it right now. Oh,
Elmo visits the farm.
Oh, he dusty. How comes How comes I can
watch Elmo visits the farm on the same
website I can watch um Timmy Aldra on?
How comes I can watch like on?
That's kind of beefy, bro.
Yeah, I'm just going to have some chicken today.
I need to save money. I need to go I
need to save money for Thailand, lad.
I need to save money for Thailand.
I dusty, you know, last Monday. Yeah,
you know, last Monday I cleared out I
cleared out waxies. I approached every gun going.
Every gun going, mate.
Yeah. I swear to God. Every going. No, you know,
Dusty, I'm I'm agrophobic, you know,
cuz I cuz my my My dick's my dick's too
big. Don't obviously went out with a
boner and stuff.
Yeah, makes sense.
I clean the sink, [ __ ]
I'm angry with me. Dad. Yeah, I leave the house.
probably does now. Yeah, maybe.
She said, "I've had enough of you."
Dusty lady said to me, "I've had enough
of you and this women thing."
She's like, "Oh, I've had enough of I've
had enough of you and this women thing."
She said, "What do you even want a woman for?" That's
what do you even want the woman for? No.
Laughing at you. [ __ ] you.
Dusty laughing at you. [ __ ] yeah.
them laughing at you. [ __ ] [ __ ] young.
And I can I can lie.
I can lie. You remember that?
That was a classic. I could let them.
Do you remember that?
That makes me laugh for a little while. >> Yeah. Oh,
it's jokes, bro. That is funny as [ __ ]
right? I need to Oh, someone stop him. What's that?
laughing at you. Mocking you.
Them [ __ ] were laughing at you.
Mocking you. Oh, mocking you.
Them women were laughing at you.
That man is a mad [ __ ] you know.
He's a [ __ ] mad [ __ ] No,
>> I'm gone. Yeah, [ __ ] later perhaps.
Yeah, in a