Let's see who's still on YouTube. Let's see.
Straight on YouTube.
UK asylum. Straight on YouTube. Are you?
You're straight on YouTube.
I done two football bets for today.
Yeah. £10 worth. I just spent £10 on a football. Yeah, bro.
I done a correct score.
I done a correct score. One, bro.
I don't I put £8 on one bet. Yeah. And
then two pound on the on the correct score.
Oh, that's funny. Chip, bro. Uh oops.
I got here.
This is what I done. Yeah, I done I done
this. Yeah, I done I done Darlington FC
versus Buckton. Yeah, 2-1. And I done
another one. I done I done Ky Minister
Harris versus Peter B 1.
So yeah, bro. I need to go to the Barbers, bro. Thursday 100%.
And I done another one. I've done a
double both team score to and win, which
is probably more likely. That correct
score? Yeah. Returned £166.
That's a good return, is it? It's just
hard to get.
Yeah, it's just hard to get. Yeah, bro.
How do you know it won't win? It might
win. I put one pound on six teams before
and it won.
You can't possibly say it won't win,
lad. You don't know that.
Anything could happen. Who knows?
Think about it, lad. I done six teams
before when I was 19. One pound. I got
£75 off of a pound.
So, how do you know it won't win?
They might win. You don't know.
Do you reckon people's got him before
the correct scores? I reckon they have.
I reckon I have
I reckon I have got Yeah.
Can I have
Yeah, Timmy done a video of me.
No, I don't. Yeah, Timmy done a video of me. Yeah.
Yeah. He done a video of me and that,
bro. I just ignored it cuz he just wants
my attention. Yeah. He's not getting it,
lad. Everybody knows the virginism.
We don't have to go over it again and
again, man. Let him let him keep self
projecting when he does these balls in,
bro. Trust me. Ignore him. Ignoring him
is the best way.
Ignoring him is the best way, bro. Trust me.
He's done his balls in again. He does
this every time, lad.
Just ignore it, man. Trust me. Yeah.
I on two football bets, Dusty. I on a
correct score one as well.
This little toxic sector toxic sector.
I like this toxic sector.
Yeah, I had peppies today. I had a pepp.
I ate in. I had a Weber spoon and I had a pepp.
Yeah, bro. [ __ ] hell. Yeah, I had peppies earlier.
roll on on um
yeah, roll on Thursday. I'm going to be
sending it. I had two beers today as
well, Greavvesy. Is that okay with you
if I had two Guinnesses?
Yeah, I met up with someone, so I kind
of had to.
No, not tomorrow. The next day, lads.
It's going to be fun.
They were laughing at you. Mocking you.
>> Mocking you. You don't understand what I
was planning to do that night, bro. But
it was a Monday, in it, so um not as
many people was out. I was going to pull
someone and start kissing them and
sending it to people and that. Bro, you
don't understand, Gres. You don't know
what I was going to do.
>> Yeah, everybody knows that you're a crazy [ __ ]
>> I mean, three free numbers from three
numbers, bro, on a Monday was sick. So,
Thursday is going to be even better.
Trust me. Trust me, it's going to be
even better, bro. He ain't stopping,
bro. We ain't stopping
laughing at you. [ __ ]
Trust me, that it's going to be a madness.
So, you can kiss goodbye to this two pound. You can
No, I'm going out on Thursday.
I was out today, but going out on Thursday's
coming back. Oh, really? That's nice.
Like, we're not giving him attention, bro.
I'm not giving him attention.
It's as simple as that. I'm not giving
he's bro he's a [ __ ] [ __ ] So yeah.
Yeah. First day I'm going to be it. Bro,
I'm lagging. I must be the old Must be
the old VPN. But yeah, DH10, I was
talking to Ant-Man. Yeah. and was saying
about how like you you're just going to
go out to socialize. Yeah, pretty much.
Pretty much, bro. You're you're actually
like you're actually going back to
socialize. Yeah, pretty much, lad.
Because you're not going to meet anyone.
It's never going to be any different.
So, you're just going out to go out. But
in theory, when you think about it, it
does make no sense. Spending £150, which
we'll probably be spending, and
nothing's going to change. But it's a
laugh, is it? So, why not, bro? I said I
was going to do it anyways. So 100% it's
on. I'm I'm not [ __ ] down now, bro.
Just going to send it, bro. Get pissed
and do a madness in it.
Yeah, I saw that thing you sent me on Instagram. Greavvesy,
can you hear me? Am I still lagging?
you still uh you can hear me or am I
still lagging, bro?
Yeah, I went on my Meoo channel. Yeah,
I went on my Magoo channel and I got
this comment lad from um
from um from this mic guy. I'm sure
you've seen the account and he was
saying about how oh, you call women
[ __ ] but it's you're the problem, not
them. Yeah. Okay, bro. Even though I
pull up messages. Okay. Okay. Even
though I put up proof of what they've
done, I'm the problem. Okay, bro. You
keep telling yourself that because these
people, lad, like they'll learn the hard
way anyways. They'll be virgins all
their life. Let them do what they do.
Let them keep defending women, bro. [ __ ]
them in it. They're the ones that are
going to be still in the same situation
[ __ ] 20 years later.
They're They're in denial. These people
are in denial, bro. Trust me, very in the Nile.
I went, "Hi, bro. Bro, I went on the
Virgin's video." Yeah, Greavesy.
And I see a comment. Yeah, I read it and
you know what it said? It said, "Lad, I
don't normally comment on videos, but
don't bother with this coward and I
suggest everyone else do the same
because he shouldn't be on here at all.
He's the biggest weakling going. You
could have him easy. I promise you."
And I'm thinking, "What? You're writing
that on Nlegs's channel? The one who I
put up posters about never got me back.
the one who who I went to the [ __ ] area
multiple times never got me back and I'm
and I'm the coward. You see what I mean
with the biasist on this community. Um
Grezy and I'm the coward. Someone that's
actually met people and backed up half
my talk. Okay. Yeah. Like you just laugh
at it in it. And it was some account
you've never seen before. It was an
account that I've never seen before. Um,
so it was obviously someone it's been
made 6 months ago and I'm thinking
you're saying that I'm a coward.
You're on a on a coward's channel saying
that I'm a coward.
You You think you'll end up going to
prison? Why are you asking stupid
questions? Why would I be going to prison?
What a stupid question to ask, bro.
Stupid stupid stupid question. That
doesn't make any sense. Why Why are you
asking stupid questions?
What a stupid question that is, lad.
But yeah, that person
that doesn't make any sense. How you're
going on his channel saying that I'm the
coward. Oh, please, bro.
Yeah, you you never win with these people.
Greasy. You never win with these people,
lad. Why do you think I don't get in
with it? I don't get in to it with Timmy
and stuff. I see the guy making a video
about me earlier. That's fine, bro. You
can keep making videos.
Yeah, it's worrying. I've heard it all before, lad.
Yeah. Go away, you little white knight.
You little white knight. Lavy mong.
You're irrelevant, lad. No one cares
about you. And guess what? Women Women
sense that you're a virgin. That's why
they don't get with you. And that's why
you're still a virgin. Because women
sense that you're an ugly virgin. And
that's why you're alone and you was on
here Christmas day. That's why you was
Mr. Lonely on Christmas with no family
cuz women can sense what you are. Mr.
Lonely. That was the same time [ __ ]
uh Monty man was trying to copy what I
was doing about seeing the people on on
YouTube Christmas. You [ __ ] [ __ ]
sat on YouTube Christmas. You sad
bastard. Don't you ever try and talk
about me. You ly mong. Don't you ever,
ever, ever, ever try and talk about me,
you creepy, ugly, single, no girlfriend,
no family on YouTube Christmas Day. You
loser, ever try and talk about me. You
[ __ ] little virgin.
Sim little virgin. Don't ever try and
talk about me, bro. There's certain
people you got to say that to, bro.
Uh, Lord J. And you know what? I'm
coming off this community soon anyways,
bro. Like I'm going to do Thursday. I
said I was going to do Thursday. You
know what it is with people on here.
DH10. Yeah. I was I was on here
yesterday. Yeah. I don't I don't know if
you was on here. I don't think he was.
Uh and I won £100. Yeah. And I said,
"Oh, I'm going to send it Thursday."
Bro, I had to block like 20 30 accounts.
I was talking about this earlier when I
was in the pub and it's like they tried
to bring the energy down. These fat old
ugly men sat on YouTube every day. No
life. You can see how much Yeah. They
tried to bring the energy down. They
tried to bring the vibe down because
they're fat, ugly, no money, no life.
Yeah, they were proper trying to bring
the energy down, bro. I had to ban God
knows how many accounts. It's madness.
You don't know. Oh, well, yeah, they
they're trying to bring the energy down. Yeah.
So, I had to block like 20 accounts.
Most of the people in this community,
lad, they're just fat old men. They
ain't got a life. Mo most of the people
on here, lad.
Just sat skin on YouTube every day.
Ain't got nothing. That's what most of
the people are like on this community. I
don't know if you noticed, but yeah,
they try to bring the energy down. They
try to bring the madness down, you know,
cuz they're sat at home alone, nothing
going for themselves. That's why they're
on YouTube for 15 years speaking about
men they don't know. They're weirdos,
bro. Proper weird. And then when you
tell them about themselves, when you
when you talk about uh these people that
like what they are, they try to say like you
basically um you're reacting when you're
not reacting. You're just telling people
what they are.
Um, I done an experiment Christmas day
where I put my phone upstairs, I went
live, went downstairs, didn't look on
the phone, I went straight back up and
this little weirdo was on YouTube.
So yeah, I done a little experiment to
see who was on YouTube Christmas Day
before going to my sisters and lo and
behold, these people was on YouTube Christmas Day.
Yeah, let him keep talking about me,
bro. No one cares. Uh, a white knight is
basically people that just defend women
for the sake of defending women. No, no,
no. It's not. I've already explained it
to you. I'm not explaining it to you
again. I just told you that I done an
experiment where I left my phone
upstairs and then I went downstairs and
I left my phone upstairs. I went back up
after I made a tea just to see who was
on YouTube and I quickly ended the live
stream. No, YouTube. What you people was
on Christmas Day. No, big difference.
Now, don't try to reverse the psychology.
Don't try to reverse the psychology now.
Yeah, that little experiment proves who
the low lives were. Yeah.
Yeah, they are.
Okay, I'm not explaining it again. I've
already explained it to you and I'm not
explaining it again. Like I said, if you
don't understand it the first time,
that's that's on you, lad.
That's on you. Okay, whatever. If your
brain don't work properly, go to your
doctor's land. I'm not explaining it again.
Anyways, moving on.
This is what you have to do with the
people of this community. Yeah. Anyways,
I can't wait until Thursday. It's going
to be a madness. I got a new top, by the way. for Thursday.
Yeah. It's going to be a madness. Anyways, so yeah,
I need to go cinema as well. And this is
something I got that to do as well. Yeah, man. Really?
That's interesting. Dusty, what about
people What about people that come
online for 15 years stalking men every
day? Do you not think that's a bit
weird? Like what Red Star does? Do you
not think that's a bit strange
considering I wouldn't even do that to a woman
and I've been obsessed in the past and
mad in the past and most people don't
think the way that I think. Do you not
think that's a bit strange to sit there
and stalk men every day for God knows
how many years?
Bit weird I think. But
I think that's very very strange. It's
very very strange how like they've not
got bored after like 6 months like I
keep saying it's not like they've done
it due during co or they done it for 3
months they've been doing it for years
and you know at the end of the day they
they say to people like time's a healer
isn't it whether someone's in love or
whatever or they get bored of stuff they
that is very [ __ ] weird you I
couldn't stalk anyone for four or five
years bro man woman, [ __ ] dog,
whatever the [ __ ] they are, that is that
is beyond mental health.
And that's what it mainly is. It's what
they actually do on here that people, a
lot of these people hating, talking
about people that they don't know.
That's what it mainly is. It's actually,
it's what they're doing on here also.
Cuz believe it or not, uh people can sit
on uh people can sit on YouTube for 18
hours a day, Dusty, and talk about
religion. There's so many communities
out there where they talk about religion,
um you know, and and and and stuff. And
they'll be live all day talking to each
other. But I mean, that's that's a
different story, you know, than than this community,
you know? This community is
[ __ ] up, bro.
tent dweller who Monty.
But yeah, you can tell Timmy's
definitely done his balls in, lad. When
he keeps going on about me, you know
he's done his balls in.
I had two Guinnesses today. I couldn't
help it, bro. [ __ ]
I didn't want to drink. But it's only
two Guinnesses, isn't it?
Yeah, it's only two, isn't it?
If I get hungry later, I can't eat cuz
of um I've already ate twice today. So,
hopefully we get one of these football bets today.
I don't give them a reaction. I just
think what they do is weird.
The truth is not a reaction, lad. It's
not a reaction. What they do is weird.
It's not about reacting. I don't react
to any of these people. I think what
they do is very weird.
Don't know. I don't know.
Half chicken and a half chicken and chips.
Half chicken, chips, and uh drink.
14 pound it cost. [ __ ] expensive, bro.
No, there's a difference between having an opinion
and um and reacting. I'm not reacting.
I'm just stating the people are here
biased. That's not me reacting.
So, yeah, it it tastes much better when you eating.
They had some they put some onions and
and and lettuce by the chicken. Um here,
don't get lippy. Don't get lippy. Greasy.
Maybe I want to get lippy.
Maybe I want to get lippy, bro.
So, listen. What's the odds? Uh, okay.
So, what's the odds, Grezy, that I'm
going to go out on uh
What's the odds, Grezy, that I'm going
to go out on Thursday and not get one lumber?
Yeah, but it's expensive, bro. It's still expensive.
Is expensive, bro. £14 for a chicken meal.
No, I'm just stating like or something.
And that's not Lando's. That's
expensive. That's almost the same price.
Really? It is. It's getting there, bro.
It's too much, bro. It's nice, though. I
do like it. It is too much though for
something that's not [ __ ] branded, bro.
You know what I'm saying?
Bunch of me not getting a number is a
one in about 500.
I don't know. You have to ask Grezy if
I'm a copycat.
You have to ask Grezy, man.
What's your opinion, Grezy?
I was watching a Harry Potter interview,
Indie, and then Timmy popped up. Timmy Eldridge.
Uh, really greasy. Yeah.
And what about when LJ goes drinking in
the pubs and puts his camera on
and speaks to one of the member of a staff?
What's that being?
Okay. Well, what about when L J has curry? Greavvesy.
Yeah, but the thing is Greavvesy,
Greavvesy, Grievy, Greavvesy.
One second. Do you not Do you know one
thing these people have not been able to
copy of me?
Indie go. Do you know what one thing
these people have never been able to
copy that I do? I'm sure you can figure it out.
There's one thing they haven't been able
to do. Seaside mark a they've never been
able to do that. drunk, sober, they've
never been able to do it. No one else
but Peter Belly can do it.
But that's because they've got anxiety.
They would they would they would try if
they could, but they ain't got the
balls. So, I mean,
um, yeah, that's the only thing they've
not been able to do because of anxiety in it.
They ain't got birds. Nor a J single.
Seaside Mark single. Timmy single.
No. Most of the people in this community
single. Same with me. I'm single.
But they ain't got birds, have they?
That's the thing.
L ain't got no one. Timmy ain't got no
Virgin boy didn't approach when uh he was single.
There's no way that I would go out and
not approach. Why would you go out drinking,
spending 100, £130, whatever, and not approach?
I just couldn't. I just wouldn't see the
point unless you was in a relationship.
I don't see why you wouldn't do that.
I'll be doing it all day on Thursday,
bro. I'll be getting there early, bro. So,
I don't know. That seems weird to me.
Is it out drinking in it? So why? Yeah.
It's not cheap either to go out drinking. So nowadays,
is that right?
Then I'm going to go cinema greasy and
get a pick a mix.
Yeah, I'm going to go cinema some point.
It's called Dolly.
It's a horror movie called Dolly.
All right. What do you think of my
football bets, Dust? Uh Dusty, right?
Darlington versus Buckton, correct score
2-1. Hiddy Minister and Peter Burough.
Uh correct score 1-1. No,
no. I I made posters of you, mate, and I
stopped you doing what you love.
Um and then uh I done slow and um versus
Hampton and Richmond. SL to win both
teams to score
and then do to win and both teams to
score against uh yeah do and Tumbridge.
So yeah, I got some [ __ ]
it's it's kiddo minister. Why did I say
kitty minister? It's kiddo minister.
No, no, he got her from the disabled
club. Okay, I'll answer I'll answer your
question. He got it from the disabled club
because he ain't got the looks to get
anything normal cuz he's an ugly bastard.
Gregy loves that. Is it
because he's a [ __ ] ugly [ __ ] Ugly bastard.
Ugly [ __ ] that resembles a rat. NO ONE
WANTS THAT UGLY RAT THEN. So he started
going for the smash sticks. You know,
yeah. Do you know what I might do? I
might I might get with Britney.
She's of age, you know. I probably have
a chance with her. You She weren't
interested in you. Didn't want to know
you, mate. Didn't want to know you. She
just weren't interested in you.
And you know, she [ __ ] rejected you,
mate. She was a [ __ ] adult. You know
what I'm saying?
You know, she [ __ ] rejected you.
Hey, do you know what, bro? My It's
funny you should say that. Yeah. But
it's funny you should say that. My
sister said the same thing. My sister
said the same thing the other day. I was
sending voice notes to someone. They
forward it and she was like, "I'm
tapped." You remember when I was in
central London? Like, I'm going to get
that. I'm going to go to Elen. Yeah.
Let's meet up. Come on.
Dusty. Dusty and Greasy. Yeah.
I need to be on medication.
I need to be on meds.
You know, I'm hyper. I think it's all the sugar.
She was like, "I'm tapped." Yeah, but I
was going to pull up. I agree with you.
I was gonna pull up.
I was gonna I was actually gonna pull
up, lad. I'm not even joking cuz I was
in the middle. I was in like central
London in it. So, bro, you even want to
do it? You either want to do it normal
or do it bad
or do it bad,
mate. The only one that's got Down
syndrome is that [ __ ] ugly Sarah
you're [ __ ] with. So, you know all
about Down syndrome. Yeah,
I was I literally uh I was literally in
the middle. I was going to I was going
to go there. Greasy, you don't believe
me, do you? You don't believe me. I
said, "Let's meet up now. Come on. Come on."
Yeah. Anyway, see you later, mate. No
virgins. Flip rule, mate. So, yeah. Seriously, Dusty?
Yeah, you're talking about yourself,
lad. Stop self projecting.
Yeah, that's self projecting your life,
lad. See you later. But yeah, anyways,
bro, I was in I was in the middle,
but I was I was going to go there.
You don't believe me? I would have went
there. Then I got called scary. I'm a
[ __ ] bro. I'm not scary. I'm actually
not scary, you know, bro. Like, I hate
it like [ __ ] calling me scary, bro.
I'm a lovely fellow,
I'm a lovely I'm a lovely fellow.
You know that and I know that. I'm a lovely fellow.
I'm a lovely little fellow,
you know, just just just misunderstood at times.
No, I didn't. But your mom did. She told
me yesterday when we was drinking wine
together on the sofa.
No, but your mom did cha
cha cha cha cha cha
cha cha cha cha cha cha.
Grezy's Grezy can't wait until Thursday,
can he? What a [ __ ] Make up for um
lost time, eh? Make up for some lost
time. Hey, Grezy.
Okay with you, boss.
Look, mate. More like counting down the seconds. M 100%.
Would you do it? 100%. Yeah.
I 100% I would have went 100%. I said
you want an apology so bad. Come and
meet me. Come on, meet me, Grezy.
But it's weird though, Grezy, cuz I I I
started off like local. You know where
my mom lives? I I I I started off local
and I ended up in central London.
So what I mean, Grezy, is going wherever
Peter Belly's little legs take him.
Just going wherever my little legs take me.
Wherever my little legs take me. Grezy,
it's not right.
Wherever my little legs take me.
Oh, that's not going to stop us.
No, but seriously, I'm just going to be
sending it on Thursday and that. No,
seriously. I'm just going to
have to try and find a new mama. No,
seriously. Seriously, I am going out though.
I am I am actually going out though.
I was thinking I thinking of going to
Birmingham, but I don't know. Will
London Taylor see that music?
I might go to Birmingham, maybe sort
Timmy out, but but um
I don't want London Taylor seeing it,
but maybe he won't see it because he's
not on YouTube,
so I'm not sure how that would uh work.
cuz he doesn't always come on YouTube in
it. So maybe he might not see it. Grezy,
what's your opinion on that?
>> Toxic sector.
>> I love that, bro. I love that. Toxic
sector. Yeah. Yeah, that had me howling,
bro. You people are energy vampires. But
no, it's actually true though because
you do try to bring the mood down. When
I was when I was happy yesterday. Yeah.
Oh, I'm going to go out Thursday. I'm
going to go out Thursday. I'm going to
go out Thursday. You You lot was trying
to bring the energy down.
You trying to kill the vibe, man. Toxic sector.
Yeah, it is a toxic sector though. You
don't like toxicity, do you Greavvesy?
You're probably wondering why I'm not
out today drinking. And that's purely
because there's no there's not going to
be any people. There's not going to be
any women around Tuesday. Not really.
So, you have to wait a couple of days.
Thursday will be perfect.
I will send it, lad. I will be sending
it. Don't you [ __ ] worry, bro.
I can't believe I went out Monday last week, Greavvesy.
It weren't even It was actually all
right for Monday.
It was all right. It actually was all
I already had two pints today, Dusty. I
already had two pints.
You never know where little Peter
Belly's legs going to are going to take
him in it, Greasy. Going wherever my
little legs will take me.
Going wherever my little legs will take me.
That's cute, isn't it, Grezy?
Oh, bless you.
Make sure you don't do your balls in Dusty.
How many beers you have in Dusty? 2 3 4
5 6 7 8 9 10 11 12 13 14 15 16 17 18 19
20 21 22 23 24 25 26 27 27 28 29 30 31
32 33 Or will you have
34 35 36
37 38 39
40 or we have 41 or we have 42 43 44 45
46 47 7 48 49
50 51 52 53 54 55 56 57 58 59 60 61 62
63 64 65 66 67 68 69 70 71 72 72 73 74
75 76 77 78 79
80 You're going to have to wait.
I'm going to have to wait.
Yes, until I stop counting. 81 82 83 84
85 86 87 88 89 90 91 92 93 94 95 96 97 98 99
100 beers Dusty.
What if you had a 100 beers now at all
the amount I count is the amount you
have to drink and you have to do a
video. Thank you very much. 101 102 103
104 105 106 107 108 109 110 111
OH, I can't count anymore. This is what
these women do. They make you lose your
mind, Grievy. They make you lose your
mind and your soul and everything. God, they're horrible.
Weebsy, they make you lose your mind, Greavvesy.
They make you lose your [ __ ] mind.
They really do, Grezy. Oh gosh.
N no no no m
dusty why don't you go to waxis it's
active Monday Tuesdays lad
three numbers on a Monday that weren't
That weren't bad.
Dusty, why don't you go go waxies, lad?
In the place I was drinking, Greavves,
it was £4 a Guinness. Where you go,
central London, it's about £780 a
Guinness. That is steep, isn't it?
Yeah, that is steep to be fair.
Yeah, that's steep, lad. Yeah, man.
I'll be going where I want. Thank you very much.
I'll go exactly where I want. Thank you
very much, Greavves. I'll be saying tomorrow.
No one's going to be tomorrow, Thursday.
No one's going to be telling me nothing.
They're going to be telling me nothing, bro.
Got some money.
and then tried scamming me, [ __ ]
by scamming me, greedy. But it weren't
going to work, was it? Cuz Peter Belly's
one step ahead of these [ __ ]
[ __ ] off, ice cream. I don't want your
silly ice cream.
Well, I'm trying to send some money
over. What's going on?
I don't want your stupid ice cream. [ __ ] off. Right.
Hold on a minute.
Don't get lippy with me.
I can't believe she said what I told you
she said, Greavvesy.
That's horrible, bro. Is it?
All I can say to you, Greavvesy, is good
luck to you.
Good luck to you, lad.
Where's my gallery, bro?
Yeah. Good luck to you, mate. You're
going to need it. Bless you.
What you up to? Mush. Look at all that
mush talk, bro. Who is it? Grezy.
So, Grezy, what are you what are you
saying that they were laughing at me,
mocking me? Is that what you were
saying, Grezy? They were laughing at
you, mocking you. Really?
Were they actually doing that? Grezy.
Who? Grievesy. Who?
Yeah, that Christian easy turned into a
proper [ __ ] bro, with what she was
saying in it. I didn't even clock it until earlier. Yeah.
Yeah. They're [ __ ] in it,
busy. No, they don't mock me, bro. They
don't mock me because when they try to
get rude, I tell them about themselves.
I tell them about themselves and they
shut up. So they definitely definitely
don't laugh, mate. Cuz they're not
laughing when I stick it on them. So
yeah, I don't see any of them laughing,
mate. I see them running to the police
when people get their family involved. I
see people [ __ ] [ __ ] themselves
when they get stuck on. Don't see any of
these people laughing. Yeah.
They definitely don't mock me, lad.
This chat GBT is really good though.
Greavvesy, I've been asking it a lot of stuff.
It's quite accurate, bro. Oh [ __ ]
Oh [ __ ] man. M.
Did you say one of the women's numbers I
got looked westernized? Grezy,
was it the eyes?
Was it the eyes? Greasy.
We are the eyes.
I'm laughing at you. [ __ ]
I got three new mumas last week, didn't I, Grezy?
I got three new mumas last week.
None of them replied to me. I'm have to
give them another little message.
We Ant-Man said that they're not
interested in this country.
I think he was right, lad. You know, we
we know we take the piss out of it.
Yeah. But I think he's right, you know, bro.
Obviously, he's right, bro. it because
if it's if it's been going on for years
then I mean yeah of course he's right in it.
I think he's right, Reezy. I don't know
about you, but yeah.
I reckon. Yeah, I reckon so.
But people on Reddit say it's easy, Grezy.
People on Reddit say, "Put yourself out there, Grezy."
What's your opinion on that?
What's your opinion on that, bro? Please.
So, I go to the pictures today.
People on Reddit say you'll meet someone, Dusty.
Yeah, people on Reddit say you'll meet someone.
I'm just going to take Reddit's advice, Dusty.
Yeah, I just go on Reddit in it.
Yeah, I just listen to Reddit, bro. I'll
be out Thursday. [ __ ]
His films are on until very late, bro.
It's not on until very late, lad.
They just aren't interested in this country, Dusty.
[ __ ] bro. 10:00. That is late, bro.
I'm not going out at 10:00, lad.
Yeah, I do. That's nice, lad.
Oh, yeah. There's a new scary movie
coming out, isn't there? Oh gosh.
Is this like Let me have a look.
I don't see him live. He's not live.
I don't see him alive, lad. Where is he?
Where is he, bro?
Where is it, bro? Oh,
what was he saying? I I was out, lad.
Cuz some of us have got a life. I was
out. I didn't see anything.
What was he saying? Greasy. Really?
Yeah, he can [ __ ] off, bro. He can [ __ ]
off. He's probably not even in Birmingham.
He's probably Yeah. Why am I going to
meet someone? Yeah. Why am I going to go
to Birmingham and meet someone on the on
the same website you can watch Ry the Bear on?
Why am I going to do that greasy?
This is supposed to be a fun place, not
a toxic sector. Why am I going to go on
the same website you can watch the bear one?
Yeah. Really? What he wonders every day?
He says Squeezy Monty man said, "Yeah,
do you know what I wonder every day? why
you got me on this community. I wonder
that every day.
That's what he said, Grezy. That's I
wonder that every day. You know, he said
because we [ __ ] live for toxicity. Do
you understand, bro?
I had I had I had pepp. But no, it was
his own fault as well, Grezy. It was his own fault.
It was his own fault cuz he had chances
to get off YouTube in its
He did have chances to come off it
though, didn't he? Yeah,
I got my mama fund ready for Thursday. Greavvesy.
Hey with you, boss.
Is that okay with you, boss?
Uh hopefully one of these football bet
win these football one of these football
bets win too.
Imagine they both win. Yeah, right. Oh gosh, Grezy.
I'm going to find a mama on Thursday.
Somebody that can love me for me.
What do you think about that? Grezy one
that can love me for me.
What do you think? What do you think, Pip? H.
One that can read me bedtime stories. You know,
one that can read me bedtime stories
like Elmo gets read bedtime stories. Greavvesy.
A Looney Tune. A Looney Tune. Greavvesy. Ah, that's funny.
That's really funny, Grezy. No,
I'm going to bring her back to your mom's house.
Keep it a secret. Oh gosh.
No, but seriously, I'm hoping one of
these football bet wins. Imagine the
correct score wins. Grezy,
I reckon it will win. That correct score me?
I reckon that's a banger, bro.
I reckon so, bro. I reckon that's we're
in there, lad. Oh gosh,
that [ __ ] in the park weren't mocking
me, was she, Greavvesy? She ran away
when I was shouting.
Yeah, she was [ __ ] She ran away when
I was shouting, isn't it?
Yeah, [ __ ] wasn't laughing then. You
[ __ ] [ __ ] pair of [ __ ] Remember
that greasy pair of [ __ ] on that Sting
video? You call yourself security pair of [ __ ]
You remember, bro? You got [ __ ] um
the one that got nicked.
You got the neighbor got nicked with it. You could
[ __ ] call yourself security [ __ ]
pair of [ __ ] Oh gosh. Yeah. Please.
So what you're saying is when I come
back Thursday night, Greavvesy Kieran's
Kieran's going to come on my live, isn't
it? He seems to always come on when I'm drinking.
Yeah, he seems to always come on when
I'm drinking that [ __ ]
I got a bonus on Frankie Grevy. I got excited.
I got excited, Grezy.
And then it paid me [ __ ]
We're getting on it. Thursday.
I've been looking forward to this.
Please. I've been looking forward to this.
You probably more than me though. Huh?
Yeah. Fake Monty
laughing at you, mocking you.
Yeah, that's fake Monty, is it?
That's fake Monty, ain't it? Yeah.
Monty, listen. Listen. Yeah.
Is that Is that Is that the real Monty?
No, it's not.
No, it's not the real Monty.
Nope. Fake one. This looks
So, Pip, I've got a question.
So, why did people used to say Chev's
attractive pip smoker?
Nah, bro. I was out. I was busy, bro. I
Why do people say it? Uh, Pip.
Oh, like even even nonslegs. I mean,
that accent alone just makes them [ __ ] ugly.
I mean, the accent alone is is terrible, bro.
Imagine being with someone that's got a
[ __ ] Jordy accent. Oh, Pip, you're
funny you are, bro. You're a little
copycat. I'll tickle you. I'll tickle
you. You copycat.
Nons said it to fit in.
All right. Nons legs literally said it
to fit in.
Smokey said it to fit in.
To fit in, lad.
I'll never forget when Barker said that
to fit in.
No, sorry, bro. It does tickle me sometimes.
You want to feel left out? Let's
see you later.
I've seen him recently. Yeah,
I've been seeing some of his videos.
He comes up on Instagram. Yeah, I see him.
He looks a [ __ ] though.
Yeah, it could be up on the thing sometimes.
I agree with you. Do you remember? Oh,
do you remember Barquest?
Barquest. Why is he saying that? Bar and
Bquest was like to fit in to fit in to fit.
Oh, that's funny, bro.
He was saying it to fit in with the
crowd. You didn't want to feel left out.
You didn't want to feel left out at school.
You didn't want to feel left out.
That's why he was saying she's
attractive, isn't it? Hi. Um,
Steven, I'm going out Thursday.
Yeah, I'm on the piss on Thursday. [ __ ] hell. Darling,
don't get lippy with me. Darling,
you want to go there, mate? You want to greasy?
You want to go there, mate? You want to
go there, man?
You want to go there, mate?
I think I'm getting
you. I actually think I'm getting
taller. Like my little legs are growing.
My little legs are growing.
I swear to God, bro.
You want to go there, mate?
You want to go there? You want to go
there, mate? That's what I was going to
say. Pick smoke to that Christian. I was
going to say, do you want to You want to
go there, mate? You want to go there,
mate? And see see them what you're saying. Look.
Yeah. Don't know who that I don't know
who that is.
Do it, mate.
I love laughing.
My favorite thing to do about making myself a minute. Uh,
I give him a one out of 10.
All right, focation link
where virgin boy can can we get we can
raise some money for the virgin so we
can get an escort and he can finally get
laid to lose his virginity.
That sounds like a perfect [ __ ] idea, is it?
So you will no longer be the 31y old
virgin. You only be [ __ ] owners that ma.
What do you think about the donation link?
Uh oh. Gives you a big virgin.
What do you think?
What do you think, lad? Huh?
you want to go there, mate?
Uh, you only skin only skin people are
you lads s on YouTube every day and and
to get and and and for an escort pip
smoker and for an escort so you can get
[ __ ] laid. Pip smoker. I also need to
get [ __ ] laid.
I also need to [ __ ] get [ __ ] laid.
Not a virgin. He's a big virgin. He's a
Oh, lovely lad.
Yeah, but he doesn't need a donation
link for the dentist because the dentist is free
for people on benefits, mate. They're free.
Yeah, it's free for people on benefits.
So, he need to get laid.
I couldn't imagine being a 31y old virgin.
Couldn't imagine it, mate. I had sex
when I was 17, mate. Probably shouldn't
be admitting that, mate. But I [ __ ] well did.
Can imagine not having it at 30 [ __ ]
one ever once in your life. That's [ __ ] madness.
Yeah, he hid in it. Where do you think
he was when I was live in the house? He
must have been hiding somewhere, ain't
it? You must have been hiding somewhere, ain't it?
cuz the cab was still there and
everything. And he didn't get he didn't
get on a bus straight away, lad.
Cuz you never got in the bus, mate. Cuz
the buses take ages here. So where was
you, you [ __ ]
Where [ __ ] was you? H
They told me to go to the pub. I went to
the pub. He wasn't there, lad. What the [ __ ]
Don't get lifty with me, darling.
Don't get lifty with me. All
right, I'm going to end the live stream
now. Yeah. And I'll be back later, maybe.