Oh, [ __ ] hell. Hang on.
Why is that still plugged in?
Yeah, it's still happening tomorrow,
bro. It's still happening tomorrow.
Oh, he's straight on YouTube again. UK
asylum, bro. [ __ ] hell, man. I've
gone out done some washing
straight on YouTube, lad. every day. You
You need to get yourself a You need to
get a little life for yourself, lad. Yeah.
It's so mad. Yeah. To think that I'm
going to be wasting £200 in this economy. Yeah.
I'm going to be wasting £200 on
something that's just going to be the
same. It's mad when you think about it,
is it? Like
Like actually wasting 200 on nothing basically.
How mad is that?
It is actually pretty mad when you think
about it, isn't it?
Nothing happens and nothing changes.
It's mad, isn't it, in this day and age,
bro? Quite a lot of money in this day
and age, isn't it?
It's wild. I was going to go out today,
but we said Thursday in it. Yeah.
Some more bad experiences tomorrow, lad.
I can't wait.
I can't wait, bro. No, I'm getting my
haircut tomorrow when I go out.
No, they didn't. No, they didn't.
Now, I'm getting my haircut on um
tomorrow. I'm going to go out tomorrow.
I was going to get my haircut today, but
I thought I might as well get it done tomorrow.
Saying that I could get it done today, ain't it?
might get on today. Yeah.
I'm not going to style my hair tomorrow.
I don't think I'm just going to leave it
like curly in it.
Is that what I done last time, man? I can't remember.
Yeah, I think I did. I just left it.
I might get my haircut today.
I don't know.
It'd be better if I do do it today, actually.
That way I don't have to rush tomorrow
in it. Yeah, I'll get my haircut a bit
later. Yeah, [ __ ] it.
Just going to wear casual.
casual top with jeans. Doesn't really
matter what you wear, does it? It's
going to be the same result anyway,
isn't it? So,
no, I'm going out, Grezy. I'm going to
send it, bro.
Be sending it all night. I'm just
wearing I'm just going to be wearing
jeans and a top. That's it. I don't need
to dress up.
Not Spider-Man t-shirt. Nope, I'm not wearing that.
It's mad, isn't it, Greasy to think that
you'll throw away £200 on nothing. Like
literally nothing. It's mad when you
think about it, isn't it? There's
absolutely no chance.
But remember, Grezy, the more you think about it,
them [ __ ] were laughing at you. Mocking
Yeah. So that's all the reason to do it.
Laughing at you. Mocking you.
[ __ ] that, bro. So, yeah, I got the
money here, so I'm going to need to take
£50 for a haircut. Yeah, man.
I'll get I'll get some nice food
tomorrow as well, Greasy.
You would know all about repeating, lad.
And you're going to get a timeout. See
you later, lad.
Yeah. So, that leaves money for the food
and the drinking.
Yeah, I probably will get my haircut
today actually. It makes more sense.
I need a I need a fresh pillowcase
though cuz I don't want to put my like I
don't want to put up my face on a dirty
um pillow. So, I had a shower anyways. So, yeah.
Yeah, bro. Look. [ __ ] hell. I need to
go to the barbers. I need my hair to dry
first though, bro.
And I'm just going to leave my hair like
curly. I'm not even going to style it. I
don't give a [ __ ] Yeah.
Grey Grey Grey
laughing at you. Mocking you.
I'm having a steak to eat today. I got
myself a steak.
Yeah, I got myself a lovely steak,
which I love later. Went out this
morning. I was going to get my haircut,
but I just didn't.
But yeah, it saved me rushing around
tomorrow. That's the thing.
Just saves me um Yeah.
What a life. Hey, Grezy. What a [ __ ]
life. Remember that, Grezy? What a
[ __ ] day I've had.
What a [ __ ] day I've had. Unfortunately. Yeah, unfortunately.
We're actually wasting We're actually
throwing away £200 for no reason.
>> Is that right, Grezy? We're throwing
away. How many DVDs can you get with £200?
Probably quite a lot. No,
I' I'd imagine quite a few.
and we're just casually throwing it away
on something that's just going to be the same.
But when I say when I say I'm going to
do something, [ __ ] I'll do it.
Simple as that.
When I say I'm going to do something,
I'll do it. I'll do it. Simple. 100%.
So I say I'm going to do something, I'll do it. What's up?
Goodness, bad experiences being led on.
That's all that's going to happen.
Should we do a bet on it, Grezy? Should
we do a bet on it? 100%.
I reckon we should 100%.
That's something I definitely bet on.
But I said I'm going to go out, didn't I? So
So yeah, no, no turning back now cuz
this will be it now. So
yeah, be no turning. I'll probably be
out really early tomorrow as well. I'll
be sending it all day.
So um so drunk. So,
let's see what a full session looks like
in um 2026. Rezy,
let's see what a full session looks like in 2026.
What do you think a full session looks like?
could go out today, but more people will
be out tomorrow. So,
Thursdays will be better. Um, yeah. Yeah, bro. That's that.
And then I'll probably be starting the
gym and then I won't be on there much.
So yeah, you'll get your content
tomorrow, Gre. Yeah, that'll be it, lad. Um,
that's it, bro. What more can I say? Poor [ __ ] Yeah. So,
um, that's what will happen.
I might try the Carolina Reaper burger
tomorrow, part two, but I don't know if
it'll be a good idea, bro. I don't know
if it'll be a good idea.
If I'm being completely honest with you,
bro, I don't know if it'll be a good idea.
I don't think I'll be able to beat it
even this time to be honest with you, bro. man
until May. Probably later than May.
Probably later than May, bro.
This dating thing is very, very
depressing. Very, very, very depressing.
I know it sounds funny to you, Grezy.
I'd laugh as well if I was if I was like
watching someone [ __ ] talking about
it, but it's so depressing.
It actually really, really is.
Really, really, really is so depressing.
Thursdays are the day that I normally go
out, so that's why I picked Thursday.
I know some people like Saturdays, but I
like Thursdays. So, it will be Thursday.
Just tomorrow, so I need to get my
haircut in a bit. Going to go to the
barbers in a bit. Yeah.
Big day of disappointment tomorrow.
Isn't that right, Grezy?
That's what it's going to be tomorrow.
Big big disappointment.
Hope you're looking forward to it.
I most certainly am.
Especially after that Christian Izzy
thing. Who wouldn't want more bad experiences?
Who really wouldn't want more bad experiences?
Who wouldn't want more bad experiences?
Like anyone would, you know.
Anyone would want more bad experiences.
I know I [ __ ] would and do.
Just going out getting pissed.
Just getting more bad experiences with
women and getting pissed. Yeah.
And then I'm coming off here for a long
time. And I'm not drinking for a very
long time as well. I made up my mind
earlier to be fair. Yeah.
Too depressing, lad. Too depressing.
Well, no, it's not a normal day out cuz
I'm going to be out all day.
Cuz I'm going to be out all [ __ ] day.
These simps are mad, ain't it, Grezy?
These simps are mad.
What do you think, lad? They're very
mad, is it? These simps.
These simps are very mad. They're very
crazy, aren't they? Uh, greasy lad.
They make me laugh, bro.
These white knight simps make me laugh.
What I don't understand, Grezy, I'm sick
of repeating this, bro, but [ __ ] it.
Just throw it out there, bro. What I
don't understand is how they can defend
them when they're shown what they've done.
That's the thing that makes me laugh.
That's the thing that I find quite
funny, how they can defend
when they're shown what they've done.
That's what that's what that's what baffles me. Yeah.
They also defend um
uh they also they also defend leading on
and [ __ ] as well.
Well, they dismiss Well, sorry, Grezy.
They also dismissed the leading on and stuff.
They Yes, they also dismissed them
leading people on and stuff.
It's Thursday tomorrow. Pull it on your
pull it in your calendar.
Pull it in your calendar, man.
Yeah. No one. Hey, bro. Listen. If that
guy If that gay guy comes up to me
tomorrow, Grezy, I'm gonna record it. Yeah,
I'm gonna record it, lad.
So, I'll record it for you, bro. I'm
going to go live anyways, but I'll
record it for you. I might do some videos
with a bit of like updates and then
maybe go live later or something like
that, but I'll record everything. Yeah,
trust me, bro. I will. Trust me. I will record everything.
tell him to [ __ ] off and mind his own
business. How about that one, Greasy?
For some for some toxicity.
It's already bad enough. You get bad
experiences, bro. And then you need you
need people trying to put loopholes on
you. What the [ __ ] Nah, bro.
So, I said, I'm just going to say I'm
just going to say, Grezy, like, unless
you're going to call the police, you're
not physically going to be removing me from anywhere.
It's as simple as that. You will
physically not be removing me from anywhere.
And I like to see you try as well.
No, not not intentionally going on a mad
run like, but if it happens again, then
I'm going to say something simple as
well or I said something anyways. I've
always defended myself either way, but I
say that like I've never defended
myself. of defending myself but never
too no never to that extreme if that
makes sense. So that's what I will be
doing. I'll be I'll be doing it to the
extreme. I'll take it to the extreme, you know.
That's it in it. Like, yeah,
you get what I mean, bro.
You get beat.
No, I'm going to do it maybe um Friday or Saturday.
Yeah, I'll probably do it then.
But you're forgetting something as well,
Grezy. People also ignore all the bad
things they do as well.
So, it's not just about the free meals
and stuff. They um they will defend any
and every bad thing that they do.
So that's another thing you need to take
in consideration too.
Why they do it, I don't know.
Um but they do do it. So strange. Yeah.
And I was thinking about it um when I
was walking earlier. I went on a long
walk on purpose. I'm thinking why do
they do it?
Like you actually think to yourself, why
do they do it? Cuz
it doesn't make any sense why they
actually do it.
Do you get what I'm saying? Like why do
they do this?
Women don't like them. Women are not
going to sleep with them. They're either
virgins or had less women than you.
Always the case. Yeah, but women don't
like them. Women are not going to sleep with them.
It's not going to get them a shag,
though. But I know I know what you're
saying, bro. But it's not going to get
them a shack.
Women don't like them. They've had less
women than you. They will always have
less women than you. And some of them
are virgins. So, it's like it's why are
they doing that? It's not going to get
them a shag.
100%. It's not going to get them any
kind of shag. And they and and they
should have they should have known this
by now. Like, what is it 2026? And
they're still sing. They're still white knighting.
We got a white knight. try and come up
to me tomorrow and see what I will
rearrange his face, bro. Yeah, we'll see
a little white knight try and come over
to me tomorrow.
Let's see a little white knight try and
come over to me tomorrow. I'll rearrange
his whole face, bro. Like the alphabet.
I'll rearrange his face like I'll
rearrange the alphabet. How about that
one, Grezy? Yeah.
Yeah. I mean that's more logical but
it's different though when you go when
these people are laughing at you mocking
you [ __ ] that I mean logically it makes
more sense isn't it
200 this £200 right here is going to be
gone on nothing but bad experiences
um tomorrow I can safely say 200 is gone
for no reason
well haircut drinking food that's it gone
It's mad when you think about it, isn't it?
It is actually mad when you think about it. Really is.
Cuz it makes no sense, does it? I know.
I'm aware, you know, but yeah, I don't
care, bro. Going out tomorrow.
No, I'm going out, bro. Don't forget I
won £100. So I mean
uh I won £100. So that will basically
pay for most of it.
Haircuts 50 and then 50. Yeah, it'll pay
for most of it anyways. Even if I have
to dip in 20 whatever. That's the only
reason I'm doing it. That is literally
the only reason I am doing it
because obviously I won £100. So
yeah. Yeah. 100 enough for night out loud.
It's enough for a haircut and a night out.
So, it's definitely something if we can
pay for a haircut on a night out,
brother. I don't only have £100.
This is This is This is for going out,
lad. This is not all my money. This is
literally for just going out.
So, yeah, if you win £100, you can get um Yeah.
And that's it. No, I'm going out tomorrow, bro.
Why you Why are you talking about
£1,000, bro? We don't only have £100. We
don't only have £200. This is just money
to [ __ ] around with.
This is just money to [ __ ] around with.
And £100 is definitely definitely
something. If you win if you win a £100
Grezy in the space of 10 minutes, it
definitely is something.
Definitely definitely is something to go
out and get pissed with. Would you agree Grievy?
Definitely is in the space of what 10
minutes? Yeah, it [ __ ] well is.
Imagine you could do that every time.
Of course it is, bro. £100. What? In 10
minutes? Come on, bro. Even the richest
person would tell you that.
Even the richest person would [ __ ]
tell you that.
I mean, Grezy,
it wasn't for the haircut, that £100.
Yeah, if it wasn't for that haircut,
£100 would definitely um that would
definitely get you a night out, bro.
Sometimes it's 50, sometimes it's 100,
sometimes it's 80, sometimes it's 120.
But even still, bro.
And then I won't be going out after this
and I'll be saving. So yeah.
How can you say £100 is not nothing, bro?
That's just so silly to say that in this climate.
I remember when [ __ ] I remember when
I remember when that Lee Lee for Jones
was trying to say four grand is [ __ ]
all. I said, "Mate, I could buy you with four grand.
I could buy you with £4,000.
I could literally buy the city in Wales
that you live in with £4,000."
So many fantasists on this community, bro.
He was trying to I was like, "Bro, you
live in you live in a little village in
Wales. What are you talking about?"
Like, how how and the way he was going
on, it's like they just ain't got no
clue about life. They really got no clue
about life or anything. Some of the
people in this community,
so yeah, if you win £100 in 10 minutes,
how is how is that nothing, bro?
So, obviously, I might have to dip into
a little bit of my money, but it's not
that it's not that bad.
But the point I'm trying to make is the um
the point I'm trying to make is um£100
is two takeaways.
Yeah. Now you're just being stupid, lad.
Now you're just talking stupidness.
Isn't that right, Grezy? Yeah. Now, now
you're just Now you're just talking silly.
Yeah, you're talking just silly now, lad. Yeah.
Oh, for [ __ ] sake, bro.
Yeah. 100 pound is two takeaways.
Yeah. Okay, bro. More like maybe five
takeaways or four takeaways.
Yeah. If money, if you got all of this
money, why are you sat on YouTube every
day? Then if you This is what I don't
understand. If you have got all this
money, right, this is what I'm going to
ask cuz I'm going to be off here
Thursday. I'm going to give Grevy this
content. I'm going to give Grievy this
griev I'm going to give Greed Grezy this
content. Then I'm gone. Right. If you
have got all of this money, why are you
sat on there every day?
And I asked you that question and I want
to be wondering it after Thursday as
well. If you got all this money, I'm
happy for anyone.
£100 is nothing. That's good, bro. Then
you should you should be traveling the
world with all this money that you've
got. You should be you should be doing
stuff with all this money that you got.
You're not a millionaires, bro. Like
actual millionaires. If you got all this
money, bro, then you're a damn fool to
sit on here all day from the time you
wake up to the time you go to bed.
And when I say 200, obviously I've got
more than £200.
But the point is I'm going out because I
won some of that money, which is the
point I'm trying to make. Because how
can I justify using my own money now? I
can't justify it.
When when places are trying to ban you
for approaching people, why would anyone
give them your money?
Your money that ain't one. It doesn't
make sense. It does not make it does not
make sense, does it, Greavvesy?
And the whole toxicity that come with you, lad.
Okay, bro. I've only got £200. If that's
what you think, then that's what you
think. I've only got £200.
I'll let you think what you want to
think. That's the joys of not knowing people.
Yeah. That's the joys of not knowing people.
Yeah. This £200 I've got in cash will be
gone tomorrow. Yes. Well, half is going
to be gone in a minute cuz I need to get a haircut.
Yeah. So what?
But yeah, you can say that. Yeah, bro.
Whatever you think. I don't I don't care
what you think. You can think I'm skin.
I don't care. I'm not proving myself to
people anymore. Why do you think I'm not
even showing the money? I could show
[ __ ] £200 right now and no one could double it.
It's boring, lad. All this money talk is boring.
How am I keeping it? I'm going out, lad.
I'm going out because after this I'm saving.
After this, I'm going to the gym. I'll
be making money and I'm saving. I'm
done. I know what I'm doing, lad. I know
what I'm doing.
Believe me, I know what I'm doing. Hey baby,
should I get some chicken from the shop we maybe?
Okay with you, boss.
Is that okay with you, boss?
Probably buy some nice trainers with
this money, isn't it?
Yeah, you can probably um get some nice
trainers with this Wongo, isn't it? Yeah.
I can't keep the 100 cuz I got to get my haircut. So
that leaves me Yeah. No, leaves me with
150 which will be gone tomorrow. So no,
I can't keep the 100 cuz I need to get
my haircut and that's expensive cuz all
of these things cost money.
So no, I can't.
No, I won't still have 100, you idiot.
How How do you How do you make that one out?
The haircut is well, I get everything.
So, the haircut is 50. That's 150.
You know, I'm going out. I'm sending it tomorrow, bro.
And I might try the Carolina Reaper burger, too. So, yeah,
cuz it is 100. Because it is 50 100
because it is 50.
Cuz I get the full C cuz I get full
service when I go to the barbers.
Okay, bro. It's £30. Okay, I'm not going
to argue with you, bro. It's 30 pound.
It's not £50. Okay. Yeah. Okay. I'm not
going to sit here and argue with someone, bro.
I need to get my eyebrows done and
everything. And the cinema is more than £25.
The cinema is more than £25, but okay,
whatever. You You know everything, don't
you? Okay, whatever. I'm not going to
sit here and argue, bro.
I'm not going to sit here and argue.
Waste of my time. So yeah, realistically
we'll have 150 left
and I will be going on drinking and
that's just money here, right? This is money here.
This is this is money here.
That's not money we got.
I'm not touching the money I've got. I'm
saving the money I've got.
Yeah, you're weird, bro. Weirdos saying
stuff like that. That's just weird, lad.
That's not even funny. It's weird.
Um, so yeah. Okay. side. Yeah. So, yeah.
I need to go out of it. Seriously.
But yeah, I've got my own money, but I'm
not touching my own money. I'm saving my
That's what I'm doing.
>> Oh, [ __ ] man.
>> Yeah, I bought a top yesterday. It was
£10, so I might wear that tomorrow.
No, I'm not forgetting about it, bro.
I'm not forgetting about it.
No, I'm not forgetting about it, lad.
No way am I forgetting about it. Cuz
this is going to be it now.
This is going to be it. So, yes,
this is going to be it, lad.
It's all Yeah,
you never know. Um, pending. It might
change tomorrow, lad.
Tomorrow might be different.
Tomorrow might be different, lad. Who knows, right?
I need to put my socks on cuz I need to
get going. But
No, I'm asking you. I'm asking you. I'm
asking you. What do you think's going to happen tomorrow?
I'm asking you. Ah,
I'm asking you, lad.
Yeah, I'm asking [ __ ] you.
But no, this isn't all the money I've
got. I've got money, but it's savings.
Nah, mate. Hey, we need a new mama,
don't we, Greasy? We need a new mama.
I reckon one more bad experience, bro,
will send me in the grave. I'm not even joking.
Yeah, I reckon one more, lad.
That's going to send me in the [ __ ] grave.
Yeah. So, we got 150 left of the mama fund
after this haircut. Is that okay with
you, Greavvesy boss?
I wonder how much change we're going to
get out of that.
It's going to be interesting, isn't it, to see?
Oh, that's actually bad. Well, so how
much is the haircut? So that's 50 is
easy with 50. So with £50,
yeah, you're probably getting smashed on
Guinness, bro. Even seven Even 78 pound
a pint. I don't think you can drink 50
worth of Guinness, Greasy.
I don't even think you could, bro. Maybe
like How many do you How many do you normally have?
[ __ ] knows, bro. Maybe four. So maybe
maybe I could actually do I don't mind
spending all the money anyways.
I mean, I can I can I don't mind, bro.
The money's there to be spent. This is
the mama fund. I don't mind. But I don't
think you would actually be spending
more than about 60 to be fair. If you if
you drink Guinness, bro, it [ __ ] you.
It doesn't matter how much it is. It's
bad. It's [ __ ] I had two Guinnesses yesterday. Greasy. Yeah.
Yeah. I had two Guinnesses yesterday.
Was [ __ ] bro. Actually [ __ ]
[ __ ] no, bro.
But I'm going to get some nice food from
Dave's Chicken. So, I'm going to be out
all day tomorrow. So, probably around
this time I'll still be out. So,
no, I don't need to take another 200
out, lad. I bring I got my bank card
with me. So, if that needs to happen,
that will happen.
Yeah, I'm I'm going out tomorrow, lad.
Yeah, I'm going out tomorrow.
Yeah, Thursday. We said Thursday in it.
I'm going to go get a haircut in a bit.
More bad experiences with women coming
on strong tomorrow ads.
More bad experiences, eh?
You don't need to worry about any of the
other money. Call it savings anyways, lad. Cuz
you should call it savings anyways
because um you're not going to meet
anyone. You can have a positive mindset
all you want, lad. You're still going to
get bad experiences.
I got a bad experience recently. I think
another one will just send me in a grave, lad.
You can you can be positive all you want,
but it's still going to be negative.
I've been positive speaking to someone
for a month. They still [ __ ] me over.
Does it help? Not really. I mean, I'
I've been [ __ ] over recently. Yet
again, I was positive the whole way through.
So, not really, mate. You can think
whatever you want and you're still going
to have bad experiences.
Simple as that. I'm only doing this
because I Yeah. won £100. So,
yes, you did. Mhm.
Yep. On to the next and the next and the
next and the next and the next and the
next that does exactly the same thing.
Onto the next that will always do and
act the same. Yeah. Um
what happened? Oh, I was just speaking
to someone in it and I tried I tried
meeting them and then they were using
their um exams as an excuse and then we
was talking every day and I tried to
meet them again and then they were
making excuses and they started like
acting up and [ __ ] and being all like
weird. Um so yeah. So yeah, being
positive does not change nothing. You
can be as positive as you like, but
you're still going to have bad
experiences. It's like what me and
Ant-Man said. It's like you're you're
actually going out to just go out in it.
You're actually going out. You're
actually just going out to to socialize
in it. I think cuz you you know you're
never going to meet anyone. Keep in your
heart, you know, it's never going to
change. I know it. He knows it. Everyone
knows it. So, I mean, you're just going
out to just just to go out.
No, she did actually have No, no, she
did actually have them. She showed me
them and everything, but yeah, she just
started being being a [ __ ] basically. So, yeah,
just like tomorrow is going to be bad experiences.
You just expect it.
I don't think it's fun, Annas. I don't
think it's fun. There's nothing fun
about going out.
white knights, toxic people, people
trying to tell you you can't approach in
environments. I don't find it fun. Um,
if I didn't win that 100 pound, I
wouldn't be going out.
I'm not using any of my own savings.
No, she didn't turn. I can't be bothered
explaining it again, bro. I've already
done a video on it.
She just went weird when I was asking. Um,
see you later, lad. um
when I was asking to meet after the
exams and stuff and she was giving me
mixed messages. So yeah, see you later, lad.
Just the same old, isn't it? It just
gets worse and worse and worse and worse and worse.
So it just gets worse and worse and
worse and worse and worse.
That's all that happens.
Isn't that right, Greasy? Nothing
change. Nothing happens and nothing
changes. I need to get that tattooed on
me, bro. For real. Who's that?
Um, just Guinness, lad.
Yeah, LR11. It's never going to end. Oh,
do you know what she said to me as well? LR11.
I was I was going up on the on the
messages um day before I think it was
the day before yesterday was winding me
up, bro. It was actually [ __ ] winding
me up, bro. I'm not even joking. People
are lethal, lad. It's not even a joke.
People are so bad nowadays, bro.
It's [ __ ] It's actually bad, bro.
So, when I was arguing with her and
stuff, yeah, I said, "You're the one
that's sending me 23 messages." Like,
she was trying to be all like trying to
like try and get rude and stuff. And
then she was like, "Oh, um, [ __ ]
yeah, I don't need to waste my breath on
someone that I don't care about." I
said, "Don't care about. I'm thinking
you're sending me 23 messages every day.
You're sending me 10 minute voice notes.
Like, are you okay in your head?" Like,
"Are you actually okay in your head?"
Seriously, I know. I know. agrees. He
loves the toxicity and the madness and
stuff, but he won't like it one day when
[ __ ] goes down, is it? Yeah.
And you're and you're saying that to me,
you messaged me 23 times at [ __ ] 2:00
in the [ __ ] morning. What the [ __ ]
So yeah, these people, bro, people in
this generation, Yeah. are bad. Or bad.
They're bad, bro. And they're getting
worse as well.
You need to remember that. It's never
going to change. never going to change.
It's never going to change, lad.
Especially not in 2026.
I don't f I don't love the drama. I
think it's [ __ ] stupid, bro.
Yeah, I I best do, though. I best do
cuz people need to stop giving hope,
bro. Like people need to stop telling
you things are going to be different cuz
they're never going to be different.
Once you've accepted that then you're
fine in it. Once you've accepted that
you are fine. It's never going to
change. It's [ __ ] So yeah, that's it.
Where are you drinking anyways tomorrow?
Where you where you going? Got
my little track suit on, bro. It's clean
as [ __ ] bro.
Definitely drew a barbers trip, though. Yeah.
So, yeah. If you got like Yeah. Even if
you win, if you if you if you won £100,
bro, you can get a haircut. You can get
you can get on your merry way. You can
get on your merry way with drinks. Oh,
yeah. Today you said you're going. Yeah,
my bad. You get on your merry way with
50 pound, bro. I'm going I'm going central tomorrow.
So, I'll be going central London tomorrow.
Yeah, I'll be going central. Um, yeah.
Okay. I don't mind dipping into a little
bit of my money, but I don't want to dip
into too many savings, bro, cuz I can't
justify it. So,
uh, yeah, a little bit.
So, we send it all day tomorrow and then
that's me done. I don't even know why
I'm sending it. I don't even want to
meet anyone. It generally doesn't even
make any sense.
Like, at this point, it's got to be a
connection. Like, I don't even want to meet anyone.
Like, it doesn't it just doesn't even
make any sense, does it?
You're going to spend £200, £130 on just
nothing. But I'm still going. I said I'm
going it, so
I'm doing it. It just doesn't make sense.
Really doesn't make no sense.
Irreversible damage. There you go.
Well, I go out to try to meet people usually.
Usually it is to try to meet people.
There's not one time I go out I don't
approach anyone. But like let's just say
by the 1% chance less than 1% chance you
met someone which you won't I'm sure not
going to be happy because the because
the damage is irreversible.
Irreversible damage. That's it, bro.
Because of all the bad experiences I've had.
That's it, bro.
Maybe a girl could approach me. Yeah,
maybe pigs might fly, lad.
Maybe pigs will fly over chimneys. Who knows?
Nah, no one approaches you, bro. No one
approach. It's so corrupt this society.
Nothing will ever change either. Nothing
ever. I know it and you know it. So that's that.
I don't know how people can still have
hope. It's mad. I lost hope ages ago,
maybe 3, four months ago. I don't know
how people still say there is hope.
There must be tripping, bro.
Yeah, it must be tripping, bro. God
knows what it's going to be like
when kids are my age now.
God help them poor [ __ ]
It doesn't matter if I'm 28, lad. It
doesn't matter if I'm 28, 18. It's not
going to change.
Uh I done a football bet yesterday.
Yeah, they lost. It doesn't matter how
old I am, bro. It doesn't matter how old
I am. It's not going to change. So why
does why does my age matter? You're not
going to randomly bump into people that
are different. This has been going on
for years. And at the end of the day, if
you truly didn't dismiss people's
struggles, you would know this. This has
also been going on for years. Not
months, not half a year, not even a
year, you know. This has been going on
for [ __ ] years,
you know? And that and that says it all
as well. Like, so that's another thing.
It's not just randomly going to change
all of a sudden.
Uh there I done two correct scores and
two teams and lost lad. So I was nowhere near
six out of 10. Even they've got
attitude, lad. They've all got
attitudes. Two out of 10, three out of
10, four out of 10.
Does they've all got the same bad
attitude. It doesn't matter what they
look like. They everyone's the same now.
They've all got I mean there's there's
there there's there's people with free
[ __ ] there's people out there with
free kids that think they're better than people.
You know what I'm saying? There's people
with free kids they think they're
[ __ ] better than people. You know
what I mean? Like [ __ ]
How much do you think you're going to
spend today drinking ADZ?
I know what I'm going to do when I
drink. I'm going to get on that [ __ ]
phone, bro. I used to do it all the
time. Hey, listen. This is why it's
dangerous, Gregy, cuz I used to do this
all the time, bro. Yeah, I might drink
some whiskey tomorrow
after a while as well. I might drink
some whiskey. I'm going to I'm [ __ ]
Trust me, bro. I'm actually I'm actually
mad, you know. I'm Hey, I'm actually
mad, you know, bro. Cuz I started off
like I started off last Monday. I
started off locally. I started off
locally. Do you remember? And I was
like, I'm not going to drink. I'm not
going to drink. I'm only going to have
Coke in it. And then I had
then I had one drink. Uh [ __ ] bro. I
had one Guinness and then I was like,
"No, I'm in it too deep now."
I'm in it too deep. I can't just have
one. Once I have one, I'm out. I'm out. Out, bro.
Straight on that train straight 50 miles
away. You know what I mean?
Yeah. [ __ ] that, bro. No, I'm straight
out, bro. [ __ ]
Yeah. How much do you reckon you're
going to spend today drinking?
How much you spending drinking? You reckon?
I can't just have one me. That makes me
sound like an alcoholic, bro.
But I can't just have one with Zy
cuz all I'm think all I'm thinking is
when I'm drinking. Yeah. The only thing
I can think of is they were laughing at
you. Mocking you. [ __ ] that, bro. No.
[ __ ] that. Even if it was a Monday, bro.
No. No. No. Even when it was even when
it was a Monday, bro. It was still It
was still active. It was still active.
[ __ ] you. That's the That's the first
thing that's the first thing I thought
of today when I woke up. Yeah. [ __ ]
that. [ __ ] that. it. No. Why do you
think I'm going to Why do you think I'm
going to hit up the same place? You're
going to spend £50.
Yeah. Well, the pints in London are £8. So,
saying that, I'd probably spend £50 on
alcohol as well, to be honest. It
depends, isn't it? It depends what
you're drinking. But yeah, last time I
went out, I think I spent 50 quid,
but it doesn't matter. We got We got
150. So, I got 150, bro. So, it's fine.
That's not all I've got, but that's the
money to go out with. So,
if you I think it's more when you drink
like spirits because they just water the
spirits down. See, with Guinness, it's
harder for them to water down beer.
So, you you you'd probably spend what? I
don't know how many Guinnesses I don't
know who drinks Guinness, but I can't I
can't drink more than I don't know, bro.
They're [ __ ] I had two yesterday and
that was me, bro. I reckon you drink about five
Guinnesses, you probably drink about
five Guinnesses. I don't know what other
people drink, but depends what beer it
is, isn't it?
But with rum,
oh, I can drink and drink and drink and
drink and drink. I used to drink white
rum all the time. Captain Morgans's
white Captain Morgans's.
I used to drink white Captain Morgans
all the time
when I was younger, bro. But I can't
drink that [ __ ] anymore.
Yeah, Guinness. I'll probably say about
four or five.
Yeah, who knows? We might have money for
the cinema tomorrow after we go out
drinking. We might have some change out
of that money, but I doubt it, bro.
because I'm going to go all in.
You know, I can't justify going out
drinking here anymore unless unless I
win. And I've got money as well. Don't
think I've not got money to do it. I
have got money, but I don't want it to
be my own money. You understand?
It's okay. It's okay if you've won
money, but if you don't, like that
sounds that makes it seem like I've got
no money, bro. I do have money, but I
just don't want to spend it
on that kind of [ __ ] You get me?
Did that make sense?
Even if you worked, like even if you
were working, bro, like I wouldn't I
wouldn't do it. I didn't used to gamble
when I worked and I definitely wouldn't be drinking.
I definitely wouldn't be drinking if I
were I still wouldn't do it even if I was working.
I couldn't justify the the the the way
the country is and spend like I just
couldn't justify it
even if I was working for the money you know
cuz it's just a corrupt country in it.
You got 10k. Congratulations. Yeah. So yeah.
Yeah. I like going out Thursdays. Me.
Yeah, it's all right, man.
The most I've ever had was nine grand.
That's the most I've ever had. I think no.
But yeah, this dating thing is
depressing, ADZ. It is depressing, lad.
Well, you don't need to know how much
money I've got. Worry about your own finances.
Maybe I've got
88 888 lad. Sorry. 88 899.
Worry about your own finances, lad.
This is what a lot of these people in
this community, they need to do. They
need to focus on their own lives, you know,
instead of bouncing out of of other people's.
You need to worry about your own finances.
Keep thinking I've got £200 in my name.
That's good, bro. The least you know,
the better. That's it.
You people in this community are very
obsessed with money as well. I've
noticed that when I used to go on large
js, you're very very obsessed with money.
Probably because none of you have got
money. That's why you're so obsessed
with money. People show me this, show me that, show,
I'll double. It's like, what the [ __ ] bro?
But you know, even if you got money,
you're still depressed.
You know, this is the way that I see
this idiot. If you win money, Yeah. It's
like gambling is like a dopamine high or
a dopamine low. So, say right now you
won £50. It doesn't even need to be a
lot of money, bro. Yeah.
But you could win like £50 and it's it's
a dopamine high. 100 pound. It don't
even need to be a lot.
Money doesn't make me happy, bro. And
I've got money.
And I've had even more money before.
doesn't make me happy. Winning money
does. If you win, it does temporarily.
Winning does. Yeah. But not like just having it.
Cuz money ain't going to change my
problems even if I had more money. So
it's not going to change my No.
So you think like if you had a broken
heart Yeah. or someone's broke your
heart or they've led you on and
whatever, you think that, oh, just cuz
you got money, it's going to make it
better. No. Look how many people that
Look how many celebrities kill
themselves. They're [ __ ]
millionaires. They kill themselves.
How much money do you reckon these
people have? Trust me, it's like
and I was thinking about this as well
like a couple of years ago when I had
more. Like I still have money now. I
still have but I was still depressed. I
think I was still exactly the same. I'm
sure I was. Unless I won, then I got a
temporarily high. But
money's not going to fix being led on.
It's not going to fix a broken heart,
bro. It doesn't matter how much money
you have. It's not going to be mended.
So that's the way you got to look at it.
Depends what you're depressed about, but
never made a difference in my life. So yeah.
Yeah. Money doesn't make a difference to me, bro.
No, I'm just saying in the past and
stuff. it like past experiences I've had
cuz I've actually thought about this as
well when I've had more money like and
it still never made a difference.
Unless you win money, it's a good buzz.
If you win money is a good buzz. Don't
get me wrong, it's it's a good buzz if
you win. That's a that's a temporarily
that's a temporary dopamine high.
Yeah. Six out of 10 aren't interested
either. No one's interested in this
country, lad. Doesn't matter what what
you rate them, what ratings they are. So, um
yeah, it never made a difference.
Never made a difference. So,
the only way I I'll ever be happy is if
I give up dating completely,
which is what I'm going to be doing
after F. I've already have anyways, but
I mean I'm not going to try again after
Thursday. But yeah, so yeah,
you make it sound so easy, ads. If only
it was as easy as that, lad.
If only it was as easy as that.
What do you think of that though? Um,
greasy. People calling me tapped.
Not [ __ ] tapped.
They call me tapped and stuff.
Yeah. It's not nice, bro. Speaking to
people for a long time or a while and
then then and then
um being abandoned.
It's not nice being abandoned, is it, Greezy?
Oh my just my sister in it. Yeah. I was
out I was out last Monday in it and I
started off with the Guinness like near
where like my mom lives like the town center
and I just went straight into the city
in it and I was like oh [ __ ] hell.
Yeah. I was [ __ ] pissed in it. I said
[ __ ] come meet me now then. Is it
remember I was like meet I think I went
live. Yeah. And I was sending her like
friends something in it and I was like
like bam the voice not started happening
in it. The voice note started happening.
Isn't that right, Beezy? The voice note started happening.
It was a [ __ ] madness.
It was a It was a [ __ ] madness, bro.
It's not even funny, but a madness. Absolute madness.
Cuz I started off locally greasy in it
when I [ __ ] ended up in the city in it.
What do you think about that?
Yeah. He was laughing in it. He was
laughing it. Yeah.
People have called Hey, the thing is
Grezy, people have called me erratic.
What do you think of that? Erratic.
Who would be [ __ ] erratic, bro?
That's a bit mad, isn't it? Nah, no.
Cuz someone was like, "Oh, yeah, listen.
Like, I've had I've I've had people
break up with me or whatever." And he
said, "But they don't go up the way that
you do." No, no, no, no, no.
Yeah, but you got to understand
different greasy there's a difference
when someone was laughing at you,
mocking you. I feel screamsy. No,
seriously, when they're laughing at you, mocking you,
mocking you. [ __ ] that, bro.
He was He was egging me to go on to go
out Monday, weren't you, Grezy? He was
like, "Go out. Go out. Go out." in it.
I was like, "Oh, should I?" I said, "Is
that okay with you?" You said, "Go on, in it."
You said, "Go on, didn't you?" Yeah.
I said, "I'm just going to have a coke
in it." I had to get out of the house
for a little bit, Greasy. Do you remember?
I had to get out of the house. Do you remember?
>> Yeah. I had to get out of the house, bro.
>> And like I said, I was drink I was
drinking a Coke cuz I was I ain't
drinking on a [ __ ] Monday, bro.
One Guinness is not going to hurt. Isn't
that right, Grezy? That's how it always goes. One.
That's how it always goes, is it? One
Guinness is not going to hurt, is it? Music.
Then I had one.
Then I was like,
then I had one. I think I had one. I was like, nah.
Them [ __ ] were laughing at you, mocking
you. Then I [ __ ] then I down then I
downed the then I down the second one
and I was like drunk for like 2 hours, bro.
Yeah, I was drunk for like [ __ ] two
hours and then I was like, "No, I'm I'm
[ __ ] I'm selling it." I didn't sending it.
>> Uh, that you like to hear that.
>> You got 600. You got pended. You got
£600 to your name.
>> That's funny, bro.
You know, I'd actually buy a bottle of
Captain Morgans, but I don't know where
you can get the [ __ ] Grezy.
I don't know where you could actually
get the [ __ ] It's so hard to get. I'd
probably have to go back to my old area.
I could get it.
My wife Captain Morgans.
Oh, [ __ ] hell, bro.
You know what? I could actually do that.
You know, bro,
I'll be [ __ ] for like two, three days
after that. It's called White Captain Morgan. Yeah.
Try it, bro. I tried it. [ __ ] you right up, bro.
What do you think, Gra?
>> No, just stick to the Guinness in it.
But if you want to see a proper proper
madness, UK island, we'll get we'll get
that [ __ ] um Captain Morgan.
If you want to see a proper proper madness,
that [ __ ] gets [ __ ]
Similar to it's similar to any kind of
like white rum.
Don't know if any of you bastards have
ever had it, but
I think we'll just stick to the Gillisy.
I think you need to chill out.
Oh, is that right?
>> Yeah. Everybody knows that you're a crazy [ __ ]
You never say that. You need to say that
like when I when I'm getting like bad
and stuff. Everybody knows that you're a crazy in it.
Yeah. I'll be sending it tomorrow. Don't
you worry about chilling out.
Is that right?
>> Yeah, everybody knows a crazy man.
>> Yeah, there's one called Dolly. I'm
going to be watching it on either Friday or Saturday. Yeah,
I'll be seeing some couples in cinema.
I see couples in the cinema, but not all the time.
It's funny these people, you wonder how
they actually got in relationships.
Well, you know how they got in
relationships obviously, but like like
think of it now in 2026 ads. You tried
to speak to someone, it's straight away
I have a boyfriend, straight away I got
interested or people that lead you on and [ __ ]
but obviously they probably met through
a dating app or got lucky years ago or
met through work. Obviously,
that's obviously how they met, in it.
Yeah, I saw it as well.
I saw that as well. Um
uh what was I saying, bro? [ __ ] yeah,
I'm just going to get my [ __ ] hair
done. my beard done. Going to dress [ __ ]
I'm just going to dress casually
tomorrow, bro. I'm just going to
literally I like it. Yeah, it was all right.
It was a bit [ __ ] up, though.
Seeing someone do this mass mass mucked, aren't they?
Yeah, it was a bit [ __ ] up though, bro.
That's the only thing you can really do
is go to cinema, is it? Nothing else,
lad. Literally nothing else [ __ ] do
nowadays, isn't it? It's boring, bro. Boring. falling.
England is uh is such a depressing
country is it lad?
England is such a depressing country. People [ __ ]
You have to wait around for everything.
What a time to be in this country. E,
this dating thing gives you really bad
anxiety as well. I've noticed that like
whenever I do this dating thing and I
get [ __ ] over again, you start getting
anxiety, which I don't ever really get.
I don't I don't ever get anxiety. So,
it's [ __ ] up, is it, bro?
No one tells you this [ __ ] though, do
they? Before you um start like
approaching and stuff, no one tells you
this [ __ ] Now you work that out for
your [ __ ] self.
Where's better? Don't know, bro. [ __ ] Thailand. Brazil.
And the only thing is ADZ. Yeah, you can
actually get banned. Yeah, you can get
you can actually get banned for
approaching in the premises.
I can tell you a story if you want. It happened last
was it Monday?
Yeah, it must have been Monday cuz I
went out Monday, don't I? Yeah.
Yeah, lad. I can tell your story if you want.
Yeah, it's [ __ ] It's crap. That's
what I'm saying. You can't justify even
spending your own money anymore.
I've approached thousands. I've lost
count. And guess what, ADZ? They're all
the same. None of them are good.
No matter how many times they how how
much they'll try to portray portray
they're different. They're all the
[ __ ] same lad.
None of them are different in any way.
Yeah. You get banned from places now
just for just for talking to people.
So yeah, it's just just annoying country.
Depressing country. An annoying country.
I think that's why so many people are [ __ ] anti-depressants.
I'm guessing they are.
Oh no. I'm guessing they [ __ ] are. So yeah.
Yeah. My friend lives in Thailand.
My friend I got a friend in Thailand. He
lives there, bro. He moved there because
of the whole dating and women thing.
Yeah, you a lot of people have moved to Thailand, bro.
This country is finished, bro. It's finished.
No bets. Nope.
Can't believe I won £100 on a fy. That's
sick, bro. So hard to win anything now.
Well, he gets about£600 a month, but
that's a lot of money over there. So
Yeah, but obviously £600 is a lot of
money. No, I didn't record it.
I got a I got a bonus
because he teaches English.
He's an English teacher and obviously
600 pound over there is a lot more than
it is over [ __ ] here. So
he's done the right thing to be fair, bro.
You can't knock a man that's um tried to
tried to change his situation to be fair.
Yeah, he doesn't. He used to be on this
community YouTube. He just left never
come back. Doesn't look nothing
>> which you know anyone that that is like
that deserves um utmost up roast
>> utmost credit to be fair. I just put a
wash on ready for tomorrow. I like when
I come back drunk I like to go for a
shower and get clean clothes. So yeah man. Yeah,
you I'll pull tomorrow. Yeah, you keep
telling yourself that, lad.
Yeah, look what happened last time I
went out. I got led on for a month and I
got three numbers. I didn't reply. Yeah,
pigs might fly, lad. Pigs might fly.
Now, what I don't understand yet is if I
if I told you right now, I'm going to
the bookies to gamble. Yeah. If I was to
tell you right now, I'm going to go to
I'm going to go to the bookies and gamble. Um
and and why do I not have faith? Uh
because of my experiences that you keep dismissing.
Duh. Because of my experiences that you keep dismissing.
If I told you I was going to go to the
bookies right now and then you said to
me, "Oh, um, yeah, you might, um,
you might, um, you might win some
money." I believe it. But, you know,
exactly it's going to be the same.
It's never going to change.
Why would you have faith? It will never be different.
Why am I going through the pain? Because
I've got nothing. I've got nothing
better to do. And I said I was going to
go out and then after this I'm done, lad.
I'm going to be going gym. I'm going to
be off. I'm going to be too busy. And that's it.
And I want to drink because I've had bad
experiences and stuff and I don't feel
good. Which is why I drunk last week
twice. And I drunk Well, I drunk
yesterday. Well, I didn't drink
yesterday cuz of that. But yeah, so I
drunk I drunk yesterday. Um twice last
week and stuff.
>> I don't want to stay indoors, you know.
No, I'm not going casino, bro.
I'm just drinking tomorrow, approaching.
That's me done. Simple.
That's that. I've had some really nasty,
shitty experiences lately as usual.
[ __ ] hate it. I do, bro. I hate it.
I hate [ __ ] people that do that [ __ ] bro.
Really do hate people that do that [ __ ] £4,000. Yeah. £4,000, man. Yeah, man. From 150.
But yeah, there's it's not going to be
no different uh tomorrow.
You know that and I know that. So
yeah, I won four grand from 150 in the casino. Yeah, years ago.
Well, a couple years ago. It was a
Wednesday as well. I remember it cuz I
was supposed to go to America the next day. Bro,
I was always depressed. Even then, bro,
when I had a lot more money, I was still depressed, weirdly enough.
I think it was like bad experiences and
[ __ ] and being abandoned. See, that kind
of stuff, even if you got money, yeah,
you might feel good temporarily when you
win money, but I mean, like long long
term, you won't. You understand? So
it never made a never made a difference.
Oh, just like just like [ __ ] in the past.
Just like women in the past and stuff. Yeah.
How much change you reckon I'm going to
have tomorrow from 140? Sorry, 150. ADZ.
I'm going to go out on the piss with
150. How much change do you think I'm
going to get left? None, lad. I'm going
to be getting some nice food, too.
None in it.
Ah, [ __ ] me, bro. Yeah.
So, yeah. Um, I normally go Weather
Spoons and have a burger and Weather
Spoons, but then I eat again at the end
of the night.
That's what usually happens.
No, I'm not betting tomorrow.
No, lad. Maybe Saturday, but I'm not
betting tomorrow. Are there even games
on Saturday and Thursday? Who knows? So yeah,
that's that in it, bro.
Yeah, I got a I got a bonus on fishing frenzy.
That's what I usually do at ADZ. both I
I do I do both teams to score in the
first half but it never wins
but obviously it can happen. Yeah.
I got a correct score yesterday, but
I'll show you my bets for yesterday uh
yesterday if you want.
Probably won't put them in the same
place now to be fair.
If you can see that.
Can you even see that?
That's one of them.
Then that's a correct score done.
I know I was far off with that one, but
Oh, it's worth putting two pound on it, is it?
I think it weren't a bad bet to be honest.
Anyways, I'm going. Yeah. Um, I'll be back later.
Yeah. End of it. Peace.