a little bit. No.
I need to get a roast coming pork
today. Yeah, I need to get roast curry
pork. The Chinese I went here yesterday.
Well, I just felt that
instead you can [ __ ] put up with it, mate.
Got a nice breakfast. Breakfast
hand. It's always worth the freedom today.
on the wall. [Music]
Tie, tired, tired, tired, tired.
Right. A hard one. That is
e. So I don't really come there nowadays
because it's just the
same same atmosphere, same [ __ ] same
[ __ ] I only really come on here
when I'm like really drunk. I'm just
about to go to sleep. It's literally
just the same same people every day, same comments.
That's been mocked. Good. probably just Um. Oh
[ __ ] This a
bridge. Sit down there. I can sit down.
A little bit
tired. So tired, bro.
At least we got three numbers with the text.
E my short stay in a [ __ ] it t-shirt
cuz you know doesn't really make a
difference what you [ __ ] wear, does
it? So yeah, that's what I was wearing. It's good,
bro. Hey, you got yourself mixed up with
me. Stop talking about yourself. It's no
good for your mental
health. You got yourself mixed up with me again,
buddy. Don't get
confused. So, that's why I don't really
come on here much anymore because they're repeating.
same roasts, same people, same
atmosphere. Like if you're on it for a
day, no, no, not a day. If you're on it
for a day, it's like, okay, and then
you're on it for like a second day, it's
like, uh, then the third day you're on
it, it you feel this atmosphere. Like if
you ever go on LJ's chat or you get the
same spastics on that chat on my one,
it's like a it's an atmosphere. It's
like if you ever if you ever gone into
the casino, right, and you you have an
atmosphere when you gamble or something
similar to that. I don't know what I'm
trying to explain. It's literally just
the same atmosphere. I can't I can't
explain it. It's It's hard to explain
it. It's hard to explain different
atmospheres. It's just like a weird atmosphere,
lad. Yeah, I did get
it. It's working good. So that's why you
don't really see me on here, bro, cuz I
can only take it in small doses because
the stalking, the
weirdness. Yeah, I'm not back. I'm not
back. I'm not back. I'm hard of now
because it's the same atmosphere. I was
just explaining this like just a minute
ago. I went to see that film yesterday.
I had a good day yesterday. done some
approaches, watched the film, got an
escort, played Frankie, had some food,
but I didn't pay anything for the
alcohol because I found some alcohol on
top of the old fridge cuz I didn't even
know it was there. So, I just mixed it
with co I didn't buy one drink yesterday.
So, don't know. Don't care. Stop. Stop
um bringing up weird rumors on my
channel cuz I'm going to block you if
you make up stuff on my channel and you
bring any and this is why I don't come
on here no more.
Uh, well, you thought wrong. But guess
what? I can take a day off of YouTube,
unlike you. That's the difference. I can
take a day off of YouTube, unlike you
people. It's not in Albert Square. You
don't know where I
live. So, anyways, I'm going to block
you if you keep being weird and you keep
being stalker. And I'm just going to
block you now, actually. Bye-bye
now. There you
go. And you're gone, buddy. There you
go. Bye-bye. Now you were in bars and
you didn't buy a drink. No. You know
why? Because it's called being
smart. It's called being smart. You
don't need to go out in London and spend
£300 drinking to show you've got money.
I thought, listen, today I'm going to
try and get some women, right? I've got
nothing better to do. I don't want to
spend I plan to buy two or three drinks.
It just never happened. I'm not spending
more than 20 30
quid. Why the [ __ ] am I going to be
spending more than 20 30 quid? I don't
need to. I'm not going to. Um, no I
didn't. I lost I got the 150 to 200 and
I lost the 250. I know mad I say 12
game. That's the only thing that really
cost me um
yesterday. But it's all right anyways.
So yeah, it's too expensive, mate. And
that money that I spend drinking, I can
put towards something
else. No, I haven't text her yet. I
didn't even plan to go out yesterday. I
just done some approaches before I went
to the cinema cuz I was early. And oh my
god, it was just the same old Bye-bye
now. It was just the same.
It was just the same old
[ __ ] Same old [ __ ] Yeah. But when I
got three numbers, I thought I'll just
call it quits. Three numbers enough.
Yeah. It was just the same old [ __ ]
which prompted me to go out. It's the
same old [ __ ] in this country. I got a
football bet on for today as well. So £7
with the change I got from the curry.
But yeah, I thought I was going to buy a
drink or two or three, but I just never
cuz I already got the numbers and I was
like, "Oh, it's getting on now. Let me
just go back."
But it's called being smart, mate. It's
not called being skint. It's called
being smart with your money. And you
know what? When things are cheaper, it
feels better. Even with traveling, you
know? Well, unless you go abroad,
obviously, but like it the little the
least you spend makes it more fun
because you know it didn't cost you
much. It's called being smart with your
money. It's called being smart with your
money. That's what it's called, being
smart with your money, not being skinn.
It's called being smart with your
money, you know?
So even traveling the cheapest you could
travel just makes it that much
funner. But obviously if you go to
America you spend five grand. I mean you
know that that's different. You're
abroad. It's what it's one in a lifetime
experience as an example. You know you
spend what you want but in terms of like
drinking in London and
that. Yeah I
did. So all in all it didn't really cost me much.
I've probably done in one day yesterday
more than what these people done in
their whole life. It's a madness, isn't
it? Yeah, it's a madness.
Yeah. Yeah, we know he's stinking.
They're all stinking on here.
All of them are
man. Stinky little monitors ain't got a
life but YouTube. No life but the
YouTube. But yeah. Do you know what's so
mad is that I didn't when I was
approaching around the different area
yesterday, I wasn't getting I've got a
boyfriend. I didn't get it once. All it
was was this unimpia and disinterest.
And then as soon as I went to central
London, literally I couldn't stop
hearing it. Obviously, I got free
numbers in the end. I thought, "Oh my
god, this country is just [ __ ] up." I
didn't even plan to go out anyways. I
got a Weather Spoon's approach and put
it on my channel, but if I bothered any
I just told you I'm not a football,
bro. Is your bro is your brain broken or
something? I I literally just told you I
don't a football bet.
Respectfully, I think some of you have got
um I've got no plans today, man. Just
going to go and get a breakfast. I went out
yesterday, approached and done I done
loads of stuff yesterday. So, no, it's a
four-fold. No, I don't
um No, I don't think yesterday. I don't
know. Yeah, I'd done enough
yesterday approaching cinema and the lot
mate. So, I'm probably done
today. Yeah, I'm done out of
love. Oh, I can't even remember the
football bets in the other room. So, I
went to get a curry and I got
change and I just stuck the change on it.
I trying to just budget money now. I
don't want to spend more than I need to
spend. Even though I feel like doing a
100 pound football bet today. I'm not
going to lie. I actually feel like doing
a 100 pound football
bet. Oh Jesus. I'm so degenerate. But
obviously I'm not going to tempted
though. I don't need to. I have enough.
So nah man that was just a drunken
mistake yesterday. And to be fair, the
money I spent on Frankie is the money I
would have spent on the drinking and
that. So all in all, escort cinema approaching
drinking cost less than £200 and I
gambled. So I'll take it any day of the
week. Meant to be saving as
well. Hard to save when it's like this
when it's nice when it's nice weather
outside. The protein's definitely
getting worse in this country.
I gave one person my number and I got three
numbers. I think one of them no four
numbers but one of them I think were
fake. So three numbers. Yeah.
just just to save, man. Just to get myself
ahead, you know, just I don't know,
really. Just to get myself ahead and
just live a stable life, you
know, holidays and stuff, you
know? So, really, yeah, I'll text them
free numbers later, obviously. But
yeah, not even Thailand. I don't need to
save. I get enough money, but I just want to
save. I just want to save, you
know. But it's hard because you do get
tempted to go out every I didn't get my
haircut. I get my haircut every 3 weeks.
I didn't get my haircut yesterday. I
just sent it with shorts to the top.
And yeah, it's very hard. I would say
nowadays trying to find someone in this
country, you probably got more chance of
winning the lottery. They're all NPCs. I
was saying this yesterday, everywhere
you go, right, you meet the same people.
This is this is why I don't I don't
really waste I don't waste money in this
country box. You see the same people,
you see the same women, you see the same
men with the same attitude, the same
nosy people. Everywhere you go, you meet
the same people. I don't know if I'm the
only one that's noticed that,
but yeah, like no, they're literally
just like NPCs. I swear to God,
non-playing characters. Do you remember
like NPCs in the
games? Obviously, I've saved a lot of
money with that fridge as well. But I
did do a lot yesterday. So, losing a
150. Yeah, it was annoying. But you did do a
lot. You spent You did a lot of stuff
yesterday. So, at the end of the day,
like worth it, in
it. Just hard to say in this weather
though. You just want to go out, but
we'll get there. We just have to put
[ __ ] 70 of gas and
electric. They're just all the
same. Um, well, I
approached I approached before I went to
the cinema. Nothing. just disinterest
like looks and disgust a lot then I went
to central London [ __ ] boyfriend boy
oh mate it weren't stopping it must be
that bad Friday I'd even done in the
weather spoons and um but in the end I got three
numbers then I went back to like the
other area then I got another so I got
three numbers four but one of them make
up so three real numbers so got some in the
Yeah, it was all right, I
guess. Yeah, I'll text these numbers
later. It's [ __ ] hard. I'm telling
you, it's got [ __ ] harder. I was just
saying yes, last night before before I
met USA Izzy, I was trying in London for
like a year and a half. It can actually
get that bad. It's bad, bro. It's hard
in these country, in these westernized
countries. And I was just saying that
people on here, right, they take the
piss and they think they know about
women and stuff. I'm saying like what
would they know? These people probably
don't even leave their house. Greasy. At
least Greasy Mi Mixie doesn't leave the
house. Anyone that would go out and
actually interact with people would know
what they're like in this country. And
you know, it's it's men as well. You
know, like I'm just saying like you
would know. I know cuz I'm living proof
of it. I leave the house every day. I
know what they're
like. Well, congratulations. But what I'm saying
is, and it's like, do you know what,
Grezy? Yeah. And then this guy was like,
how do you know they don't have
boyfriends? I was like, listen, mate,
I'm not going to sit here and argue with
you, right? Who has boyfriends and who
don't have boyfriends? It's I'm not
going to sit here and argue with you.
Yeah. It's pathetic. It's boring. It's
immature. And you know what I'm saying?
But it's weird. I didn't get it before
the cinema though. I was literally
walking around grievous. I was like, "Am
I in Am I in England? Hold on. I've just
approached like seven, eight people and
I've not got I've got a boyfriend." No,
I can't be in England. There's no way I
can be in England. Then I went and then
I went to watch the um horror film and
then when I went to um central London, I
started hearing it. I was like, "Yeah,
I'm in England. Definitely definitely
England." For a moment, I thought I was
in a different country like maybe Asia
or even somewhere like Canada cuz I
weren't hearing that I've got a
boyfriend. I was like, "Yeah, yeah,
we're in England." Definitely in
England. I've always called to be fair.
I've already done a
bet. I've already done
one. I feel like doing another one
though. I feel like doing 100 pound on two teams, but yeah. [Music]
Let's see what the returns are.
Yeah. And where I've not been drinking
for two weeks drinking for a bit greasy.
I had time to think about
this. Like I was like, that's mad. At
27, you should have a child. You should
be married. You should have found
someone by now. At
27, like you're where you kind of need
to be. You're living independent. Just
got yourself a fridge. You save money.
It's mad. So, even when you know you
you're stable living, you get to think
of these things. It's [ __ ] up. And
it's only getting
worse. All because you weren't born in
19 [ __ ] 88.
AZ. No, I'm not even joking. I'm being
deadly serious. It's [ __ ] disgusting,
mate. Oh, you know your friend Terry is
a little [ __ ] bro. Tell your boy to
stop emailing me, bro. I had to block
his [ __ ] email. This guy, I'm telling
you right, he's no different to these
little clowns that you hate on
here. My team's I don't know. It's in
the other room. Listen, bro.
You know that Terry? Yeah. He is no
different than these people that you
despise on here. I'm telling you, bro.
He's no different to any of them. My man
was emailing me all night the other day,
bro. Yeah. And I had to find out how to
I didn't even know how to block emails
up fast. This guy don't know no bad
family, bro. I'm telling you. Yeah. He
claims that he knows where I am. I said,
"Bro, if you think you know where I am,
[ __ ] Just email him. [ __ ] bro.
He's nothing different than these people
that you don't like. Fruit King, Bomb,
um, Virgin Sea. He is no different to
any of these people. He's a keyboard warrior.
Yeah. This guy took his time out of his
day to start emailing me. He is some
little inshloth [ __ ] bro. You know what I'm
saying? Yeah, maybe not, but still.
Yeah, it's a
madness. Guess what? Do you want to look
what's in the old
fridge? I got this fridge. Yeah, the
light don't work.
But yeah, you can't not have Billy Bear
sandwiches. Yeah. Got some
beers. Get some coke. There's no light,
but still cheap for still cheap for
[ __ ] 100 quid. That was [ __ ] a
bargain, man. You can't not have bitty
bear sandwiches. But yeah, he just keeps
emailing me, bro. Being annoying.
Yeah, he keeps emailing me being annoying,
man. No, I went back after central
London. I went back to [ __ ] No, brand
new. Brand spanking new, mate. I I would
never buy a second. You [ __ ] mad.
It's brand new. It was
£103.99. I know. Couldn't believe that
first. I was like, there's got to be
some catch to it. This is a bit too
cheap. It just doesn't come with a
light. No, it's brand
new from uh from the print shop. It's
brand new, man. It just doesn't come
with a light. Don't know why, but it's
brand new. Believe you me, man. I unboxed
it. Yeah, can't get away with leaving
things outside now. It's becoming
summer, so save a lot of money. I need
to go for a breakfast soon,
man. But yeah, anyways, this Terry guy was emailing
me. Oh, watch that Woman in the Yard, by
the way, LT. I wouldn't um I wouldn't I
wouldn't recommend it. It was proper
[ __ ] I feel like I'm just done watching
Horrors now, man. They just don't make
him like they used
to. I wouldn't recommend it, bro. I was
waiting all month for this film. All
month. I was counting down the [ __ ]
days. I was disappointed. I was the first one
there. But it was pure
[ __ ] It was proper proper
[ __ ] So they just they're just not even
worth watching anymore of these horror films.
Sadly, LT. Yeah, your boy's been emailing me,
bro. So, it's hard to like think that
he's about nothing when my man keeps
emailing me. Stop emailing me. You look funny, you know?
Yeah. These people are weird on here,
bro. I don't keep losing my time. I
don't really come on here much anymore.
I come on like every couple of days cuz
Yeah. Well, it's Antman's turn today to
get I've got a
boyfriend. Oh, and I had to go inflation
early cuz I don't have no jeans. It's
all up my mom. So, yeah. Feel like I
done good yesterday for that
200. No, they're just friends in it.
But you know the maddest thing is with
this [ __ ] monster legs right and this
teller you can beat them with one
hand literally with one hand you can
beat both of
them. It's just a [ __ ] madness.
So yeah, that was good yesterday to
spend 200 pound doing all of that.
Escort, cinema, drinking, approaching. You
know, that's what it is. LT, I went out
yesterday. I didn't even buy a drink. I
had some alcohol. I didn't even buy a
drink. Because the thing is is I was
going to buy like two, three drinks, but
I was like, it just never happened. And
it's not called being skinned or being
trampy. It's called saving money, bro.
It's called budgeting. Think of it. You
went out, if you go out every week,
think of how much money how much money
you would save. If you went out every
week and instead of not pre-drinking,
you pre-drunk for six weeks. And how
much money you would save, you could you
could go on holiday with that money that you save.
The only time you should not worry about
what you're spending is if you go on
holiday. That's the only time you should
not worry about what you're
spending. You're going into London or
you're traveling around the UK, you
should make it as cheap as
possible so you can save that money for
other things. You understand? I'll give
you an example because I didn't go out
yesterday spending 150 2000 on drinking
even though I lost the 150 in the end
but gambling right so without that 150
so I budgeted right so I I fitted in the
drinking I fitted in the escort I fitted
in the food for less than
£100 rather than spending hundreds and
hundreds that I don't need to
spend it makes perfect sense
man unless you're going like [ __ ]
America the Caribbean one-off
experiences. That's the only time you
should not care about what you're
spending because it's a one-off
experience. That's the only time. But
bro, and it makes it and it makes it
funner that the least you spend, the
least you can get away with spending, it
just makes it that much funner where you
don't feel like you've been ripped off.
But yeah, buy four drinks, five drinks.
I'm not saying don't spend nothing. If
you're going prop if you're going on a
proper night out, yeah, spend
£450£50 maximum. £40 maximum, bro. You
don't want to spend more than
that. Back in the days, you should be
able to go to a pub and spend [ __ ]
have a night out for 70 80 quid. That's
the way. It should be no more than
£40. Obviously, unless you meet someone
and stuff, then it's a different story.
You know what I'm saying?
So you got a good old breakfast
soon. One second. someone. Amen. Amen. Sorry about
that. You got yourself confused with me again,
buddy. You got yourself confused with me
again, bud. It's not nice to be that
confused. Oh, [ __ ] hell. Yeah, they
don't get they don't get banned, LT. The
accounts don't get banned. I just don't
come on here
anymore. I just don't really come on here anymore,
bro. Because it's the same atmosphere.
Boring. We've heard all this before. Oh,
boring. You're sending me to
sleep. And this is what I'm saying, bro.
It's the same atmosphere. This is why I
come here like every 3 days or 4 days.
It's the literally just the same
atmosphere, the same stalking, the same
weirdos, the same
atmosphere. You You can take it in small
doses. You can take it in small doses.
You know what I'm saying, bro? Like small doses.
like every, you know, you can come on
once and then that's it. But you stay on
it any more than two days, you you'll
start feeling it. It's an atmosphere.
I'm telling you, bro, you go on Lord J's
go on Lord J's or like mine when all the
spastics and you feel this weird
atmosphere like it's a [ __ ]
atmosphere. I can't I can't explain it,
bro. How can I explain it? It's like
explaining a gambling
atmosphere. It's like explaining being
high. It's a proper
weird weird autistic atmosphere. I can't
explain it. And that L J has definitely
got autism. That L J is definitely
autistic. And And it's not minor autism.
He's definitely he's definitely got
autism. That's why I don't bother
anymore on here, bro. I don't really
come on here when I'm pissed before I go
to sleep or something.
Yeah, we've heard it all before.
Something's going to come in your door
in 10 minutes. It's boring. You send me
to sleep. Boring
now. But yeah, it's proper. But LT, it is
autism. It's not maybe, bro. It is It is
autism. It is autism. It's definitely
autism. Stay alive and own that clown
now, mate. I got stuff to do today. I
don't have time to be arguing with
spastics that come from LJ's channel,
mate. I'm an adult. I'm not a
child. I'm an adult, not a child. I've
got stuff to
do. So, no, I just went to put something
back. Same atmosphere, same
repeating. Yeah. Literally the same old
[ __ ] Let me sleep. We've heard all this
before. I'm going to come on your door.
Even though they don't know where I live.
Boring. We've heard all this before.
It's only 10 minutes. It's only 15
minutes. You're sending me to sleep.
We've heard all this
before. Oh, that was a big yield. We've
heard all of this before. It's boring
now. And this is exactly why I don't
come on. You remember what I said, LT? The same
atmosphere. Do you remember what I told
you? It's the same
atmosphere over and over and over and
over and over again. Someone's coming
your door in 20 minutes. [ __ ] you got
arrested, bro. How do I explain it? My family
owns. Anyways, I'm going to get breakfast now.
Anyways, kick kick kick. So yeah, I'll
see you all later anyways. Peace.
Maybe later. Maybe. I don't know. Maybe
a week. Probably. I got stuff to do in a
bit, bro. In a bit. In a bit. In a bit.
I'm out of being ad.