Oh [ __ ] Yeah.
Yeah, I think I do,
man. I think I got
[ __ ] tell you
that. Yeah, I've got above
to meet today. They always come back to
good old Peter B, don't
they? They always come back to good old
Peter Bell, don't
they? I thought, you know what? One
football bet is not enough. I have to do another football bet.
[ __ ] I stuck£100 on a football bet. Yeah.
I'm a crazy cat. I'm a crazy camp,
mate. Crazy [ __ ] Crazy [ __ ] Crazy
[ __ ] I think I've got hay fever, man. I
don't know if it's the plugins I'm using,
but Oh, I can't stop rubbing my [ __ ] nose,
man. I'm sure I've got hay fever. I
don't had it before.
Yeah, [ __ ] woman wants to meet today,
bro. All come out once, don't
they? Just bought some more stuff on the good old
fridge. Yeah, for a good old
fridge. There we go. Fric
calls. I'm going to have some roast pork
today, I think.
19year-old wants to meet. I mean, I can
get a [ __ ] I had one yesterday, but
I can get one from her.
Yeah. Don't know if I can be bothered meeting today,
bro. Yeah. I got two football bets. 100
returns 329 and I got one here. That's
£7. Can't really [ __ ]
I might go for a drink and a [ __ ]
[ __ ] [ __ ] bo to meet her today
though. Situation's awkward
now. They always come back to good old
Peter Belly. I went out approaching yesterday. Brick
Bonk. Yeah, I went out approaching
yesterday. A lot of them said they had
boyfriends, but I got three numbers. I
haven't text them yet. Yeah.
Very hard in this country. Britbong.
Britbong. Britbong. Yeah, I said
Britbong. Please. I like that name. Yeah. Yeah,
man. I got all different ages yesterday.
I've got a 20-year-old, a 23 year old,
and a 33 year old, which they're all
different [ __ ] ages, isn't it?
Yeah, I don't know. This football bet
wins. I don't know. I might go
Blackpool. I'm not
sure. I needed to win, but just if it odd, you know. Yeah, baby.
Wheels is the best one. One second. Let
me just take my washer out. Hold
on. I'm definitely allergic to
something. I I'm definitely allergic to something big.
Sorry, mate. That took a That took a
while. No, I've not text them yet. Going
to meet this 19year-old later. She
texted me again. I know she's got
bipolar. What is wrong with people?
Hey, and I put another football bet on.
I put £100 on this football bet. It returns
£329. Oh man. I know. [ __ ] madness, isn't it? £329. It
returns. Yeah, I put £100. I got two
football bets.£17 and100. I thought [ __ ]
it. I'm not going out.
So, but obviously if the bet wins cuz I
need to save. Just count that 250 300
for three days. If it if it wins then
I'll go all out today and just send it
all night long. If not, then I'll just
chill. Oh, I don't want to spend any
more of my own
money. Oh, that is mad. Hey, fever, bro.
What? Where is it coming
from? I've got these little plugins. It
makes the kitchen smell nice.
Made the whole house smell
nice. Yeah, it's
good. Maybe I should just stay with that
19 20 year
old. That's probably the only chance of
having a baby Peter to be
honest. Probably the only
chance. You got 100 pound football
bet. Oh dear
me. 100 pound of [ __ ] football bet. Crazy
bastard. No, I don't need that
energy. That energy wanted Peter Benny.
Nah, I'll just stick with that [ __ ]
19 20 year old. [ __ ] it. Hold on. 27.
Yep. Gave me a good [ __ ] last time.
hell. It was [ __ ]
ace. Oh man. I want another
one. [ __ ] a meeting today. I got
stuff to do. I'm busy. I'm working to
save money, you know.
chance of this football bet coming in.
Double both teams to
score. There was 229
profit. Seems like a lot
it seems like right there.
What's the time?
12:30. The I the best thing today would
be this football bet wins. Either of
them win. Both of them win. Would be
even better, but that's pretty unlikely.
They're both going to win. One of these
football bets win. We go out. We send
it. Send it. Send it. Send it. Send it.
Send it. Send it. And then get the
[ __ ] 19year-old as well. But we can
do that anyways without winning the
football. We don't need the money, but
it's just nice to win a bet. We don't
need the money. Like I said, it's just
just be nice to win
the football bet. You
know, that's a plan. Or the other plan
is the football bet wins and then I'll
just put that money in a separate
account and just send it all night long.
That should be enough.
£329. Go out drinking. Yeah.
So, and then obviously just use that as
just sending it.
But depends how you look at it. E
I did send it yesterday, bro. I did send it. Sober
drunk. I did [ __ ] definitely send it,
mate. Who the [ __ ]
Sounds like some ghost [ __ ]
Yeah. How I got that 19? [ __ ] it up.
But I haven't been able I wasn't able to get
anyone anyone since to be
fair. They're just
NPCs. To be honest, I've only got two
people off the street approaching in
London. A 19year-old
and USA is here.
So that just goes just how [ __ ] hard it is.
But I I like you should go in with like
you should go in with the fact that more than
likely, right, you're not going to it's
not going to happen. But you just drink
anyways. That's what you really have to
go in with cuz more than likely, bro,
you'll get numbers and they don't go
anywhere. It's like winning the
lottery. It's nothing like what people say.
believe nothing like what people say on the
interwebs. It's hard, man. Yeah.
So I could just go out for a few drinks
anyway meeting up. But the problem with
it is but the problem with doing that is
obviously I can't do any more approaches
obviously when I'm with her.
So yeah, when you meet someone you're
you're kind of stuck with them for the whole night.
You can't go wander off and then [ __ ]
leave then. You know what I'm
saying? So I put you in a
position position there.
[ __ ] off [ __ ] hay fever. [ __ ] [ __ ] It's
annoying. God, it's
annoying. Put it [ __ ] back.
Um, what else?
Let me have a look. Hold on.
I kind of killed it
like Yeah. This one that I met, we sort
of live in the same area as well.
Sorry. Yeah, we live in the same area,
which is a good thing.
text to all of them. But to be fair, I
still think I done good
yesterday considering like I went out by myself.
Oh, this both teams of squares coming
in, mate. It's [ __ ] coming in. I'm telling
you, it is coming in,
bro. It's coming in. It's coming in. Yeah, man.
I spam these [ __ ] mate. I done it
sober. I actually done a cold approach
in the weather spoons. [ __ ] sober,
bro. Imagine that. Stone cold sober. I
didn't even start drinking yet. You crazy
bastard. You crazy [ __ ] I
think maybe I knocked some
good something like that.
No, I don't think
so. Yeah, that's
good. Anyways, I'm out of here, man. Yeah.