[ __ ]
What the [ __ ] is this [ __ ] body man
in the [ __ ]
tent. I don't understand. Why the [ __ ]
is he in [ __ ]
tent? Strange, isn't
it? Why is he in the tent? Why is he in
tent? Is he actually homeless?
Sorry I didn't come back on last night,
bro. Can't be on him all the time, lad.
Always the same spastics, same
atmosphere, same repeating. Boy, don't see me
much. Haley kicked him out. Yeah, but
how is he getting in? How is he charging
his phone in the tent? That's what I'm
wondering. How is he charging his phone in the
tent? Let's go get some food there a bit
quick there. Got the good old frigy
coals. That's the fortune. The good old frigy
calls. What do you think? A the good old uh fridge
Uh had some rice beef sandwiches
yesterday. It was
noise. But how this phone? I don't get
it. If he's in a tent, how is he charging his
phone? Unless he's buying like power
batteries and just has a few of them
and going to somewhere charge it all.
But how is he charging his phone in a
tent? Bling hell. That's almost like
Virgin Shield. [ __ ] hell. It's a
[ __ ] virgin moving thing. But no,
seriously, how is he charging his phone?
I got a lot of yesterday.
Oh, the 19y old come around. She sucked
my [ __ ] dick, bro. A nice Chinese,
too. Oh, they always come back to old Peter Belly.
But she's so skinn. Yeah, she reminds me of
Sean. She is so skinn. She actually
reminds you of that Orington virgin. I
lost £100 on a football bet yesterday. I
can live off a [ __ ] grand a month. [ __ ] skin.
You think I can live off a [ __ ] grand
a [ __ ] month? S.
Yeah. So he's charging his phone inside the house.
Yeah, she's proper skin. She reminds me
of [ __ ] legs. She's that skin as
well. That level of skin.
Yes. Wait for this food shop to open. I
need to get some food. Make a banana
today, I think.
We get some more bills to be fair. I
imagine I hope I die. I don't like I
play. It should be enough.
Yeah. So, out of them three numbers, one
of the numbers replied. Um,
so it's [ __ ] better than nothing, is
it? I got I bought some alcohol
yesterday. I was having a few drinks,
but didn't drink all of it
obviously cuz of
um yeah, I didn't want to wake up with the
hangovers. Dashed up.
[ __ ] tape in her mouth. She swallowed it as
well. Oh yeah. Lost, man. Got [ __ ]
hammered under a [ __ ] football.
E. Oh boy. [ __ ]
football. Not good. Not good.
something but in no
bones you a little bit but I see that he's
uh he could potentially be getting with
this um that huh
I remember back in the day when Body
used to argue B uh sorry Body
G we were all arguing. I remember Yeah, I
think the base just call All right.
Sorry about that, bro. [ __ ] sister
called never gets his sister called his
mom called [ __ ] virgin. His family
[ __ ] that he's family, mate. Listen,
it's that [ __ ] virgin a long [ __ ]
time ago. Creepy little
virgin. I'm telling you that virgin creep.
I can't I can't believe these people in
this community. They actually think that
they believe people and all they do is embarrass themselves.
It's actually a madness, bro.
And all they do is [ __ ] embarrass
themselves. Embarrass themselves. themselves. Yes.
Yes. Yes. Yes.
How much do you basically
like or you can buy chicken breast and
one two three four maybe like or something probably