Clear. Clear. [Laughter]
Yeah, I [ __ ] porn bombed myself and
got my [ __ ] channel
terminated. Doesn't even let me appeal.
It's madness, bro. What the
[ __ ] Yeah, I [ __ ] porn b my [ __ ] self.
Yeah, I porn bomb
myself. So, all right. Now, I've got all
my approaches and my memories. So, I
don't really care about that channel. I
saved everything from that channel when
the [ __ ] Orton Virgin got it banned
like two months ago. So, I saved
everything. So, I don't really care
about the channel. It's fine,
bro. Not a
problem. All I really cared about was
the memories on there. You know what I'm saying?
Strange. Let me see.
It's so strange.
They don't make it easy, do they? To [ __ ]
appeal. They don't make it easy, mate.
Yeah. Yeah. [ __ ] him.
That's bad. He lost everything over
YouTube. See, I lost that main account,
but that was that wasn't
uh that wasn't these little retards. I
literally pawn bomb myself yesterday
when I sent someone something and I p I
privatized it. So, I don't I don't care
about the account. [ __ ] it. I've got all
my memories on here anyways now. So, I
don't care about the account. It was a
[ __ ] community anyways. Just full of
self little bit of self projectors.
So, um, I don't really care to be
honest. Don't care at all to be honest, man. No.
Yeah. Is what it is,
eh? Oh, well.
Got some stuff for the old
fridge. How do you
feel? Go back to the old thingy again.
E, I had a banging T-Bone yesterday as
well. I had a [ __ ]
burgers, hot dogs. I got a bion t-bone
yesterday, mate. Oh, it's
lovely. Got a banging t-bone yesterday.
I'll show you
it. Where is
it? Where the [ __ ] is it?
a picture of the
continu. Sure. I did my Where is
it? There you go. It was [ __ ] 17
[ __ ] quid. Cooked it myself.
Yeah. Went to the old
supermarket. Good old supermarket. Yeah.
What to do
today? But yeah, I don't care about the
main. [ __ ] yeah. I got all my got some I
got some recent approaches as well which
I'm going to put on my new channel and I
got all my other
ones. Yeah, I got some sick ones, bro.
So, all gone on this device. Got the
Amstand videos, got the play videos. So,
it's all good. I got my
memories. Who cares about some stupid negative account
buddy? No, man. I'm I don't really
gamble much anymore.
got that uh 19 20 year old a few round a
few times gave me a [ __ ] and
yeah then basically no I still got some
alcohol there I ain't drunk but yeah the
main got banned cuz I p myself sending
something to this Scottish person but
again it doesn't matter I've got all my
memories on this device I just upload on
another channel I wasn't making money
from the [ __ ] channel was I so don't
really care about
See, you're still gambling. Why do you
keep playing them [ __ ] rigged [ __ ]
machines? I don't understand
it. [ __ ] hell, bro. Them same old
rigged machines you keep [ __ ]
playing. I I gambled like I think it
was maybe 10 days ago when I was drunk.
I was like, "Fuck
this." You know, [ __ ] this [ __ ]
You're mad, bro. You're [ __ ]
mad. Can't believe you're still playing
them [ __ ] rigged machines.
[ __ ] I lost 100 pound with the football
bet last Saturday. [Music]
Oops. But Joe, look what I've been
doing. I've been stocking up the old
fridge. So yeah, I had a 20 pound T-Bone
yesterday. Yeah, I just went to get some
more meat, pork, got some
hippos, jalapenos. I've been eating
good, but boy, I haven't been having lamb,
chicken with marinade and
[ __ ] few beers. Good investment. Good
investment, eh? I literally had a 20
tone yesterday. It was [ __ ] massive.
Uh yeah, I don't mate. The only time
I'll probably do it again is probably when I'm
drinking. Probably when I'm drinking on
a night out. I can't promise I won't do
it, but I'll budget myself. I'm back to
saving again for like 3
weeks. Get out of this [ __ ] Get out
this [ __ ] old country again. So
obviously I've been saving and my eating
in I've been saving and just going back
to the old school Peter Belly days
slowly but surely.
Eh I probably gamble when I'm drunk like
before going home. That's just normal. [ __ ] I
mean, nah, not like I used to, bro. [ __ ]
that. I don't have a save.
E, and then just go out. I haven't, you
know, when I went out on ch um where was
it? Friday. It was Joe, I didn't even
spend anything. I bought my own alcohol
with me, but then I lost 150 gambling.
But if you didn't spend 150 gambling,
you would have spent 150 drinking. So, I
just took the L to be honest. So,
yeah. Yeah, it was better
yesterday. It was better yesterday. It yesterday. Trust me. So,
bye-bye. Yeah, I've got some hot
dogs. Oh, yeah. I got the milk by the way.
For some reason, this fridge didn't come
with a light, but believe you me, it is
brand new. Cuz I wouldn't buy a fridge
if it wasn't brand new. Got some coke.
Yeah, I still can't believe this was [ __ ]
£100. I still can't believe I got this fridge for
£100. I was like, it's got it can't be
working properly. It's brand new and
it's £100. There's some sort to this. It
just seems so cheap, but it works fine.
And there's a freezing compartment, too.
So yeah, it's a
madness. Might get that 20 19 year old
man today and [ __ ] get a Chinese and
get a [ __ ] I haven't had a takeaway
for like 4
days. No, like four days. Just get a nice Chinese. Yeah.
had to buy some pans and [ __ ]
but it was all
right. Bought some pans.
Yeah. Got a couple of [ __ ] on the
gojo. Couple of
[ __ ] So, we're kind of back to where we started
now. I haven't had sex for ages. I don't
sex. I know it's madness. I don't. And
she hates doing it as
well, which most people, it's like me.
You couldn't pay me to lick someone out.
I'm not eating [ __ ] I don't eat [ __ ]
You can't pay me to do it, bro. And
that's probably what a lot of them feel
like when you stop their money. If they
don't like doing it, they don't get
nothing out of it. But I don't care for sex,
bro. I don't have I don't want to put
energy into [ __ ] I haven't had sex
for like I don't know, six months.
Is Sean still a virgin? I haven't heard
from him for ages. She's not getting
nothing. I mean, except from drinking
some alcohol and getting some
food. She hates doing it, but she's so
[ __ ] good at it. She swallowed it as
well the other
day. Yeah. So, we're kind of sort of
back to where we were last this year,
last year. just we just don't have as
much money. But we're getting there.
So, we're getting there, man. We should
save a lot of money cooking in.
So, yeah, it's
mad. So, I could get a takeaway today,
but the problem with getting a takeaway
today is I just bought food.
So, takeaways are expensive, man.
They're so yummy, bro. They're so
yummy. They're so
Yeah, but I've not had sex for months.
I'm not a virgin. I just prefer them [ __ ] you
know, than the actual sex.
So yeah, it's all good,
man. Uh yeah, I got three numbers on
Friday. One of them replied, but I don't
care because I know I didn't pay I didn't spend much. Bye-bye,
[ __ ] Cuz I know I didn't I didn't spend much. job.
Yeah. Applied for some work,
Joe. Oh [ __ ] I don't Honestly, bro, how
do people live on a grand a
month? Joe, even with no outgoings, how
can you live off a grand a month? I
don't understand how you could live off
grand how people live off a grand a
month. I I swear down, bro. I'm not even
taking a piss.
Look, I'm I want a lot more than that.
And I'm trying to f and I'm still trying
to [ __ ] save money. Not telling you
what it is because of these little grasses. But
yeah, three, you know, three, four grand
a month is good, but you still have to
be you got you got understand when
you're used to having thousands and
thousands and thousands like I've had
thousands and thousands and thousands,
you get used to it. That's why I'm
trying to adapt by eating in again and
not going out as much. So, it seems a
lot because it is a lot. It is a lot,
but when you live a lifestyle that I've
been living, it's not, you know, it's not a
lot, you know, cuz it's not enough, bro.
Cuz sometimes, I'll tell you why.
Because there's days,
[ __ ] there's days where I'm bored and I
think, "Oh, I can just go out and make a
100 pound or make 150 pounds." There's
days where I get bored. I don't always
like to go out drinking. I don't always
like to go out approaching. And days
where I'm bored, I'd rather earn a bit of extra
money. So, trust me, no money is ever
enough money, but at the same time, I'm
getting it to seem like a lot again
because obviously I'm I'm worth it. I'm
um cuz obviously I'm eating in now and
not eating out as much and then
obviously not drinking every week. So
I'm cutting back. So it seems a lot like
it is a lot. Don't forget last last year
I had thousands then I had another 4,000. So
yeah and you get used to it. So that's
the problem. But you got understand you
live up north it's a lot different. London's expensive. London's expensive,
but London's expensive life. Oh,
yeah. I need to get a TV at some point as
well. My one packed up.
Yes. [ __ ] it's a lot of money obviously, but
still if you go out every week, no money
is enough money, mate. Trust
me. But there could just be one day
where you're super
bored and you know, you can easily just go and
[ __ ] But it makes sense. Why would
you work? You don't need to work. Yeah, obviously. [Music]
You know it [ __ ] a know it [ __ ] a
mate. I remember going to Scotland. I
was talking to someone from Scotland
yesterday and when I got my KFC order,
it's a normal KFC
order. Um, it was
cheaper. It's not the same, bro. It's
not the same. Maybe if you go to like a
Tesco Express. Well, I remember when I
went to Scotland, it was [ __ ] cheaper.
See Edinburgh. Yeah, people say, "Oh,
Edinburgh is expensive." Yeah, it is
expensive compared to other places in
Scotland, but I remember when I went to
the Hive, I got a double ramen and Coke,
£5. You're never getting that anywhere
London. And that was past 10:00 at
night. And then [ __ ] the KFC is cheaper.
Like, yeah, and that's up north. It's
Edinburgh. But that's my second favorite
city. I like Edinburgh in terms of how
it looks, the the buildings. It's cheap.
It's quite cheaper than London as well,
even though not cheaper than Scotland.
Uh, it's cheaper than Glasgow, but they
say Manchester is second London, but I like
Edinburgh. So, to if I was to live
anywhere else, I think I would pick
there. I actually think I would pick
there cuz there's work. It's busy, but
it's not too busy. The buildings are
nice and it's a lot more cheaper than
London, even though it's expensive. I'd
pick there. I honestly would pick there
if I had somewhere else to move to.
just go drinking somewhere else.
But you even said yourself Guinness was
Yeah, but it's not as cheap anymore.
It's like £4 in the Weather SP. No, no,
no, no. If you go outside of central
London, the Guinness is £4. If you go in
central London, the Guinness is
£550. So, it depends where you
go. No, no, that is still quite
expensive. That's going up though. But
that's going up because it's like it's almost
£3.95 local areas in Weather Spoon.
Central London is
£550 which is expensive but that's still
Weather Spoons. If you're going to a
normal pub in central London you're talking £7. So
yeah, it probably is the same drinking
prices. The only place that's probably
different is Blackpool maybe.
But yeah. Yeah, I know what you're
saying. Yeah, cuz I remember when I went
to Leeds and that was expensive. It was
like £45 a haircut. The hotel was 170. Yeah, even
even Leeds was
expensive. No, I remember going to Leeds
and that was definitely expensive. That
That was like two years
ago. I spent 170 on a hotel.
Yeah, it's expensive
everywhere. Yeah, I know what you're saying.
Yeah, everywhere is expensive. Everything's
expensive. I just got [ __ ] 20 t-bone
yesterday and I really fancy the t-bone.
You know what I'm saying, bro?
One second. That man sent me a voice. Hold on.
Yeah. Here we
go. Subzero uh games. I'm not
uh I'm not off um I'm not Monty, man.
I'm not Timmy. Don't try your [ __ ] on my
channel. everything going up and there
come benefits. So you're better off work
and save save money as well by not being
not being in all
day. They're not cutting people's
benefits. They're not cutting people's
She wants to come over today, but I want
a [ __ ] break,
man. No, I'm not going out this weekend.
I'm saving money, so
no, unless one of these people want to
meet me. I'm not.
No, [ __ ] that. I mean, well, I
technically could go out every week. I
could go out. I've got a bowl of
alcohol. technically could do, but that
means getting my haircut and I don't
like getting my haircut often because it's
expensive because that money could be
going on other things rather than
wasting it in this [ __ ] country.
Obviously, you go out every now and
then, but obviously like you live here
in it. But I'm saying you don't want to
be doing it. When did I get lost get my
haircut? I think it
went No, I don't think it was last
Tuesday. It was Tuesday. I get my
haircut every 3 weeks.
So I remember Bomber when he tried
saying that he used to get his haircut
every week. He doesn't have no hair to
cut. He's [ __ ] bald and he's skinned
as well. So I remember that. I remember
that little lie. That just made me
remind that just reminded me of
that. I get it done every 3 weeks to
like every 3 to four
weeks because it's just a waste of
money. Other than
that, yeah, all it is is simply getting
your hair done and then just
pre-drinking. I can spend about £50 going out,
but just can't be bothered. I want to
break from it
sometimes. Last time I drunk before the
last time before
Friday, I came back and pissed all over
the floor and smashed my mug. I had to
get another [ __ ] mug. [ __ ] Spider-Man
mug. [ __ ] [ __ ] cost me 18 [ __ ] quid. So yeah,
maybe this person wants to come around today,
but just give me a [ __ ] break,
mate. Give me a [ __ ]
break. I'm trying to be saving money and
then when people come around, I've got
to offer them food and drink and you
have to do it when people come around.
You know what I'm saying?
So, don't know. I mean, yeah, I have to
get a [ __ ] take away,
but I just bought some food. I bought
food. I bought pork. I bought [ __ ]
hot dogs, you
know. But to be fair, I've not had a
I've not had a takeaway for four days.
Yeah. When I made that 90 like two years
ago. No, it weren't two years ago. He
was definitely 18. So it was like a year and a
half. That's why like you you can just
leave this country now because again
because you've obviously got somebody
that will [ __ ] you and [ __ ] So you
know but I still like to go out and just drink
anyways. It's just all money is
it? more money,
bro. Don't know if I fancy blow up
today. I don't know, bro.
trying to decide what to do.
That's hard in
it. Sure is hard. [Music] One second. step I'm lost.
[ __ ] expensive living there, man.
I don't know if I can be bothered today. I might just [ __ ]
e I'm going to have a bath and get into
the same clothes.
in the same
clothes. That's why I always have to get
into the same clothes. I'm like
that. I'm mad. Like I always wash my
clothes and have to get into the same clean [ __ ]
ones. I'm [ __ ] saying, broki.
haven't got any bombs I can sort of wear
with it. Yeah, I like wearing the same same
[ __ ] right? I'm going to go and
[ __ ] get ready and [ __ ]
[ __ ] some boss stuff, too. [ __ ] clear. [Music]
actually wear the same same shorts, different
t-shirt. So, I don't know,
man. Speak to her every day and that.
We're cool, but I just I just ain't been
back. Kind of used to my
life. I'm kind of used to my
um life, you know, by myself. So, I will go back. Uh,
yeah. Yeah, we're cool. I speak to them,
my sisters and [ __ ] Just don't back
spend like in my own
company, you know, live the fast track
life. Oh, yeah. I don't need to wash
this cuz I've got another t-shirt. The
super dry t-shirt. So, I can just wear
the same shorts, but just change the
boxes. Yeah, they always come
back. Yeah. [ __ ] tall [ __ ] is that that England
manager. Oh, I was watching some more of the inbetweeners
yesterday. I was watching some more of
the inbetweeners yesterday, man. The
[ __ ] when when Will gets thrown in the [ __ ]
water. [ __ ] um when he gets Oh, that
just killed me, man. I've laughed my ass
off. Yeah, I know. But the thing is,
Sam, I'm trying to [ __ ] save money.
How am I supposed to [ __ ] go to
[ __ ] America again and see baby Peter
if I've got [ __ ] vultures around me,
you know? I've stopped the [ __ ] fridge
up. I've stocked the [ __ ] fridge up.
Yeah, you know, obviously save money.
Look, some hippos and stuff. Some pork
and a t-bone yesterday. I've been eating
good. How am I supposed to [ __ ] live
when I got [ __ ] vultures around me?
Nah, not with that virgin. That's why
he's still a virgin, you
know. How come someone on a grand a
month try to call anyone else
skin? That's funny to
me. That's funny to me,
mate. That is really funny to
me. But yeah, that channel, my main got
[ __ ] terminated cuz I pred myself.
But like I said, I've got all of these
videos. I'm going to put them up later
on my other channel. All I cared about
was my approaching videos
and [ __ ] And I've got them all anyways
cuz I saved them all the last time. The
virgin tried to keep getting the [ __ ] channel banned. So
yeah. So, it's very hard to find someone in this
country like USA Izzy and that 90 year
old who's almost 20. They're like rare
rare approaches. It doesn't happen. I
went out on Friday. I was getting it
non-stop. I've got a boyfriend. I've got
a boyfriend. I've got a
boyfriend. It's all you get. But I got
free numbers. But I don't care anyways, bro. Cuz
like, and I said to Ant-Man, like, I'm
still going to go to Thailand. I still
hate women. Even if I get sex, I hate
them. They're just so entitled. You You
know that even when you meet them.
Yeah. And stuff. And you get them, but
they're still entitled. They've got
mental problems. I'm telling you, bro. I still hate
them. That's just the way I am, bro. I
just don't like them. They're just nasty people, you
know, and they're very entitled as well,
which is something that you don't get in Asia.
I just use this [ __ ] country as a
[ __ ] buddy. Speak to my old
neighbor. I'll go and see lady at some
point, but I just can't be
bothered. I just really can't be asked,
man. [ __ ] sake. How am I supposed to
save money when I have these people
[ __ ] coming around? I will never be
able to save money, you know?
I'll never be able to [ __ ] say money with
these money, money, money cuz I'm all
[ __ ] skin. I need to be home. When
people come, I have to get a take where
I have to [ __ ] buy Coke and [ __ ]
Never been able to save,
man. I remember that time when I was at
my mom's, I saved like four grand in
like a [ __ ] month. It was [ __ ]
hard though. But I got into a routine of
it. I was just living off like 10 pound
day. But it's [ __ ] hard, man. And I
didn't drink for like six weeks. I think
it was like four weeks or five weeks.
But there was a time where I didn't go
out for 6 weeks. Never be able to
[ __ ] save money, bro. We keep doing
this. Yeah, I see him in a tent. That's
his own fault. [ __ ]
him. He's a little [ __ ] you know. I
could probably have him somewhere to
stay, but he can go [ __ ]
himself. That's all you get for being a
snake. And these people on YouTube, they
think they ruined my life. They did ruin
my life. All of the things that happened
wasn't even to do with YouTube. Like me
and the neighbor. That's cuz I made
noise and nothing was ever to do with
YouTube. Yeah, people got me nicked a
few times and then the police just got
bored of them. But they've never ruined
my life. Monty's life has been ruined.
He's homeless. [ __ ] hell,
bro. His life is
[ __ ] His life is [ __ ] I p
myself. I sent my dick to the Scottish
person and obviously they they banned it.
So yeah, [ __ ] I'm trying to appeal.
Yeah, mask is in a 10 in
it. It will never be me. It will never
me. It would never be
me. It would never ever be me.
Yeah, she keeps coming around and coming
around. How am I supposed to [ __ ] say
money? Know what I'm saying, sucking
vultures around me. How am I supposed to
[ __ ] say [ __ ] money?
It's [ __ ] a nightmare, mate. It's a
nightmare. It is a nightmare, is it?
No, I'm not paying nothing. But when
people come around, I cook them food or
like I buy takeaways and
[ __ ] cuz I always do it when obviously
people come around. Then obviously when
people come around you feel obliged to.
So it's going to just be harder to save
money. That's the thing. Obviously I
have money like it's not a problem but
I'm still saying I want to say more more
and I can't do
that. I can do it again. I'm used to
it. Yeah. We've heard it all before. If
you're now shut
up expect to knock on your door in 15 minutes. Bye-bye.
And and to be honest with you, bro, when
when my when my channel got banned, like
I didn't really care because it was just
the same spastics. The only the only
thing that I cared about is the
memories. But I got all the
memories, you know, because all this
community have this just
bitter bitter self-p projectors that are
angry at themselves and angry at their
lives. So they come on YouTube and take
it on other people talking about people
that they don't know.
So, I didn't really care about the
channel. This was what was on the
channel. No, I don't want to be in a relationship,
right? I don't want to be in a relationship. I'm
good. I've had many chances to be in a
relationship and I don't want to be in
one. I'm I'm all right as my
own. I'm I'm enough alone. Simple.
I don't really care about [ __ ]
anymore, bro. I don't care about women
anymore. Trust me, I don't really care about
it. And you'll notice that when when you
live somewhere like London, you'll
always get bored of one
woman. I don't need all my bills. I
don't really have any bills.
in terms of like living alone. Yeah,
that's the thing. Like, yeah, if you're
in a relationship, yeah, it's probably
better to live alone. It's probably
better because the rent is shared.
That's the only good thing if you're in
a relationship. But I I'd want to live by
myself. Like, say say I moved to a nice
place in Edinburgh. Yeah. Say I went to
a nice place in
Edinburgh. That's where I' i'd want to
be bound myself. I wouldn't want to be
with anyone else. I'd want to be bound
myself. I don't want to [ __ ] live
with another [ __ ] person. I don't
even sh I don't even share a bed with
someone else. I don't like sharing beds.
I don't like sharing anything, you
know? I wouldn't live with another
person. I don't want to live with
another person. It get my [ __ ]
nerves. Nice having the whole place to
your [ __ ] self, you know.
Nah, we can't do that, Sammy,
unfortunately, because we've got a uh greeneyed
monster. We've got a little greeneyed
monster that um on his YouTube. So,
yeah. Yeah, we've got a greeneyed monster. Green eye
monster. You know what I'm going to do?
I'm going to [ __ ] probably
uh Yeah, I got some burgers. I got some
hot dogs. I got some pork. So, I'm going
to have to cook. I can't afford to
[ __ ] keep getting these takeaways.
But today would be bad to get
one, you know, cuz of
uh I haven't had one for 4 days, but
then I've got to eat the pork today.
That's the problem. I would literally
have to eat the pork today before it goes
off. I spent about £50 at the butchers, you
know. Nah, she wouldn't, Sammy.
and she'd miss that
money. Be my protection. I don't need
any protection, bro. If anyone ever sees
me on the street, they're going to get [ __ ] up.
Simple. So, you're just going to have to
settle for pork chops today, me, love.
Yeah. I [ __ ] I spent I spent [ __ ]
£50 in the butchers.
Yeah. Like load of chicken, diced
chicken, diced lamb. Got my friend over
to cook it. It was [ __ ]
bagging. I know it was a lot I spent in
the [ __ ] butchers, but oh my god, so
much lamb, so much chicken. It was
[ __ ] beautiful. And I got a pace as well.
So yeah, I do fancy Chinese today.
can get one.
But yeah, I can get one, but I'd have to
um I'd have to
uh Oh, I had to pay for a criminal
record check, by the way, Joe. Yeah, 41
[ __ ] quit. It cost
me 41 [ __ ] pound. It cost me for a
criminal I know I don't have a criminal
record, but I had to pay for it.
Yeah. Yeah. I had this, like I said, I
had this t-bone yesterday. I cooked it.
Oh, it's [ __ ]
bagged. It was [Music]
bad. Peter Bennett. Peter Benny will be
getting his muscles back. Hey,
daddy. Yeah, I'm going to get a [ __ ]
today, I think. [ __ ] cup of tea, and a nice Chinese.
Yeah. Oh my god.
Yeah, it was £41 criminal record
check. Oh, no. I don't have a criminal
record. I've never been convicted of
anything. Imagine it just comes up that
you've just been nicked over YouTube about 10
times. That you've been nicked over
YouTube like 10 times. Everybody think,
"What the [ __ ] Oh, [Music] imag [Laughter] it.
Yeah. Wish I could try and get this account back.
I peeled, but they said that there's no
use. I'll have to sort out later when I'm 100%
focused. You need a lot of focus for this. Yeah.
Yeah. Doesn't matter how long it is,
they always come back to Peter
Belly. You know, even Izzy can't resist
me. She knows she likes me more than her
boyfriend, but you know, she has to put
up a front because why else does the [ __ ] watch
me? Talking about you crazy, by the way.
Why else do you watch me?
[ __ ] Yeah, they always come back to
Peter Benny, man. They love Peter Belly. Never.
Never. I was thinking of USA's tit
yesterday. That's just fat. That's just fat. She's
fat. You know what I'm
saying? She's just
fat. No, I'm joking. I wasn't
really. I got three numbers Friday. One
replied, I'm not asked anyways cuz I
didn't pay any money. So, I just pre I I
brought a I bought a bottle in by
myself. I went out with shorts, no
jeans. I brought a bottle with me. I
didn't The only money I spent was the 150
gambling. So, yeah, I didn't spend
nothing. So, I don't give a [ __ ] bro.
I'd done a lot of approaches in the
shopping center the other day as well
before the cinema. I'd done so many
approaches. Oh my [ __ ] god. I done so
many I done so many approaches,
man. What? They
uh No, it was it was a Captain Morgan
bottle. I don't skin. This was why am I
going to go out and
spend it's either you go out every week
and you pre-drink with a bottle or you
go out every 3 to four weeks and you
don't care what you're spending. You
know, either way, you shouldn't be
spending more money than you need to be
spending. Think about it, right? You
spend more money than you need to spend
every week. Yeah. For four weeks. In
them four weeks, you could have went
Disneyland. Think about it, bro. It's
called being smart. It's not called
being skin. It's called not spending
more than you need to spend. You
know, you could in in that month that
you went out pre-drinking and you
brought that bowl with you, you can
afford a holiday then rather than
spending money that you don't need to
spend. Do you not do you not
understand? That's the thing with it,
bro. It's called being smart with your money.
And you know, this is a [ __ ] country, so
you don't really want to spend more
money than you need to be [ __ ]
spending. So that's what it is, bro.
Like, but the thing is, but at the same
time, if if I've got gone out for four
or five weeks, then I'll have a big
blowout like when I got that pass, I
don't give a [ __ ] We'll have a good
piss up. But obviously, if you go out
every four or five weeks and do that,
there's still saving. Can't do it every week. You
know what I'm saying? Like say I don't
go out for another two two and a half
weeks, I'll get my haircut and spend as
much as the drinks cost, maybe 150. It's
not going to make a difference. But
obviously if you're doing it every week
then because you know it's even when I
used to travel I used to do it cheaply
cuz it just feels so much better doing
cheaply. You know when you spend too
much money it takes the fun out of it.
That's what I think as far as England
goes. But at the same time, if you went
to like Thailand or you went America or
you went somewhere in another country,
then it doesn't matter how much you
spend. It's a one it's a lifetime
experience in it. You don't care. But in
terms of this
country, you know, you I remember when I
bumped the train back for Middlesbrough,
it makes it that much more funner that
you've that it's not cost that much.
It's hard to explain, bro.
But it is hard to
explain. Open that front door. You don't
know where I am. You're
boring. One second. Piss.
Sorry bad. I just had the piss in the
sink. Um, where am I going out this weekend?
Nowhere. I'm not going out
anywhere. No, nowhere at
all. Need to ban these
retards. No, I'm not going out anywhere.
He's not at mine. It's the same people
that's been doing it for months show.
Oh, I'm coming 15 minutes. He doesn't
even know where I live anyways. And they
like, "Oh, someone's coming in 15
minutes. Someone coming in 20 minutes." Um,
uh, depends. Where is
it? It depends where it is. And is that
200 pound of return? I don't know, man. But it
depends depends where it
depends where where it is. Um they've
been doing it for months now for 3
months. Oh, somebody's coming in your
door in 10 15 minutes because they think
it's going to give you anxiety. The same
anxiety that they live with every
day. The same anxiety that these people
live with every day. They try and This
is what I'm trying to say to you, Joe,
that they don't It's like before when
you was trying to say that they
psychologically [ __ ] with any people's
heads. They don't psychologically [ __ ]
with my head. Like, speak for yourself.
These people don't [ __ ] with my head.
They don't make me rage. They just bore
me. Like, a lot of the time, right, when
you don't see me on YouTube, it's just
because they just bore me to death. And
I'm and I'm busy with other things. They
don't torment me. They don't [ __ ] with
my head. They don't psychologically make
me doubt myself. They're just boring,
you know, and that's
it. And this guy, this guy's boring.
We've been hearing it for three, four
months. Someone's coming on your door in 10, 15
minutes. 10, 15 minutes. Someone's
coming knocking on your door. We've been
hearing it for like 3 months. It's boring.
This is probably like the only decent
like thing decent chat we've had for a
long time, bro, where people have not
said, "Oh, your skin and they're self
projecting." That's why I can't be
bothered with it. That's why I got on
here really like on
here cuz it's just just boring, isn't
it? Watching a bunch of adults talk
about themselves. It's [ __ ] mad, isn't it? But
yeah, it depends where the coach
is. See, if you said a Euro store to
France, then I would have said the Euro
store. If it was like £50 on the Euro
store and then £200 on a plane, then I
get the Euro store cuz it's quicker and
it's easier as well. So, it depends
where it is.
I don't know. Depending where it is, it I guess
Um, don't know. I was I was planning to
go to Disneyland,
Paris, cuz I've never been to Paris before.
Maybe go to
Disneyland. Yeah, maybe go to
Disneyland. Nah, I'm not taking anyone.
I want to be by
myself. I just want to be by myself, bro.
Honestly, these women have caused enough
trouble in people's
lives. Think of it. The whole thing with
the neighbor I mean not me not living
with my mom anymore is partly because of
women. Don't you think they've caused enough
trouble? Don't you caused enough
We'll see you store. Bye-bye.
Now, you know what's so funny about
Bondi? Yeah. He's so dumb that he
doesn't even realize that people are
taking the piss out of him. Like, he'll
go live talking to these people and he
doesn't even realize that they're taking
the piss out of him. Like, they're
actually taking the piss out of him.
And the same people that he's talking
to, right, are the same people that contributed to
the where why why he is where he is.
It's a [ __ ]
madness. You know what I'm saying?
So he's kind of dominate. [ __ ] him.
Anyways, and what's so mad is that he
always used to defend the women and that
looked his life got ruined by one.
Yeah. Yeah. He can barely read, but still, you
know, so I don't know what to do. Take
away or not take away.
[ __ ] this life,
man. [ __ ] this
life. No, it's good, man. But it's like I don't
know. And I had to pay £41 for that
background check. That cost money,
so it's too hard, bro. But it's good. I
invested in the fridge and invested in
pans and spatulas and [ __ ] Otherwise,
I'd be spending I don't know why I
didn't Well, I didn't do it before
because it was cold outside. But yeah,
without that fridge, I'd be [ __ ]
basically. Yeah. Then when I when I when
she find like another
room. Nah, I'm good, bro. I'm taking a
break. When I go out drinking again is
when I'll gamble again. I'll tie the
gambling in with the
drinking. So, we'll have it all together
like the haircut, the drinking, and the
gambling. But I'm not doing that for a
while. And I lost 150 on it last when
did I go
out? Just Saturday I went out. No, it
was Friday I went out. I lost 150 on it.
I got it to 250 and it rained the
[ __ ] lot. Then I lost 100 pound with a football
bet. Nah, bro.
When I go out
again, you'll do
it. But you can't win on it, bro. The
[ __ ] You can't win on that
[ __ ] I was thinking about the days when
I used to play online roulette. Bad news,
man. Bad bad news.
I used to man [Music]
[ __ ] feel [ __ ] though.
Yeah. And the worst days come from it as
well. The worst days come from it as
well. I don't know. Pas I'm just going
to have mushrooms with it. moves
it. Maybe I could have a baby with that
[ __ ] and then
[ __ ] get get housing from the
council. Could it
go? That would be bad.
No, that would be bad, would
it? Is that okay with you, greedy
boss? Is that okay with you,
boss? Okay with you,
boss. So, I can [ __ ] this just a moment,
I'm joking. I'm
joking. Yeah. Look what happened to Monty
Many. Look what happened to [ __ ] Monty
man. Madness, isn't it?
in a helium in a healthy environment. Yeah.
I should go and see Lady
Joe. I can't believe that was 6 months
ago. That was almost 6 months ago. All that
madness. [ __ ] time flies, isn't it? 6
months almost. I think it's almost been 6 months. [Music]
Yeah. Some spare moves or something.
You're not green. Nobody
over. or whatever. Anyways,