Why have I got a picture of my [ __ ] keyword?
Yeah, beautiful cup of
The [ __ ] would I do it? What the [ __ ]
would I do?
Six. Yeah. Hold on. That was
the Yeah, I don't really can't worry much
anymore because it's the same [ __ ]
every day as somebody uh used to say. Literally
is same spastics every day.
Not every day. Every [ __ ] day it is.
So you don't really catch me much on
here anymore. You don't catch a boy on
there much anymore. It's the same
atmosphere. At least when you used to go
into the casino, it used to be a good
atmosphere. Just saving feet and
people. I mean, it's cute when I say that, is it? You
know, I'm tired,
bro. Just made myself a beautiful cup of coffee. Yes, I
did. Was port. I was supposed to make it yesterday,
but I didn't D no.
I've not had a takeaway for like four or
five days to be honest. Don't miss it,
man. How am I ever going to go to
Disneyland and see Mickey Mouse if I
keep wasting money on
takeaways? How the [ __ ] am I going to go
and see Mickey
Mouse? You know, it's never going to
happen. I wanted to see Mickey Mouse this
year. I want to see Mickey.
Oh, you see Mickey. That's never going
to [ __ ] happen. You keep wasting all your
takeaways. It's been about four or five
days. I'm sure. When was the last time
when thingy comes
round? I'm not doing nothing, mate. I'm
saving money. I need to get out this [ __ ] old
country. I'm not doing nothing, mate. I
need to save. I've had a takeaway for
like four or five days.
It was very tempting yesterday, but I
was like, I've got load of food in the
fridge to just
cook. I got some pork chops today for
dinner. So, I'm not doing nothing this
weekend. Potentially next weekend,
maybe. I'm not doing nothing this
weekend. Maybe do a football
bet. [ __ ] this country. It's [ __ ] The
people in it are [ __ ] as well. I don't
care if it'll be busy. Good for it being
busy, bro. It's nothing I'm not missing.
It can be as busy as it wants. It can be
busier than [ __ ] New York, New Year's
[ __ ] Eve. I'm I don't care. Let it be
busy. Results are not going to change
whether it's busy or not. Again, you're
watching an approaching channel, bro.
This is This is somebody that's done
loads of approaches. Let me remind you.
And trust me, it's always the same. It
doesn't matter whether it's busy or not.
So yeah, I'm staying all weekend. I'm
not going out [ __ ] wasting two,
three, 400 pound. [ __ ]
that. Trying to get out of this [ __ ]
country. Oh yeah, you go for a nice
walk. Yeah, but in terms of like going
out drinking, I'm not doing it. [ __ ] off,
bro. I'm going to see Mickey Mouse this
year, Grezy. How can I see Mickey Mouse
if I keep wasting money in this [ __ ] country?
or you know keep wasting money. I've not
had a takeaway for like 5
days. To be honest, don't miss him, you
know. You know.
Yeah. Mickey Mouse. Disneyland
Paris. I want to go Disneyland Paris this
year to see
Mickey. Yeah. I want to see Mickey
Mouse. What's wrong with that?
I had two drinks yesterday. That's cuz
my friend come
over. You sucked my podger
again. Yeah. So, you're talking like
7800. It's not that bad. But
yeah, you can come too if you want,
Greasy. Imagine taking King Oh, imagine
taking King to Disneyland. Oh my god.
That would be a lovely site, isn't it?
taking King to Disneyland to see all the little characters.
Yeah, that would be a lovely site. Yeah,
bro. But yeah, I went out on
Friday. Yeah, I went out on Friday, so
I'm not going to go out this
week. I went out approaching and [ __ ]
Yeah, I went out approaching. It was
mid. Yeah, I'm not happy with one woman anyways,
Grezy. Would you be happy with one
woman? Nah, you need multiple women.
Peter Belly needs multiple women, not just
one. Have you ever, you know, you get
bored? Let me tell you this, right? You
know, when you go to the gym enough
times, you get bored of that gym or not
necessarily a routine. Well, yeah, you
get bored of a routine in ter in terms
of in terms of in terms of um in terms
of wanting to change up the routine a
little bit. That's the same with a
woman. You will get bored of a woman,
especially when you live in somewhere
like London, you know, you'd get bored
of a woman, you know, and it's the same
as if you went to the same gym. You get
bored of the same routine and you do,
trust me, because I've done this million times before.
So, I can get this [ __ ] 19, 20-y old.
I could have her forever if I wanted.
She was here
yesterday. He can't stay with me. Sorry.
And I wouldn't even if I could let him
stay with me and [ __ ]
off, you know? Like he's his life has
actually been [ __ ] ruined over
YouTube. Not mine. I always have
somewhere to go. I always get money, you
know? And that's what made me laugh when
Joe used to say, "These people
psychologically [ __ ] with my head." They
don't [ __ ] with my head, mate. They make
me [ __ ] laugh. These little YouTube
retards like Jamie Thompson.
I think that Jamie Thompson definitely
wants to be me. He's such a weirdo. He's
a creep. He doesn't psychologically [ __ ]
with anyone's head. He's just a bongo.
And then you see that as well, Vivy. You
just laugh at these people. He's a
[ __ ] bongo. That Jamie
Thompson. I think these people target
anyone that's got a better life than
them and self-reflect their misery so
they don't have to be alone no
more. Is that accurate, Joe? Yeah, it
is. I am going to go to Disneyland Paris. I
reckon go by the
pool. I said, "Lady, can you come?"
She's like, "I can't afford it this [Laughter]
year. I'm not
back. I should be getting my other
YouTube account back soon. They said
they'd contact me within 24 hours. I've
not heard from
them. And then if not, I've got to put
all these approaches on this [ __ ]
channel. I've got all my memories, so
it's not a big deal losing the channel
because I got all the memories. I
[ __ ] saved it last time that [ __ ]
virgin kept reporting me, that [ __ ]
Kent virgin. So, like, in case it
happens again, but I actually pulled
bomb myself, you
know? See, these little mongos on
YouTube, they think that they ruin
people's life, but everything that I've
done was basically
self-inflicted. I got my own channel
banned. I'm the one that had problems
with the neighbors with the gambling
and all of it was all because of me in
the end. If you think about it, these
people don't [ __ ] ruin no one's
[ __ ] life. The little
bongos. It's good to be able to sit
there and [ __ ] say that as well. Like
even with Izzy. Yeah. In the end it was
me. Yeah. They caused a few problems at
the start. There's no denying that. But
then towards the end it was actually me.
It was actually me and not
YouTube. No, I'm going to Disneyland Paris
first. I'm going to Disneyland Paris to
see Mickey Mouse and this by TV as well.
So I'd rather save I'd rather save than
than go out wasting money drinking, bro.
Like I need to save. And you can tell it
got a fridge, got pans, and just need
the TV. My one and my mom's broke down.
So, I'm going to get like an 85 in.
Yeah, I'm going to go by myself.
Yeah, I'm boring now. Thank you. So are
you. You don't want to go there
alone. I would have took king, but
there's a few issues, but yeah, I'll
just go by myself. [ __ ] it. I don't want
anyone with me. Do not understand. Well,
I wanted to take my M, but she said she
can't afford it. So,
yeah. I bet you I can, mate. I bet you I
Joe. Oh, here we go with the pedophile
jokes. Yeah. Yeah. Cuz we've seen stuff
like in America where they've I've seen
that where they've like the Predators
gone to see kids. I'm not interested in
no kids. I just want to see Mickey. I've
been watching Mickey for years, you
know. Yeah. I was thinking of doing like
Central Paris, doing some approaches
there and then going to Disneyland, but
then I'd have to be there for like three
or four. I'd have to be there for like 3
days. Yeah. Boy stuck in a man's body.
Why? Because I would go to Disneyland
Paris. Do you not think it's weird
though? Apart from the kids. Well, no,
because it's for anyone's
age. No, but it's for any Yeah, I know
what you're saying, but it's for anyone's
age, you know? Like, I still like
Scooby-Doo. I still like Spongebob
because that's my childhood
memories. Yeah, obviously I know what
you're saying, but I like I like Mickey.
I like Goofy as well. They're my little
friends, you know. So,
I would have invited Sean to come with
me, but he's too skinn. So,
well, who the [ __ ] do you want me to go
with? I The only person I would take is
my mom, and she can't afford it. So, you
either gay or high on spectrum. Listen
to yourself. You've got me confused with
yourself, buddy. I've never I've never
suffered from autism. If you get your
sister to go, she can bring her kid.
Nah. Nah. I like to solo travel by
myself. The only person I would take is
is my mom. I wouldn't take anyone
else. Going to places by yourself has so
many perks. It's so underrated. People
don't understand. Like people obviously
if you're going somewhere like [ __ ] I don't
know. Okay. Greece for example. Yeah.
Okay. you go with other people. Yeah.
But um you know so many places are so
better to go by yourself. People just
don't understand. They don't understand
the perks of traveling alone. They
really don't understand the perks of
it. And there's so many perks of
it. You know, you go out, you go by
yourself, you're forced to meet new
people because you're by yourself. You
get to do what you want when you want.
because you're by yourself. This is what
people don't understand is that when
you're with someone, you're stuck with them basically.
So, nah, people wouldn't say that I'm
disabled. Why would people say I'm
disabled? You got to be confused with
yourself again, Money. I know there's a
lot of confusion on this um
community, but yeah, Money Man's not
been live for like a day or two, has
he? No, I'm not taking her. [ __ ] her,
man. She come around yesterday. She suck
my dick and then she left. She
left. Yeah, I'm nearly 30. Um I'm 27.
I'm nowhere near 30. Nowhere near 30.
I've still got 3
years. That's like telling a newborn,
baby, you're almost 3 years of age.
Nah. Okay. Hey, well, I'll go by myself then.
Simple. It's quite expensive, Joe. Disneyland
Paris. Yeah, it's called Underground
Adventures or some [ __ ] like
that. I don't feel sorry for him though.
[ __ ] him. I don't feel sorry for
him. [ __ ] him. Anyways, he's a
wter. I hate him, bro.
He's a little snake as
well. I wouldn't save that [ __ ] if he was
[ __ ] I don't know how I'm getting
there yet. Um I I won't I wouldn't piss
on him if he was on [ __ ] fire, bro. No. [ __ ] Yep.
So his life actually did get ruined over
Eugene. Mine didn't. He's did. Brian
didn't. And trust me, I I give it to
these people. They did try. They [ __ ]
did try. Like I give credit when credit
is due. These people did try with me.
They tried getting all my money stopped.
Worked. They tried [ __ ] getting
neighbors to kill me. Never worked. They
tried [ __ ] They tried something else.
What else did they do? They put me on
street drama trying to get me killed. Never
worked. They tried everything with me.
They try as much with um
body. But what I learned with with this
[ __ ] like people like Traal and these
people is that they do all of these
things because they hate their own life.
I I learned they're very unattractive.
They're very fat.
They've given us small little town where
every time they try to leave the house
they get bullied. So this is why they're
on YouTube every day and they can't get
off it. It painted pictures of their
own. It paints a picture of their own
lives, their own reality. Why they do this
stuff, you know? It makes sense. It's
like putting the pieces of the puzzle
together and then find out what it is.
They did try though. I give them that.
So, but yeah, I still I still have
people stalk me to be
honest. That Jamie Thompson still stalks
me every day. I think he wants to be me.
They target anyone with a better life
than them. That's what they do. They
target anyone that's got a better life
than them. You'll notice that. You'll
definitely notice that. Well, the main's
banned now anyways from myself. But
yeah, [ __ ] him anyways.
That's what it
is. Yeah. Yeah. Limited virgin again.
You got me confused with yourself,
buddy. You're getting me confused with
yourself. Confusion. You got your
confusion, lads. Nah, no, no. It's not
because of all of the stuff you said.
Um, Joe, I don't know how long you've
you've been on here for. How long have
you been on here for? Was you here when
I was 22? No, no, no, no, no. These
people started way before kids. Way
before women. Like, they'll come in here
and hate and hate and hate and hate and
hate. You can't ban girls and be like,
"H, you got yourself confused with me,
buddy. I think you need a timeout.
I'm not going to ban you, but I'm going
to time you out cuz you're getting me
and yourself confused again. Anyways,
um uh what was I saying is uh no, they
target anyone that's got a better life
than them. They they targeted me or
anyone that's better looking than them.
They targeted me when I was like
21. Well, there you go. So, these people
t No, I tell you exactly how it all
started. Yeah. I I know I was watching
Timmy since I was 19. I come on YouTube
and made an account when I was I think I
was 21 or 22. Yeah. And um I used to do
these rants about women. Oh, they're
shallow. Oh, they're this. Oh, they're
that. Oh, they're this. Oh, they're
that. Like just normal things saying
that kind of stuff. This was back when
Craig Goodston was on here. And people
would still target you. They would still
target you. Yeah.
Um and then um they still target you,
they still target you and then um what
happened was Timmy would was getting
[ __ ] from Pat Mustard and then when I
defended Timmy, Timmy then snakes you
and then they all went for me and then I
said stuff about women which the kids
[ __ ] didn't come like two years after.
Monty was actually the first one to say
stuff about kids then I copied him and
thought [ __ ] it, you know. So no, these
people have been doing it way before the
kid [ __ ] Way before the kid [ __ ] And
that dove. Yeah. He just wanted to try
and [ __ ] He just wanted to try and
show off. Yeah. Without Beck sex because
he knew that, you know, you're younger
than him. I would love for that [ __ ] to
come now, bro. I just put a slap over
his [ __ ] head. I would love for that
G to try and ever come for me again,
bro. I swear
that I'd love for him to come now four
years later and see what happens to him.
I'll give him my new address. But these people
started these people
started before all of that. They started
before all of that. And if it's not one
person, it would have been other people.
Trust me, they [ __ ]
did. How do you think LT's got to be
these people? They do. They will. They
will. They will. They will, man. It's
not about what you said. It's the fact
that you've got a better life than them
and you're better looking than them and
they hate it. Truth hurts. I know. But
that's the way it
is. Cuz they've been doing it years, [ __ ]
years. It's like that Orington virgin,
that little Kent virgin. I don't even
know what the [ __ ] his problem is. He
doesn't even [ __ ] know me, you
know? Yeah. That little virgin don't
even know me, Joe. that little [ __ ] K
virgin with erectile dysfunction, but he
still likes to talk people's [ __ ] name. You
know, he still likes to talk people's
[ __ ] name and he doesn't know them.
So, no, what you said might not helped
yourself, you know, but nah, these
people have been doing it before that.
And if you've been on here, you would
know what these people have been
doing. So, yeah.
And and at the end of the day, what you
say about women is none of these
people's [ __ ] business. You know, I
get the kid [ __ ] but why why would
these people care what you say about
women? Respectfully, why would these
people care what you say about women?
And don't tell me they've got bumps and
sisters. No, bro. Why would they really
really care? It's not like they get
women. It's not like these people even
leave the house. Why the [ __ ] would they
even care? It makes me laugh.
It makes me actual laugh. It makes
That's the bit I don't get. The kids
[ __ ] I do get because, you know, kids
are innocent and [ __ ] you know? They
don't know what they're doing. I
understand why people would be pissed
off if you said stuff about kids. But I don't understand
why you would be pissed off about what
people say about women. They're not
innocent. They know what they're doing.
You know, I had it today with some [ __ ]
when I woke up on WhatsApp. I still
don't get why people defend him. I just
don't I just don't care anymore. It's
simp I don't I haven't changed what I
think. I just don't care about them
anymore cuz it's a waste of time, bro.
Let them do what they got to do with it.
But I still think they're evil. I still
think they're [ __ ] up. And rightfully
so. You know they
are. And you don't understand with these
women, Joe, is when they get with people
that they shouldn't get with, they then
turn into [ __ ]
Yeah, they then turn and I've seen it.
I've seen it myself where people have
changed, where people have gone with
someone and then all of a sudden they've
changed. I'm not going to get into it,
but I've seen it
myself. Don't talk to me like a kid that
I don't know anything, mate, cuz I [ __ ]
do. I understand why people would defend
children, but I don't understand why
people would defend
them. I seriously seriously seriously seriously don't.
But then it goes back to do two do these
people actually have life experience?
Because if they actually did have life
experience in this [ __ ] modern day
and age, they would know what they're
like. Trust me, man. They're [ __ ]
They're just they're [ __ ] up in their
head. Why do you think I would go to
different countries to get away from to
get away from it, you
know? and I'd give up my new address for that [ __ ]
governor. Yeah, we're just talking about
memory lane. That's how it all started.
Anyways, so what you're telling me if
you didn't say anything about kids and
you didn't say anything about women,
everybody would just start loving you?
No. Everybody would just start loving
you. I won't understand. Yeah. Yeah.
Okay. Okay. Okay. Right. They have
girlfriends. They have girlfriends that
they that they care about. Okay. Are you
attacking their women? Are you doing
anything to their women? No. You're just
saying it [ __ ] generally. You're just
saying it [ __ ] generally. It doesn't
matter if you It's like me, right? If I
If I logged on right now, I speak to my
mom, I speak to my sisters, I've got
friends or women, and they turn around
and said, I would be like, "What the
fuck?" And I'd click off. So, is it
autism? That's what I'm saying. That
could also be a form of autism where you
people, you know, get so involved in it.
If I heard somebody saying mad stuff,
I'd be like, "This is a madness. This
guy's fucked." And then I click off of
it. I wouldn't go on the way you people
go on. Whether it was Ben, but that's
what I'm saying. It must be autism with
with with that
Trampson. It's got to be autism. It has
to be. It literally it has to be, bro,
cuz it's not
normal. It's not normal. Women need to
be protected. That just sounds like, you
know, when you when you when you say
that stuff, it just makes you seem like
a white guy. You know, it makes you seem
like a white guy. See, again, you're
defending women, but women are not
innocent. Women are not innocent. I
don't know why people go on, Joe, like
they're innocent. They're not. But I've
had madnesses with with one recently.
Not someone that I was trying to get
with. I'm not going to get into it
either, but I know what they're like.
I've got life experience. I just simply
don't care anymore to talk about it. So,
when when you have people like this
stupid account, PJ's B. I was like, hold
on. Do these people actually have life
experience? Do these people actually
leave the house because they can't do
the way that they're defending women the
way they do? They literally can't
do. They just sit there and defend them.
I don't know. It's It's got to be
autism. It has to be autism. Like look
statement right here. It's so white
nighty. I know you don't like me using
the word s. Women need to be protected
as weirdos like you walking the street.
Okay. I'm a weirdo walking the street.
Whatever. And what about what they do?
And don't say, "Oh, they reject you."
No, no, no, no, no. Look, what about what they do?
Exactly. You got to say, "Oh, probably
what you feel is good against you." You
come across as very I come across as
very unlikable, but guess what, Joe?
I've got loads and loads of friends. I
don't need to come on YouTube every day
hating on people that I don't know. Am I
the one that's coming on YouTube every
single day hating on people that I don't
know? No. These people do
though. You're the one. No, no, no.
We're not We're talking about generally.
We're not talking about them approaching
and me approaching weapons. We're talking
generally. No, we're talking generally.
You know what I don't understand about
them? And I don't care. Listen, I've got
I've got this 1920 world. I can get
something. I don't care about that. What
I don't understand about these people,
right, is that they moan and winch that,
oh, they can't find someone. Oh, we
can't find someone. No, no, no, no, no,
no, no, no. Can't find someone. And then
you know when they get offers they turn
into they're a normal person. They're a
person. Yeah. And then then they get
with someone that's bad and then they
also bad. How do I know this? Cuz I've
got life experience. I know these
things. You know what I'm saying, bro? I
know I know these [ __ ] things.
You're generalizing them like they all
have the same traits and personalities.
They literally have the same traits and
the same personalities. They literally
are exactly the same. See, the thing is
you you might think that I'm being a bit
difficult and you might think I'm being
awkward. They literally are exactly the
same, you know, and now and now and and
now you're gonna like make make all the
same. They literally are all the same.
They're all NPCs. They all do the same
stuff. They all have the same excuses.
They all go for the same people. They
are literally the same. This is what I
used to say to nonslegs. This is
literally what I used to say to
nonslegs. They're NPCs.
you. It's like when you go out in this
country, you see the same women, the
same guys, the same [ __ ] guys. No,
I'm not proving how deluded I am. I'm
pro, okay? I'm literally telling you
what I'm experiencing. I'm literally
telling you what I've seen when I go
outside the house. They are literally all the
same. They all have an evil side to
them. Yeah. Obsessing over surely. Well,
guess what, Dex? But I don't have a I
don't have a channel on me like that
virgin does. you know. Um, okay. How how
am I back with her? Um, do you want me
to know how I'm back with her? Cuz she's
also a [ __ ] as well. She also acts
entitled. Yes, she does. And and I was
telling Antman about this as well. I was
telling Antman. Yes. Whatever you say
PJ's bought about maybe about 20 years
ago. But if you go out in this country,
you would know what it's like. You've
got no Trust me. I I might be younger
than you. I assume I'm younger than you.
I've got more life experience than you
will ever ever ever have and I've spoken
to more women than you ever have and you
probably ever will because I ain't gonna
stop. Yes, she is a [ __ ] The 1920 or
Oh, what? So, you think just because
somebody has sex with you, just because
somebody sucks your dick? That's No,
they're a [ __ ] as in they're entitled. I
get the same vibe from them. And I was
telling Ant-Man about this as well. I
was telling Ant-Man about this. I was
saying, "Listen, yeah, it's all well and
good. the person comes around, I get
what I want, but I still get this
entitled vibe from
them. Yeah, they are all the same.
Literally, every single one of them,
trust me. You know, since having this
new phone, I have had they're NPCs. They're
NPCs. There's nothing else to say about
them. They're NPCs. Since having this
new phone, I have had
101 101 contacts on my phone and load
and literally not one single woman has
proved me wrong.
All the Americans are the same. All the
English are the same. They are literally
all the same depending on what country
they're from. And call me deluded all
you want, bro. I can take it. I don't
care. Yeah, I can't even have sex. Okay,
bro. Yeah, you Yeah, I can't have sex.
Okay. So, to answer your question, Joe,
that 19year-old is a [ __ ] So,
yeah. They did. They just have this
entitled attitude. Anyone that goes out
and deals with them would know what
they're like. They're all the same.
You'll never get some The day I meet
somebody like they were they were back
in the 1980s or I'd say I'm wrong. As
soon as I meet somebody that's not like
that, I'm wrong. But I've never been
shown different. So, how can you speak
if you've not been shown different?
You'd be lying to yourself. Anyways,
we're not going to go on about this
anyways, bro. We just agree to disagree.
But yeah, just because you you're date
someone or you get head from someone or
you have sex with someone, it doesn't
mean it's like, okay, I'll give you an
example that USA is I'll give you an example of
entitlement. She said that it's my lucky
day. [ __ ] her [ __ ] saggy loose ass
[ __ ] [ __ ] when she's the one that
got [ __ ] a steak and a drink out of
me. No, it's your lucky day, [ __ ] You
know, that's what I'm saying. It's it
it's a sense from entitlement. The
discs, I'm not talking about them
anymore. Yeah, I only get head because I prefer head. Simple.
Uh I don't [ __ ] talk about that.
[ __ ] I just I just come on here
sometimes and talk about how much of a
virgin he is. Dex, that's it. But
yeah, but no, they are literally they
are literally literally all the same.
The only time they're not the same is
when they're in their 40s or 50s.
Actually, sorry, let let me let me
retract my statement. The only time that
they're not different is when they're in
their 40s and 50s. Sorry, I was actually
going to say 30s, but they still come to
their 30s, too. So,
yeah, they are literally all the same
unless they're in their 40s or 50s.
Modern day women, let's just say, are all the
same. Hey, guess what? I was speaking to
this woman from Scotland and she seems a
bit cool. She seems a bit okay. But
guess what, Joe? She's
transgender. Yeah, you just sound like a
white knight. You're the most weirdest
guy I've ever come across. I'm being
serious. Maybe that might be the
problem. You little white knight. This
is what I'm saying. You're white knight
defending women. Yet you don't get
women. This is what is wrong with this
society, bro. There's so many simps and
so many white knights that they just
defend women. Even though women don't
like them, Joe, they still defend them.
It's mad. They literally just defend
them. But women don't like them. Like
this PJ, I guarantee you any money, bro,
I get more [ __ ] than him. And they
they don't have It's got to be It's got
to be a condition. It's got to be a
condition that people were born with. I
can't see the reason just to defend
people based on their gender. But these
people do it. These people do it. again
or they just have no life experience. We
probably had no life experience. No, it
was somebody that messaged me when that
Twitter thing went
up. Yeah. Okay. How How do I know you're
not in a relationship? Because if you
was in a relationship, you would know
what women are like and you wouldn't be
sat here defending them. You would not
be sat here defending them the way you
do because you would literally know what
they're like in 20 25. That's how I know
you're not in a relationship.
You're a white guy. People that are
actually in relationships don't defend
women the way you do. They don't. They
just don't say anything or they just be
like, "Oh yeah, they're all the same."
Cuz they generally generally are all the
same. They generally generally are
exactly all the
same. Cuz if they weren't all the same,
right, when you've gone out and you've
got people's numbers, it would be
different. Okay, let me get Okay, you
you say that women are not the same, Joe.
Yeah, even even French women are all the
same. If you ever meet a French woman,
what will happen is they do exactly the
same stuff. French women, this this is
going to sound so mad to somebody that's
not done this. Every single time you go
out, they will do exactly the same stuff
in exactly the same way because they're
all the same. They're NPCs.
That is not love and isn't how most of
society goes about things. Yeah, but
that doesn't change the fact that
they're all the Why would I stick to
one? They're all the
same. They generally are all the same.
French women are all the same as well.
They're all the same. And it's like
Americans are all the same. Um, English
are all the same. They are literally all
same unless they're in their 50s.
So that's how I know you're not in a
relationship. Sorry about that. What a
bit. You're telling me I've never been
in love. Self injection. You got You got
me confused with yourself. You've got me
confused with yourself, buddy. Again, a
lot of people on here have got their
lives confused with mine
lads. So yeah, they literally are all
the same. Like the games they play, the
stuff they do, they literally are all
exactly the same. All got [ __ ] attitudes
as well. But people on YouTube still
defend them. It's just one of them fingers groups. Yeah.
Yeah. They are all exactly the same.
If uh oh, imagine you what?
Yeah, exactly. Or or imagine being a
poor guy out there and have to deal with
uh or deal with these women that have
got insanely st insanely high standards
that have attitude problems. Imagine
being a poor guy as well having to go
out and deal with these women with these
attitude problems and their [ __ ]
Nah, you wouldn't say that, would you?
Cuz you defend [ __ ] women all the
time. So imagine being that grey.
Imagine having to go into a nightclub
and having to deal with their [ __ ]
attitude. You wouldn't say that though,
would you? cuz it's not licking women's
asses. We'll keep our opinions to ourselves,
buddy. These people, you can tell this
person right here gets no [ __ ] The
way he defends women, right? The way he
defends women. Yeah. You can just tell
that he's not in a relationship. You
know, they think they're good trolls,
but they're not good trolls because
they're just white knives. I go for
saying he's never had a woman. People
that genuinely defend women the way this
guy does. People is people that's never
had women. They have no life experience.
Probably a lot of them are still
virgins. Because if you went out in the
real world, you would know exactly what
they're like. It's like seeing what the
sky is like when you go outside. When
you go out and you see exactly what
they're like, you wouldn't be defending
them anymore. But these people still
defend them because they don't get them.
You know, most of these people, they,
you know, they're in their 30s, they're
in their 40s, they don't leave their
house, and even if they do leave the
house, they don't even speak to women.
They don't know anything about life.
Especially in 2025, this is why they
they sit there and defend women. And and
and the thing is, Grezy, they think by
sitting there and defending them, a
woman's going to automatically appear
and give them sex. That's their you
don't understand, Grezy, that that
that's their actual goal. Their actual
goal is to defend them thinking that
that will get them women. I swear to
God, bro, like these little white
knights, you see them in real life as
well. They actually think that defending
them is is going to get them, but it's
not going to get them. It's
madness. They literally look for their opportunity. They're
opportunists. They literally just wait for anyone.
You're just that unlucky. Um, I could
have been in a relationship about three,
four times and no, 95% of the world have
not been in a relationship. Stop making
up statistics because I just told you
about your white night ass. I've had
many chances to be in a relationship and
I I have a chance right now to be in a
relationship if I want to, but I don't
want to be. So, at least I'm not unlucky
as you older than 20 [ __ ] seven
happen to s over women. I can't be as
unlucky as you, buddy. That will never
be me, bro. I will never be that guy
where I have to come on YouTube and
defend women. I will never be so much of
a loser. The day that I'm so much of a
[ __ ] loser, I have to come on YouTube
under a fake
account. Being too much of a loser, I
will start looking at my own life. I'll
literally get that mirror and start
looking at myself. I could never be so
much of a loser where I have to defend a
gender just because they're a c just
gender. No, that's a matter, bro.
I'll never be a loser like that, bro.
Never. Never be so much too much of a
loser as you. And you're talking about
relationships, buddy. You're not even in
a relationship. I got a [ __ ]
yesterday. You're still a virgin again.
You got yourself confused with me. I
don't know why these people keep getting
their like theirelves confused with me,
bro. It's a [ __ ] It's mad.
Yeah, they're not okay for you either, bro.
They're not okay either for you. That's
why you're still a [ __ ] virgin,
bro. That's why you're still a virgin.
You have to defend women. You're a [ __ ]
loser. Yeah. Imagine having to defend
women. Oh my god. Madness. I could never
imagine being so much of a loser. You're such a
loser. Oh my
god. Doesn't matter what I have to
offer. You don't need to know what I
have to offer a woman. We're not talking
about what what I have to offer women. I
just think that they're all the
same. It's boring. They're like NPCs.
They're like NPC characters. Have you
ever Have you ever played Star Wars,
right? And you ever seen them little
what what the [ __ ] were they called now?
Them them druids. Them droids. Was it
Was it Drews? It was Drews. No, they
were Drews. They were called Drews.
They're little white things. And they go
around like [ __ ] ants, bro. And
they're all the same. That's literally
what every single woman is like. They
have the same mindset, the same way, the
same outlook. They are literally all the
same. I don't need to get bitter or hate
about it. They literally are exactly the
same. Same games, same piss taken, same
attitude, same entitlement, even what
you get, what you want. They're
literally exactly the same. And to be
honest with you, I think we should
basically just leave it here because how
am I ever going to make people in their
30s and 40s that don't leave their house
understand? They're never going to
understand. I'm wasting my time and I'm
wasting your time as well. Get some life experience.
So yeah, there's no
points [ __ ] So yeah, there's no point
trying to explain to people they ain't
got a life any life experience in this
day and age.
See, this is what I'm saying. This is
exactly what I'm saying. Career again,
you got no life.
Yeah, women don't like me, but I've had
more women than you. I know. It's a
madness, isn't it? I've had more women
than you in it. Career prospects are
very important. Again, lack of life
experience. Again, this is exactly what
I'm saying. Oh, no. No. Listen, I'm not
saying these people have never had life
experience. They've had life
experiences. Again, you're talking about
yourself, PJ Monro. You're still a
virgin. And that's why you defend women
because you're the weirdo virgin that
has to come online defending women
because you don't get them. This is what
I'm saying. Career prospects are very
important. Again, lack of life
experience. This is exactly what I'm
talking about. These people have got no
modernday life experience. They don't
know nothing. They literally literally
literally don't know nothing about life.
You remember before, right? Back when I
was at my mom's. Yeah. And there's like,
oh, once you once you live once you um
once you once you live by yourself,
Yeah. then once you live by yourself,
you know, it'll be easier. But a man
lived by himself. And guess what? It was
the same [ __ ] They got no life
experience. They literally have no life.
These people are living in the ' 90s,
brother. I wouldn't even say the 80s.
These people are living in the [ __ ] ' 90s,
man. They have got no [ __ ] life
experience at all. I've never known such
lack of life experience. It's like me
when I was 20, 21. They actually have no life
experience. They literally have no life
So you think suddenly if you live by
yourself and you live by yourself and
you have career prospects then all of a
sudden all of a sudden you're going to
women are going to stop being [ __ ] Oh
my god. You have no life experience. You
have no like grieving. Okay. Let me ask
you this then. Do you remember back when
I used to live with Laney? Back when I
used to live with the dog, people always
used to say to me, "Oh, you need to move
out. Nobody wants to be with somebody
that lives with their mama that lives
with Laney. Do you remember that or do
you not?" And guess what? I moved out
and I was facing the same [ __ ]
problems. Okay. Yeah, I got the same
now, but I was saying [ __ ] problems
again. It's lack of life experience.
These people don't know
nothing. Okay. Okay. Of course, careers
and houses, etc. won't matter because
you ain't okay. I'll give you an example
again, right? There's a reason Big
weirdo. 99% of 99% of the internet.
Okay, there's literally, bro, this
community consists of
0.0000001 people. Where have you got 99%
from? Bro, there's barely 50 There's
barely 40 people in this community. No,
99% of the people don't think I'm a
weirdo. Only you little YouTube virgins
do. So, yeah, these people have got
absolutely no life experience. It's
class comedy. It is literally Clark
comedy. Class comedy. It's literally
literally literally. And you know what,
Grezy? I've actually proven it with my videos as
well. I've actually proven it with my
videos as well, Greavesy. I've proven
with my videos,
too. I've proven it with my videos. when
you try to strike up a conversation with
somebody and they pretend they've got
boyfriends. I mean, that's enough.
That's enough evidence right there, you
know? And I I've showed you these videos
as well. 1 million people on Twitter
think you're a weirdo. Anyways, I'm
blocking these little retards now.
Anyways, I'm wasting enough time talking
to them. [ __ ] these
spatics. Yeah, I've wasted enough
time. Yeah, Greensy, you're another one.
You've got absolutely Why am I
explaining myself to people? I've got no
life experience. I'm wasting my time.
I'm literally wasting my time. I mean,
you know, I only prove that with the approach to
videos. I'm out here like making noise
to people that ain't got no life
experience. What the [ __ ] are you doing
with yourself, man? Have a Have a
literally just told me I just told myself that now.
Yeah. Yeah. I mean, I proved all of my
points right with these approaching
videos. I've actually got um some more
approaching videos when you try to
strike up a conversation. Yeah. And see
the thing is greasy, right? What you say
and what these people say and what
people on Reddit say is completely
different to real life. It's completely
completely different to real
life. You know, you got you got what
people say on the internet, right? And
you got and then you got real life. So
on the internet people, oh, women go for
this, women go for this, women go for
that, women go for this, women go for
that. And then as soon as you go and you
try to strike up a conversation with
somebody, they pretend they've got a
boyfriend. So it's like what you hear
online versus what you experience in
real life does literally not match. They
don't match. It doesn't matter what form
it is or whatever it is, internet,
whatever it is, it doesn't match. It
literally does not match what people say
on the internet because the reality is
internet isn't when when well when
people give dating advice on the
internet it's like fairy tale. It's like
Disneyland. It's it's it's not real.
It's it's like a fairy tale land. And
then when you actually go out in real
life they all give attitude and pretend
they got violence. But what you will
understand is in real life you'll never
hear real life in fantasy world.
fantasy world as oh women can never do
no go wrong. They're all innocent. But
then when you actually go out and you
actually interact with them, you will
know exactly what they're like. And
that's what happens when you go out in
real life. How do I know? Cuz I've done
it. So real life people pretend they got
boyfriends. Real life people pretend
people have attitude. That's real life
on the internet. Oh, women go for goals.
um you know good personality. This is
all false because again when you apply
it in the real world you get shown completely
different. Again you got fantasy land
and then you got real and then you got life. You
know I'm sure you heard all this stuff
before on you know on Reddit.
So I don't think anyone's going to
persist to really give dating advice
because they don't know
anything. Okay. What? Okay. Let me ask
you this question briefly. Say that I
really wanted a relationship and I
didn't want to shout. I just want a relationship.
Yeah. Okay. And I go right I go out
today in the shopping center. What's
Thursday? And I tried and I tried to
strike up a conversation with someone.
What do you think they're gonna say? I
can show you some new approaching videos
if you want. Well, they were like from
last week before I started saying
them. What do you think they're going to
say? So then it just contradicts
everything other people say. It
literally contradicts everything. your life
experiences in their advice contradicts your life
experiences. I think that's a banger. I
think that is an absolute banger of a
word to say. I think you can't say it
perfectly. Their your experience their
advice contradicts your
experiences. Yeah, I think that's it.
Yeah, I think that's I think that's a
perfect way to describe it.
But you think, I sure don't get messed
around by these [ __ ] I do, but I
just don't say anything anymore cuz I don't really
care, you know? I know what I need to do. So,
yeah. Anyways, I need to go anyways. I'm
busy. I need to make myself another
[ __ ] tea. It's going cold. some catching it