I'm not even looking forward to this
roast today. Not one thing, it's
another. Boring. That's boring. That
is That is [ __ ] boring. That
is. It's not one thing, it's
another. I'll get into that anyways. [ __ ] in
it. One thing is [ __ ] another, man. The hell?
Um, started waking up.
These dirty mood swings again. And I've
not had them in ages, man. Only time I
used to have them is when I used to deal
with women and [ __ ] drinking. I ain't
had them for
ages. These nasty [ __ ]
moods. They're [ __ ] horrible, man. I swear to
God, they [ __ ] are, man.
Reddit is no good for you as well, man.
Because like this stupid [ __ ] was like,
"Oh, have you ever bought a woman
flowers?" And they literally just ignore
like everything you say and just make
everything a pity party for women. Like,
if you know you're right, you don't
argue. Why argue? That's no good for the
mental health. If you know you're right
about something, why are you going to
sit there and argue? What's the whole
point of arguing? Are you trying to like
get people to understand your
experiences? Because they're not going
to. So why are you sat there arguing
with people? Just woke up with these nasty mood
swings. Oh yeah, and the washing
machine's packed up as well. Yay. More
money spent. They'll be out on the
street. They can stay out on the street.
I'm done with them. They can stay out on
the street all they like. All day long.
I'm done with him. I shouldn't have even
went out last week. I wish I didn't go
out last week. If anyone says to me,
"Yeah, before I ever die, what's your
biggest regret in life?" I think it was
me going out last week. It [ __ ] the
whole routine up. It literally [ __ ] my
whole mood up cuz I've had to deal with
women again that are all the same. Even
though people claim that they're not all
the same, they are all the [ __ ] same.
I literally wish I didn't go out. I wish
I literally stayed in. Stupid me, man. I
don't know what what prompted me after
five, six weeks to go out again when
it's they're all the same. Same women,
same people, same outlook. What the
[ __ ] bro? What was I even thinking in
my head? They're they're going to be out
today. They can stay out on the street.
I'm done with him. Which I was done with
him five, six weeks ago. I'm done with
him. I hate him. [ __ ] [ __ ] they
are. Yeah, I hate them. They're all the
same. I put them all into one bracket.
All into one bracket. That same bracket
that you put the TV on the wall on, I
put them I'll throw them all into one
bracket cuz they're all the [ __ ]
same. They're all the
same. We're not all the same. I've been
saying it for years, man. But it weren't
until I really like met a lot to know
that they're all the same, you
know? But yeah, maybe down, lad.
Yeah, I've seen them years ago, bro.
They're nothing new. They're old. Them
pranks. I'm just sick of them. Me. I'm
sick of them. I wish I didn't go out
last week. Yeah. I went, you know, there
was one I went on a date yesterday with
this woman from Birmingham and I just
ditched her. I just ditched her. She was
like a three out of 10. Yeah. And um
yeah, she expected me to buy all the
drinks and all the food. I just ditched her.
I literally just ditched her. Like even
though there was a vibe and stuff, but
um I just ditched her. Not because she
was like three out of 10, it's cuz like
what? You're not going to pay for
anything? No. I'm so done with these
[ __ ] I went I went on a two dates in
the space of a week. I'm so done, bro.
You don't even believe. I'm so done.
Yeah. Yeah. You'd have sex with them,
but I'm not sat there buying drinks for
someone all day and buying food for
day. So, yeah. I'm done. Done anyways, bro.
It's going to be a year since I got laid
from approaches. What are you talking
about, bro? I got a [ __ ] literally
two weeks ago. What are you on
about? What the [ __ ] are you talking
about, bro? That doesn't even make any
sense. I got a [ __ ] like two weeks
ago. Uh, from the same person. And the
only reason I didn't have sex is cuz I didn't want
sex. What happened with Thailand? I'm still
going. So, yeah. No. So, yeah, man. Uh,
it [ __ ] up my whole mood, bro. I was
good. Like, I was eating in, stopping
drinking. I was stable. And ever since I
went out dealing with women again, bam,
I'm back to where I started. [ __ ]
man. You can [ __ ] off as well, you
weirdo. Like, you you I feel like I'm
going backwards now, bro. That's kind of
scary. I did cook a meal yesterday. I
cooked a T-bone steak with onion rings,
but I actually feel like I'm going
backwards. generally feel like I'm going
backwards, bro. Well, I was going
backwards. It's just the same old. It's
just the same old boring. They're
boring. They bore me,
bro. No, I'm not well, mate. I'm not
well at all. Sick of women. Bad
experiences with women
again. Shame on me for going out last
week, thinking that it was going to be
different. Thinking that it was going to
change. Yeah. Wishful thinking that
was. They're all the same. They're
literally all the same. They're all the
same. You need to get You need to get
laid, mate. You're probably still a
virgin. You need to get laid. I've had
more sex than you've had sex, Sunshine.
You need to get yourself laid. Get off
of YouTube. I come off of YouTube for 3
weeks, mate. You can't even take a day off YouTube,
son. You know what I'm saying? Speak for
yourself. Get off of YouTube. Look, you
answered your question, mate. There's so
many ladies on the street today. Okay,
get off of YouTube and go talk to them.
What are you doing on YouTube? What are
you doing on YouTube? I was off of
YouTube for [ __ ] 3
weeks. Who the [ __ ] is that bomb or
something? I don't know who this
is. Nah, I'm all right, mate. I don't
want nothing to do with women. They're
all the same. No, Grezy. Grievy actually
isn't, mate. No. Funny enough, it isn't
Griezy. Did you not listen to the live stream
yesterday? I gave up for five, six
weeks. I was doing my own thing. I
wasn't drinking. Didn't care about them.
But the point I'm trying to make to
YouTube is whenever you go out drinking
again, dealing with them again, you you
you go you go backwards. They're
absolute [ __ ] They're literally
all the same. Like you literally go
backwards. I lie. You go backwards. You
feel like you go backwards in your
routine, everything cuz of them. They're
[ __ ] I hate them. I generally do.
I don't know how people sit there and
defend them. It's mad. They're [ __ ]
mad. Like they're [ __ ] and then
you'll get people on like Reddit like
defending them, bro. It's [ __ ] crazy.
They're all the
same. I went on a date yesterday, Grezy.
Yeah. She's from Birmingham. She's about
a three out of 10. Yeah. Didn't care
about that. I was, "Okay, whatever. I
can't be picky." Then I bought a round.
Then I bought another round. Then she
wanted food. And you know what I done? I
ditched her. Yep. Said I was going to go
toilet. Didn't come back. Yep.
Well, he Well, I was in that Weather
Spoon yesterday, actually. Um, so I
don't think he proper proper banned me.
He just probably banned me for the
night. Yeah. He He ran to the manager. Little [ __ ]
Yeah. Yeah. I literally said I was going
to go toilet and I just [ __ ] off.
Yeah. Just ditched her. But that's not
cuz the way she looked or anything like
that. It's because like what? I'm not
going to sit here spending money all
day. You know what I'm saying? And then
it just w me up even more. Then I went
to the butchers and then Yeah. I I'm
done with them, bro. I'm done with them
there. It's a negative. Dating as a man
is a negative. Doesn't matter. No.
Doesn't matter how people tried to
sugarcoat it. I wish I never went out
last week, Grezy. Cuz we wouldn't be
here now having this rant. We literally
wouldn't be here now if I didn't go out
last week. I should have just stayed in.
Stayed in. You know, all women are the
same. It would always be the same. Ain't
no one can tell you different. The only
thing that can be different is different
experiences that you're never going to have.
So it's like this guy who's trying to
change my mind in a pub. 34. The manager
is 34. And he says, "That's my
experiences." He says, "Yes, it is my
experiences which I'm going to go by."
Yeah. It's my experiences which I'm
going to go
by. You know what I'm saying, bro? It
doesn't make sense. Your life is [ __ ]
mate. I I'm glad I hope I'm glad I make
you feel better about your life. I've
got more money than you. I've got more
friends than you. You're sat You're sat
on YouTube. You don't have a life. Oh,
actually, oh, wait one second. Let me
rephrase that. You don't have a life.
You're on YouTube. You're on YouTube.
You don't have a life. You said, "Hold
on. Wait. You just said, let me do that
again. Always makes me feel better about
my life." You ain't got a life. You live on
YouTube. Sorry, man. You just stuffed yourself in [Laughter]
there. You ain't got a life. You on
YouTube. You on YouTube, mate. I was off
of YouTube for two, three weeks. You
ain't got a life but YouTube. Think of
it, mate. Yeah, I remember. Right, LJ
literally deleted his channel, right?
And I would watch Monty's live streams
back occasionally. And guess what,
Grezy? You'd see the same spackers even
when the community is dead. Even when
the community is dead, you'll see the
same spackers. What life do they have?
Other than coming on here every day
trying to ruin other people's lives,
they ain't got a life. They don't even leave the
house. I'm going for a [ __ ] roast
dinner today at Mommy
F. Um, Grezy Mummy Laney. You understand, bro?
Yeah. Do you know what I'm
saying? But Grezy, bro, you missed me
for like five, six weeks, bro. You don't
know. You don't know the kind of stuff I
was doing. You don't know the kind of
stuff I was doing. As soon as you drink
again, as soon as you deal with women
again, or as soon as you gamble again,
bam, you go backwards. It's a negative.
It's a negative. We hear about negatives
all the time. [ __ ] gambling,
drinking, [ __ ] eating [ __ ] But we
never hear about women being a negative,
which mate, it is a negative. It is a
negative. It pissed me off last week. I
wish I I wish I didn't go out, bro. And
I'm a patient person as well. I'm sick
of them. I am [ __ ] sick of them. You
re I'm literally sick of them, bro. Sick
to the stomach of them. You don't understand.
Yeah. Yeah. It ain't good, bro. It's not
good life in England.
Eh, I was just eating in just like binge
watching stuff. Just didn't care about
women. Weren't asked. That's why people
thought I changed my [ __ ] mindset. I
don't change my mindset. I just don't I
just didn't care about him, bro. You
know what I
mean? Uh, no. I lost 80 pound two days
ago. Didn't get a bonus. Well, no,
sorry. I did get a bonus on Eye of Horus and then [Music]
um and then um one
sec. Wait, what is that? Yeah, so I lost 80 pound,
bro. I'm done with it anyways. I'm
booking a holiday in two days. [ __ ]
this. I'm out of here, mate. I'm done. be
black. Yeah, I was I
was slim bro. Are you the guy from
Scotland? Bro, I was literally Listen to
me, bro. Yeah, I didn't I didn't drink. Yeah.
Um, bro, like I was off for like five,
six weeks drinking, gambling. I I g I
didn't gamble. I don't think I gambled
for ages. I didn't drink for ages. Yeah.
I had my friend come around, suck my
dick and that's it. And all about like I
had that, bro. And you know the maddest
thing is, bro, I gave up with women and
drinking for weeks and weeks and weeks
and weeks and weeks. I was stable. I
used to get a takeaway every Saturday.
I'd eat in all through Saturday. And
bro, I was the stablest I could have
been. I went out last week, bank
holiday, bam, all these problems come
back again. The mood swings, the bad
experiences, the depression from
alcohol. Bro, I wish I never went out. I
literally never went out. And how rare
is that? Like my friend even said, "I
don't think you should drink. Like,
you've been off with me for ages." And I
wish I [ __ ] never
now. I wish I never, mate. I wish I just
stayed in or done something else or went
swimming or something with the electric
bike. I wish I just done something else, bro. You know,
so what a life, eh?
Yeah, that's it, bro. And and you know
what it is? Yeah. It's not because she
was a three out of 10. No, to be honest,
she was a nice person and we was vibing
and it was a laugh. And that's how I
know that her last state wasn't me, bro.
Because I know how to deal with people.
I've met loads of people. I've got loads
of friends. Like, I know how to I'm not
going to say that I'm an extrovert all
of the time, but I know how to deal with
people. So that date compared to the
last date, it was a big
difference, you know, but you know,
someone's and I didn't leave them
because they were a three out of 10. I
know, I know. Shocking, eh? They're a
bit fat. They had tattoos, but Oh, [ __ ] well. Sure. Yeah.
Can't believe this, bro.
Yeah. Sick of it, mate. I'm sick of
them. I'm actually sick of him, Slim.
Actually sick of him. You don't understand,
lad. I'm actually sick of these women in this
country. You always seem to go backwards
when you go drinking and dealing with women
again. Let me see how much money I have.
You see anything? You
can't. I don't understand how this
[ __ ] machine is packed up. I honestly
don't understand how this machine is packed
up. Honestly, I don't. How the [ __ ] has
this [ __ ] machine [ __ ] packed
up? I really don't understand, mate.
Right, let me buy this [ __ ]
machine. Have to buy a new [ __ ]
washing machine. It's [ __ ] [ __ ] up, eh?
Mate, did you just listen to what I was
saying? I said my best life was when I
gave up with women and drinking. I was
literally living my best life. As soon
as I went back to drinking and women
again, I'm miserable. Miserable again.
Miserable. They make you
miserable. But no one ever says that
because it's never the woman's fault, is
it? [ __ ] them,
bro. I'm going to buy it, but I'm not
putting no gas and electric in. I'm
going to buy
it. Putting no gas and electric in this
month. Hand off. Huh?
That's it, bro. [ __ ] washing
machine's packed up, mate. My fridge
packed up, then my [ __ ] washing
machine packed up. I had it for [ __ ]
10 years to be
fair. What a life, eh? Better better
next month. Hopefully, we have a better
month next month. Uh
yeah, women are evil, big boss. They
generally generally are evil and they
generally generally are all the same. I
wish I didn't go out last week. I really
wish I didn't go out last week. They're
all the same. They're literally all the
same. I have one to I have one to I have
yet one to prove me
wrong. Yeah. The day I went on
yesterday, they were from Birmingham. So
I had to listen to their [ __ ] accent
all [ __ ] day, mate. [ __ ]
me. Nah, not humans are evil. Women are
evil. No, no, no, no, no, no, no. Women
are evil. Not humans. I'm a human and
I'm not evil. Women are evil. Don't try
and change it as, "Oh, men are as well."
No. We're talking about women, bro.
Women are evil. End of. Women are evil.
Cuz I'm a human and I'm not evil. So
women are evil. Every single one of
them, I put them in the same bracket. I
put each and every single one of them in
the same bracket that you put on the TV
to put on the wall. I am generalizing. I
am sat here and I am generalizing. Yes. So yeah,
right. Go skydiving. Never would I ever
go skydiving, bro? I love basketball. I
love basketball. I love swimming. Would
never go sky. I'm I'm I'm I'm going on
holiday soon. I'm going on holiday soon
again. That's what I need to do. I need
to I need to leave this country. It's
depressing, you know. It's enough to get anyone down.
Women are so evil. But you know the
thing is big boss, they claim that they
can't find a normal guy, but then look
at all the [ __ ] they do. It's crazy,
isn't it? Look at all the [ __ ] they
do. Look at all the [ __ ] that they do
when they do meet a normal person. It's
mad. But then they moan that all men are
the same. [ __ ] them, man. They're all entitled
[ __ ] All the
same. Literally all the same. Every
single one of them.
Right. I know it's cuz I went out last
week. That's what happened, bro. It It
was going out last week for four or five
weeks, bro. I was good. I was eating in
doing weekly food shopping, having
hobbies, going out on the old ebike. I
didn't think of any of this stuff. As
soon as I went out again and I dealt
with him again, I feel like I'm back in the same
position. Generally think I'm back in
the same position that I feel like I'm
back. As soon as you deal with them
again, you're back. You don't realize
how bad and evil they are until you
actually deal with them. It's such
mad. It's [ __ ] madness, bro.
And I hope you're going to come to this court date,
Grezy. Yeah. You don't know how much
evidence I've got on these people that
are trying to play the victim. Mate, as
soon as I get that trial date, I'm going
to give you the date and you can come.
I'm that confident. I'm that confident.
So, if this stuff if this thing actually
goes to trial, bro, um I'll give you the
date and everybody on YouTube's
welcome. Oh, mate, you don't know the
amount of [ __ ] I've got on these people. Trust
me, you know, and sometimes it's got to
be that way, bro, until people learn you
stop coming on YouTube. You stop annoying
people. Stop annoying people every
day, you know, and that's
it. Maybe it's true about your
disabilities. Your brain seems to be
missing something. Self projection.
Talking about yourself,
buddy. Talking about yourself there,
buddy. I don't have any disabilities.
talking about yourself there, buddy.
Boo. Get me confused with yourself
again. It's not good.
order to this washing machine.
Yeah. Yeah. You actually don't leave the
house, do you, Greavves? There's nothing
wrong with not leaving the house, man. I
was living my best life when I gave up
with drinking, gave up with women. I
felt the best I ever was, but people
might see see it was boring and
that, you know, and do you remember when
people Well, I don't think he was on the
live stream that time, but people Grevy
used to say to me like, "Oh, like, oh,
so did you admit you was wrong about
women? Did you did you admit you was
wrong about women?" I was like, "No, I'm
not wrong about women. They're all
[ __ ] but I just don't care about it
anymore." That's what I said to them. Like, literally
So yeah, I do learn from the same
mistakes. I don't learn from the same
mistakes, James. Mate, I didn't go out
for five, six
weeks. I stopped having takeaways. I
used to get a takeaway every
week. Every Saturday, I used to get a takeaway. every
Saturday. Um, didn't go out, didn't go
out, didn't go out drinking, just went
out on the old
ebike. It was good, man. Life was good.
Soon as you deal with women again, oh
boy, you go backwards. I literally made myself a
t-bone. Um, I made myself a t-bone steak
yesterday with onion
rings. It was lush, greasy. It was very
lush, you know.
But I think you could go out dealing
with women. You could go out dealing
with women. If you got a holiday booked
in it, Grezy, because at least you can
say, "Oh, I've only got five weeks to
go. I'm out of here. I've only got six
weeks to go. I'm out of here." It's like
what Ant-Man does. He knows that he's
got something to look forward to. I
ain't got anything booked yet. At least
you can say, "Oh, well, I'm gone in a
few weeks, so it doesn't matter." That's
another way you could do it.
You know, that's another way you could
do it because at least you know you're
not going to be here for much longer. This
country. So, I mean, that's a way you
could do it, I
guess. From this [ __ ] country with these
[ __ ] women. [ __ ] country. [ __ ] women. Something to
do. This country is just [ __ ] It's
[ __ ] [ __ ] mate. I wish I was born
somewhere like [ __ ] Thailand.
Yeah. Oh, that's where we're at,
man. Yeah. Yeah. I don't really get
takeaways much anymore. Gia cooking nice
pork chops, nice
steak, you know. It's actually good.
It's actually good cooking, you know.
It's actually good for your mental
health. Even not not just like cooking
healthy food, but it's just something to
do. Cooking is quite good. You know, you
should try it,
man. You save a lot of money,
too. And every Saturday, I just get an
ebike to go to KFC and then come back.
Simple. You should try cooking, bro. You
should get into it. It's hard at first.
It takes discipline at first, but once
you do it, bro, you're never going to
want to eat out again. You're never
going to want to eat out again.
until like every
week. Have you tried [Laughter]
it. No rest for the wicked,
eh? Hey, Grezy. No rest for the wicked, mate. Huh? [Music]
And what's that? What's that
achievement, man? What's that
achievement? Yeah. What's that
Anyways, I'm gone.