There we go. Just sorted a new channel
out. Want to change the avatar purple
that. Yeah. Good luck trying to find me
out. [ __ ] stalker.
Oh yeah. I made a new
channel. Oh me. Oh,
mate. There we go. Lovely. So, I just
working on a new
channel. Now, I think this [ __ ]
found me through [ __ ] Instagram.
That's how he found me. they somehow can
like track your combos, but obviously I
won't be giving anyone my new channel on
Instagram now. So, good luck trying to find
me now. Definitely not. They found me through
Instagram. [ __ ] stalkers. Ain't got a
life. I ain't got no
life. Yeah, it shouldn't find me now anyways.
Yeah, sorry about that. My friend on
Instagram. Yeah, he Yeah, he found me on
uh he found me on Instagram. He did. Definitely did. There we
go. I can't delete it now. Anyways, no bother,
man. No bother. Yeah, man. I made a new
channel. Get up there. No one's going to find it
now. There's no way of them literally finding it.
These retards are going to find
it. They're absolute stalkers, aren't
they? Are there,
bro? Ay, ladder. that Instagram
thing. Am I so lonely? You have to talk to a
fridge. Yeah, bro. I'm very lonely.
Yeah, very lonely, bro. Very, very
lonely. But I went on two dates in the
in the past week. I've been out with my
friends. Yeah, I'm very lonely.
But you people must be lonely though.
Stalking people on YouTube every day.
You can't get off of YouTube every day.
All right, bro. I spoke to a fridge for like 15
minutes. You You sit on YouTube every
day, man. Can't get off it. What's that
say about your life? Hey, I I put my
hands up, though. It I put my hands
up. So, let's let's ask you people. Why
do you do this every day anyways? Why do
you come on YouTube stalking people? Is
it because your envy of anyone that's
got a better life than you? Is it
because people are better looking than
you? They've got more in life than you?
Like why do you sit online every day doing
this? Like why I'm I'm actually curious.
Like I'm actually asking a serious
question. Why do you do this? You call
everyone else skin. You call everyone
else this. You call everyone else that.
Yeah. You sit online every day. You
can't get off of YouTube to save your
life if your life depend on it. Like
bro, get real, man. What is wrong with
your lives on here, please?
It's [ __ ] p.
I don't even have a bed. I don't have a
bed. I've got a£500 bed. Yeah. You don't
know what I have. Yeah. How do I not
have a bed? I've got a£500 bed.
Yeah. I was staying at my friend's
house. You don't know anything. How do I
not have a bed, you [ __ ] I've got a£500 bed.
Yeah, get it right. You know what is
there to envy, bro? More money than you,
better looking than you, got more of a
life than you, got a holiday booked
unlike you, bro. Listen, if there was
nothing on here to envy, then you people
wouldn't be on YouTube. You, bro, do you
not understand? Yeah, I was off of
YouTube for 3 weeks. If there's nothing
to envy, why are you on YouTube every
day with no life? It's it's a simple
question. Yeah, that could you could
give a simple answer to. Why are you on
YouTube every day in your life and you
can't answer it, bro? So, I'm right. So,
the bed, bro, I'm not showing you
nothing. I've got money right here and
I'm not showing you nothing. If you're
so good-look, why are you single? Well,
you are single. Okay, bro. Bye-bye now.
Not getting into these pointless
arguments. Yeah. You don't know what
people have what people don't have. Stop
talking about people that you don't
know. Silly bollocks. Have you ever
heard that? Staying around someone
else's house, bro. [ __ ] man. Come on
now. Please. Stop
embarrassing. I don't have a bed. Oh,
[ __ ] hell. I've got a 500 bed, mate.
And I've had it for two years. Try
again. Try again. I ordered a new
washing machine as well. Try again.
Like literally, bro, try again,
man. You really need to stop talking
about people that you don't know.
Cuz you say you got a girlfriend but
you're on YouTube. How? That makes
sense, is it? You got a girlfriend but
you on YouTube, bro. I was off I was off
YouTube for 3 weeks when I had my friend
[ __ ] come around. But you got Yeah.
But you're on YouTube every day. Yeah.
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. What you
doing, man? But you're on YouTube every
day. Every day. Every day. Not even like
once a week. It's literally every day.
Oh boy. It's like every day is
it? Sad lives these people
lead? I pity them, bro. I really do pity
them. They bounce off their own lives.
[ __ ] hell. But it's not a problem,
bro. I just made a new account anyways.
You [ __ ] are going to find me. You
found me through Instagram. You literally
found through [ __ ] Instagram, bro.
Instagram. Don't think it's Reddit. It was definitely
Instagram. Yeah, cuz now no one can find
me. So, it's it's got to be that Instagram thing.
Yeah. What I'm going to do is a new
channel to put all my approaching videos up
on. I'm going to go on other like
communities and saying, "Listen, this is my channel.
people won't find me again. And that's
why I made another channel is because
you people ruin everything. You people
literally ruin everything. The whole
channel you hate. You ain't got a life.
That's why I made a new channel. It's
why I made a new channel to begin with.
Shame you found that one though, cuz I
like the name, but oh
well. It's not a problem, is
it? You know what I'm saying? Okay.
Well, what's my new channel then? Okay.
Okay. What's my new
channel? Oh, [ __ ] What's my new channel
then? I've got no clue. Tell me what my
new name Tell me what my new YouTube
channel is then, fatty. Tell me Tell me
what my new YouTube channel
is. Tell me what my new YouTube channel
is. Go on. Tell me what my new YouTube
channel is then. Let's see how smart you really are. Exactly.
Exactly. We will see you in an hour.
Yeah, of course we will, mate. And make
sure you comment as well. You know, you
found it through
Instagram. You found it through
Instagram. Yeah, you've got you've got a
real bed with your wife. Yeah, that's
why you're sat on YouTube stalking men
every day. Yeah, of course you are,
Fatty. Yeah, of course you are, Fatty.
That's why you're on YouTube every
single day stalking men, ain't you? Cuz
you done it to London Taylor as well,
mate. You don't have anything in your
life. You go around the internet
stalking men. You ain't got a life. You
done to LT as well. You ain't got
nothing. Literally nothing, mate. But a
but his face. That's all you have is a
but his face and a weight problem.
That's all you got, mate. You ain't got
no wife. You ain't got no nothing. So
when you when you find my um new
channel, yeah, make sure to comment on
it. You're not going to find it, mate.
You are not finding it. Trust me.
You found it through
Instagram. You found it through
Instagram. Mark my words. It was through
Instagram. You sad sad
bastard. God, you're
sad. Sad, mate. I say you really are
Yeah. Yep. I'll be stuck in rainy old
England. Yeah. You keep telling yourself that,
buddy. You keep telling yourself that,
Sad. How we doing, Mark? If that's the real
Mark, how you doing, man? And I had to I
made a new YouTube channel to get away
from these [ __ ] stalkers. To get away
from these [ __ ] hating [ __ ]
weirdos, bro. They [ __ ] follow me
everywhere, mate. I had to make a new [ __ ]
channel. And then they somehow found me.
Then I had to make another channel.
[ __ ] absolute weirdos, mate. These people
are weirdos. Stalkers. No
life. I think me and you, Mark, are the
only ones on here that's got a life. and
Timmyish. But I mean, in terms of like
actually going out, I think like we're
the only ones,
bro. Genuinely think we're like the only
ones. I ain't even joking, mate.
Seriously. Seriously, Mark, I think we are,
bro. It's crazy, Mark.
Crazy. It's [ __ ] It's [ __ ] autism,
isn't it? It's got to be autism with
these people, Mark. It's got to be
autism, lad. It's got to be autism with these
people. It's weird,
lad. Why are you on the beer? You drinking,
Grezy? Yeah. Yeah, I had a channel um
Greavvesy called Found My Mama and these
people found it so I had to make a new
channel. I had to make a new channel
because these weirdos found my new
channel so I had to make a new one. It
was called Found My Mama. You know, I
was dying to give you the [ __ ] um the
name of it, Grezy, but
[ __ ] Yeah. So, I've had to make a new one,
lad. Yeah, they're sados, mate.
So why you saying four pints only and
it's lunch and it's
lunch? Get a milkshake then? Was it hot
out there? I just made some I just made a pork
dinner. I made pork chops, vegetables, and and
chips. I'm recovering the best I can
from this foot injury. Is
it? Well, it's it's 90% better, but
still not 100%. That's why I was eating
some vegetables, just chilling, you
know. It was a nasty injury, Grezy. Nasty
injury. Yeah. I was just talking to my
friend on Instagram about women and
their their unrealistic
standards and they only want like top
10%. Even though like a lot of them are
monsters themselves and that they watch
too much of Love Island and that which
is something that I forgot about. Oh
yeah, Love Island. Love
Island. Yeah, Love Island.
Yeah, they go off Love Island. Yeah.
Yeah. That's what these women do. They
have unrealistic. And he was even
saying, yeah, that like, yeah, if
somebody claims they don't feel
like, yeah, bro, I had to make a new
channel. I had to make a new channel,
bro, cuz of these [ __ ]
weirdos again. I had to make another
channel cuz they found me and I don't
want these people following me.
Um he was like, "Oh, like maybe if they
don't feel the vibe, they should give
you another chance because you don't
always feel a vibe the first time
meeting somebody." Which is true because
I've met somebody the first time and I
didn't feel a vibe. It takes a while to
get to know someone we he was basically
getting that and I was like, I agree.
But with these women, they'll just go
out with somebody, have an unrealistic
expectation in their head, and if you
don't hit that unreal if you don't
um if you're not that ex uh that um
unrealistic expectation that they're
looking for, they just swerve you. And
that's that that's what it is because
yeah, like I said, I've not liked people
before. And then like I have then liked people. So
yeah, trust me. But they they're like,
"Oh, we want the top 10%. unrealistic
expectation. When you're not that, they
swerve you. Done. So that's what I was
basically saying in that fringe
video. So yeah,
man. But glad you liked it anyways,
man. Cuz I knew that if I made a new
channel, I'm not going to get these
haters. You might get a few people, but
you won't get these little stalking
jealous weirdos with [ __ ] autism
watching you every [ __ ] day like you
do in this community. which was why I
made a new channel to get away from
them. And obviously, I can't put
gambling videos on it because if I put
gambling videos on it, they're going to
find me because they're all gambling
addicts. So, but I don't think they'll
find me again. Fingers
crossed. So, I didn't even tell them I
made a new one. They still found me,
lad. They still [ __ ] found
me. Yeah, man. I had a couple of dates
last week. They were [ __ ] It reminded
me why I gave up for five, six
weeks. Yeah, it reminded me why I gave
up on women and just going out as much.
I'm sure you heard about the
story. Sure you have so many accounts,
bro. I I lose count, you know. So, but
yeah, it reminded me why I gave up for
five, six weeks. And he got these little
bastards on here [ __ ]
stalker. And the way I put it to this
guy is that if we had a six or seven out
of 10 women, we wouldn't turn them down.
They would turn down a 6, seven, 8, 10
out of guy. That's the difference. Their standards are
unrealistic. No, that's what I'm
saying. No, no, I went out um ghosting.
Yeah. Listen to this.
Yeah. I I'll tell the story again just
for you cuz I remember you. Yeah. So, I
went out um bank holiday, which was not
last week, the week before that. Sorry
if I'm boring. A lot of you've heard it.
I thought, "Oh, let me go out drinking."
I haven't been out for five, six weeks.
I was eating and saving money and then
just going out on the good old electric
bike, right? So, I thought, "Fuck it.
It's worth a try now because always told
to keep trying." went out the Friday,
went out the Saturday, got seven numbers
in total. Got three replies and one of
them approached me saying, "Oh, how good
looking you are. where gave me a number,
texted me every 2 minutes, we met the
week after," which was last week on a
Thursday. And do you know what this
[ __ ] said to me? Even though the date
was fine, it was like an hour. And even
though the conversation was fine, she
claimed that she didn't feel the vibe. I
was like, "Fuck this. I am so [ __ ]
done. I'm booking a holiday out of this
country. Then this other woman wanted to
meet me from Birmingham. She was better,
but she was literally like a three out
of 10 and she was just trying to use me
for like food and drinks. So then I just
ditched her because purely cuz she was
trying to use me, not because she was a ma.
So yeah, typical. She traveled a whole
hour ghosting. A whole hour and she
claimed that she doesn't feel the vibe.
Even though she approached me, even
though I'm above average looking, yet
she claims she don't feel the vibe. I'm
so dumb, bro. And do you know what made
it even worse as well? She was 32 years
of age, which means that she is lower
value than me because she's hit the
wall. She was like average. Five out of
10. I didn't really like her that much.
It's not the point. It's it's the
principle that bro, we have women now
that have hit the wall thinking that
they're better than you. 32 years of
age, you're like average looking. You
ain't getting loads of guys approaching
you. But then they will claim that they
can't find a normal guy. And then
they'll winge and moan and we have to
listen to their winging. Then on that
Thursday when they done that, I just
sent it, sent it, sent it. Same old
[ __ ] I've got a boyfriend. Then I met
this bra. We went on a date and that was
just bad for different reasons. She was
just trying to use me. But it's safe to
say that it's it's a waste of time
dating in this country, trying in this
country as far as I'm concerned.
But yeah, that's how sick in the head they are,
bro. That's how sick in the head they
are. Yeah, they're [ __ ] And no,
older women are as well, mate. It's only
It's not until they get into their 40s
they're different. It's not until they
get into their 40s, I'd say. Cuz look at
her. She was like 31, 32. She hit the
wall. I'm way higher value than her and
she still thinks he's better than me.
So, [ __ ] them, bro. That's why I gave
up, lad. That's why I gave up. I had my
friend come around like a few times and
that, but and then she went to Wales, so
she's a bit like bipolar, but
yeah. A proper waste of time this country
lad. Yeah, it is her loss. But remember
ghosting. Yeah, I don't care really. But
do you know what annoyed me is me
getting my time wasted? That's the bit
that annoyed me, bro. It's not like I
went out and loads of people said they
have a boyfriend because you're always
going to hear that [ __ ] But it's
the fact that they've actually
approached you and actually have wasted
your time. That was the annoying thing about it.
Um, but then like I said, bro, they're
going to moan and winge. They can't find
anyone. They will moan and winge and
moan and winge and moan and winge. They
can't find a normal person or they can't
find a decent person. And all the other
all the people that they come across are
domestic abusers and drug dealers, so
they say. But then when they actually go
on a date with a normal person, they
claim they can't feel a vibe, whatever
the [ __ ] that means. But anyways, yeah.
Same old it lad. This country will never
change. I had a lot of stress this these
past couple of weeks as well. Ghosting.
Yeah. I had a foot injury, washing
machine broke, fridge
broke, stuff something to do with a job
that I was applying for. It's not been
an easy couple of weeks, bro. I was like
I couldn't walk for like two weeks. And
I thought, "Oh, okay. Now this person
wants to meet and they've approached me.
It's a bank holiday. Now we're getting
somewhere. Now all of this stress has
been for something and they just wasted your time again, you
know. Yeah. No, but I it was all in two
weeks, mate. I had a madness in two
weeks as well and other things as well
I'm not going to get into. But yeah,
that's why I don't
um I think I banged my foot bro in my
sleep. I had a thing called paranal
tentonitus. I can't pronounce it. And my
whole foot was swollen, bro. Like, I
literally It was throbbing, bro. I
thought I was going to
die. I literally thought I was going to
die, bro. It's not even a joke. But
yeah, it's it's getting better now. It's
like 90% better, but it was
bad. And I literally took medication
just so I can go on a date. I literally
took painkillers just so I could go on a
date. No, it wasn't, bro. So, yeah. cuz
obviously as stupid as it sounds that we
don't get many options in this country.
So when you do have an option, you know,
you want to grab it by the [ __ ]
horns, you know what I mean? So So it
kind of like set me back a few days for
the recovery because of that just to get
your time wasted. I know it's crazy, is it,
bro? It's crazy, is it,
lad? That's why I don't really go out
much anymore drinking ghosting. I just
stay in just do just cook some food and stuff. Just chill.
Yeah. Probably going to have a bath in a
minute. I can't wash no clothes until
tomorrow cuz my washing machine broke as
well. I had to buy a new
one. What a life. E. What a life.
Uh u went on his door, but I'm not I'm
not involved in the drama no more. I
think it's pathetic, bro. It's been
going on for years. Like, I hear that
Arsenal Mark still makes videos about
me. And the way I see it is, bro, most
of these people in this community are
grasses. If they were about anything,
they wouldn't be on YouTube making videos.
Maybe that's just where I'm from and I
know a bad ass when I see a badass. But
mate, honestly, they would not be sat on
YouTube making videos if they were about
anything like, and I know it because and
the fact that most of them are grasses
as well. So, I stay away from any drama.
Like, I'm not even really on here
anymore, but I was off here for like 3
weeks. They go on like they're about it,
but they're sat on YouTube making videos
to each other. Does that sound like what
a gangster? It's like that Arsenal Mark.
He will do videos,
right? Um trying to get my attention
because people tell me it's like, "Okay,
you know where I live. That's it."
Because he's trying to get attention. He
wants me to start making videos back to
him and start arguing when we all know
if this guy claims to be this cocky
gangster, he wouldn't be on YouTube
making videos. He knows where I live and
if he comes on my door, he will know
what I'm about.
Simple. So that's it. It's laughable.
That's It's literally what you said. It
is actually laughable,
bro. And what I don't understand is
Timmy has took so many L's yet. Why does
he still come on here calling people
out? Doesn't make any
sense. Like, it's they're not serious
people. I don't know why they keep doing
this. It's me. I don't argue with no
one because I know like they're just
grasses on here as well.
grasses. They like to give it, but they
can't take it. There's literally no
point arguing with anybody on here.
Literally, not one
person. They know where you live. They
know where you live. That's it. You
know, they're about something. They'll
come and do something. Simple, bro. You
know what I mean?
Yeah. Even that Lord J bro, like when I
saw that the other day, I was so tempted
to be like, "Oh, come on my door. You're
in Birmingham. Come on my door. I'll
wait all day for you. I will wait all
day for you. But I was like, I'm not
getting into it with these people
anymore, bro. I've been nicked enough
time over this, you know, enough times
over this website and I'm not doing it
with these people, bro. They know where
I live, apparently. So, you feel about
it, you'll come and do something.
Simple. That's it. I'm, you know, I'm
not going to argue with them,
bro. And these people are older than me
as well. They should know better, mate.
Arsenal mark is what in his 40s, 50s and
he's still coming on YouTube acting like a bad
man and and he's still acting like a bad
man. Bro, the guy would get
levered. Like it's not even a joke. Like
I saw that I saw that Rick Mace thing.
Yeah. With that fat guy. I was like,
"Bro, what the [ __ ] Did you Did you see
that with Rick Mace with that fat guy?"
That like two weeks ago. Yeah. LT sent
me it. I swear to God, bro. Yeah, that
guy looked exactly the same guy as that
gay neighbor where I used to live. Um,
and he approached one of like my friends
and that and I was like, "Wait until I
see him. I'm going to confront him,
bro." I told him like, "Who do you think
you are approaching?" I said, "Record
me. I will smash the camera out your
[ __ ] hand." That's what I said to
him. And he was bigger than that guy
Rick Mace was um trying to have this
scuffle with, bro. He was He was He was
like same kind of like fat. He remind me
the same as him, bro. You know what I'm
saying? I weren't going to back down
from some [ __ ] [ __ ] You know what
I'm saying? Comes here, starts recording
people. I said, "This is cuz he thought
I was he said he said he thought I was
um he was me. He thought the guy was
me." I said, "Bro, this is me." Yeah,
this is me. It's not him. Cuz we looked
alike. So, what are you going to do
about it? Try and record me. I'll smash
the camera out your [ __ ] hand.
and stamp on it. That's what I said to
him. Like these people, like when you
actually see real life, bro, and then
you see these people, they're laughable.
They are generally laughable,
bro. It's like Rick Mace. Like, I don't
have nothing against the guy. Yeah. But
he wouldn't last a day in London. I
swear to God, bro. Like, people don't
even get in it get into it with
[ __ ] you know, like that over
here. like he really really he wouldn't
we wouldn't last today, bro. Trust
me. It's crazy. It is
crazy. But I don't get into it with any
of these people, man. Cuz they're just keyboard warriors.
That woman from Birmingham was stinking
sand. She was [ __ ] stinking
sand. So the way is if I could get with a stinking
woman. Yeah. If I could get if I if I
could get with a stinking woman, then a
woman can get with an above average
looking guy like me. That's the way I
see it. If I could get with a three,
four out of 10, which I have done, then
a woman can get with somebody that's a
six, seven out of 10. I'm like, that's the difference,
bro. I was just telling people before
like two days ago when I first met that
USA Izzy, I didn't really like her. I
was like, uh, she looks a bit different,
whatever. But what did I do? I gave it a
chance. I gave it more than an hour. I
gave it a chance. And I gave it more
than an hour. And look at all the [ __ ] it
caused. So that's what I mean by you
can't you have to give people time. You
understand? You know what I'm saying?
You have to give uh you have to give it
um you have to give this stuff time,
bro. So if you can give if you can give
a three, four out of 10 the time of day,
they can give a six, seven out of 10 the
time of day. There's no excuses and
that's why I probably am a six or seven.
I don't [ __ ] know but you know within
that ballpark. But yeah, I was I was
happier. It might have sounded boring
but bro like I said my my routine was
cooking. I was saying just bro here's
the thing ghosting.
Yeah. Sorry to repeat myself cuz a lot
of people have heard it. Yeah. Like when
I was cooking I'd get a takeaway every
week which was every Saturday. I'd go on
electric bike, go to KFC, come back, do
the food shopping. Life was good. To be
fair, my friend came around. She did
come around and like done stuff with me
a few times, but it wasn't a point.
Yeah, there was times where she didn't.
She um she uh so but the thing is when I
went out drinking that bank holiday, it
just went downward from there. I was
just like on a I was on a like downward
spiral, bro. I was on like a downward
spiral from there. And then it was hard
to then cook again and get into that
same routine again because all of the
stress, the shitty dates, like it was
hard. Yeah. To like pick yourself back
up again cuz it's like you you go 10
steps forward and 65 steps
back and like I was saying to this guy
right here. Yeah. I wish I never went
out that bank holiday. I wish I stayed
in and that's it. And that's honestly
what it is. Or I wish I met people and I
just didn't get my time wasted. But
that's obviously never going to happen
in this country clearly.
So yeah, and it just it just annoys me.
Like all of them just annoy me. They
piss me off. And I just figured to and I
just said to myself, what you need is a
holiday, bro. That's why I booked a
holiday because that's what you actually
need, mate. You need a holiday by
yourself. Like not even with anyone
else. You need a holiday by
yourself. You know what I'm
saying? Yeah, exactly, bro. Yeah, of
course. That's why they're jealous. Of
course, bro. That's why they're
jealous. But people never say this stuff
though. Ghosting. People never say, "Oh,
a woman is a negative." It is a
negative, lad. Dating as a man is a
negative. It doesn't matter how many
people want to sugarcoat it. It is
negative. Drinking's negative.
Gambling's negative. Eating [ __ ] all the time is
negative. You know what I'm saying, bro?
Like, it is, of course, it's negative.
It is all negative, man. But that's why
I just sort of like I just gave up with it.
But and yeah, like I said, bro, everyone
I've approached and I didn't really feel
I stayed with
them. And the the times I didn't stay
with them is cuz I was pissed off at
someone else. It wasn't even them. So I
know exactly what I'm talking about as a
[ __ ] 27 year old, mate. when I've
been up and down up and down the [ __ ]
country. Like you you don't know how bad
women are until you start dealing with
them again. That's what I like until you
start dealing with them
again. Um because the thing is like
Ghost I figured I figured this out.
Yeah. Ant-Man had the right idea. Yeah.
So I applied for a job. Yeah. And I was
going to make money and the money that
I'd make every week is the money that I
I go and drink to go out with. But I've
got the holiday booked, so whatever
happens ain't going to piss me off
because I know in six to eight weeks I'm
out of here. I'm gone. Douches. Adios.
Simple. So, I mean, you could do that.
There's there's a few ways around that.
I mean, you can keep going out and it
ain't going to piss you off because you
know you're leaving in 6 8 weeks. 6 to 8
weeks of earning money for that and
you're leaving, bro. So, that's what the
plan was. He had he had the right idea,
but obviously I've applied for this job.
Need him to contact me back. I'm gonna
make money for the for the Saturday.
Well, I'll just go out once a week. You
don't need to go out once a week and you
know you're leaving. So, whatever
happens, you know, because the thing is
if you get more bad experiences, all you
got to say is, "Yep, well, I'm gone in 6
weeks anyways. I'm gone in 8 weeks
anyways." So, douches.
Adios. So, it's that's you know, but I
won't go out now for like two weeks. I
need a break from it. Even though I do
you know what? I do want to go out this
week cuz it's bank holiday and I like to
go out bank holiday. That's the only
reason I went out is cuz it was bank
holiday. It was cuz it was bank holiday.
That's why I went out and I actually did
do two days. I actually done two days
and I can never do two days in a row,
but I did. Maybe cuz I detoxed. I don't
know. But I done Friday and Saturday
because it was a bank
holiday. Got loads of numbers on loads
of approaches. But it's just Yeah, it
turned [ __ ] bro. Like people's like,
"Oh, well, it doesn't matter. You don't
like her. You don't like her. It doesn't
matter if you don't like her, bro. It was the
principle." This is what I'm trying to
This is what I'm trying to explain to
him, Ghosting. It's the principle that
the [ __ ] wasted my time. Like, somebody
that that's like that should be happy to
have someone like you. Do you know what
I'm saying? They should really be happy
to have someone like you. But you know,
and then what happened,
Ghost, was after that date, I was pissed
off, bro. Yeah. I got into this round
and and I walked to the [ __ ] table,
bro, with my Guinness. And I said, I'm
sick of these westernized women. Yeah.
I'm sick of these westernized women. And
then this old guy was like, I don't want
to hear it. I said, well, you're going
to [ __ ] hear it, whether you like it
or [ __ ] not, [ __ ] You know,
that's another thing that I'm sick of,
like these [ __ ] around like London
with their attitude. if you get enough
in that Weather Spoons. And I said, "If
you don't like it, [ __ ] off." Basically,
then he went to the manager and he
grasped me up to the manager and the
manager was like, "Oh, what you saying
about like you something about West Eyes
Women?" And we literally had a debate.
Yeah. For about 10 minutes, 10 15
minutes. Yeah. It weren't even a heated
debate. The [ __ ] bouncer come over
and I was like, "Mate, listen. You might
be 34. I'm 27. I'm from the West. I know
what these women are like." Yeah. You
can tell me this, you can tell me that.
I know what I know. I know what I
experienced and what I've just
experienced. Again, like actions speak
louder than words, bro. Talk is cheap.
You know, you can say women are
different all you all you all you like,
but I believe it when I see it. Like,
bro, you're 34. Okay, you come from
another country. Okay, fair enough. You
probably don't know anything but working
in that pub. You know that. You know
what I'm saying? You probably don't know
anything more than working in that pub.
I know I've done stuff other than
working in a pub. I've been about, you
know what I'm saying? So, but yeah. No,
it was just in the Weather Spoons. It
weren't like fighting or anything, but
don't be a [ __ ] to me. Don't be I've
already I've dealt with already enough
[ __ ] today. I don't need to deal
with another [ __ ]
[ __ ] You know what I'm saying? If
you don't like people coming up talking
to you, [ __ ] off.
Don't be in a Weather Spoons then. I had
it with that Scottish guy like [ __ ]
was it two months ago. He said, "Oh, I I
was trying to be normal to him." Yeah. I
was sat there literally chilling, bro.
And he starts giving an attitude. He
said, "Oh, I don't say where you put." I
said, "I'll put my feet where I want."
That's what I said. I said, "I'll put my
feet where I want to put my [ __ ]
feet." You know, [ __ ] these people in
this country, I can't stand some of
them, bro. I swear to God, it's not even
just the women. It's just some of the
people like I can't explain it, bro.
Maybe it's a London. Maybe it's London
thing, but bro, some people just can't
stand. Sorry, it's just negative. And
that's why I just stopped going out,
bro. Just started doing my own thing.
So, just all negative in it, lad. It was
in a Weather Spoons pub,
but it was never going to turn
violent. It was never going to turn
But yeah, it's just negative in a ghost
indo nothing anyone can really say,
bro. Cuz the thing is, bro, if people
were right, you would have met different
women by now. You would have met
different women, not narcissistic,
selfish, devious women, if they were
actually as different as people
say. Think about it.
like it's just negative that um so
yeah I know a lot of people like
sticking their nose in mate they do it
with like they do it they do it a few
times bro they do it a few time bro it's
it's London it's full of [ __ ] mate
get used to it yeah I remember I tried
to go into this O'Neal before I was
banned. Yeah. And the guy tried
searching me. I said, "Why are you
searching me? Obviously, I'm not a
criminal. I don't carry knives." I was
like, "Why are you searching me?" Um,
you know who I am. I've been here about
a million times. Then I was like, "I
don't want you to search me." Not like,
you might think, "Oh, I'm being awkward
and being difficult." I don't want you
search me. It is a pub and I'm not going
to let you search me. And then the other
guy was like, it's his job. I said, did
anyone ask you? Did Did anybody ask you
like why you butting your nose in? Like
it's his job. Yeah, good for him. That's
for him to tell me that. Why are you
butting your nose in? They love button
their nose in, mate. White Knights. It's
just a typical London [ __ ] thing.
You do it when you approach
um you do it when you approach people as
well. When you approach people, they do
it as well. They they will literally
break their neck to literally look at
you. London's full of [ __ ] It's
full of [ __ ] They give us a bad
name. They give every London every other
Londoner a bad
name. They're really embarrassing. Like
especially when you go like Liverpool
Street as well. They're egos. Oh my god.
And they're really nobodyies. That's the
thing. They think because they're from
London they're just this and that, but
in reality they're just no ones. They're
just nobodyies. They don't even really
have much money. Anyone would think,
mate, they're [ __ ] Anybody would
think these people are literally Taylor
Swift the way they walk around like
they're billionaires, but in reality
nobodyies. That's the thing. But they
they [ __ ] got an ego, mate. I tell you
that. You know what I'm
saying? Yeah, it's I don't want to talk
about it, bro. It's
annoying, but you get the point. Take
this. Yeah. Women do make you unhappy.
Yeah, that's the point. They
do. Yeah. Been to cities. Yeah. I've
been everywhere, bro. I'm from London.
Yeah. Especially like Soho and that like
O'Neal's. They all stuck up. They all stuck up,
bro. Yep. I've been to Bank Station. Yeah.
Yep. They seem to think that they're
better than people, but I've probably
got more money than them. That's the
funniest thing. It got It gives us a bad
name, though. It does give us a bad name
because I've been to Middlesbrough, bro,
and I've never thought I'm better than
anyone, mate. And I'm probably rich compared to
them, you know.
Nah, I'm done with the UK, bro.
Everywhere is the same. I'm done, bro.
I'm done wasting money in this country.
I mean, I live in London. I mean, it's
the best city for going out in. It's
big. I don't need to I don't need to
move. I've been everywhere, bro, except
Blackpool and Glasgow. There's no reason
to to to go anywhere else.
Only place I've not been is
Blackpool, Blackpool, Southampton, and
Glasgow and Plymouth. There no reason to go anywhere
else. People are not all of a sudden
just going to be different. You
know, yeah, I know it's a dump, but
yeah. Nah, I'm going Thailand, man. And
Thailand. I think it's about that time,
bro. I'm 27. I'm not getting any
younger. We've rinsed this country.
Yeah, I won't go. I was thinking of
going to Manchester again cuz I used to
go like once a year,
but I don't really see the point.
Sometimes I just prefer I just like to
go away to get out of London, but
there's really no
point. I don't see there's there being a
point of going there. to spend like
£400. So that's how much you'll probably spend about
£400. What do you reckon it'd be like in
New York City? I think it would just be
impossible. I reckon it would be
impossible dating there, bro. It would
just be impossible. What do you
think? New York? Yep. Just like London,
eh? Full of
[ __ ] Who's this?
Yo, don't know who this is. But
yeah, that Jamie Thompson guy is
you. That's your Tommy. And that's how
you found my account through Instagram.
Cuz you know that I got a friend in the
army. You know that I got a friend in
the army. That's why you That's why
you've made that your name.
Jamie, you're a stalker
lad. You're a stalker lad. It's you.
Yeah. I got some friends in the army,
acquaintances. Yeah. Long, man.
Yeah. Country's depressing, lad. Yeah.
Uh, bye-bye. See you later. Bye-bye, Jamie Thompson.
Thompson. Get a life. Jamie
Yeah. Yeah. Gian. So, I've been
everywhere but Glasgow and Blackpool,
lad. No, I wouldn't stay in Thailand.
And I'm only going to go for 2
weeks. But no, I don't think I'd stay
there. Antman's actually staying there.
When he goes again, he's actually
staying there. I don't know about
staying there, man. I've got like my mom
to look after and [ __ ]
And I don't
know. I don't know. It makes
sense for an Aussie bird in Thailand,
bro. That's never going to happen because they're
westernized. They're westernized.
Like they are [ __ ] just like the English. They're
westernized. Yeah, you get Australians
that go there, but they're the same as
English. Oh my god, bro. English, Canadian, American, Kiwi,
[ __ ] Australian, [ __ ] French,
Belgian. It's the same. They're all westernized.
We'reized. Yes, I know there's loads of
Australians. I've seen videos and
thingies told me, "But they're
westernized, so you're not going to pull
them." Yeah. Just two weeks. Yeah.
You're not going to pull an Australian
woman, bro, because they're
westernized. They're the same as
um they're the same as uh they're the
same as the English. Well, no, no,
they're not the same. Well, there's a
bit of a difference. No, there's a
difference. They're more politer and
they're more nicer. How do I know? cuz
I've approached loads of Australians and
I've never ever had one be rude or walk
away. Funny enough, I've never had one
be rude and walk away, but they're just
going to pretend they got boyfriends
because it's happened all the time.
Like, I will go and approach an
Australian. They'll they'll talk they'll
stop and talk. Yeah. They'll stop and
talk. They'll stop and talk and um they
will stop and
talk. Uh more evidence for me. Thank you.
Um they'll stop and talk, but then
they're just going to pretend they got
boyfriends because it it always happens.
I've never been with an Australian. I've
only kissed a few, but I've never
actually had sex with one or pulled one.
They're impossible, bro.
They've just got unrealistic standards. So, don't
know. Don't know. How about something I'm bringing? So
go refresh that. One
second. Sorry about that. 97
now. 97 in my harassment folder. Thank
you. Keep it coming. Um, but anyways,
yeah, I don't know how much I'm going to bring,
but yeah. Anyways, anyways, Ghost and I,
I wasn't gambling much either,
but yeah, lad.
You They're all obsessed with me, bro. I
think they want to bum me, bro. They're
all obsessed with me. They're all
obsessed with me, bro. I had to make another channel
again. They're all obsessed with me. I
think they're jealous of me or
something, bro. It's
weird. They're all obsessed with me,
man. They're envy of anyone that's got a
better life for them. Anyone that's got
a better life than them, they envy. I'm
telling you, bro, it's
weird. Just a They're just jealous fat
people. They ain't got nothing. What
else can you say about
them little stalker?
But you got no
chance. Um, you've got no chance of putting an
Australian. No chance of putting an
Australian, bro. No
way. [ __ ] probably got more chance of putting in English. Dope.
But yeah, they never they've never been
rude. They've always stopped and
spoke, but they're too entitled with unrealistic
standards. So, it's the same as everyone else,
lad. So, yeah, more evidence. Keep it
coming. All right. This is why I made a
new channel to get away from these people. Literally,
Mark, to get away from these people. I
reckon the women in China will be used
to Nah, you won't be. You won't you
won't find it hard like here, mate. You
won't find it hard like here. It's
harder than it was 10 years ago. But
yeah, and you should have to humiliate
yourself to find a partner. And it comes
to the point where it's like like you're
27, bro. You've been you've basically
been by yourself most your life.
So, you know, you're you're enough
alone. And that's basically what it is,
bro. Sad as it sounds, it's the way it
is. Like, you're enough alone. So,
nothing's changed in 27 years, like longterm wise.
So, you know, there's no point in in
like I said, still go out. If you want
to go out, go out. Don't expect anything.
But you know, but you know, you know
what I'm saying?
Like, and when I went out, I wasn't
expecting anything. But when somebody
wastes my time, that's what pisses me
off. It pisses me off when they waste my
time. That's what pisses me
off. Yeah, I was getting with her. I was
getting with her, but she's gone to
Wales and she's 20 now. Yeah, she came
round. She used to come around all the
time and give me a [ __ ] I don't
really want to have sex. Yeah, we was
doing that for ages and then she went to Wales.
Yeah, she come around like two weeks
ago. So, I was just sticking with her
and not going out
basically. But she's weird. Then she
blocks you, then she unblocks you and
then meets you again. She's very weird.
Because I prefer
[ __ ] Everyone's different, isn't
it? [ __ ] feel better. Sex is overrated.
Yeah. So, yeah. So, yeah. But she's
weird cuz she will block and then she'll
unblock and then she'll want to meet you
straight away and then she'll do it
again. It's [ __ ] weird. Got like
mental issues or something.
But yeah, like when they come back,
which they will come back, that's
basically your only hope
really, is her. And she's good-looking
as well. There's nothing wrong with her.
She's actually good-looking. And she's
put a bit of weight on now as well.
So yeah, like she's she's actually good,
man. Yeah. I'm not doing it right, bro.
I'm 27 and I've never had sex the right
way. Yeah. Okay, bro. I've never had sex
the right way at 27 years of age. I
know, man. Sucks to be me in it.
Yeah, I know, bro. It sucks to be me,
huh? And yeah, anyway, she's not ugly
and she's actually gained a bit of
weight, so she actually looks even better
now. She's actually good-looking as
well. That's the
thing. But yeah, I'm 27. I've never had
se I've never had um I've never done sex right bro never never
bro hopey I don't find this [ __ ] account
bro just talking about a 19year-old but she's 20
now she's 20
now well I will get with her when she comes
back. Femosis. I don't have Formosis,
bro. My My skin goes all the way back.
Nope. I don't have Formosis, but Ant-Man
has it. I used to have Formosis when I
was like 19 and then I pulled my skin
back. I don't have
Formosis. But Ant-Man has
it. Nope. I don't have that [ __ ] I've
not had that [ __ ] since I was 19. So,
but yeah, if she comes back, well, she
will come back. They always come back,
then I will.
But yeah, we used to have like Chinese
food. She used to give me a [ __ ] and
that like she sucked my like six times
now. But just something I don't know,
she goes weird a bit. I think she has
issues. But yeah, I just stayed with
her. I just stuck with her. That's why I wasn't going
out, you know? That's why I just wasn't
going out cuz I was just with her.
Chilled. She'd come
around. She swallowed my [ __ ]
greasy. More evidence for
me. Thank you. Keep the evidence
coming. Thank you for the evidence.
That was a girl. People were trying to
say Yeah. They were trying to say she
was disabled, bro. They're trying to say
she's disabled because they've never had
anything as good as her. That's why they
say they say that she's
disabled. Um because they're
jealous. Yeah. Yeah, she did. Oh,
basically someone called the police on
me and I have to go to court. Um, yeah.
I got arrested for apparently calling
somebody a gay virgin, but I've got so
much evidence on them that when I go to
court, I'm going to I'm going to take it
to trial and I'm going to show like the
judge what these people have been doing
for years. So, what's going to happen is
they're just going to throw it out
because I've been collecting evidence of
like all the harassment, all the golden,
all the [ __ ] I've had to deal with with
these people for years. Like, these
people are going to get themselves in
trouble. Like if it goes to trial, these
trouble. So it's no it's no biggie. It's
no biggie, bro. You know what I'm
saying? Like I've got I've got about 100
pages of harassment, golden, stalking of
all of these people. So I mean, yeah,
like I said, I I'll see these people in
trial in two three years. It's not a
problem. Yeah. But anyways, we'll sort
it out, bro. It's not a problem. But
yeah, she did. We're not talking about
this anymore anyways.
So yeah, but we did talk about trying anal
anyways. Yeah. Well, it is because I am going.
Yeah. So yeah. Anyways, I'm not talking
about this no more, bro. Anyone that
keeps bringing up, I'm going to block
them because I don't want to talk about this.
So yeah, I'm not talking about this
anymore. Just know that these people are
going to get in trouble with the amount
of evidence that I've got on them.
They're they're going to get in trouble.
End of. Believe you me, they're going to
get in trouble with the amount of [ __ ]
that um and and I'm not going to get
into it, bro. I don't want to talk about this
[ __ ] Um so yeah. Anyways, we spoke
about trying anal because I've never
tried it and Ant-Man likes it. So yeah.
Anyways, so I've got so much evidence on
these people. I'm more than happy to
take it to trial. I'm more than happy to
take it to trial. I'll wait the two
three years you know it's not a problem
because at the end of the day the law
does not apply to one person you know
because what these people do is this is
one of the reasons why I come off this
community right what these people do
right what these people do is they sit
online right people go
people and then when you retaliate to
them they run to the police crying
crying crying him like they're the
victim crying, he's bullying me, he's
bullying me. And then when they do it
enough times, this is another reason why
I don't [ __ ] with this community, the
police have to do something. And I said
to them, basically, I've got all the
evidence I need on these people, and
we'll see what the judge has to say
because what will happen is is they're
going to turn around and say, "Okay,
well, we're going to take it to trial.
Have you done anything to this person?"
Because this person has said you've got
evidence. And that's when they'll be
[ __ ] And that is literally when
they'll be [ __ ] And if they don't
drop it, they're going to they're going
to get done for it. So it's like it's no
it's no skin off my nose. You know, I've
got all the evidence, all the
harassment, all their faces laughing at
me, bullying me. I'm taking it all to
call with me. Everything. My house
getting smashed up. I'm easy, bro. I
don't mind. That's why I'm not worried
about nothing. That's why I'm not
worried about nothing.
So, it's not a problem, bro. No problem
whatsoever. So, that's another reason I
don't [ __ ] with these people like Mark
Samson and any of these people because they're just
grasses, you know? But it's all right,
bro. I've got enough evidence on these
people anyways. Trust me, bro. And when
the trial date is, I'm that confident. I
will give you I'll I'll give you it.
I'll give you the actual date. It's not
a problem. You know, that's how
confident I am. So
yeah, system's [ __ ] in
it. The system's [ __ ] And I've got
all the I've got their faces as well
saying stuff. So yeah, there was no
point. There was literally no point even
deleting anything because I've got
everything. I've literally got about 100
stuff in a 100 things in a folder, mate.
There was literally no point you
deleting anything off that channel.
So yeah, it's not a problem, man. It's
whatsoever. The judge will sort it out. So
yeah. So yeah, trust me, mate. You're
not quick enough to delete stuff. I've
got everything. I'm not going to tell
you exactly what I have. Um I'm not
going to tell you exactly what I have,
but I have everything. Trust me, mate. I
I literally have everything. And it's
not going to look good, mate, when
there's a whole channel dedicated to
harassing and bullying someone, is it?
That's not going to look good, is it?
That's not going to look [ __ ] good,
eh? So, oh [ __ ] this is good. That's
not going to look good, eh, mate? So,
yeah, we'll have a [ __ ] strong
[ __ ] defense. All the screenshots,
all the videos, everything, all the
threats, everything, bro. I'm easy, man.
I don't care.
Simple. So, anyways, they're not going
to bait me anyways. I know what they're
trying to do. Like I said, I'll see them
in court. End of story. That's all you
got to say to someone, bro, is I'll
literally see you in court. That's all
you got to say.
Yeah. Don't need to worry about it, man.
I'm not worried about anything. I'm not
going to argue with these
people. You know what I'm saying? I
don't need to sit here and argue with
these people. You know, I've got nothing
to hide, bro. I ain't going to
prison. So, that's it. So,
yeah, that reminds me. I need to
actually call the police again
um tomorrow probably. Yes, only a
source. Have to keep following up with
this report, mate. I mean, I told Kevin
Murphy, I'm the biggest [ __ ] I'm the
biggest [ __ ] now when it comes to
people in this community. I told him
straight. I'm the biggest [ __ ] when it
comes to people in this community. These
little grasses, I'm the biggest [ __ ]
going now. I said I said it, but at
least I admit it when it comes to you
little grasses. Yeah. And I have to like
put that bit at the end as well.
So, we'll stay tomorrow, Tuesday. Yeah.
[ __ ] I've lost track with [ __ ] time, bro. Yeah. So,
yeah. Anyways, trust me, these people
won't be laughing in court, mate. They
won't be laughing in court. It's all I got to
say. Got free
notifications. Free notifications, de lad. Oh,
damn. No, no, no. What's taking these
[ __ ] people so
long? I've also got the ones where
they're telling me to come and fight
them as well and they're walking down my
road. I got everything, mate. Literally everything.
It's not going to look good, mate. It's
not going to look good. Right. Let's Come on
here. It ain't going to look good.
got it where these people put up posted
of me and they've made comments about it
as well. It's not a
problem. It's not a problem
at I've got it where these [ __ ]
[ __ ] have been at me for the past
[ __ ] god knows how many years, mate.
So, in a way, it's a good thing, you know.
also gave me even more evidence there as well. Funny
enough, still [ __ ] pending, but apparently it
is. Of course, I got a load of missed
calls as well, so it's all good, man.
It's all good.
So yeah, these people think they're
smart, but really they're thick as pig
[ __ ] and they actually don't know the
law. These people think that they're
smart, but they're not smart, mate. And
they're going to know that when they're
in court that they're not smart. So
yeah, got all the harassment, all the
golden. I've got all my little pack of
evidence of this
harassment. Oh, it's going to be a sexy
trial. Oh, it's going to be a sexy
one. It is going to be a sexy one, mate.
skin, big nose, bullying. I've got all
of it. Oh, I've got
everything. Oh, I've got everything,
mate. I'm literally rubbing my hands like
Timmy. Like, actually looking at this.
Yeah, all this golden, all this
harassment, all this golden. Literally,
I got golden after golden after bullying
after bullying. It's going to be lush. I
really grieves you. I actually want you
to come to this trial. I actually want
you to come to this trial, lad. Like,
I'm not going to tell you everything
that I've got on these people, but
everything is going to discredit them.
Literally, everything that I've got is
going to discredit them as I quote,
whatever they want to call themselves.
Bro, it's lush, man. It's actually lush. Trust
me. It's not a
problem. Come on, Grezy man. You got to
come, bro. You really have to come in 2
3 years, bro. I want you to come in 2 3
years. Please do, bro. Yeah.
Yeah. I've already had tea, mate. I've [Music]
tea. I'm going Thailand soon. I'm not
going to give you the exact
dates, but yeah.
Yeah. No, I'm not staying there
forever. Yeah, I'm
going soon. I booked it. Not going to
give you the exact dates, but
yeah. You're an armchair viewer. Well,
you're going to have to get a [ __ ]
taxi, mate, if you're a [ __ ] armchair
pewer, aren't you, mate? Yeah. But
yeah, but this evidence is lush. I look
at it every
morning and there's literally no way
these people getting out of it as well
because it's got their face, it's got
them talking, it's got everything. got
their number, where they've called me a
million times, where they've harassed
me. I've got everything, mate. So, it's
it's not a
problem. Like I said, people need to
stop deleting stuff from their channel
because I literally save everything. Literally, so
yeah. Anyways, back to Thailand. We're
not talking about these idiots, but um
yeah, Joe, it's going to be a typical
thing of Grezy. Six, six and a half.
What? Six and one and half a dozen.
What's it called? It's going to be tip
for tat. That's what they're going to
see it as. Tip for tat. Trust me,
Greasy. Trust me. Literally, trust me,
lad. That's exactly what's going to
happen. [ __ ] hell, mate. You're going
to have multiple women in one. You're
going to have multi multiple women every
day. That's what you're going to have.
Multiple women every day. So yeah.
Yeah. And these people think Grezy
because they're not like threatening or
they're not doing this or they're not
doing that. These people think they can
get away with it. But what they're
actually doing is harassing and
stalking. If you actually look on the
law, right, it comes under harassment and
stalking. So that's it.
yeah, and that's it, man. Like they
don't understand that you they them
doing what they're doing is stalking and
harassment. You don't need to threaten
people. That's how thick they are.
That's how thick these people are. 100
things. I got everything. I can't wait
to show this to the judge. I literally
can't wait. I literally can't wait.
Honestly, it's going to be lush, mate.
It's going to be Yeah. [Music] More
evidence, more evidence for
me. Anyways, I'm out of here. Bye.