Well, that aim [ __ ] down.
[ __ ] hell. Yeah,
man. Drags you back in. Do it.
Hey, I don't know how people do it.
Honestly, don't know how people [ __ ] do it.
This whole [ __ ] gambling
[ __ ] smash my [ __ ] mug. I can't even
have a cup of tea
now. Form of entertainment my ass.
Yeah. So they say, huh?
I literally smashed my mug. It's mad. Is
it even up to you now?
Well, wasn't very entertained.
Wasn't very entertained. It put me into
a [ __ ] depression
again. And at least we know that it is
gambling and it's not about the money.
At least we can actually know that now
cuz obviously the machine and that. So yeah.
You get told it's a form of
entertainment. Oh, that's going to make
me wake up feeling depressed as
well. What a
bust. What a doubter. It puts on your whole
day. Yeah. People think that you need to
lose a lot of money or you need to lose
your last bit of money for it to affect
you. No, just lose them. Just losing is
enough. And it's constant as well.
That's another thing. That's another
thing. It's constant. It is
constant. The the few times I've
gambled, I can remember all you seem to
do is lose on it when if it was really
gambling and not fraud, which it is, you
would win. There's there'd be times
where you'd win. But I've made sure I'm
not going to lose any more money in this
whole month cuz I'm starting it now from
the first. We're trying first. No more
than 100 pound this month. I am down.
[ __ ] that. [ __ ]
that. 300 on a washing machine don't
bother you. Yeah. 100 pound losing
gambling bothers you. It's gambling.
It's definitely definitely definitely
gambling. doesn't need to
be. I've lost 20 pound in weather
spoons. When was that? I think it was
like a week ago. I'm not even going to
tell you what I felt like doing. It's
gambling, bro. And them machines. I'm
telling you. I'm [ __ ] telling
you. It doesn't matter how much money
you've got left over. Doesn't matter how
much money you lose.
Yeah. 100 pound for the month. If we call it
£100, I do any more than that. I am
done. Done. [ __ ] that. That's
enough. That's enough. And we lost a few
bit. I lost like two weeks as well. Not
even one single win. I can't remember
being up from gambling in the last
month. Six months. But it's gambling
they say. That's what annoys me.
I'll probably have to go to bed thinking about that
today. I can't get over it. You know
what I'm saying? That's why people like
me shouldn't gamble. That like anyone
that takes losses personally. Yeah. You
shouldn't gamble. If you're anything like
me, if you're anything like me, bro, you shouldn't
gamble. You literally shouldn't gamble
if you're like me.
Honestly, because I'm scared I will end
up doing something one day, bro, and get
myself in serious serious serious
trouble. You know, I smashed my mug,
which cost £20. So, I've had to order a
new mug. So, just walking into one shop cost me £120.
Yikes. But then you get people like
Secular Slot saying that it's
entertainment. Bro, I'm not even going
to tell you what I wanted to do today
and the other day. So, and it was all
brought on by gambling. It was all
brought on by gambling again. Money I
could afford to lose. That's how you
know these people are
not. No, you just don't like losing.
Simple. It's just
losing. It's You just don't like losing. Continuously
losing. But I think it's continuously
I think it's continuously losing. Not
just losing. I think it's continuously
losing. That's what I think it
is. I fake
Natalie. Yeah, I think it's continuously
losing. That's what I think. It's a
problem. Am I fake? Natalie
G, how we doing? I know you're fake. [Music]
I will come. Yeah.
Yeah, I'm not doing good. I lost 100 pound
gambling. I got mood swings for an hour.
Smash my mug
up. [ __ ] had an argument with my mom,
which we don't argue anymore. Good old
gambling, eh? You can always count on
gambling to ruin everything. Now I'm sat
here. I can't even have a tea cuz I
smashed my mug up and I'm not going to
go out and buy another mug. Yay for
gambling. Yay for gambling. Eh,
um, I do have a
bed. Um, I do have a bed. Actually, I
was staying at my friend's house,
[ __ ] I've got a 500 bed. Try again.
I'm nowhere near 30. And I do have a
bed. A 500 bed. Just plastic.
I was at my friends. So, try again.
[ __ ] Yeah. And I'm nowhere near 30.
Show us your in bed. I'm not showing you
nothing, mate. Suck your mother. How
about that one? How about you go and
suck your mom? I'm not showing you
nothing. Get blocked. Don't come here
and ask me to show you [ __ ] [ __ ] off. I suck your mother. So,
yeah, it is boring.
It is boring, bro. It is
boring. See how this gambling can escalate stuff.
Bye-bye. You see how it can escalate with um gambling, you
know, like it's bad, but people say it's
a form of entertainment.
It's not even funny because you will end
up hurting someone one day, bro. Like
seriously, you will. You will end up
hurting someone one day cuz of gambling.
Doesn't matter how much the amount of
money is. It's
irrelevant. Yeah. It's
irrelevant. People I don't know why
people seem to think it's about money
though. That's what I understand when
you come in a community like this. Yeah.
They seem to think that you a either
lost all your money or b you've lost a
lot of money. No. No. Why would it have
to be that way? Just losing is enough.
Bye-bye. Get a life, Jamie Thompson. You [ __ ]
weirdo. Get a life, you fat weirdo. And
stop pretending that you got a [ __ ]
wife. You ain't got a wife. You ain't
got nothing. You're a sado. All you do
is sit online every day stalking people.
And you're not a master hacker. You're a
master low life because I made a new
YouTube channel. I made a new YouTube
channel and you're never going to find
it. You [ __ ]
weirdo. You [ __ ] sad bastard. Ain't
got a life. Just like most of the people
in this community, they ain't got a life. So
yeah, nothing but stalking men on the internet. Wow.
Yes, man. I don't know how people can do this, bro.
I'm trying to understand how people
gamble and they're fine with losing. I
don't understand how people are fine with
it. It's not cuz I'm weak. Not because
I'm born with a different personality.
Nah, it's none of that. Cuz I've
actually got a lot of patience. Nah.
Nah. That's what I used to think it was
at first. Maybe you're weak and you're
childish, but nah, it's not that. It's
got to be more than that, mate. Because
you would just be able to switch off of it, you
know. It's crazy. People like me shouldn't
gamble. People like me shouldn't
gamble. I don't think I've ever met
anyone else like me, to be
honest. They seem to lose and not
care. It's a basket. It ruins the whole day.
Don't know about anyone else. Ruins
literally the whole
vibe, the whole [ __ ] day. It makes
people want to do a Uturn and go back
home. You're going out drinking. It
ruins the whole
vibe. The whole vibe. Any vibe that you
got going on, it's a buzz kill.
No, drug addiction.
Uh, but I don't think I've ever met
anyone like me in terms of gambling. I
actually smashed my mug up when I got
back. I smashed my mug up. Crazy,
bro. It's crazy, isn't
it? It controls your whole body and your
whole mind. It's like you got a parasite
in your whole in your body, bro.
It's like you've got a parasite in your
body, but I can't explain it, you
know, and it feeds negativity as well.
I've noticed that with the scam. It
feeds negativity. Doesn't matter how
much money you lose. It literally does.
Like, it's going to take me like two
days to calm down now. Literally like
two days. £100 I can afford to lose. Got
all my bills paid. So, it's not that.
See, it's not that. That's what people
think it is. They've lost all their
money or they or they've lost loads of
money. No, it's
not. Not that at
all. It's not that at
all. No, I just done 100 pound today,
bro. And I felt like killing
myself. I was going [ __ ] mad, bro.
Almost lost my [ __ ] voice.
Came home, smashed my
mug. Yeah. Came back, smashed my mug up,
which cost me 20 pound. Had to buy
another one. I wish I never walked in. I
don't need to go to gamblers anonymous.
I can control myself. It just I can't
control how it makes me feel. And I've
never ever met anyone else that's like
me. Like I It's not about I can't
control doing it or losing my money. I
just can't control it. Makes you so
down. Like I can't explain it. It sounds
immature to anyone that has to deal with
it. But me, I would lose and I would
actually I would actually want to kidnap
someone. Like you you don't understand,
bro. Like you don't understand my
temper, right? I'll have it in my head
like I'll get mad things in my head like
I'd want to actually go out and kidnap
someone. It's not even a joke. And it's
all brought on by gambling or it depends
on like what environment I'm in. That's
how you know it ain't a form of
entertainment. That's how you know it
ain't, bro. Because it should not make
anyone feel like
that. Like today, bro, I was by I
thought I might I might just go and
[ __ ] kidnap someone. Like, I swear to
God. I'm not even joking, bro. And it was only
£100. You know what I'm saying?
So, no, I was playing I
Horus. That's a bit swollen
again. No, I was playing I Horus.
Yeah. Yeah. I was playing I Horus on one
pound. Got a bonus. It paid 16 quid. Shocker.
It feeds negativity as
well. It does. It's literally the worst
thing you could
do. It's literally the worst thing you
could do is gamble. I swear to
God. And how you know it's not about the
money is because look, you just paid
£300 for a washing machine, right? You
could have got a lot cheaper. Does it
bother you? No. You lose 100 pound
gambling, it bothers you.
So obviously there's a problem there,
isn't it? But I don't need gamblers
anonymous, mate. I've always got my
bills paid. Always got food in my belly.
It's not to do with that. There's no
gamblers anonymous. You literally just
have to stop doing it
because well, no. Well, you do need to
go to gambless anonymous because you
need to remember every single time. It's
crazy how you you forget. Yeah. when
you're just about to do it again, you
forgot how it made you feel the last
time. Like, you can't do it. It's not an
option, you know? You're just going to
continuously lose and continuously get
these mood swings time and time and time again, you
know, and that's what's going to happen.
Uh, so it doesn't matter, bro. You can
have all your bills paid. You can have
all the money in the world. Losing will still affect
you. Well, it [ __ ] affects me
anyways. I think it's just losing on it.
That's what I think the problem is. I
think the problem is just losing on
it. I think it's honestly I think it's
just losing on it. It's not even about
the money. I think it
is, you know, but it's continuously
losing on it as well. I think it's just
it. But I don't need gamblers anonymous
because I'm not addicted and I don't
lose all my money.
So, everyone's everyone's going to be in
there like, "Oh, I lost my money. I lost
my house." And you're going to be there
like, "Oh, it gives me mood
swings." That's what's going to happen.
and you'll be like, "Oh, it gave me mood
swings." And that's another thing that's
negative. Women, gambling, alcohol,
they're all negatives. And gambling is
also negative. You see how they're all
they're all linked to each other,
though. They're all linked to each
other. You go out, you drink, you get
bad experiences. Oh, [ __ ] gamble. And
then you gamble. And then you get a bad
experiences with women again. And then
it all goes round and round in circles.
You see, you see how a ne negative feeds of
negativity. I don't need GameStop. I don't gamble
online. I don't even gamble much. I just
tried £100 today. Look what
happened. But that will be the my last
100 pound this month, mate. I'm not
doing it no more. [ __ ]
that. Smashed my [ __ ] mug up. Can't
even have a [ __ ] tea now. Yay. Thanks to gambling.
Yeah, thanks to gambling. Yay. So, yeah.
Yeah. Con actually smashed my mug. It's mad. Yep.
I've only got one mug. I smashed it on
the floor. It was pissing me off.
[ __ ] continuously losing on this bro.
Yeah. I could have got into serious
trouble today, bro. I'm so glad I didn't, you
know. Yeah. No, I'm not going Tesco. I
don't want another mug. It has to be a Spider-Man mug.
No, it has to be a Spider-Man mug or I
can't drink from it.
Simple. Well, thanks Gambling for
ruining the day again. We can always
count on you. Yay. Backwards again. 10
step forward and 65 steps
back. Yeah, that was only £100 as
well. So, go figure.
I'm going to be depressed tomorrow
probably having to wake up thinking about
it. Oh, it has such a mad impact on
Peter Belly, don't it?
Yeah. So, I won't be having a tea now
for probably a few
days. So, yay. Gambling. always counting
that to ruin the day, ruin the vibe,
ruin your whole mind because it makes
you feel like you're losing your mind as
well. Women, gambling, alcohol, it's such a
negative. Such a negative. I was so good
and [ __ ] five, six weeks. I didn't go
out. Didn't go out. Didn't
gamble. It was good, man. Yep.
Some messed up, bro. [Laughter] No. Lose.