Yo. Okay, so this is going to be my
response to the [ __ ] ratfaced
lanky stringer piss simp white knighting
virgin. Um, so yeah, Steven Howard said
do a video. There's been a lot of
content today. So I thought, you know
what? Why not? One of the brothers wants
an ownage video, so that's what he's
going to get. He's going to get an
ownage video. Disclaimer. Yeah. Um,
before anyone continues watching this
video, um, I just wanted to say that 99%
of the time I do not react to these
clowns because they're clearly jealous
of something. They clearly have got
absolutely no [ __ ] life. So, you
know, you're best off just ignoring them
and living the life that they wish that
they had. Um, that's why they come on
here every day having channels dedicated
to other men because they're just
[ __ ] weirdos. Um, but you know, uh,
to be fair, a lot of it did make me
laugh today and I thought, you know
what, why not? So, anyone who's watching
this, I'm not going to keep going back
and forth and back and forth because
this keyboard warrior is never going to
meet anyone. He's never ever going to
say anything to anyone's face. So, just
let him keep embarrassing himself on
YouTube like he did today. Cuz that's
all he done today was embarrass himself.
I went on his channel earlier, right?
And I was watching this video that he
put up and I'm thinking, bro, what the
[ __ ] Like, I was actually laughing,
bro. Like, I was actually pissing myself
laughing. And then I had to pause it,
right, and think, Jesus Christ, is this
the same dude that's claiming that he
laughs at me? Like, I couldn't even
describe in words how many laughs I had
out of him today. And then it got worse.
Yeah. because then he went live and then
I'm thinking, bro, what the [ __ ] This
dude is actually having a autistic
um meltdown slash breakdown
in his bedsit owned by the [ __ ]
council. Like, it was funny as [ __ ]
bro. I was laughing my ass off. And and
to be honest with you, you're thinking
that these people are trying to trigger
you, but all he's done today was make me
[ __ ] laugh. Um, and it was funny, but
then there was a bit part of it where it
wasn't funny. It's clearly a cry for
help. You know, when he's when he's
coming on here saying that I'm I've got
a big nose and I'm ugly, you can tell it's deeprooted
projection and insecurities because he
hates the fact that he's too ugly to get
anything but a disabled bird. Um, sorry
to put that out there, but that is the
truth. like he is, you could see the
pain and the anger um in his voice and
in his eyes when he when he's tried to
call me ugly. It's clearly a cry for
help. Um and at the end of the day, I'm
thinking, bro, if this guy shouted any
louder, that bedset that's owned by the
[ __ ] council is going to literally
come falling down. Like, you know, you
know, have you ever watched it on TV
where someone shouts really loud and the
glass starts [ __ ] breaking and [ __ ]
I thought that was going to happen with
his council bedset today. But anyways,
before I get into like other things that
he said, I just wanted to start with
this. Right. So, um I just wanted to say
that it's 2026 and I don't know why
you're showing £1,100.
Um you have £10,000 to be showing from
back in 2024 when you got shown
thousands and thousands of pounds by
myself. Now, think about it, bro. You
didn't beat me at the money game. Joe F
didn't beat me at the money game. L J
didn't beat me at the money game. And
none of the other people in here. If you
generally generally had money, just like
L J and Jo F, brother, why didn't you
show me money every single time you got
shown money? You got shown three grand,
5 grand, 5.7 grand, 4 grand. Every
single time I have shown you and other
people in this community money, you've
done the opposite to double it. That's
how we know that you have no money. and
it was just a self-p projecting thing
that you did. So, we left that in 2024.
That's why we stopped showing you people
money because every single time you got
shown money, you wouldn't show anything
and then it would just go around and
round in circles. So, a wise man learns
from his mistakes. But, bro, you got
shown 5.7 grand and you're showing,00
you've not won. Only in your autistic,
stupid, damaged brain would you think
that's winning. But that's part of the
whole thing. Like you can't win with
these people in this community. You beat
them at the money game. They show you
less. They still pretend they've won.
Like you can't win with these idiots.
This is why I don't get into arguments
because you just end up losing brain
cells. Like they've been shown money
multiple times and they had absolutely
nothing to show. End of phenito. Done.
Like that's that's it. But then I want
to ask you this before I get into the
other stuff. um is see you you keep
calling me um a virgin now. I I don't
understand. I mean I got your channel
two of your channels banned for the
porno that I produced. I mean I showed a
woman sucking my dick. I showed me naked
in bed with women. I mean I've had women
that you've stalked that's admitted to
you that they [ __ ] me. Like there's
every bit of evidence there, including
your channel getting banned, that I'm
not a virgin. You called me about you
called me a virgin about 30 times. Now,
let's put the shoe on the other foot
here, right? The only thing that you can
say is that you've got a disabled
girlfriend, and that's not proof that
you've had sex. Whereas, I mean, I've
literally I've literally shown more [ __ ]
than than I should have shown. I
shouldn't have even shown the [ __ ] I've
shown. And and you're still calling me a
[ __ ] virgin when I've shown more than
a [ __ ] disabled fat, chubby, ugly
girl that can't even consent to sex. And
and you're still calling me a virgin. I
mean, there's there's there's no there's
no winning with these retards. But yeah,
then then I wanted to say um this as
well um this part um is
you need to stop sing over Autumn Rose.
you need to stop sing over all of these
other women. And do you know what? You
was raising your voice and it was
actually it was scaring me a little bit.
And I was thinking, why didn't you have
the same energy when somebody went to
your area three times and put up posters
of you? Why didn't you have the same
energy when people had you stop going to
the events that you love for one month?
I mean, it's very easy to shout and and
go mad in your cancel beds, but I mean,
[ __ ] me, bro. someone put up posters of
you all over your area. You knew where
they lived and you done jack [ __ ] So, I
mean, if you do want to talk [ __ ] um,
keep it out of tone. Don't don't raise
your voice because I mean, you're trying
to act big, but we all know the real
you. Um, when somebody goes to your area
and puts up posters of you, um, you go
run into the police crying and stop
going to events that you love. So, just
be a bit more calmer when you're saying
stuff. Now, again, I don't know why you
keep sing over white night. Um, why you
keep white nighting and sing over Alton
Rose, bro? She's not going to [ __ ] you.
She's not going to have sex with you.
She's not going to touch your penis. So,
I don't know why you keep singing over
these women. This is the thing that I
don't understand about white knights is
women don't like them. I mean, in your
case, you're with a disabled girl
because you're too ugly and abnormal to
get anything normal, which is what we're
going to get on to in a minute. They
don't get women. Women don't like them,
but they will still lick their asses
and women don't like them. It It's like
there's certain things. I'm sure
everyone's got their own thing that they
have in their head. What What doesn't
make any sense to me? It generally it's
like why why would anybody [ __ ]
defend women when they're not they're
not going to [ __ ] you? They're not going
to let you hit it. They're not going to
let you go from behind and stick your
dick up their ass. Why are you defending
them? It's just to me it's just it's got
to be some some disorder or whatever.
But I mean I don't understand why
there's so many white knights and women
don't like them. It's it's it's [ __ ]
weird. But um they they they still do it
anyways. And then you were saying about
um what was it about Rihanna? You were
saying about how uh how um how can
anyone say that uh Rihanna is not
good-looking? I don't know, bro. People
might just not like black women.
Maybe. Maybe. Maybe. Some people just
don't like skinny women. Some people
just have different preferences with
women that they like and they don't just
copy based on what their name is. A bit
like what you do. Oh, you see Rihanna um
and then you start calling her
good-looking just cuz her name's
Rihanna. You're literally just copying.
I mean, yeah, there's a lot of people
that don't like black women. I mean,
[ __ ] all it would take for somebody
to not like Rihanna is to not like black
women. But you where you copy and you
try to fit in to look good, you just see
the name and you just start copying
other people. Oh, they're good-looking.
Oh, they're good-look. And it just it
just it just doesn't um make any any any
sense. You're literally doing anything
to fit in. Um it's pathetic at 31 years
of age. Oh, [ __ ] Yeah, cuz you tried
saying that I'm 30, bro. I'm not even
30. And you're past 30. So, I mean, it's
just like it just doesn't make any
sense. Um, and then you were saying
about how um how I how somebody that
lives with them mom and
can't judge people and ret they can't
say what is attractive and what's not uh
attractive. Uh, now before you start
telling people who they live with and
who they don't live with, you might want
to own your own house. You might want to
actually get yourself a little job. You
might actually want to like contribute
contribute to society before trying to
look down on people because to me it
just does not it would not and does not
make any sense how someone
that lives in a bed owned by the council
could look down on anybody. That to me
doesn't make any any [ __ ] sense. And
then then I'm thinking the same thing is
that how can someone that live in that
lives in a council beds it owned by the
council try and talk about me? It just
it just does not um it just does not
happen. It doesn't happen and it will
never [ __ ] happen. and all of this
[ __ ] about, you know, you're ugly and
you're this, bro, you are talking about
your [ __ ] self, like proper talking
about yourself. You know, it's it's
similar to Monty man, right? He knows,
right? Okay, it's similar to Monty man,
right? If he broke up with Natalie G,
he's [ __ ] He's never ever going to
meet anyone. It's the same thing with
you and SA. If you split up tomorrow,
you'd never be able to get anyone
normal. You ain't got the looks. Um, you
ain't got you no normal woman would ever
ever ever ever go near you ever in a
million years. Um, because the way that
you look, you're [ __ ] ugly as [ __ ]
Um, you know, you you know, you can't
speak to people. You, you got nothing
going for yourself. And then because you
know that you can only date disabled
people, you try to project that onto me,
someone that's actually been with normal
women, that's actually had sex with
normal women. And then you say that
people ain't got a girlfriend. Um, yeah,
bro. Just like you tell people that they
ain't beat you at the [ __ ] money game
when they have. Just like you tell
people that they're [ __ ] virgins when
they've literally got your channel
banned for [ __ ] pornography that they
were in. Yeah. Yeah. Just like you say
all of that [ __ ] Like nothing you say
makes any [ __ ] sense because even
when you get proven wrong multiple
multiple multiple times, you still act
like you won. So there's a bit like
Timmy and the [ __ ] pigeon [ __ ]
[ __ ] all over the chessboard when it
loses. Triple H will love me for that.
But it's like you're clearly an insecure
weirdo that just needs to [ __ ] get a
life. And do you know what? You're
counting up this money and you're
talking about [ __ ] getting a band and
getting a band and how you going to uh
go to a band. [ __ ] the band off. Go buy
yourself some [ __ ] decent clothes,
you [ __ ] scruffy bastard. I mean, the
fact you're telling me that I I can't
judge women because of this. There's no
way somebody in charity shop clothes in
a [ __ ] bed suit owned by the [ __ ]
council for one second can [ __ ] try
and [ __ ] talk about me. That is that
is that is mental. There's no way
someone like that. And I was thinking
like with some of that money, you could
actually go to the dentist and [ __ ]
fix your [ __ ] missing teeth. But I
mean saying that it's free on the
[ __ ] NHS. like you're you're a clown.
Like you just nothing you say makes any
sense. Like it it's clearly a cry for help. Um
you know, you hate the fact that you can
only get disabled women due to your
looks and that's what you try to project
onto me. Like it's not even like no
one's seen what you look like. Then you
can kind of keep keep on with this lie.
You can keep on with this lie. But bro,
we know that we've we've seen you and
you're uglier than me. You've you can
only get disabled women. You can't get
anything normal. You're with a fat ugly
girl that can't talk. And you're still
coming on here in 2026
still doing this [ __ ] You ain't got a
life. And you know what, right? If it's
not even like, yeah, you can say, "Okay,
well, people have got different types."
Cuz nah, it's not because, bro, if you
really loved your girlfriend, you
wouldn't be on here stalking men. You
wouldn't even be you wouldn't even be
trying to bother me every day. If if if
that was really your type and you really
saw something in that girl, you would
not be coming on here bothering me every
trying to bother me every day or doing
stupidness. You hate the fact that
you're too ugly and too disabled to get
any of the things that I've got in the
past. And that's where the jealousy
comes from. You can see it in your face.
We It is a cry for [ __ ] help. Um and
you know, at the end of the day, I swear
to God, I'm not just saying this. Do you
know what? Yeah. As as much as we slag
off Natalie G. Yeah, I reckon if if we
had about 70 p pints of Guinness and the
bits offered you a [ __ ] you might
just accept it. Come on, bro. Like,
let's, you know, but with Sarah, bro,
you wouldn't go near that if someone
paid you. I mean, for [ __ ] sake. You
you you're with someone because you know
you can't get anyone better. It's the
same with Monty Man. You know, if you
split up with disabled, spasticated
Sarah, you'd be [ __ ] You know, you've
never been with a normal woman in any
other way. Anyway, whether it's a
relationship, whether it's a one night
stand and because you know I can
jealousy comes from because [ __ ] it,
bro. Does it does it matter what I look
like? I'm better looking than you in
every single [ __ ] way. Better body
than you. I'm better looking. I got more
hair than you. I've got a better face
than you. I'm better than you in every
[ __ ] way. And you're still coming on
here projecting your [ __ ] Like, you
need to get some help. That was a cry
for help earlier badly, bro. Right. I
feel sorry for you.