Okay, so this is a video to Monty. Yeah,
I need to correct you on a few things
because I see you live talking about me
and very I just want just get some
things straight. Okay, firstly, right
when Timmy was on the door, right? Yeah.
I was out and as soon as I see him
confront my mom, I was straight in that
plaque in that black cab. Straight in
that black taxi. Got the time of the
video. Got the video. I made a couple of
videos to be fair, but I just put the
best one up. I got the time of the video
and I've also got the message where I've
said to my mom, tell him to wait. Yeah.
So, I got straight into that black taxi.
Right now, I got off on the side of the
road. Yeah. Where there was a black cab,
which must have been Timmy's. Thinking
back on it now, that must have been
Timmy's. I looked I looked through it
and if he was in there, I was going to
drag him out of it. Yeah. Because Yeah.
Like, and then I went through the whole
road and he wasn't there. That was his
black cab, bro. There's no one on that
road that's that that's a black cab
driver. No one gets black cabs. That
black cabs would me. So, he must have
heard me when I was walking up saying,
"Timmy, Timmy, Timmy, whatever." He must
have been there for 2 minutes and then
bounced, right? So that black cab must
have been Timmy's. Where was Timmy when
I had come back cuz that black cab was
no one else's, mate, right? Which is why
I got out there and and at the end of
the day, um then people like, "Oh, you
got to go to the Weather Spoons. You got
to go to the Weather Spoons." Charged my
phone up for about half hour. Went to
the Weather Spoons. He was gone. Where
was he, bro? Cuz he wasn't back in
Marley Bone. He wasn't back in
Paddington. So where was he? So, at the
end of the day, Monty, stop [ __ ]
talking [ __ ] because I can put the
messages where I've told my mom to to
tell him to wait. I can also put up like
Yeah. the the video and I can show you
the time if you don't believe it. Um, at
the end of the day, mate, he must have
been there for a minute or two maximum
before he bounced because I didn't see
him. And I was running up that road,
mate, and that black cab was there. So,
where was he? Where was he? Where was
he? He must have known that I was back.
And that's it anyways. And then then
everyone's like, "Go to the Weather
Spoons." Got a cab. So I've wasted about
50 60 pound on taxis today. Then I went
to the pub. The Weather Spoons people
told me to go. He wasn't there. Running
up my mouth. They barred me. He wasn't
there. He wasn't. So where was he then?
Where was he? If he wasn't in the town
if he wasn't back in the town center,
where was he? Um and and and that's it
to be honest with you. And the thing is
Monty. Yeah. I want to make you right on
a couple of things. I've never ever
doxed any of my mom's addresses. Yeah.
Back where I used to live, they found
out where I lived. Yeah. They I don't
know how they found out where I live,
but they found out where I lived. This
address right here, they found out where
I lived. Yeah. They found out my mom's
address even when I wasn't living here.
Like I was back at the old house. I
don't think I ever used to go to my
mom's and they found out where my mom
lived and they put her address out
there. I've never doxed my mom's address
or any address that I've lived that you
[ __ ] They've always found it. So, you
might want to get your facts right,
Monty. You are the one that has docked
every single address that you've been
at. I've never doxed any address because
if I did, then I'd blame myself. Um, not
that it really makes a lot of
difference, but people shouldn't know
where you live, you know? It's how are
they finding where you live? It's weird.
It's stalking. So, yeah. And then you
were saying Monty. Yeah. About how like,
oh yeah, I bring trouble. I bring
trouble. I mean, bro, at the end of the
day, Timmy started this one. He's the
one that made videos on me. I said, if
you don't stop making if you don't stop
mentioning my name and trying to join
me, I'm going to message your family.
Which I didn't even do, by the way. And
then it somehow progressed. So, yeah.
Yeah, I mean I have started it a lot of
the time, but there's a lot of the time
I [ __ ] have not, mate. And people
will just find any excuse. It's the same
with with LT. Yeah, he claims that he
leaves he's left YouTube and as soon as
you mention his name, he's back trying
to go on your road and [ __ ] It's weirdo
[ __ ] So, I mean, yeah, I mean there are
times like in the L incident um where I
have called people to my mom's. Yes. But
I mean this time around like Timmy
literally started it um just like a lot
of people have before. Um, then that's
and and and that's it at the end of the
day, bro. So, yeah, I've not and at the
end of the day, I actually was thinking
of Laney because I was trying to diffuse
the situation. I was like, "Okay, if I
ignore him, he's just going to go get
bored and just go back." Um, so I
actually done the best thing. But then
as soon as I saw him confront my mom, oh
no, [ __ ] that. That's why as soon as I
saw that, bro, straight in that black
cab, mate. Straight in that black cab.
And then I went to the And then I went
to the [ __ ] um pub where um people
said he was, and he wasn't, and I never
heard from him again. So, shut the [ __ ]
up, Monty. Shut the actual [ __ ] up. And
before you want to start talking about
um dead uh uh uh people's dead relatives
and dead brothers, mate, go get your
kids back first. Yeah. You can't even be
a father to your kids and you're trying
to talk to me about [ __ ] um about
[ __ ] dead relatives and stuff and all
of this and all of that and all of this
and all of that. The thing is, Monty,
yeah, you can sit there and tell
yourself all you want that, oh, people
can't get a woman can't get a woman. Are
you forgetting I could have had your
woman when she was in her prime, bro?
Like I'm like one of the first people
that the woman that you're with now um
fancied. The woman that you're with now
fancied me, bro. Yeah. She's probably
like thinking of you when she's [ __ ]
me. Like that's that's not even a joke,
bro. Like so. And you're trying to tell
me I can't get a woman. Monty, listen,
bro. Yeah. When you was on that break
with [ __ ] Natalie G, all you was
doing is crying and crying and crying
and crying cuz you know your [ __ ] ass
can't get no better. Yeah. So don't come
on here saying this, that, and the
other. And mate, I'll show you the
messages what I sent my mom to to tell
him to wait. I will show you the time of
the video. Yeah. It's not a problem at
all. It is not a problem at all. Timmy
normally is full of [ __ ] and he
doesn't turn up. So I went out. I was
going to go out anyways. I wanted to get
some food. What am I going to do? Stay
in the house for 10 hours? Yeah. It's as
simple as that.
And he was on that road. He definitely
definitely was on that road cuz that
black cab is his. There wouldn't have
been anyone else's, bro. There was a
black cab with no one in it.
So, I mean, yeah, bro. Like, you might
want to you might want to get your kids
back first before trying to [ __ ] talk
about me. Yeah, cuz you are the [ __ ]
reason. I've never doxed my mom's
address ever. These people found out
what it was and then they start [ __ ] and
then they use it against you. Yeah. Not
saying I'm innocent because I'm not
innocent, but don't don't try and make
it seem like it's always me. I mean, how
how do people even know where my mom
lives? I never gave it. They found it
somehow. So, yeah, just get your facts
right in future, please.