Yo. Okay. So, this is my response to um
Timmy. I don't know why you're um trying
to call me a virgin when I've literally
proved numerous times that I've been
with women. And I've actually proved a
few times that I've actually had sex. Uh
one being on video, but yet you still
come on here and call me what you are
yourself, which is the virgin. Um which
is a bit like your followers. Like they
all call me a ma when they're the m
themselves. They all tried to call me
skin when they're the ones that skin
themselves. Else they wouldn't be on
YouTube all day every day if they
weren't skin. I mean, we all know that.
But to be honest with you, Timmy, this
is exactly why I don't show money
anymore because it's like no matter what
people show you people, you just pretend
like you've not seen it because you're
biased. Because you're not liked. You
know, if if anyone comes on here, right,
like me, that's better looking than
these people, that are younger than
these people, that's got a better life
than these people, that can actually
leave their house on like these sad
acts, they're probably [ __ ]
housebound, most of them. Um, you know,
got a glance of hope, they just dislike
you. Um, and then they just start
hating. So, like, you're never ever
going to be liked by these um sad act
people. And they can't even take one day
off of YouTube. Imagine that. Like not
even oh you you come on YouTube every
[ __ ] day. Yeah you know they can't
even take one day off of YouTube.
Imagine their life yet they come on on
on YouTube every day trying to call
other people the manta and call other
people skimp. I truly think these people
right on L J's and yours tibies. They're
so disabled that they don't even realize
that they're talking about themselves
when they're calling other people skin
and other people ugly. They don't
actually realize that they're just
talking about their own life. You know,
that's why I don't come on here
entertaining a bunch of fat, ugly
self-reflectives that ain't got a life.
So, if you had actually listened, I
actually explained why I went live to
me. It was for you, which is why I
mentioned you. It wouldn't have been any
other reason. Like, I I don't have no
business on here. What? Going live to
entertain a bunch of fat ugly people
that ain't got a life? That ain't me,
bro. I'm not interested in that anymore,
you know? Um, and then you was
mentioning, oh, like, yeah, no one can
get my attention. So, Timmy, the reason
they can't get my attention is because
it's been the same [ __ ] with them for
years coming on here self-reflecting.
It's boring, you know? It's boring.
These keyboard warriors have been doing
it for [ __ ] donkeys years. That's why
they don't get my attention. But the
reason I went live is like like I said
if you listen to it right
um you know you you were saying the
other day you actually mentioned me you
were saying oh like if you gamble money
you can afford to lose it's okay. No
it's literally not okay. Right. I lost
money today. Money that I can afford to
lose cuz it's always been money I can
afford to lose you know for the past
three and a half years. And this was
actually the first time in maybe 5
months, like literally about 5 months.
And guess what, Timmy? I didn't have to
go to rehab. And I literally felt like
killing someone. Like, I'm not even
joking. Like, it was it was really,
really bad. If I didn't stop in them 5
months, I would have ended up killing
someone eventually cuz I know what I'm
like with my temper. I would have ended
up in court paying loads and loads of
fines, which is one of the reasons why I
stopped doing it. It's all about
breaking the cycle. when I knew that it
was just always going to be the same.
And um yeah, it it's like I I don't like
losing whether it's £10, 20, 50, whether
I've got a million pound left, whether
I've got £1,000 left, whether I've got
no money left. I don't like losing.
Simple. You know, I I lost a football
bet um last week. It was 20 on the
football. It was a goal off
um it was a goal off a win and it ruined
my whole day. like I literally didn't go
out because of it. Um, so I shouldn't
really be gambling really if it makes
you feel like that. Which is obviously
why, like I said, why I stopped the
roulette and why I stopped the slots
because of that because it was even
worse. The other week I wasn't raging or
mad or anything. It was just a buzzkill.
It was just depressing. Um, you know, I
dressed up to go out and it just ruined
my whole day. And don't try and say that
I never had the money to go out because
I did have the money to go out. It's
just a [ __ ] football bet killed a
[ __ ] vibe. So, how can you go out
when there's no vibe? So, people like me
should be gambling really. Um, but it
didn't make me the football bet didn't
make me angry. It was just a buzzkill.
So, yeah. Um, it doesn't matter if it's
£50 you lose or 20 whether you could
afford it. I don't like losing. I do not
like losing. So, um I had really mad
thoughts to go and smash that bookies up
today, bro. I'm not even joking. But
then I just figured like what's the
point? But obviously, if I had kept
doing it and say I was doing it like you
do, I would have I would have ended up
seriously seriously hurting someone if
not killing someone. So that's why I had to stop.
And that's the thing to me. If you don't
break the cycle, um you're [ __ ] So
that's why I broke I broke the cycle and
now I done it 5 months later. It reminds
me exactly why I stopped doing it
because I don't like losing. Simple.
Don't you know what I'm saying? So
that's how it is. Um and there's nothing
that anyone can say or do that's going
to change that. It's just you just have
to stop gambling. You know, if you're
someone like me, you you you you know,
you just need to stop gambling. Simple.
Um, so that's what I did. It's like
secular stock. She says, "Oh, if you
stick by the rules, right, it's fine,
you know, if you if you uh if you gamble
what you can afford to lose um and
you've got money left over for bills and
stuff, that's what we were doing for 3
and 1/2 years. We never ever gambled
irresponsibly once. I haven't been
skinned for three and a half years, and
it would still give me these mood
swings." So, I mean, yeah, it's crazy.
Absolutely [ __ ] crazy. You know, I've
actually smashed machines before from
losing. You do realize that I've
actually smashed up machines when I've
actually lost and I've actually smashed
a w a window before. Yeah. Not going to
get into it, but yeah. So, that's why
people like me shouldn't gamble. Um,
so yeah, that's that was basically the
live stream to you and me to explain
that I don't like losing. So that's it.
So I'm off here again anyways to me
because unlike you and your uh Skint
followers, I've actually got a [ __ ]
life. So yeah,
there's your response video. You're
lucky you even got one to be honest. For
[ __ ] sake, you're not even worth entertaining.