Yo. Okay. So, yeah, this is going to be
my response to um Joe. Um yeah, just
before I do, um yeah, to I've read that
comment um that Flash account saying
about just because I have nothing in my
life, um that means everyone on YouTube
has nothing um in in their life. If you
had so much [ __ ] in your life, why is it
every single time I have shown you
money, you've all ran away? If you
people like you 40year-old bums really
had anything in life, you wouldn't be
sat on YouTube hating on people that you
don't know that's half your age every
single [ __ ] day. You know what I'm
saying? And to be honest with you, from
where I'm standing, I know from an
unbiased biased point of view, I've
proved to be the best looking on here. I
proved to show the most money on here.
I've proved to had the most life
experiences on here. So, I mean, I don't
really know how long these 40 year old
[ __ ] bums that don't even leave the
house are going to keep trying to
project their misery and their failure
onto other people. I mean, it's it's
just just just think of it. They're
supposed to be setting a good example,
you know? You know, they're they're
they're older than me. Um, but yet
they're the ones that are sat there
projecting their bum old man life onto
me, you know, when they're saying about
how you ain't got this and you ain't got
that. all of these things that these
people wish they've had that they never
have that they tried to put on to you.
It's ridiculous. Like, how long can
these disabled people keep doing this
for? It's It's crazy. So, anyways, Joe,
um I just wanted to start by um saying
uh what is the actual point of your
channel? I don't actually get the point
of it. You know, you're not doing full
gambling videos. Um I don't actually
understand the point of your channel.
Could you tell me what the point of it
is? Um because you're Yeah. You're like
showing money and stuff and then you're
show you're saying that you've asked
you've shown me what I've asked for. No,
you have not. Right. This is the last
time I'm going to do a video on you
because we're going back and forth and
back and forth and back and forth and
you're clearly not understanding what
somebody is saying to you. Right. Let's
start with the whole bias again because
this is where it all starts. Now, when
you are not fat and ugly like these
people on this community, people find a
reason to not like you. I'm going to
explain it to you like a simpleton cuz
you obviously don't get it right. And
what happens when people do not like people?
They get jealous of people and no matter
what they do, they then become biased.
So whether they've took L's or whether
they took W's, people will never ever
admit the truth. All of this, you
showing 1,500 pound, 1,000 pound, 300
pound, that is not you winning. In your
head, that is you winning. Just like
it's in your head that I didn't go to
Mark's area two times whenever he used
to come on YouTube acting like the big
[ __ ] again and it would start all over
again, right? That is not you winning,
right? You're trying to say that I don't
understand things, bro. You don't even
understand the game that you invented,
right? You kept coming on here every
single day saying that people don't have
anything, trying to give a lecture as to
why people don't work and why people
should work. You have been shown
thousands, thousands and thousands and
thousands. You didn't show anything.
Virgin boy didn't show anything and Lar
didn't show anything. The evidence is
there, which is the indication on the
vehicle that you are the skint ones.
Every single thing that you're doing
right now, right? Um, you know, showing
a,000, you know, it goes to show that
you've been skint all this time because
if you had money, you would have shut my
ass up a long time ago when I was
showing you that 5.7 grand. You
literally waited until I put that money
in the bank and I said, "I'm never
showing you people money ever again."
And then you start your [ __ ] again. You
start showing less than the amount that
I have shown you and act like you've
won. That's not how that works. I don't
know how many times I have to explain it
to you disabled people, but I won't be
explaining it again. And then I got
backdated money. Joe, a wise man learns
from their mistakes. Just like when I
used to show you little skimp
self-reflecting bastards thousands and
thousands and thousands and then you all
run away and you don't show anything and
then I say okay well I'm putting this
money in the bank now I'm showing you
nothing again cuz you've shown yourself
is what you really are self projectors
and then you come back showing £800 to
about a,000 acting like you've won. Bro,
you're pathetic. Why do you think I've
not gone to I didn't go to Birmingham on
Friday to call that Timmy and that um
Mike out? Because a wise man learns from
his mistakes to get better, right? And
we all know how the GTA V city stories
go. When you show these people money,
they all run away. We all know what
happens when you go to people's area and
you call them out. They all forget it
never happens. It's a waste of our time.
Joe, if you really really really are so
adamant that you beat me at the money
game, show us your £10,000 in cash. Stop
making excuses that you know you don't
have the money in cash and ret mate.
There's so there's something called a
bank, right? This is another thing you
actually did answer yesterday. You was
about um you were saying about how oh I
don't have um I didn't have that money
in cash. Okay, go to the bank and get it
out in cash. What's stopping you? You
must have knew the day was going to come
where somebody beat you at the money
game. So, it's like we all know what
you're about. So, when you and Virgin
Boy or you know a few others show
20% of the amount of money I've shown,
I'm just laughing at you because that is
not you winning. That is you losing and
have it in your head that you've won.
Because if you was actually winning and
you actually had money, mate, you would
have shut my ass up that first week that
I was showing that 5.7 grand. But you,
LJ, Virgin Boy, you all went running
away, [ __ ] losers. And then you come
online like you've won, showing a less
amount. Do you know this ties in with
the whole biaslessness when I say that
you people actually forget your L's. You
know, you you you might remember a lot
of people's L's on here, but you seem to
forgot forget a lot about yours. And do
you know what? This is going to be my
last response to you because we're going
over the same thing over and over and
over again. If you want to keep thinking
you showing less than what I've shown
you means you've won. Okay, you've won.
But we all know the truth deep down. You
know, whether people want to admit it or
not. And do you know what? When you if
you're going to respond to this video,
do you know what you should do?
responding a video talking since you
like to tell other people that they've
got anxiety. You you know what I'm
saying? So, you know, you haven't won.
You've not beat me at the money game. Um
and so neither as Virgin Boy as and
neither has Lord Jay. You coming online
showing less than what I've shown acting
like you've won is exactly what Mark
Samson used to. It's similar to the Mark
Samson thing. It always goes back to
that, you know, when he used to come on
acting like he's one and then everyone
just forgets about it. This is why we
don't waste our time on you anymore.
It's not because people don't have money
or people. It's because we know the Vice
City stories already what you people do.
Just like I know if I went to Birmingham
today, I know exactly what would happen.
You know, I'd waste my time. I'd waste
my money. None of these people would
show up and then they'd all forget about
it. Same old boring [ __ ] Vice City
Stories. You know what I'm saying? A
wise man learns from their mistakes.
Joe, you showing all of this silly money
that was nowhere near close to what I
showed you before I gave up because you
clearly was never ever going to beat me
at the money game. You're lying to
yourself. So, that's my last response to
you anyways. Um, you know, and if you
are going to show money, at least
[ __ ] show double the amount that I've
shown, not [ __ ] 20% of what I've
shown. [ __ ] pathetic.
Get a grip, Joe. For [ __ ] sake. Act
your age and not your shoe size.