Okay, so I'm at the restaurant now. I
said I was going to go for a meal
earlier. Oh my god, this is lush. Oh,
this is lush, mate. [snorts]
Just waiting for the other stuff to
come. So yeah,
you should appreciate this. Grezy
spent over200 today just giving you content.
Just giving you content.
Yeah, I'll pause and resume when the
rest of the stuff comes.
The light went off. That's why the
lights off in case you was wondering.
>> There we go.
>> Yeah, man.
>> There we go. Lovely.
>> Thank you, Captain. >> Yeah,
I know that. Jesus Christ. I mean, how
long have I been going to these uh indie bums?
Yeah, this is lush, man. Then the curry
is going to come after.
So what you do? You dip it in a bit of mint sauce.
Like that. Yeah. [music]
Bit of lemon on it. [music] Okay.
Yeah. Going to enjoy it and uh show when
the when the curry comes and the na
better. I got to choose nom. I don't
know what we're going on, but today I
fancy the cheese on. Yeah,
I literally smashed that [music] in like
sure was under a minute. [snorts]
That was delicious, man. I paused it um
cuz I wanted to enjoy it without filming.
Yeah. And I'll resume when the curry
comes. [music] Like I said, look at
that. I ate so fast. And it's not cuz
I'm rushing it. It's just so yummy.
And here it is, man.
Lamb vanilla and the cheese. Na, I said,
"Can you put lots of cheese on the
naan?" Cuz you know, sometimes
when you order it, [music]
they will um
not put a lot of cheese on the naan. Oh, mate.
Look at that. That is lovely. Look how
fluffy the rice is.
It's so much different when you actually
go to a restaurant and eat it, you know. Beautiful.
Anyways, I'm going to finish this
and uh yeah. Beautiful.