Yo. Okay, so time for a new video. Um,
the lamb's cooking in the oven. It's
smelling very, very nice. It's not quite
ready yet, so I feel like, yeah, whilst
I wait for the lovely Sunday roast lamb
to be cooked, um, I want to talk about
uh, double standards. Um, I was live
earlier and somebody said to me that,
you know, just because you went out and
you was brave and you approached women,
um, it doesn't mean that they owe you a
date. Now, here's the thing, right? If
you went to I can use this in a few
different examples. If you went to the
gym and you put effort into going to the
gym and you worked out and you would get
something out of it, you know, you'd
gain muscle, you'd have a better body,
you would just be better overall um
because you've put effort into it. You
because you've put time into it. Same
thing if you went to work and um you put
the hours in, even if you didn't really
like the job or you you know,
you didn't want to go to work, but you
did. You put the hours in, you get paid
at the end of the week. It's no
different than dating. I feel like if
you're prepared to put yourself out
there and do what most people don't do
and are scared of doing, I kind of feel
like you are owed something. I generally
like I know a lot of people will feel
like I'm being delusional when I'm
saying this, but why wouldn't you be
owed anything? You put the time in, you
put the effort in, you've been
confident, yet women claim they like
confident men. So, I mean, I I don't
know what's the problem with expecting a
date. What's the problem with you going
out, putting the hours in, putting the
effort in, and expecting a date at the
end of it? I mean, it's not exactly
asking for too much, is it? And I always
feel like that whole women don't owe you
anything is always used to try to
justify their shitty actions. So, for
example, like say you um you're texting
a woman and she leads you on on purpose
or she arranges to meet you and then she
doesn't turn up or um you know they they
don't reply to a message or some shitty
thing that they do on purpose. You'll
always get these people come and say,
"Well, they don't owe you anything
anyways." It's such a lame attempt to
try to cover up the fact that what
they're doing is wrong. So they try to
paint it as, oh well, they don't owe you
anything. That's not what that means.
Um, you know, it's it's used in the
wrong context. Just because somebody
doesn't owe someone something, it
doesn't um excuse the right for them to
be ignorant and lead people on and do
all of the shitty things um that they
do. You know, it's used in the wrong
context. They use it to cover
up women's shitty behavior. Whereas if
you was, for example, lying in bed every
day moaning that you got no money, you
know, I mean, yeah, then the world
doesn't owe you anything because you can
go out, put the hours in work, make some
money, you know, but I don't know how
they can try and tell you a woman
doesn't owe you anything when you've put
the time, the effort, the hours in, and
the fact that what they've done is
shitty. It's like, and here's the thing,
right? This is how you know it's double
standards because I have never ever
heard about um a man not owning a woman
anything. Never in a million years. The
amount of times, right, I have seen um you know
uh women complain about men. Never once
is a woman ever told, "Well, the man
doesn't owe you anything." But if you're
a man that has to go through negative
experiences with women, well, they don't
owe you anything. No, they don't owe you
nothing. But then it's when it's a man
doing it to a woman, um there's
absolutely no problems. Get on with it.
You know what I'm saying? So, it's like
I have never ever ever heard um someone
say a man doesn't owe you anything to a
woman. And if it was really about people
not owing people anything, um it would
be both genders and it would also be,
like I said, men not owing women
anything. It's just used as a little
cover up to just dismiss any
kind of woman's shitty behavior. I think
that's the better word for it for it. A
woman does something shitty and then
they'll try to dismiss it by saying,
"Oh, well, they don't owe you anything."
When that's not what that is and that
doesn't justify it, but people still use
it. And you know there's a few other
things as well like this is going to
sound um you know quite uh personal but
you know if you Jesus Christ if you
don't want to give um a woman um oral
sex because where I'm from it's it's
frowned upon um to give um a woman oral
sex. You will get these people that say
to you, "Oh, you're gay. You're
homosexual. Gay gay gay gay gay. anyone
that doesn't, you know, eat a woman out,
you're gay. But yet, if a woman doesn't
want to give people a [ __ ] oh,
that's fine. That's her choice. She just
didn't want to do it. Um, you see, the
double standards is absolutely [ __ ]
disgusting. Like, that's just like two
um examples right there. And there's
many, many, many more. Um, but I mean,
that that one was a funny one. It's like
if you cuz there's some people that
don't like giving oral. You know, a lot
of people don't like giving oral. Some
people don't even like receiving oral to
be fair. But you know, if you don't want
to eat a woman out, you will get people
come at you with an axe calling you gay.
Um but yeah, if a woman doesn't want to
give a [ __ ] then oh well, she
doesn't want to give a [ __ ] and she
doesn't owe you anything for [ __ ]
sake. Um so it's just it's just the
double standards is disgusting. Um it
really really really is. Um
and then like for example if if if a man
struggles to um get a woman, he's all
the things under the sun, he's got a bad
personality, he has hygiene issues, retlains
about a man, um oh well maybe you just
haven't found the right one and they're
all the problem but not you. The double
standards is crazy.
um you know that women don't owe you
anything is is if if if they said it
about men as well then they'd kind of
have some argument. But the fact that
they never ever say it um to to women
about men not owing them anything. It's
so obvious. It was just that was just
invented by a simp to try to dismiss the
shitty things that women do and cover it
up like paint um by saying, "Oh well,
well, they don't owe you anything."
Because that way by them saying
something, they feel like they've got a
valid point and it ends the whole thing.
It's [ __ ] ridiculous. The double
standards is insane.
Like I'm going to title this video as double standards or insane.