Okay, so this is generally going to be
my last response um to Timmy because I'm
done wasting my time on these [ __ ]
losers now. But I'm going to throw
Tramodol in there. Um
damn Tramodo. Do you know what? To be
honest with you, yeah, before you was
actually something to laugh at, you
know, like your desperate attempts to
try to get people killed and to try to
ruin people's lives all because you're a
fat ugly bastard that ain't got a life
of your own. Like that generally was
something to laugh at. But now you're
just like generally something to feel
sorry for. Like you're you're you're
actually generally something to to pity.
Like there's there's no joke there
anymore. Like you're actually I was
listening to you for them 3 minutes,
bro. like when you was on um Timmy's
Hangouts and I've never ever heard
somebody so desperate, so angry, and so
determined to actually get another
person to make them believe that they're
as ugly as you actually are. Like, wow.
Like, you was going on about my looks
and everything. Now, Trao, listen here.
Yeah. Isn't it funny how all of these
people that have done this in the past,
including yourself, have all been a
million times uglier than me? Does does
that not tell you all you need to know? Bomb Patmastered.
You as well. I mean, everyone knows what
you look like as well. There's actually
been a picture. Is it mad how all of you
people that talk about people's looks
are just a million times uglier? It's
it's it's like it's a coincidence, isn't
it? Like, and it's it's it's crazy. And
you was sat there saying about how like,
"I'm not trying to put you down or
anything or whatever." Well, bro, if you
know that you're better looking than me
and I'm all of these things, then
wouldn't you just leave me alone? I
mean, it's it's crazy. I've got loads of
strangers on this community that are
obsessed with me, that stalk me every
single day, yet I'm the ugly one. Is it
is it funny? Like that that generally is
funny. You got to laugh at that. I mean,
come on, bro. Like, it's it's it's
embarrassing. Now, and here's the thing
that I've got to ask you and Timmy,
right? If I'm all of these things, why
am I the only one on here that's been
seen with women? Why am I the only one
on here that's had his uh sloppy seconds
stalked because said people couldn't get
them because of their looks? Why is it
that if I am all of these things,
traumador, why have I had more women than
most people on this community, then? Why
have I been seen? Why am I the only Let
me actually rephrase that. Why am I the
only one that's been seen with women?
And Timmy was trying to say about how,
oh, well, yeah, we haven't seen you with
women. Exactly why I don't play the
money game anymore. Because when you
show these people money, they pretend
they they ain't seen anything. It's a
waste of time arguing with these retards
on this community. But yeah, um you've
seen me Timmy in in bed with several
different women. Like I've actually
still got the videos on my phone, but
there's there's there's literally no
point me even putting them up. Um
because everything you're shown, you
just pretend you've not seen it. So,
it's like even though you prove you're
better looking than these people and you
prove that you've, I don't know, got
more money than these people, they will
still point blank the night because
they're [ __ ] disabled. That's why
there's like no point even with anyone
on this community and and that's why I
had no plans to come back except explain
what I was explaining to Timmy because
it's it it it's just crazy. But yeah,
Tramodol, it is it is a madness how I'm
so ugly, yet I've been seen with all of
these women in bed, on dates, kissing,
and I'm so ugly that all of these people
that have tried calling me ugly in the
past when their face has been out there,
I've been better looking than them and
they've run away. Yeah, I know, man. It
sucks being ugly, isn't it? Yeah. Yeah.
Yeah. I mean, bro, you really need to
seek some help. Like, you really really
do. Like, you can actually
you can actually sense the angle in your
voice. And bro, the only one that's not
showing their face now is yourself. So,
and we we all seen what you look like as
well. Like you and Timmy, you you are
the only virgins. Okay, let's put me,
you, and Timmy, right, in the equation.
Who's the one that's been seen with
women? Who's the one that's been been
seen? Who's the one that's been seen in
bed with women? Me. And yeah, I I get
what you mean, Trump. Oh, just because
Lisa and um all of these other women on
on on YouTube say that I'm good-looking,
it doesn't mean that I'm good-looking.
And bit bit jealous, isn't it? Because
you've never been cool looking. I mean,
yeah. But don't you think it's a bit
weird, Tra how they're calling me
good-looking, but they're not calling
you good-looking? And I get your point.
He was like, "Oh, just cuz a few women
on YouTube say you're good-looking, it
doesn't mean you're good-looking." Yeah,
but Truman, the point is that they're
calling me good-looking and not you
good-looking. And that you probably took
that a bit to heart, but no, that
doesn't prove anything. That doesn't
prove anything at all, Truman. But what
does prove something is the fact that
I've literally been seen with more women
than you've had hot dinners. That's that
I think means something. And that proves
that the only one that's ugly is
literally yourself. Because bro, you
It's embarrassing how you can sit there
talking to yourself for 3 minutes about
how I've not how I'm too ugly and I'm do
this, I'm that, but you're the only one
that's never been seen with a woman. You
and Timmy, the ones that are calling
people ugly virgins, are the only ones
that's never been seen with women. But
Peter Belly has been seen with [ __ ]
plenty. I think that says it all, Batty.
I think that I think that says it all.
Yeah, man. You You need to actually seek
some help. Anyways,
if I'm really all of these things, then
how comes I'm the one that can take a
day off of YouTube, but none of you can,
you know, cuz I I'll be doing it from
now. If I'm really all of these things,
join me and get off of YouTube. After
this video, I'm getting off of YouTube.
So, if I'm really all of these things
and you're not, even though I've proved
how you already are, get off of YouTube
and don't come back. Take one day off of
YouTube. Take take a week off of you.
No, don't say get off YouTube, never
come back. Trum, come off of YouTube for
one week. If I'm truly the ugly one and
I'm this and I'm that, bro, then how
about you get off of YouTube for one week?
If I'm really all of them things, come offline.
Exactly. Cuz you're talking about
yourself. You are generally really
subbing to pity now. I feel bad for you.
You and Timmy are the actual virgins on
YouTube. Um along with, you know, other
people we're not going to mention, but I
mean, it's really sad, bro. You hate yourself.
We can hear it from your voice trauma
though. You hate yourself.