All right. Sorry. I tried to do this a
few times, but it kept cutting off about
six times. Um, okay. So, this is going
to be my reply to this [ __ ] fat,
ugly, nerdy, skint, wrinkly, pathetic um
little keyboard warrior. Now, I know you
shouldn't give these sad acts, you know,
the the time of day, cuz to be honest,
they're already living their worst life,
having to come on YouTube every day
hating on people that they don't know,
all because they're ugly, jealous
nobodyies. But before I get into this,
yeah, me and my mom was talking about
this earlier. You know, good old Laney.
And we come to the conclusion that it's
jealousy on this community. Like, think
about it, bro. I've got like a loving
mom. I've got a sister. These people
ain't got no family. And to be honest, I
have noticed it myself, you know, being
on here for, you know, the many years I
have. Every time around December, these
people get more bitter. They get more
hateful because think about it,
Christmas is coming up. They ain't got
no family. They ain't got no friends.
They ain't got no money. They're going
to be sat on YouTube on Christmas all
alone. Despite them saying that, "Oh,
they're not going to be on YouTube
Christmas, bro." Trust me, these fat
nerdy projectors ain't got nothing in
their life. Um, despite trying to tell
other people they ain't got this, they
ain't got that. They need to literally
wake up and smell the coffee that, bro,
it's almost 2026 and you're talking
about yourself and you've been doing
this now for, you know, a very, very
long time. Like generally these people
on this community, a lot of them like
the haters, they need a [ __ ] mirror
for Christmas Day. Like Santa needs to
give them a mirror so they can look in
the mirror and realize that everything
that they're trying to talk about other
people, it's their own lives. And like I
said, these people ain't even got
family. Probably their family has
disowned them. Um this is why they do
this. But anyways, I'm going to get on
to what you've wrote. Yeah. And I'm
going to add another thing on uh after
it because yeah, you've said another
thing a few times on uh someone else's
channel. Um I've meant to do a video on
you before, but now I'm doing that. I'm
going to add you on this. Right. So,
right, own place. Uh I don't want to
live in a cancelled bedsit. I mean, I've
I've said a million times, I don't want
to live in a canceled bedsit. I'd rather
live with my mom in a house than a
cancelled bedsit. [clears throat]
Girlfriend, you don't have a girlfriend.
Um, so you know, you you might want to
think about yourself before talking
about other people's self-projector. And
he's got a disabled girlfriend. I've
never had to resort to a girl that's
disabled. You don't have a girlfriend
and you're more than likely still a
virgin, but you're trying to talk about
me. How can you talk about people having
girlfriends and not having girlfriends
when, bro, you're in your 40s and you're
probably still a [ __ ] virgin? Like,
let's face it. All of the women that
I've been with, and I put it on YouTube,
me kissing, me sleeping with, you
probably tried to wank your little
erectile dysfunction wrinkly dick
because that's the only action that
you'll ever get, bro. You don't have a
girlfriend. You don't have a woman. You
probably never seen a woman naked in
person and you're going to try and talk
about a 28-year-old. Really, bro?
Really? Come on now. It's embarrassing.
Like, it's a time now to grow up. Um,
and like I said, I've never had to
resort to a disabled girl like him. So,
that's YouTube out the way. Um, job. He
doesn't have a job. You don't have a
job. And I have had a job and I've
earned my own money. Next. Right. Uh,
has money. You don't have any money. He
[snorts] doesn't have money. And I have
more money than both of you combined.
And I've shown more money than both of
you combined ever have and ever will.
Self project. That 13 grand that he
showed was about four years ago that he
kept showing over and over again the
same video, mate. We've all seen me show
money and we've all seen you people run
away. So, you might want to remember
this when you're self- projecting your
skintness every day onto other people,
you loser. Anyways, unique dress sense.
I mean, yeah, he's got a unique dress
sense because he's too skint to be able
to afford anything normal just like you,
which we're going to get on to in a bit.
self-projecting has hobbies. You don't
have hobbies and he don't have hobbies.
I mean, you stalk me every single day on
YouTube self-projecting. What could you
possibly have? Has a life. He don't have
a life. You don't have a life. Let me
tell you something, right? I have done
more in my 28 years of life than you two
have combined, ever have, and ever will,
which is mad because you say that he's
got a life. He's got He has a future,
but I've already done more than both of
you put together at 28 years of age.
Isn't that a thing? Isn't that a damn
thing? And let me tell you something,
right? I love the jealousy on here. Um,
you have wrote on someone else's channel
that I bought my jeans and trainers and
I and I've used Kana. Never used Colana
in my [ __ ] life. So, this is what I
mean with these jealous fat, ugly low
lives that ain't got a family. Even when
you prove that you got more money than
them and you show clothes that they can
never afford like Ammani vapors, they
they just make up stuff like, you know,
you use CLA. Never in my life have I
ever been so skintike you, Mr. £300 a
month boy, where I have to, you know,
um, pay off for things, bro. Just cuz
you can't afford things and you wear
Primark stuff and you're on £300 a month
doesn't mean people pay off for their
clothes. Um, anyone that generally
believes, if you're interested, that I
pay off for my clothes, I'm more than
happy to show you receipts. Um, any
genuine people like Greavvesy or anyone
that watches me, Snapchat me. I will
show you full evidence of my purchases.
I'm not proving to some fat, ugly, low
life um, what I do and what I don't do.
Are you [ __ ] mad, bro? Like, do you
think we are born to prove fat, ugly,
familyless losers like you wrong time
and time and time and time and time and
time and time and time again? Really,
bro? Is that what you think we wake up
and get out of bed for? To come on
YouTube and prove you fat, lowife bully
victims what we have and we don't have.
Here's the thing, bro. You show that
you're not a fat ugly bastard. What I've
been calling you all along, fat, ugly,
low life. Then come back to me. I will
show you money because the irony is you
and another other person was asking me
to show receipts. You don't tell me what
I need to prove to you. You fat ugly
[ __ ] I have asked you numerous times,
you self-projecting virgin. Show what
you look like. Show your face. Show what
you look like. Show your face. And then
you don't do it. So, bro, don't come on
here and start telling me what I need to
prove to you skin ugly people just cuz
you can't afford 200lb jeans. you
jealous fat [ __ ] Um, and that's that.
And here's the thing, bro. We're getting into 2026
and you're still using the word manta.
Bro, I'm younger and I'm better looking
than you. Stop it. It's embarrassing
now. You know, you make comments along
with other people about how this
community is dying. It's It's dying
because you fat ugly losers keep coming
on here putting yourselves down, calling
yourself skin, calling yourself a ma.
I'm a manta, bro. I've been with more
women than you've had hot dinners, you
and your boyfriend. Everyone that's on
that's not biased on YouTube have seen
me with multiple multiple multiple
multiple women that you've never had.
Multiple dates that you can't get cuz
you're ugly. Yet you're trying to say
that I've not got a girlfriend. Bro,
before self-p projecting in the future,
you might you might want to think about
this. You're trying to tell people they
ain't got a girlfriend. Bro, you ain't
got a girlfriend. You never even been
with a woman. You're trying to tell
people they ain't got a job, bro. You've
never had a job in your life. You're sat
on YouTube every day, Skin, waiting for
your 300 monthly money benefits. It's
embarrassing. Now, you need to get a
mirror for Christmas and look in the
mirror and stop self projecting.
Everything that you say is about
yourself. How are you going to come on
here try and tell people they ain't got
a girlfriend when they've had more women
than you would ever have and you're
single? Do you not see the problem with
that, bro? Like single, no family, no
money, jealous of people that's got
more, which I get it. You know, I spent
over £400 on jeans and trainers, which
is more than your It's almost double.
It's almost two months of your money. So
then you say that I use colada. [ __ ]
[laughter] hell. I mean, at at first it
was really really funny, but then it
just becomes sad. Like, you fat ugly
familyless losers, if that's even a
word, need to get a [ __ ] life. You're
boring. No wonder why the [ __ ]
community is dead because they're sick
of you fat, ugly mongos. Boring people
to death. But like I said, bro, if you
ever want me to show you receipts, show
you money, you loser. I am more than
happy to show your face, prove that
you're not fat and ugly, and prove
everything Peter Belly's been saying
about you on here is wrong, and I'll
happily show you receipts. They're on my
emails. I bought them online. So, until
then, don't start asking people to prove
themselves to you fat ugly losers. I can
show you money right now. I can show you
receipts right now. Everything paid off
in full. I'm not [ __ ] proving myself
to some fat ugly little low life. Are
you [ __ ] mad? I don't wake up out of
bed to prove to some fat ugly mong that
ain't even got a mum what I have and
what I don't have. Remember that in your
head. Like really let that drill in your
head. That's not how that works, bro.
Get a [ __ ] life, you sad selfprojecting
[ __ ] little virgin.
That's me, bro.