Yo. Okay, so time for a new dating
video. So, anyone who's watching this,
count yourself lucky that um yeah,
you've got a new one so fast and you
don't have to wait months and months and
months. Um yeah, I've got some stuff to
get off my chest and um yeah, something
really messed up happened today. So, I
thought why not share it with YouTube,
link the video to a couple of people,
and you know, when I go live again,
people can have their opinion. share
their view and just yeah, just we'll
just uh talk about it. So, I'm actually
going to title this video, yeah, as just
another slap to the face because I
generally feel like, you know, when you
put out put yourself out there dating,
trying to meet women, you always just
get slapped in the face, you know? I
used to like think it's like you you go
up 10 stairs to get knocked aund 100
steps back, you know? like that's how it
always used to feel with like the whole
dating thing and and that's why I like
just don't really bother with it much
anymore. But anyways, so
let's get started. Right. So in my
previous video, right, um I was saying
about how you know whenever you approach
a woman and you get a woman's number and
you speak to them, you know, via text
message and you try to meet them within
4 to seven days, you always get people
making these excuses. You're trying to
meet them too fast. you're too pushy,
you're too clingy. Like, they will
always find an excuse to basically put
the blame onto you and basically suggest
that you need to speak to women for a
longer period of time. But the problem
is is that even when you speak to women
for a longer period of time, they still
have no intentions of meeting you. You
know, most of the time, you know,
they'll still come out with excuses.
They'll still flake. So, you know, it
doesn't matter if you've spoke to a
woman for four days, 5 days, you know,
trying to meet them or you spoke to them
for 10 years, you know, they're still
they're still going to do the same
thing, you know, at the end of the day.
So, they'd always there'd always be that
double standard. Whereas, you know, if a
woman wanted to try to meet you straight
away, they'd have no problem. Um, which
I don't understand why they seem to
think that if you speak to a woman for a
longer period of time, um, they're going
to be any more declined to meet you.
that there's more chance of them meeting
you. Um, you know, because I the only
thing I can I can think of is maybe they
think that the woman has common courtesy
or common decency that she wouldn't want
to waste her time and she wouldn't want
to waste your time. But sadly, um, hate
to be the bear bad news, but this
Christian Izzy um, I've been speaking to
for a month and I'll tell everybody the
story. Um, I can't believe a month has
gone that quickly. I swear to God, it
just seemed like a week ago that I met
her and I started talking to her in this
bar/ like club thing. Um, the last time
I went out drinking. Yeah, like it's
mad. It doesn't seem like a month. Time
generally does fly. Um, so yeah. Uh,
basically uh I was in a I went out on
Thursday uh last month. Got my hair
done, got my beard done. I needed a good
groom and I figured, you know what?
Hadn't been out trying to meet women for
3 months. haven't drunk for 3 months.
So, what a better way what better way to
get back in the game. New year, new me.
Just go out and just yeah, see what
happens. So, I ended up in this uh bore
and I approached Christian Izzy. I
thought, "Oh, yeah, she look that's her
name. We we know her as that." So, um
went over and spoke to her. I thought,
you know what? Why not? Um she looks
nice. Um she's my type, whatever. And I
was actually expecting that like she was
just going to say straight away that she
has a boyfriend or she's not interested
or um maybe give me some attitude
because that's like what a lot of women
are like nowadays. So I thought like
that's going to happen. But I mean I've
got nothing to lose by doing it. So
literally went over there and started
talking to her and she was she was
really nice, you know. Um she seemed
genuine. She seemed down to earth. Um
and yeah, like she asked me what my
heritage was. We was talking about food,
whatever. Like everything was good. Um
she told me about a couple of her exes,
but she didn't go in depth. Um not until
later on. Um but uh yeah, and she was
basically saying to me, um she was
basically saying to me, um her dating
requirements is that someone has to go
to church and somebody has to go to uni
and uh complete a degree. Um and I
thought it was a bit dodgy. I thought it
was a bit weird. I said to her, "Okay,
yeah, I'll go to church because I mean,
I've never been to church before." And
at the end of the day, people have
always suggested church to meet new
women. So, I'm thinking, you know, there
this woman's a Christian. If she's a
good woman, which she's coming across as
she is, then obviously, yeah, I I don't
mind going to church. I'd go to church.
And, you know, if anything, it's it
could do me, you know, the world of
good, you know? So, I mean, why why not?
So, I agreed to that. And I basically
thought, yeah, it's it is what it is.
But I thought she I thought she was just
saying that to sort of maybe like keep
her guard up to kind of the men that she
goes with in the future because she's
been with like guys before and stuff. So
I thought, okay, whatever. Um, don't
know where that random requirement came
from, but anyways. So got her number
right and text her the next day. Now,
obviously, I'm not expecting a response
because the I've had so many so many bad
experiences, you know, where I've got
people's numbers and they've not replied
or they've replied and they've stopped
replying. So, it goes in stages. So,
every time something has happened like
I'm getting a message on the next day,
I'm thinking like at any position like
this woman is just going to like [ __ ] me
over, you know? It's it's obvious
because what's the chances now? 6 years
down the line everything changes. um
there is there is no chance you know at
the end of the day you know patterns
tend to repeat themsel and it's only
getting worse as well if there is a
change but anyways on a positive note um
you know 2026 I thought I had good
spirits following me around doing me a
good deed she's messaged me and we was
like talking and talking and talking she
was replying back now she asked me what
my body count was which I thought was
very very strange um you know That's a
very weird thing to ask somebody that
you're saying that you just want to be
friends with and whatever and
it will make sense later on in the
story. She was asking me what my body
count was and how she liked green eyes
and so what she's doing essentially is
she's playing games plus giving me false
hope and mixed messages as opposed to
like just straight like leading. It's
it's it's a difficult one. Um and yeah,
she was basically saying about how like
yeah um this is what she goes for that
and whatever and like deep down like she
was go and then and then me being me I
was like oh like after a little while I
was like oh like do you want to just
like meet up and just yeah just get a
drink and see where it goes cuz my whole
intentions was just to meet her and just
spend time with her like I didn't care
about the dating. I didn't care about
the relationship. Didn't want sex. I
just wanted to meet someone to spend
time with just to see where it goes. So,
we kept going on and talking and voice
noting like literally all day. It was
all day for most days having really good
chats. Then I said to her like, "Do you
want to meet up?" And um she turned
around and said, "Oh, I'm busy with
exams." Now, to be fair, I just saw it
coming, but me being me, I like to give
people the benefit of the doubt. You
know, she seemed very stressed when she
was messaging me. She seemed
overwhelmed. She showed me her studying
and I thought, "Okay, give it the
benefit of the doubt. You know, I would
like to think that if someone's
messaging me for so many days and so
long, they're not going to just make
excuses not to meet me." Boy, was I
wrong. So, we then we then start talking
every day and talking every day and
whatever. And then she was she went back
to how she's not looking for anyone
despite asking me all the questions you
would ask somebody if you was
interviewing them to be a candidate
partner of yours. So that's why it
didn't make sense. But then I thought it
doesn't matter anyways is what she's
saying because you know she said that
she's going to meet me. She's agreed to
meet me no matter what way it is. Um you
know and she's stressed and she's had
bad experiences with her exes. Um and
you know she's overwhelmed because of
exams. So I just gave her the benefit of
the doubt. Whatever. Cool. Um me being
me. Yeah. I still say I'm somewhat color
to be fair. Um what what did annoy me?
It annoyed me and it upset me at the
same time because I just couldn't stop
thinking to myself when she was going on
about her ex, you know, cheating on her
and having a baby with someone else. The
only thing that I was thinking in my
head is did he need to go to uni and get
a degree? Did he need to um you know uh
go to church every Sunday? No, he
didn't. So, why are all of these requirements
um you know expected of me that I need
to do all of these things, but none of
her exes ever did? You know, I'm not
ugly. There's nothing wrong with the way
that I look. We get on fine. There's
nothing wrong. Like, we have similar
interests. We've both got decent person.
She seemed down to earth. So, I enjoy
talking to her. So, I thought to myself,
like, why don't I why do I need to have
all of these things that her her ex's
never had? And I'm thinking it did. It
is kind of bit of a slap in the face.
You know, when you approach someone and
they say they've got a boyfriend or
whatever, that's just whatever, you
know, or if you speak to someone for a
day or whatever, it is what it is. But
when someone's been speaking to you for
so long, you know, there's nothing wrong
with you and they're they're they're
making up requirements that you should
have that no one else you've been with
or will get with in the future will have
to have. It is a big slap in the face,
you know, and it hits harder when you've
been speaking to somebody for longer as
well. Um, so it is what it is. And then
we was talking and talking and talking
and talking and talking. Um, so yeah,
just normal chat every day. I said, "If
you ever need me, talk to me." Like I
the the thing is I was trying to show
her that, you know, not all men are bad
cuz obviously she had bad experiences.
If I'm the only good man that you'll
meet, you know, then I'm the only good
man that you meet. But I was trying to
show her like I'm not like this, I'm not
like that. And obviously I don't know
what these guys in the past have told
her um you know or done or what ways
they've manipulated her. So it you know
I can't be very convincing but over time
I thought to think like the thing is
that's it you know and um we was talking
and yeah I just said uh basically
um yeah like I'm I'm you know like I'm
this comes across came across as genuine
as nice as possible. And this is what
makes me laugh. you know, all of these
women like her will get cheated on by
her exes and whatever and then when she
has the chance to finally meet a normal
nice guy, they're not interested. This
is exactly they they play the runaround,
they play games. And this is what is
annoying. Like when I sit there and I
say like all women are the same where
I've never had that opportunity to be
shown different. See, in this case, you
got one person with bad experiences with
women, one person with bad experiences
with men, but the person with bad
experiences with men don't want to meet
the nice guy. There's a nice guy in
front of her that wants to meet her, and
I don't expect anything, and she doesn't
want to meet, and she wants to play
games and lead people on and and and say
she's going to meet them, but then don't
meet them. So, it's like, what what what
what do you expect? And yeah, so
anyways, we spoke and her her exams
finally finished. So, I was like, "Okay,
now we're going to know if she's really
going to meet me or is she going to make
excuses?" I said to her like, "Do you
want to just want to meet next week and
go for some food, go for some
cocktails?" Um, you know, didn't expect
anything. Just wanted to meet and
whatever it is is whatever it is. I'm
getting older now. I don't really really
expect much. Um, then she turned around
and said to me, "Oh, um, I'm busy on
Friday." Um, I said, "Okay, what about
Saturday?" She's like, "Um, I don't
know. I'll let you know." And I'm
thinking, listen, right, I know that you
don't want to meet me. It's as simple as
that. like if if people will make time
for you, right? The exam thing, you
know, that could be legit, whatever. I
gave her the benefit of the doubt. I was
a friend to her. I was nice to her. I
said, "You call me anytime you need me."
I used to wake up to 23 messages
basically. Like, I know you don't want
to meet because you would make time. You
know, I've offered to go to your like
where your area. I've offered to meet
you in like a bar. You don't want to
meet. You're saying that you're going to
let me know which obviously you're not
going to meet me. So, I'm thinking, what
was the point of speaking to me for all
that time with no intentions of meeting?
Yet, you asking me all of these personal
questions. What's my body count? What's
this? And she did say she was going to
meet, you know. And obviously, if
someone's saying they're going to meet
you 100% and they're not looking for
anything right now, you just think that,
you know, finally they're going to get
over their exams. Finally, they're going
to get over their ex. Hopefully, they
changed their mind. And she was going in
on me. You know, she was being rude and
everything. I'm thinking, what? This
isn't the same person I was speaking to
a month ago, you know, when we was
getting on every single day and she was
saying, "Oh, you're this, you're that."
I was like, "You want to say that I'm
too forward?" You literally ask me how
many women that I've had sex with. Um,
and then she just started playing victim
and yeah, to be fair, I was expecting it um
to be fair. Um, but obviously is it is a
bit [ __ ] because obviously I've been
speaking to them for a month, you know,
and I was kind of looking forward to
meeting them. But this is what I'm
trying to say. This is always the same
thing that is is going to happen, you
know, and at the end of the day, they
come across a nice guy, they come across
someone that's not ugly, and it's still
not good enough. Like, you can tick
every single one of these women's boxes
and they'd still find an excuse not to
get with you. Like, think about it. I've
said it multiple times. I've had the
money, had the clothes, had this, have
that. You know, at the end of the day, like,
I've got money, bro. Like, I've got free
time. You know, I know what I'm about.
Like it's it but that doesn't seem to be
good enough. You need to do you need to
they come up with another excuse like
the excuses just get worse and worse and
worse. Oh, you need to go to you need to
go to church. You need to do this. You
need to do that. And even when you do
all of these things, they're still not
going to date you. It's just an excuse.
Think about it. I know for a fact that
none of her exes had to do any of these
things that she's that she's requiring
me to do. So, um, and this is where they
try to make you feel [ __ ] about yourself
and make you feel, you know, insecure.
And I say, "Listen, tell tell it to me
straight. Like, I'm I'm not I'm not
scared of the truth. Like, I'm one of
these people that, you know, if you tell
me the truth, I'll respect you more for
it. Like, am I this? Am I that? Am I
this?" She says, "Oh, no, no, there's
nothing wrong with you." So, what So,
what's the problem? You know, you've
been speaking to someone every day for a
month. You've agreed to meet and now
you're saying something different. And
and this is what I'm trying to say. like
you will never ever ever win. Um you
know and it's it's sad sad sad sad sad
sad sad sad sad. Um, you know, there is
generally generally generally no hope.
Like just when you think that you you've
met someone that's, you know, different
and normal because when someone says
something to you, you believe it, it
just turns out to be exactly the same
again, you know, and I was right, you
know, giving up for them 3 months and
yeah, she just played games, gave me
false hope and just made me feel like
[ __ ] Um, and another thing, you know,
towards the end. And another thing she done,
well, she deleted my number as well, uh,
a week ago. Her picture disappeared. I
just assumed that she blocked me. Um,
I just assumed that she blocked me. Um,
and uh, whatnot. And she didn't. and she
tried saying that she just [snorts]
removed her picture when she didn't just
remove her picture because the symbol
removed as well her her Christian symbol
from the status. So, she deleted my
number. So, I was like, "Oh, damn. We've
just met somebody that plays games
again." So, I mean, at the end of the
day, if speaking to somebody and trying
to be a friend with somebody for a month straight
equals into into them still [ __ ] you
over, then bro, you get me? Like it
doesn't matter how long you speak to
these women for. You know, like I said,
I said in the previous video, I don't
know why there's these little rules why
you need to speak to them for this
amount of time, that that amount of
time, whatever. I've been [ __ ] over
royally again. You know, I've wasted my
month of speaking to somebody, trying to
be a friend to someone for no reason,
only to just come out with these loads
of excuses, her to go on about her ex,
and none of these requirements that she
wanted for me, i.e. going to church,
i.e. going to uni. None of her exes done
any of that stuff, you know, and that
was the most that that did annoy me. I'm
not going to lie. That did annoy me.
But, you know, I just didn't say
anything until we argue today. And she
says, "Oh," and I said to her, do you
know what I said to her as well? I said
to her, "Listen, you're never ever going
to come across anyone as nice and down
to earth as me. Never." And I mean it.
Um, and she didn't like it. Um, she
started trying to act the victim and she
said, "Oh, we're done until you
apologize." I'm not apologizing. I don't
need to apologize. What I'm saying is
facts, right? You're lucky enough to
meet someone like me. Yeah. And I'm not
being a narcissist when I'm saying that.
I'm not trying to manipulate anyone when
I'm saying this. This is straight facts,
you know? So, at the end of the day,
they don't help themselves. They say
that they got exes that cheat on them.
This man [ __ ] that man [ __ ] But when
they're continuously meeting somebody
that is not like that, even be it just
me, be it just Peter Belly, they don't
they don't want it. And then they make
excuses. They make all these
requirements and then go back to the
same men. And I'm not going to take back
the fact that, you know, I said that,
you know, you're the best uh I'm the
best person that you're ever going to
come across down to earth and genuine. I
think I worded it cuz it's the truth.
And I'm not going to say sorry um for
something that I mean. Um I said it
sincerely said it cuz I I I I believe
it. It's the truth. You know, it's it's
mad and and at the end of the day, it's
just their loss. But it's a shame
though. It is a shame because they say
they can't find a good man. They say
this, they say that. And when they're
given a chance to find someone that is
genuinely down to earth, um they just
make up a million one excuses why they
can't get with you.
So yeah, that's the story. Um I don't
think it will be changing anytime soon.
Bad, bad, bad.