Yo. Okay, so the bookies opens in about
10 minutes. Um, so yeah, I went through
a lot of ice and dodgy area. It's very
cold. I'm half asleep. I mean, I'm
basically trying to break down the
dedication to you all. Um, that that's
how much I hate people in this community
that I was willing to go through all of
that just so they don't get the last
laugh. Um, yeah. I mean, I don't hate
everyone in this community. You know,
there are some all right people and you
know who you are. Um, but you know,
there was no way I was going to give any
of these wankers um any kind of chance
to have the last laugh. Um, no way. Um,
what's funny is they were saying about how, um,
you know, it's only £100, £110, it's not
lifechanging. Um, when these people on
£300 a month, they don't even have £110,
mate. They don't even have £50. And
think about like this, right? £110 is
about four Indian restaurants. I mean,
good Indian restaurants. So, you know,
it depends how you look at it to be
fair. But yeah, um that's that.
So, yeah, what I'm going to do is I'm
going to come back home. I'm going to
wait a couple of hours, pretend I've
just woke up and
pretend that I've gone to try to collect
the winnings, come back and say I
haven't been able to and someone on
YouTube's done it just to play the
community and see um you know how easy
they are to fall. And I was going to say
how good my acting skills are, but to be
fair, a lot of people on here, well, the
haters again are just stupid. So, I
don't really think that's an accurate uh
view on your uh acting skills, so to
speak. Good old laddy.
Come on, son. Let's go.
Dedication. Got the Coca-Cola as well.
Has this bet been cashing?
I think we still have to wait to open. Of course. All right,
I'll pause and I will resume when I'm a bit closer.
Yeah, hold. I was about to say, hang on
a minute. This is a bit scary cuz the
shutters are down, but it does say 7:30,
so they have to They even open 7:30 on a
Sunday. Nah, can't be right.
No, it's norally an hour later on
Sunday. It's okay, though. I'll just wait.
I'll just wait until uh until they open it.
Captain, come on.
Might as well let me in. [sighs]
Well, they have to open at 7:30. I was
thinking I'll hopefully I was thinking
hope it didn't say 7:30 online and
something like 8 or 8:30, but it does
say 7:30 there. So, by the way, I've
traveled well out the area for this as well. [snorts]
You could easily just let me in now if
you wanted to.
Come on, Captain.
They're going to leave us to the right
the last minute, aren't they? It's okay,
though. I'll just wait.
Yeah, I'll just wait.
cuz I could take a seat. Take a seat over there.
Right, let me pause and resume when I'm
inside the shop or something happens. Hopefully. Yeah.
Right. I think they said 10 minutes and
they said 5 minutes, which uh time is
not on our side here with someone else's
[ __ ] But I can't imagine anyone else
on YouTube going to a Lad Brooks that
opens at 7:30. And by the way, people, I
keep having to say that this isn't the
money. I don't need the money. I just
don't want these people having the
having the last laugh. Um,
so yeah, again, I'll pause. They said 5
minutes. Fingers crossed.
And yeah, they said 5 minutes. No
problem. It is quite scary when you see
them shutters. They don't look like
they're ever going to open, do they? But
it's okay. I'll just wait
till the shutters go down.
Yeah, there we go. Lovely. [ __ ] have
to wait about [ __ ] 15 minutes.
Oh, I told you I'm going to be the first
one in the shop.
Oh, here we go. Pretty sure that door
would be locked.
Yeah, it is 100% lock. Yeah. Oh, it's locked.
It would be locked.
Get in there, son. Be into it. Lovely.
Thank you. Thank you.
No one can ever beat me be.
I'm just so tired.
[snorts] Oh man. Tired, bro. really tired. >> Yeah.
>> Oh, yeah. [snorts] >> Yeah.
Thank you, Captain.
Don't underestimate Peter Belly, mate.
Peter belly has so mind. He has it in
his mind, mate. That's that. That's
that. But I should really thank Joseph
Far to be honest because he gave me the
guide on how to actually collect the
winners. So, thank you, uh, Joseph Far.
And yeah, lovely, lovely stuff.