I was feeling a bit bored, so I thought,
you know what? Let me get myself down to
uh the Indian restaurant. I've never seen Yeah.
>> yellow mint sauce before in my life. It's interesting.
>> Thank you, boss.
>> Coke. Yeah.
So nice, you know, when you eat him. Good.
>> Oh, it's so lovely.
>> Yeah. So, I'm going to pause and resume
when the rest comes. So,
there we go.
All right. This is the uh
ticker. Oo, look at that.
It's orange this time. Yeah, it's
normally uh orange or red. Okay. Okay. Cheers, bro.
That smells lash.
>> Yeah, it's normally orange or red. This
time it's orange.
Look at that.
Never seen yellow mint sauce before.
Get it in the mint sauce.
The vindaloo's coming. It's not here yet,
>> but it's lowish.
That is tasty.
>> Oh, that's nice, man.
>> This one's nice. Yeah. >> Mhm.
It's got to be one of the best chicken um
chicken tippers I've ever had, to be fair.
It's got to be up there. It's got to be >> Yeah.
>> I'll pause when the rest comes.
I'll pause before the rest.
Right. Done the ticker in. And now uh
yeah, it's come. So going to eat this
vindaloon out. I'm going to put it on a
plate and mix it. So yeah, absolutely
lush if I must say so myself.
>> Look at that.
Open the heart.