Yo. Okay, so time for a 4 month renewal
video on this insecure, rejected little
sad bastard um cowardly stalker. Now, do
you know what? Yeah, I don't like using
the word um stalker a lot or calling
somebody a stalker because it's so
overused nowadays. You know, people say,
"Oh, someone's found me on Facebook and
they're stalking me." Or they've typed
my name three day like three times in
Facebook and they found me like they
don't actually know the definition of
stalking. And it could be quite a
serious thing. This coward [ __ ]
insecure loser behind this account is 100%
um a stalker. Now, this is my first time
on this channel in 4 months because it
got to the point where I started feeling
sorry for him. Um, you know, coming on
YouTube, being triggered every day over
me, embarrassing himself along with
these other sados, self-projecting
people that comment on his [ __ ] And it
got to a at first it was funny and then
it just become like it's it's sad. You
know, he's just embarrassing himself
every single day. And what's what's so
mad about it is he's been doing it for
like 5 years. Like every second of every
day of his life, he comes online
stalking me, recording all my live
streams. I mean, it's got to be
jealousy, you know, for somebody to sit
there all day reacting to you, which
we'll get on to in a minute, being
triggered by you every to the eyeballs
every second of every day. It's got to
be jealousy. Like there's there's
nothing else I could possibly think of.
Like it's different, you know, like when
people used to go on Timmy's and say,
"Oh, you stole from Hyperlinks just to
get a reaction." But this guy will go
through great lengths, right, to to
stalk me. And and and it's somebody with
a better life than you would not be
doing that, bro. Like anybody with
common sense would would would know
that. Um, and what's even sadder is he's
still doing it. But he's a complete
coward in real life. Like he will never
meet anyone. He will never say anything
to anyone's face. Um, but he will beg
London Taylor to do it. Like he's begged
London Taylor a few times to come and do
this to me and do that to me. But he
will not do anything but stalk on
YouTube and be triggered on YouTube all
his life. So now we're going to
deconstruct the little [ __ ] Right. So
27 receding triggered
lonely and skin. So I assume you're
trying to call me that. Now here's where
you're going to [ __ ] yourself up badly
is you're trying to call me all of those
things. So if I'm all of those things,
then I mean I'm the lowest of the low
and obviously you're opposite because
you're calling me that. So that must
mean that you're none of these things.
So, if I'm really all of those things,
why have you been coming on YouTube
stalking me every second of every day
for years, being triggered by me every
second of every day of your life for
years? Now, let me try to put this into
perspective, right? Anyone who's
watching this that works or maybe you
don't work but you just go on about your
day dayto-day. You just live dayto-day.
He he spends every second of every
moment from the time he wakes up to the
time he goes to bed stalking me to try
and convince himself that I'm as ugly as
him, which we'll get on to in a minute.
Like, think about anyone who's watching
that this video right now. I mean, I'm
sure if somebody was all of those
things, you wouldn't waste a second on
them, let alone waste five years coming
on YouTube every day being triggered
like he has. And you can tell that he's
triggered as well because look,
explanation marks, [ __ ] capital
letters. Like, bro, you're sat on
YouTube been triggered for the past 5
years, yet you're never going to meet
anyone. Like, do you not know how you're
just embarrassing yourself now? Um, and
it's like it's it's crazy. I mean, the
evidence is there. So, we go back onto
this and it's actually 47 already a
baldy bastard, which you are triggered
every single day on YouTube like what
I've just shown people that you are
lonely on YouTube just like I've shown
people you are. And your skin Oh, sorry.
I didn't mention the skin one. Um, I've
shown you thousands and thousands and
thousands and you haven't shown me
anything close to 10,000. So, mate, I've
already proven that you are skint and
you are triggered every single day on
YouTube. I mean, the evidence is there.
It's not uh, you know, a case of me um,
saying that, oh, you're this, no, you're
that. Like there's evidence right here
that you're triggered on YouTube every
day for years. Like the evidence is
literally there and you're also skint
because I've shown more money than
anyone on this community. So I mean it's
mad how you spend all your life doing
this. If if I'm really all of these
things, I mean the obsession and the
desperation coming from you. It is. It
is so sad. You know, reacting to me
every day, you know, every single day
for them 4 months where I've not replied
to you, you've still been doing this.
You've still been obsessed. That's not
somebody that's better than me, bro.
Because I know that if I was better than
someone, I wouldn't be doing this every
single day on YouTube for a reaction or
no reaction. And also, before anyone
says this, don't sit there and say, "Oh,
like they do it for a reaction." They do
it for reaction because what you don't
understand is they are reacting to me.
They are being obsessed with me every
day. So it's not like they're saying two
things to get a reaction or [ __ ] with
you for 2 minutes. Their whole life
revolves around reacting and stalking to
me. It just goes to show that they are
the skin ugly baldy [ __ ] that they
try to call other people. That's
literally the whole point because
somebody that wasn't would not be doing
this all day on YouTube every single day
for years. Um, and they're still doing
it as well. So, it's like it it says
everything about their life and nothing
about yours really. And another thing is
is the fact that you have spent years of
your life trying to make me insecure
about my looks. like you've really
really tried. But I mean, if you go up
to your latest post, I'm still showing
my face. Something that you can't do. So
imagine that, right? You've been
literally trying to make me insecure
about my looks for years and years and
years, trying to make me think that I'm
as ugly as you. Cuz you are an ugly
bastard. That's why you can't show your
face. But the only one that's still
scared to show their face is yourself.
Isn't that embarrassing? So, it's like
all in them years you've done nothing
but waste your life being obsessed with
me and embarrassing yourself because I
mean even that you're so desperate you
even try and screenshot like where I've
opened my mouth like you it's always
you're so insecure like that's another
thing that I I found like you putting
all of these pictures up of me
convincing yourself that I'm ugly you
know this all comes from the fact that
you're the insecure ugly one because
even years later, bro, why ain't you got
a picture of your face, bro? You're
coming on here saying that I'm [ __ ]
ugly, right? You still ain't showing
your hiccups, bro. You still ain't
showing your ugly face.
You really, really are a [ __ ] loser.
I feel bad for