Right, just wanted to say right, round
of applause to the virgin, bravo, bravo.
You know, I give credit when credit is
due. Like, I was just about to do a
video on you and then you done a video
on me and then I watched your video and
then I um went on your community post.
But no, no, it was it was a good try. It
was a good try. Um, probably best not to
[ __ ] with me though because remember
last time when I had you literally
crying and running to the police like
the little [ __ ] that you are? You done
it? You got owned so badly. Put it this
way. It was worse than when your mom's
boyfriend had you up against the wall
begging for mercy. Like that's literally
how bad it was. And that was pretty bad.
But to be fair, I did say to Cory Dak
yesterday that it it would be very
unfair if I can own the Virgin's
boyfriend, aka Red Star, and then not
completely rip him to shreds because
that would just be completely rude and
completely arrogant and disrespectful if
I didn't do the same to the Virgin
himself. So, I'm going to completely rip
him to shreds now. So, um I I watched
the video and to be honest with you, I
laughed. I laughed a few times at it and
I genuinely was thinking in my head if
you carry up this if you carry on this
sort of comedian uh comedy show um you
might actually have sex for the first
time. You might actually be able to get
laid in maybe about 15 years and you
might finally be able to say that you
had sex and you're no longer a virgin. A
and B, you might actually be able to
pull a normal woman that isn't disabled
that can string a sentence together and
doesn't resemble oompa loompa and little
bastard combined. So, I mean, that's
something to look forward to, but to be
honest with you, you'd probably have to
fix your ugly rat face and actually get
some teeth in that ugly mouth of yours.
So, probably women would still probably
reject you probably harder than Britney
did. um to be honest with you. Um so
yeah, I mean that's that. I mean the
thing that made me laugh the most on the
live stream is the fact that you were
saying about how um well I got a bed and
I could show it but then you don't show
it. I mean because you don't have it
because everything that I was saying
about you all of these years is the
truth. But you're not just bedless.
You're bedless. You're brainless and
you're toothless. So, I mean, at the end
of the day, you're you're a few
different lists. I mean, I wouldn't be
telling somebody about how they're
living and saying that people live with
their mom when you don't even have a
bed. You literally don't even have a
bed, which which is what most people
have. But, we'll get on to the M thing
earlier any uh later on. Anyway, so it's
it's crazy. So, I went on your which is
was what the video I was going to do. I
went on your channel earlier and I read
the paragraph that you wrote um the
virgin paragraph that you wrote because
you are a virgin and it said about uh
how you know you you were sticking up
for women and you were sing and I I
don't really I don't really understand
people like you. You need to really help
me understand. So, you're a virgin. You
have a disabled girlfriend that don't
talk, that don't give you sex. You've
never had a normal girl, never had a
normal girlfriend, but yet you're sat
there sticking up and def sticking up
for women and defending women because I
said one accurate thing which I could
actually back up with evidence. I don't
understand simps like you. And I'm not
just referring to you. I mean, it's a
few people, you know. I would say like
an accurate thing like oh like women are
stuck up or whatever it is not you know
offensive but something I could actually
prove. And you get all of these simps
like Virgin Boy um who's never had sex
that can't even get a normal woman or
people that can't even get a woman or
they'll all be there to their rescue to
save them and defend them. Yet you've
had more women than them. Anyone would think that,
you know, anyone would bloody think that
you're the one that's never had a woman
and they have when it's literally the
other way around. But they're so thick
that they don't actually realize that
sing never gets them laid. They sticking
up and licking women's asses. They're
sticking up for women and licking their
asses when you've been with more women
than them and they can't even get laid
themselves. It's I know it doesn't make
any sense um whatsoever, but I mean
that's that's that's generally um what
they do. And we'll get on to the pulling
thing in a minute, Virgin Boy. Uh you
know, hold on a minute. But the first
thing you said was skin. Now, generally,
I'm in a I'm in a bit of a dilemma here,
right? I don't know what is more sadder,
the fact that you're actually skint
yourself or the fact that you come on
YouTube every single day um showing your
little money that you probably got from
sucking your dad's dick to try to um
convince people that you've actually got
money. I mean, okay, let's just start
with this. What would give people the
impression that I'm skin and you're not
skin? You got no bed. You wear shitty clothes.
You've got no assets. It took you to 30
years of age to go abroad,
bro. I ain't going to lie. You're living
that skin life now. That doesn't really
really prove that you're you're skint
yet, though, does it? It proves 80% that
you're skin that I mean, you don't even
got your own house. Um, that's another
thing which we'll get on to your with
with the housing thing um in in a little
bit. So, do you remember now? Wait,
before I get on to that, I need to ask
you this question cuz this is a very
important question. You know, when your
mom's boyfriend had you up against the
wall and he smashed your head um the
same time when he broke your arm, um did
you develop any kind of dementia, any
kind of memory loss or because do you
remember the money game and how the
money game works? I'll I'll remind you.
So, I showed you thousands and thousands
and thousands of pounds for months and
months and months and months and months
and you didn't show me a damn thing. The
whole g the whole part of the game was I
show money, you double the money. You
got shown six grand and you couldn't
show me a damn thing. That along the
lines with the fact that you didn't go
abroad until you was 30. You wear
charity shop clothes. You've got no bed.
All the evidence points to you being
skint. And anyone does not that don't
lick your ass like Red Star will tell
you exactly the same thing. You are
skint. That's why you call people skimp
because you are skint yourself. Um, so
that's that's that's out the way. Um,
and you ain't even got any assets but a
few shitty cheap guitars. That's another thing. Now
here's another thing. You was talking
about my nose.
I've got a big wobbly conquer big nose
and I'm this and I'm that. Well, here's
the thing. I haven't got a big nose. And
if I did have a big nose, I'd rather
have a big nose and have that [ __ ]
ugly rat face that you were born with.
That gale plaque disabled face with them
triple tin chins with your balding ugly
ain't being able to grow facial hair ass
lanky skinny [ __ ] toothless [ __ ]
broken disabled arm like you are. I I I
would rather have a big nose. Now,
here's the thing. You go on about how
I'm this and how I'm ugly, but why is it
that you're the only one that can only
get disabled women? I mean, you know,
you said over the years how I've never
had a girlfriend and t
you've had two girlfriends and both of
which were [ __ ] disabled. It's so mad
how I'm so ugly, but I've had all the
women that you wish you could get. Morgan
[ __ ] the 19year-old Sig
you. I'm so ugly
that you're the one that has to resort
to disabled lumpers. Yeah. Yeah. That's
how ugly I am. And bro, stop this whole,
you know, you live with your mom, you
live with your mom, you live with your
mom. Now, here's the thing. I don't live
with my mom. And you've been using that
same insult since I was about 18.
Your mom starved you. Your mom disowned
you. Your mom doesn't want anything to
do with you. Which is probably why
you're so salty that people of 18 and 19
once lived with their mom because your
mom didn't want anything to do with you.
That's why you're so [ __ ] up because
of your childhood. You literally got
starved almost to death. You literally
got put into hospital by your mother,
which makes me laugh. When you come in
here acting like you're some kind of big
man, it's cute. I mean, I've had a big
mouth. I'd be guilty of it. But guess
what? I've backed up a lot of my talk.
I've been in encounters. I've been in
fights because of this community.
Here's a question. Virgin boy who got
starved by his mom.
Was you a big man when
you couldn't go to certain events for 3
weeks? No, you wasn't. Was you a big man
when you know uh
when your mom was almost starving you to
death? Was was you any kind of big man
then? Was you any kind of big man when
your stepdad had you up against that
wall making you scream and then he broke
your arm? Which is still there by the
way. Anyone who wants to see it, ask the
virgin to go live and he's got twists on
his arm that needs snapping back into
place. It's funny how you was never a
big man when any of these encounters was
happening, but you expect us to believe
that a lanky stringer toothless, weak
little [ __ ] like yourself is about
anything, kid. I think it's time to come
off of YouTube and and and get laid.
It's it's really really embarrassing. I
mean, that in itself is just talking
about yourself. I can't attract women, brother.
I've attracted women that you still
can't get out of your head. I've
attracted so many better women than you
that you used to start stalking them and
messaging them because of your jealousy.
Now, the only reason you didn't attract
these women is because of your ugly rat
face, which is what I've tried um
explaining to you numerous times. Think
about it like this. I'll leave you with
this. There's a reason why you can only
attract disabled women that can't talk
that look like plumpers and there's a
reason why I can pull normal women. Just
just just leave you with that. Just
leave you with that, bro. Yeah, but it
was a it was a good try. But don't you
ever try and sit in your [ __ ] virgin
Kent Karm again with no bed in it and
think you can [ __ ] do a video on me. [ __ ] virgin.