Okay, so this is going to be a video to
Jo. You really are quite the simpleton,
aren't you, fella? Like, you really,
really are. Um, you know, I'm not going
to pretend that you're as, you know,
disabled as LJ and he's self-projecting
low life followers. But you still have
quite the strong case of retardation,
sir. I must uh I must admit like your I
just seen your community post. So, I
don't even know how I've seen it cuz I'm
not even subscribed to you. And all you
do is go on about money, money, money.
How I'm poor and dare and this that and
the other. But the thing is, bro, you
don't know how much I have. And at the
end of the day, bro, if you have got all
of this money, why don't you get off of
YouTube and live up to your means? Why
do you come on YouTube every day living
like the poor person? Like, I saw one of
your things and you were saying about
how you're going to Rome. Is it mad how
you're going to Rome, but apparently I
quote the poor person who's going to
Thailand? I mean, if you had all of this
money, I'm pretty sure you would be
going somewhere other than Rome. And
it's like, bro, you got to understand,
it's more than one thing. This is what I
was trying to explain to you before.
Like, people are like, jealous of me,
like, you know, it's because I'm better
looking than them. I've got more money
than them. I have a better life than
them or had a better life than them or,
you know, whatever back then. Some
people might have left YouTube. Even if
you have more money than me, which you
don't, right? That's nothing to jealous
to and that's nothing to be jealous of.
You know, having a better life and
showing a better life is though, you
know, and obviously you ain't got no
life. So, it's like it's like I've said
a million times before, bro, I could
have £300 in my account and I'd have a
better life than all of you cuz I've
actually got a life outside of YouTube.
Do you understand? It's not one thing,
you know? No one would just purely be
jealous of somebody because they've got
more money than them. It's better life,
better looks, money. It's not one thing.
And obviously, you clearly don't have a
life. And I don't know how long you're
going to keep playing these silly games
for. I mean, Joe, you've been shown
money. The whole community has been
shown money multiple times. And every
single time I show you money, you all
run away. This is why people don't waste
their time on you anymore, you know,
getting into it with you or trying to
meet, you know, people off of YouTube
because you're all biased and you're all
going to you're all going to remember
what suits yourself. You know, everyone
knows that I've shown money time and
time and time again and I had you all
running. Yeah. Okay, bro. You come on
YouTube every day, you call people skint
every day. Fine. You've been shown money
multiple times, multiple different
amounts, and you've all run away. So, I
know why that is. So, I don't get into
it anymore. I'm not, you know, you've
been shown money multiple times and the
whole community flipped and folded, bro.
So, I mean, yeah, okay, you're going to
pretend that never happened, but it did
happen and it happened quite a few times
just like when I went to meet Mark
Samson um two times and I went live in
his area. You pretend that never
happened. He came on YouTube for so long
up until now and people used to take him
side for it. people have only just
started admitting what he is now. And
the reason I I'm bringing this up is
because this is part of like the
biasness what you people do on there.
You you remember what you want to
remember. Um like it's funny how no one
remembers when I've gone to Mark's area
two times and he's not shown up and no
one's ever said anything about it or
when I've shown thousands multiple times
and I had every single person running
not being able to show anything. that
actually happened, you know, and I'm
surprised it took [ __ ] four years for
people to finally admit what that Mark
Samson was about. They knew all along,
but I mean that doesn't even matter in
it because that's still biased because,
you know, I went to his area twice. You
know, it's not just the money thing.
It's the it's the meeting people thing.
It's the arguing. It's the show money.
People don't want to waste their time on
it anymore, Joe, because every single
time you take L's, you just pretend it
never happened. So, this is why, you
know, we don't waste our time anymore.
You know, I always say to Mike um in
Birmingham, don't waste your time. Don't
get into it with any of these people
because they take L's. They're not going
to admit it and then they're going to
come back and go for you and and it just
never [ __ ] ends. So that's why I just
said don't don't get into it. It's like
it's like Virgin Boy, the skint virgin
in a bedsit with no bed in it. He does
videos. People claim that he owns me.
Bro, I had the dude run into the police
crying multiple times. But again
something that you all choose to forget.
So this is why people don't people don't
waste their time on it anymore. You know
like when you say oh people are skinn
show money show money show money and
then you show money and then you all run
away. That's why people don't waste
their time on it anymore. You know you
can go and you know self project your
skintess somewhere else because you know
I'm not interested and you don't Yeah.
You don't understand like basic things
as well. So yeah, it's like when I say
to you, oh like this Red Star is a
weirdo sat on YouTube all day every day
stalking me from the time he wakes up to
the time he goes to bed and then you'll
say that he does it for reaction and
then I'll say to you, well even if he
doesn't get a reaction, he will still do
it. Um and and like even certain things
you don't you don't get. So you really
are quite you really are quite the
simpleton. I think you need to take um
medication to help with your to help
manage your strong case of retardation. Yeah.