Yo. Okay, so this is going to be my
reply to um Virgin Boy. Now, I just saw
your community post and you might want
to get your uh facts right. Nobody was
lying about their age. That approach was
literally 3 years ago. Yes, I've got
literally approaches on my channel.
That's years old, like going from like
four years back. and I put all of their approaches
on my channel to show how bad the dating
game is in this country and how [ __ ]
up it is. Um, no one's lying about their
age. I was literally 25 in that video,
which was 3 years ago. Yeah, that video
was 3 years ago. So, you might want to
get your facts right, you [ __ ]
virgin. Um, so I was watching your
video, man, and um, you were saying
about how if I keep calling you a virgin,
do I think that's somehow going to
convince people that you are a virgin or
is it going to convince myself rather
that you're a virgin? Now, there's no
convincing to be had. I'm telling you
that you're a [ __ ] virgin because
you're a [ __ ] virgin. I'm not trying
to convince myself anything. I I know
you better than you know yourself. And
as far as convincing I quote other
people, I mean, why the [ __ ] would I
want to waste my time trying to convince
a biased audience? That does not make
any sense. Like the people in this
community have shown how biased they are
multiple times. um you know from the um
you know remembering what they want to
remember, forgetting L's that they took,
forgetting L's they've took against me.
Why would I waste my time trying to
convince a biased audience? That just
does not make any sense. I mean, I
specifically don't do certain things
anymore because these people are biased
on this community and they'll just
pretend like they've won anyways. Like
that's literally them. They're they're
biased. Um, but you are trying to
convince yourself um, many things. Like,
I mean, you're still trying to convince
yourself that I've got a big nose and
that I'm ugly and that I'm an incel. I
mean, does that make you feel better
about the fact that you are the ugly one
with no teeth? You look like a rat and
you can only get a disabled girl. And
before you say she's not disabled, I'm
going to explain exactly how she's
disabled later on. She is your your
girlfriend is disabled. Um, so yeah.
Does does you calling me trying to call
me ugly make you feel better about the
fact that you actually are the ugly one
that can only get disabled girls? Like
your face looks like it's actually
melting your your like one of the
ugliest things I've ever seen and you're
trying to call me an incel. How can I be
an ugly big-nose incel when I've
literally pulled women that you will
never be able to pull because you're an
ugly bastard and you got no social
skills. I mean, what the [ __ ] If I'm
such an ugly incel, why have I never had
to resort to a disabled girl? Why have I
pulled more women than you if I'm an
ugly incel? Like, you never answer these
questions. It just doesn't make any
sense. And then you were saying about
how like, yeah, you would ask complain
about women for somebody that gets all
these women. I mean, yeah, women are
[ __ ] They're [ __ ] I mean, I
don't see no reason to be dishonest, you
know? You know, I'm not like a, you
know, I don't need to be a s just
because I pulled women. I mean, yeah,
they're they're [ __ ] They're
[ __ ] you know. They they are. That
doesn't mean people have not been with
women just because people [ __ ] speak
the [ __ ] truth. What the [ __ ] you
know? Yeah, they are [ __ ] They're
[ __ ] They're [ __ ] Yeah, they are.
So, so what? That means I've never
pulled a woman because I uh that's
that's what I'm saying. You're a [ __ ]
idiot. And another thing is like you
like to uh convince yourself that other
people you like to convince yourself
other people are skin like you were
saying about how I'm skin and I've never seen 500.
You're right. You got me. I've never
I've never seen 500 I've never seen 500
in my life. See we don't all lie like
you. Yeah. I haven't seen 500 euros ever
in my life. But I've seen £6,000 that
made you run away for two years. Um, I
saw £6,000 in cash, which is worth more
than euros. And it and it had you
running away for many years along with
the other people on here. So I saw I saw
£6,000 in cash, but I never saw £500.
No. No. And the thing is, why do you
keep trying to convince yourself that
I'm skinn when you are the one that's
sat in a bedsit with no bed, no life
experiences, literally nothing, and
you're you're trying to convince
yourself that I'm skin? Listen, let me
give you a fun fact.
You know that £13,000 that you're
showing everybody, right? I was looking
at my life experiences for the past 3
years earlier on my phone cuz I've got
it logged as memories. Mate, I would not
trade one year of them life experiences
for 13 grand, let alone
three years of my life, my life. You
know, you've literally had no life
experiences for 3 years. You didn't go
abroad. You didn't eat in any fancy
restaurants. No designer clothes.
Couldn't pull women. didn't go out
drinking. I've done all of them things
that you couldn't afford to do. I've had
designer clothes, have designer clothes,
went to some fancy restaurants, traveled
up and down the country, went abroad,
pulled women that you can never get with
cuz you're too ugly and too skinn. But
yet, Peter Bell is the skinned one. Do
you hear yourself? I'm younger than you.
I've got designer clothes. I've got more
life experience than you. I've been to
restaurants that's worth literally more
than your whole life. I've been out
drinking a million more times than you
will ever, but yet I'm the skint one.
You actually hear yourself. You actually
hear what you're saying. You know, I'm
the skint one. Whilst you were saving up
for three years of your life, wasting
your youth, wasting your prime years,
doing nothing, I was out there living a
life that you couldn't afford and still
had money. So, I mean, I think you'll
find the Skint one is your virgin self.
Nobody else. So, um, literally
everything screams skint about you, but
nothing screams skint about me. Isn't
that funny? Like from an unbiased point
of view. Think about it. Right. Think
about it right now. Yeah.
These little abroad holidays that you're
going on. I done that when I was 23. By
the time I was 23, I went abroad twice
in the space of a month. Two different
times in the space of a month. And
you're only doing this at 31. Isn't it
so funny how everything screams skin
about you, but nothing screams skin
about me? What? What screams skin about
me? Someone that's been to designer
someone that's got designer clothes.
Somebody that's been to fancy
restaurants. I've done all of these
things in my life that you can't afford
and I've got more money than you, but
yet I'm the good one. Yeah. Have a word
with yourself. have have a couple of
words with yourself, mate. You might
find the answer. Um, and then you were
saying about how
isn't it mad how, you know, how can two
people be together for so many years, right? And
and um, you know, not have sex. You
would have thought, you know, maybe just
once, maybe just once they'd have sex.
But here's the thing, Virgin boy. People
in relationships don't go around
stalking other people's sloppy seconds
for wank material. You've literally
tried it on with every single one of my
sloppy seconds trying to get wank
material. That's not what somebody that
has sex in a relationship does. That's
how we know you're a virgin. because how
you went around all of these women that
I've been with, stalked them, um the
ones that you could, um you tried to get
information out of them. That's exactly
what a virgin would do, which is why I
call you a virgin, cuz you are a virgin.
I'm not trying to convince myself
anything. You are a virgin. Um and the
fact that you say that your girlfriend's
not disabled, right? This is the last
bit I'm going to I'm going to um add on
here. Yeah. You say that your
girlfriend's not disabled. So, why is it
that your girlfriend had no problem with
you messaging other women about their
sex life? That's not a very normal thing
to do, is it? I'm pretty sure some other
person's girlfriend wouldn't be happy
with them messaging other women about
their sex life and trying to get wank
material from them. So, think about it,
mate. If Sarah was really giving you all
of this sex, you wouldn't be going
around messaging women trying to get
wank material, would you? You [ __ ]
virgin [ __ ] And if she wasn't [ __ ]
disabled, she wouldn't be allowing you
to do that. So, you're not a virgin.
Yet, you go around stalking all of the
women that I've been with trying to get
wank material, but yet you're not a
virgin and you're in a relationship
having sex. So, you say, which doesn't
make any sense cuz you wouldn't be doing
what you're doing if you wasn't a
virgin. And then the second thing is
that you claim your girlfriend is not disabled,
yet she has no problem with her
boyfriend stalking other women trying to
get rank material from them. I think
you're a pack of [ __ ] mate, and you're
[ __ ] full of [ __ ] because you make
absolutely no sense whatsoever. Listen,
mate, you can do this for a million
years. come on here, try and convince
yourself that I'm ugly like you and try
and convince yourself that I'm skinn
like you. But it's never ever going to
work. You There is everything ugly about
you. Everything that's a virgin about
you and everything that's skint about
you. There's none of these things about
me, bro. None of these things about me.
There's nothing skint about me. There's
nothing convergent about me. And there's
nothing ugly about me. But there's all
of these things about you. That's the
difference. So yeah, get a life and
[ __ ] get laid,
you know. [ __ ] hell.