Okay, so this is a reply to LJ. Yeah.
Now, I know I said I was done with these
[ __ ] spastics, but um somebody sent
me this video and you were saying about
how, oh yeah, he said he was going to
smash up the place, but he he never did
because there was probably men working
in the place and he only goes for women.
Yeah, I only go for women, bro. Like
like that Polish bouncer that's three
times the size of me about a month ago,
which I recorded. Yeah, that was a
woman. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. And just like
all of the other videos that I've got
sticking it on men. Yeah. They they they
were all women as well. Yeah. Yeah.
Yeah. Of course they were. You know how
much of a s you come across when you say
[ __ ] like that? Like oh you can only go
for women and then and then like you
actually sound like such a simp. Like I
don't know like how long you you're
going to do this until you realize sing
is never ever going to get you laid.
Like think about this loger. put all
your life on YouTube and you've been
sing for years. I've never had to s once
and I've been seen with women and you
haven't. Isn't that if that does not
tell you that sing will never work and
never get you laid, I don't know what
possibly will. And then you were saying
about how oh where was your temper when
I was at your door and ret
you went on the door. You didn't even go
on. You stood behind the gate and you
done absolutely nothing. You was getting
people excited for [ __ ] months and
months and months how you're going to do
this and you're going to do that and all
you done was stood behind the gate,
talked [ __ ] and done absolutely nothing.
And you've actually you'd actually had
chances to hit me as well. Um, and then
even if you did take a W then, which you
didn't, you'd lost that W when 20 30
minutes later I went to exactly where
you was and you wouldn't put your camera
on. I I was in exactly the same spot and
I said, "Put your camera on. I'm gonna
come and I'm gonna fump you in your
face." And what did you do? You didn't
put your camera on. And I mean, even to
this day now, it just proves it because
think everyone who's watching this,
think of how many times he's gone to
Birmingham and how many times more he's
come back to London. Have you noticed
he's never come back to London despite
me saying, you know, I'll pay for your
flights, I will meet you. He won't come
back. He will only go for disabled
Timmy. And like that tells you all you
need to know because last time right
before you had come here you probably
thought you was going to knock on the
door nobody was going to answer it and
ret. But because I answered it and I
told you [ __ ] off and I'll stand in
front of my mom and the fact that I
tried to meet you again after that you
know like you're not going to come here
and start messing with people. that's
why you've never come back because I
find it very odd that somebody has gone
to Birmingham as many times as you've
been because people from other countries
when they come to England they go to
London like it's not even like man even
though Manchester is second London it's
normally London people go to if anyone
comes to England for like a little
holiday or they go to London they don't
go anywhere else do not think it's
strange how this fat diabetic foreyed
freak has continuously gone to
Birmingham and continuously gone for
Timmy me. Even though I've said worse
than Timmy has, the guy is not about it.
I don't know why he comes on YouTube
acting like he is when when he's not.
And it's funny because let's let's let's
go over some of the people that you
mentioned. Oh, another thing is, wasn't
you the same one going on for months
about how you're going to go on Jaden's
door and you're going to do this and
you're going to do that and you're going
to do this and you're going to do that
and then when Crunch comes to Crunch and
you actually went to Manchester about to
board a train to [ __ ] Sheffield, you
shhat your pants. You literally had a
panic attack and then you actually shhat
your pants. But like I said to any any
genuine people that's watching this, if
you're not liked by these fat ugly
people because you're not fat and ugly
like them, they will choose what they
want to remember to see like then and
and what suits themsel like just like
for example when I've gone on when I've
gone to Mark's area two times, everyone
seems to forget about it because it
doesn't suit them to remember it. You
understand? Like that's something that
happens when you're not when you're not
liked for having a better life than
these people. I think that's what has
got the thumbs up. So, and then you're
talking about London Taylor. I was like,
bro, didn't London Taylor talk about
your kids numerous times and you avoided
him numerous times. Do you remember the
time when he said that he was going to
go to Blackpool? He was going to drive
to Blackpool to see you and you shhat
your pants. You ran away from him in
London and you ran away from him. Was it
last year as well when you was claiming
you was here again and he wanted to meet
you? Like it's funny how you can bring
up London Taylor with all people when he
has actually spoken about your kids and
you've done nothing about it. Like bro,
come on. It was You was just losing from
the start bringing him up. And then
you're talking about uh who was the
other one? Terry. Uh Terry didn't beat
me the first time and Terry didn't beat
me the second time. Again, I know you've
got selective memory and you only choose
to remember what suits yourself, but
didn't I go to Terry's area and he
didn't come out or was was that someone
else? Didn't Terry tell me to come to
his area and then when I come to his
area, he started bricking it, pretending
that he was on probation yet he's the
one that called me out to go there.
Yeah, that that guy never beat me. You
must have me confused with um somebody
completely different. And who was the
other one? Uh, Tiger, another one that
never beaten me. Tiger will literally
tell you, right, that, you know, I
outpowered him. He He would literally
tell you that on YouTube cuz he's told
people that on YouTube before. I mean,
how the [ __ ] do you think that fight
even ended? Like, he got me on the floor
cuz I slipped. That's how I was on the
floor cuz I slipped. And as soon as I
got back up, I punched him in his face
and he didn't want no more of it. Cuz
how do you think it stopped? No one
stopped it. No one come out. How do you
think the fight actually stopped? I got
back up and I fumped him in his face and
he didn't want no more. So, I mean,
that's how that stopped. And then the
last one was Prime now. Prime this,
Prime that, Prime this, Prime that. It's
funny, bro. We've been hearing about
this guy for a very long time now. Where
was he 3 weeks ago when I was in
Birmingham calling these [ __ ] ass out
for god knows how long? Cuz I know
you've all got each other's numbers and
you all got each other's emails because
you people on here ain't got friends.
You you ain't got a life. So you all do
this little weird emailing,
WhatsAppapping. Where where was Prime 3
weeks ago, big man? When I was calling
him out in his own city to come and move
me. Like I was calling him the [ __ ] out
three weeks ago in his city and he was
nowhere to be seen. Just like Timmy,
just like a few of the other people from
Birmingham. Where was where was the big
man then? Where where was the big man
prime then? when I was in Birmingham 3
weeks ago, calling him out, telling him
to go [ __ ] himself, telling him to come
and move me, and I'm in his city and I'm
not moving. Where where was the big man
then? Where where was the big man then?
I want you to like explain it to me. Um,
you know, um,
in your reply video, if you do a reply
video, where was the big man Prime then?
Where was this big man then? two years
later when I was in He City calling him
out. But like I said, we all know that
you all biased on him and you remember
what you what suits yourself, you know?
You know, like I said, it's similar to
uh the whole Mark Samson thing. This
reminds me a lot of the Mark Samson
thing, right? Is that he will run away
from people, right? You'll go to his
area two times and as soon as he comes
back on YouTube trying to call people
out again, everyone takes his side.
That's just what happens on it. You
know, people are biased and they choose
what they what they want to remember
um to to to to to remember basically. So
yeah, I wouldn't be talking [ __ ] if I
was you, you know.