Okay, let me let me tell you something.
You don't tell You don't tell me where
to go. I am recording you. Yeah,
>> I'm recording you. Yeah, listen. Listen.
>> I'm not being rude. I'm not being rude.
Hold on. Stay stay out of it. Stay out
>> You don't tell me to go. Get your hand
off my phone.
>> You don't tell me where to go. You don't
tell me where to go. You don't tell
Harassing you. I'm speaking to you. Am I
harassing you? Am I harassing you? Am I
harassing? No. No. No. You're not.
You're trying to be I will call you as
much as I want. You don't tell me what
to do. Yeah, this we I don't want you
either. I'm talking to your friends, so [ __ ] off.
>> Well, I'm with my friends.
>> Yeah, and I'm talking to your f I'm
talking to your friends, >> actually.
>> Yeah, she hasn't said nothing to me.
>> Oh my god. Tell him to leave.
>> How about you [ __ ] off?
>> Oh, my face.
>> Yeah, I'm not being rude. She's being
rude to me. She's being rude to me. And
you know it as well.
>> Yeah. Okay. No. Listen. Listen. Listen.
Let me tell you something. Let me tell
>> Why are you drinking my drink? What the
[ __ ] are you doing? Okay, listen. >> Please,
>> I don't care. You don't tell me what to
do in my country. I'm in England.
>> If you don't like it,
>> yeah, [ __ ] back to Australia. You're not
You don't You're not Listen, listen.
Put down your phone.
>> Don't touch my phone. Don't talk.
>> Go to the security right now.
>> Go to security. Go to
>> He will pick you up.
>> Let him try. Try it. Try it. Try it.
[ __ ] off. Yeah. >> Yeah.
>> Listen, I'm recording you. What are you
going to do? What are you going to do?
Yeah. So are you. So are you. What are
you going to do? What are you going to do? Please.
>> No, you don't tell me. I'M IN MY
COUNTRY. I'm in my country. >> Yeah.
>> Yeah. I'm sorry.
>> I'm not. She's being rude to me. You
know it as well. That's why you got
She's being rude to me. And you drunk my
That's why you can't say nothing. Go
back to Australia, you immigrants. Go
back to Australia. Go back to Australia.
>> [ __ ] back to Australia. [ __ ] back to
where you come from. Listen. Listen.
Listen. Listen. Listen. You're the
foreigner. You go home.
>> Yeah. Not me. You're the foreigner, bro.
Not me. What are you saying? You're
going to say nothing. Exactly. Exactly. For sure.
You don't You're not going to sit here
as a foreigner and tell me where to go.
[ __ ] back to Australia, you stupid
little [ __ ] [ __ ] security. I'd like
to see you try. Go on. Listen. The
security is right here. Go on. [music]
Who's happening? fit
>> trying to tell me where to go.
>> She's just a stupid [ __ ] She's being
rude, man. Yeah,
>> she's being rude.
>> Listen, [ __ ] off back to Australia, you stupid [ __ ]
>> [ __ ] off back to Australia where you're
from. [ __ ] off.
>> Don't trust me, bro. Please. I'm
walking. I'll go out in a minute. Yeah.
Don't trust me. Don't trust me.
>> Shut the [ __ ] up. Go back to Australia
if you don't like it. [ __ ] off.
>> Don't I'll do what I want, bro. Don't
Don't trust me, bro. Do not trust me.
>> Yeah. Don't touch me.
>> She's not being rude. She's all right.
You drunk my drink. Yeah. It's on
camera. You drunk my drink. Yeah. If you
don't like it, you go home to Australia.
[ __ ] off. The guy's not going to touch me, bro.
>> Stupid. Stupid son. Huh?
>> She's being rude to me, bro. Like, I've got
>> Well, I know what's happening. She's
being rude to me. So,
>> that's it. Every day.
>> Look, he's not even trying to do
anything. He can't even trust me. It's [ __ ]
>> It's ridiculous. Listen,
>> many wonderful ladies here.
>> Yeah. And I'm So what? Okay. And what?
>> Yeah. And I'm talking to her. So what?
You can record me all you want.
>> You can call me all you want. You have
to run to security. You're a [ __ ] idiot.
>> [ __ ] off. Back to Australia, you shitty
[ __ ] No security is going to touch me.
Ain't no one going to touch me, bro.
Stop it. Stop it.
No one's going to No one is going to
trust me, bro.
>> I'm what? >> Yeah.
>> I've been with Australian women.
>> I've been with Australian women. Yeah.
>> You can [ __ ] off back to where you come
from, you stupid [ __ ]
>> You can [ __ ] back to where you come
>> Yeah. And she's not even saying that
because she knows I'm right. Fine.
>> What are you going to do? You and no
one's going to do nothing to me. So,
[ __ ] off, you stupid gun.
>> Yeah. So are you.
>> Yeah. Yeah. So do you. A dirty, stinky
little foreigner trying to come to my
country to tell you what to eat.
>> I'll say what I want. I don't give a [ __ ] >> Huh?
>> She's being rude to me. >> Yeah.
>> Tell her to tell her to stop being rude.
>> Some of respect.
>> Learn some respect.
>> Why you guys?
>> I don't know. She
>> some respect.
>> Your face. Okay. Mind your own business.
>> I'm leaving now. She's bro. She's sorry.
>> I was speaking to her, bro. Her friend
never said nothing to me. It's her.
She's She's the one being rude, not her friend.
>> I was speaking to her friend and she's
having an attitude with me trying to
tell me what I can and can't do. And her
friend didn't say anything. So, I'm
telling her, "Fuck off." I'm being fair, bro. Like,
>> so, uh, don't you think it's just better
that she's, you know, to not pay your attention?
>> No, she's being rude.
>> Okay. That's all I told her. I told you,
man. You understand?
It doesn't matter how beautiful. I don't
care. I'm leaving. But I'm saying you
started the [ __ ]
>> Tell her not to be rude. Tell her to
shut her mouth.
>> Yeah. Don't be rude, please.
>> There you go. Thank you.
>> Don't be rude.
>> Don't be rude. Be rude to each other. You know,
>> don't be rude. I'm not being rude.
>> Let's be faithful. Let's be nice.
>> No respect. You have no respect.
>> Listen, we made something strong. Let me
let me tell you something. Let me tell
>> If you're a real man, you just
>> I'm a real man. I'm not going to take
SHE DON'T EVEN SAY NOTHING. I'm not
going to take your [ __ ] I'm not going
>> I her
say nothing. Her fail is not saying
anything. Learn some manners. It doesn't
matter. Learn learn some manners. Stop being rude.
>> Good for you.
>> No, I'm I'm I'm 50 years old.
>> Yeah, I'm 50. It doesn't matter. Don't
worry. No, obviously I'm joking. Do you
calm down? You listen.
>> I just graduated.
>> So what? I was talking to your friend.
Why are you getting jealous?
>> Why are you getting jealous? >> Why?
>> Because I'm talking to your friend. So
why are you being rude then?
>> Because I was trying to have a serious conversation.
>> And I And she can speak for herself. She
>> She can listen.
I was trying to talk and you got it.
>> Yeah, but she didn't say that. Okay.
>> And she told my Doesn't m she Yeah. And
I'm getting to know your I was getting
to know your friends. Yeah. It doesn't
matter if you're not Stop being jealous.
Stop being jealous. Someone will
approach you. Stop being jealous. You've done that.
>> Listen listen.
>> Just be nice and stop being rude.
listen. Don't let their
>> Can I talk to you?
>> Can I talk to you? I'm not
>> Why are you still here? >> Listen.
>> Let me tell you something.
>> Hey, listen. I'm not being rude. I'm not being aggressive. >> Listen,
>> don't let the S Don't let the s You
can't talk to them, bro.
>> What is your name? What is your name?
>> Nice. Yeah.
>> Sure. Okay. >> Yeah.
>> Let's hang about that one.
>> I'm I want to say something to her. I
understand. I understand.
>> Let me say something. I'm not being
rude. Okay. Yeah.
>> I'm just saying like if you you're being rude like
>> I want to be normal. I'm not being aggressive.
>> You're being nice.
>> Maybe you can understand.
>> I'm just saying maybe
>> there's no maybe. She's being rude.
>> I'm not talking to her. I'm >> okay.
>> Okay. Listen. Can I say one thing? Hey,
listen. Listen. Let me tell you
something. [music] The simp. The simps
are desperate. You're not better. You're
not better than a five out of 10. You're
not better than a five.
You're [ __ ] [ __ ] No. >> [music]