Yo. Okay. So, this is going to be um my
reply to Timmy since you done a video on
me. So, I just watched it and you were
saying about how, oh yeah, you ain't
even got £500. And I don't even believe
that you believe the [ __ ] that is
actually coming out of your mouth at
this point. And you were saying about
how I don't show money because I've not
got no money. And timmy,
you have been shown money several
several times. I can recall four months
ago, right, where I pulled £1,300 out of
the bank cuz I was drunk cuz that's the
only reason I played this game again.
And I think I was so drunk and he was
getting on my nerves. I thought, "Fuck
it, let me shut you up one last time."
You got shown £1,300 and you ran away
just like you, your followers, L and L
J's self-projecting followers do all the
time. You get shown money. This is why I
don't waste my time anymore. It's not
because people don't have money. It's
because a wise man learns from mistake,
their mistakes. Every single time I have
shown you money, you along with all of
these other people have ran away because
you ain't got no money. And I got sick
of playing the game over and over and
over and over and over again, you know.
And you know, it's funny you should say
about how, you know, oh, you should show
money and shut these people up then. No,
no, no, no, no. Timmy, you've been shown
£6,000. You've been shown £1,300. You've
been shown £700. You've been shown
£3,000. And you still haven't shut up.
You're still coming on here pretending
like you've not been shown money time
and time and time again, and you've not
run away time and time and time again.
Fun fact, when was the last time you
showed money? When was the last time
Lord Jay showed money? When was the last
time all of these people that come on
here self-reflecting their skess on here
every single day have actually shown
money? Cuz think about it right now,
Timmy. Right. Um the amount of people
that come on here every single day
calling people skin. Not very many of
them have ever shown money. Like barely
any of them. Yeah, you know, a few
people have shown money, but not very
many compared to how many people on this
community. That is because you are the
ones that are skinned. I don't know how
many times I have to say this. Um, you
know, until it gets into your [ __ ]
stupid brain, but you know, it's it's
people don't show you money anymore
because every time I show you money, you
will run away. Why would I want people
running away, you know, and then and
then and then you use the biased cute
excuse and a lot of people use this
excuse that, oh, well, it's the past. It
doesn't count. You literally live in the
past. Everything about this community is
living in the past. They talk about the
prime incident with me. They talk about
when LJ come to London and stood behind
the gate and then [ __ ] all. They bring
this up a million times, but then as
soon as you give them some home [ __ ]
cold troops, uh, well, it was in the
past, so it doesn't uh, count. And then
you try to use an excuse saying that it
was years ago. Well, Timmy, guess what?
You got shown you got shown money about
3, four months ago that weren't even
half a year ago, and you done exactly
the same thing again. ran away. Just
like everybody on here, you you ask
people to show you money because you
ain't got no money and then when people
show you money, you run away. Everyone
knows when you do that. It's the same
thing as like, you know, meeting people.
Um, you know, uh, you know, you go to
meet these people, they don't show up,
and then they pretend that they've won.
Um, you know, they act like like it
never happened. Like no matter what we
do on here, you you will never shut up
because you can't shut up a biased
audience because this whole thing is
biased. Do you understand? Like I've
shown money multiple times. Multiple
times. I've done things multiple times
that people never bring up because they
only believe what they want to believe.
They want to remember what they want to
remember, you know, because they're all
biased. So, you're never going to shut
up a biased audience. And like I said,
if you're not fat and ugly um and old
like these people, they don't like you.
They'll find reasons to dislike you. Um
you know, then when they dislike you, um
they're obviously biased. So no matter
what you do, um they'll just pretend it
never happened anyways. Like when I've
shown six grand or when I've gone to
meet people or they'll make up an excuse
saying, "Oh, well that was ages ago."
All of the things you talk about every
single [ __ ] day is ages ago. You're
living in the past, so you know, make it
make sense. Um, so, um, that's as as as
far as that, um, goes. And then even
with this, uh, NS legs, um, thing I'm
going to bring up, um, because you you
brought it up. So, since we're talking
about biasess, I mean, that's even
biased. I mean, I'm going to be the
first one to say, right, I'm not going
to sit there and pretend, oh, £13,000 is
nothing and that's bum change and all of
this silly things these skinned people
on here say every single day. You know,
they've said it about my six grand. I
had some guy in in Wales called Lee try
and say six grand was nothing. Yeah, if
I went to where he lived in Wales, I
could buy him with six grand him and his
house. So, I'm not going to say anything
like that. Like, oh, 30 grand's nothing.
No, no, no. But it's nowhere near as
much as you're making it out to be.
Like, you're making it out to be like
it's some lifechanging money because
somebody else has shown it. This is what
I mean with a bias when we all know,
bro, that wouldn't even last 6 months in
London. like it could barely get you a
decent car. Like yeah, it's money. It's
it's a decent amount of money, but it's
nowhere near as as much as your it's not
even in the slightest bit lifechanging.
Um so when you try to say, "Oh, well,
someone's going to go and rob him and
Timmy," it's really really really not
that big a money in the scheme of
things. Um and that's that's how it is.
And I'll give you an example. If I if I
came back right now, right, and I shown
29 grand, they would all say, "Well,
yeah, but it doesn't it doesn't la that
would not last a that's not even a year
salary." They would exactly say that
same thing that uh it, you know, it's
not even a year salary. That's why I'm
saying they're biased. So, with biased
people, you will never ever ever ever
win. Um, and the thing is, Timmy, fun
fact, the fact that it's took somebody
two years to show that money just goes
to show that they were skit the whole
time. And to be honest with you, I don't
even believe that is his money. But I'm
not going to sit there and pretend um,
you know, I'm not going to sit there and
be a hater because there's nothing to be
a hater about. It's not even a
life-changing amount of money. But let's
just say in theory that it is his money,
when it probably isn't. Why has it took
you two years to show 13 grand? And that
I mean that's a madness in itself. It
took you two years to show £13,000.
I mean if if that does not scream ski, I
don't know what does, you know? I mean
the one time it took me [ __ ] a month
to save about£3 grand. So at the end of
the day, I mean it's really not that
much money that you're making it out to
be. But like I said, if I showed triple
that, they would say, "Oh, uh, yeah,
well, I mean, it's okay." Or they they
they would literally say something
completely different. That's what I'm
saying. When you're not liked on here
because you're better looking than these
people and you're younger than them,
you're literally wasting your time.
They'll always remember what they want
to remember. And here's the thing,
right? Um, listen, Timmy, I don't have
no reason to be jealous of anybody.
Yeah, I'm younger than legs. I'm better
looking than nodlex. I've had a better
life than nodlex. got more life
experience than nonsense. Isn't that mad
how somebody that is apparently ski has
got more life experience and done more
things than he ever will? Um, and do you
know the reason why I don't believe that
is even his money? Do you really want to
know why? Because if somebody has all
that money that they claim to have, why
they sat there with a bed sit with no
bed with no life experience? I mean, the
life the lifestyle doesn't add up to the
to the finances. You see with me, I've
got Stone Island jumpers. I've got a lot
of stuff to show for my money. He's sat
there literally without even a bed with
literally no life experience. He didn't
go abroad until he was 30 years of age.
To me, that's very very very rare in the
in today's society. Like, think about
it. When he was doing, you know, these
holidays that he's going on now, I'd
done that when I was 23. So, I mean,
everything literally screams skin about
him. That's what I mean. It's not even
just like the money thing. It's the fact
that he's It took two years to show that
money. The fact that you don't have any life experience.
What is not skin about you. Um, and
that's the thing. But yeah, the point is
Timmy, that's why I don't waste my time
showing you money. And I will never show
you money ever again. Um, never ever.
You can try and call me, you can say I'm
skinn, you can say I don't have£1 or200.
Okay? I don't have it. You know, it's
about time you people started shutting
me up. Yeah. Why don't you people come
on the panel later on and you start
showing your money? Yeah. Exactly. You
can't. So, stop saying that people are
skinned to me because they don't want to
play your silly little self-p projecting
games anymore. Yeah. Done.