Yo. Okay, so time for a new dating
video. Now, before I get into this, I
just wanted to say that I downloaded
Tinder earlier and I downloaded Hinge
earlier and both of which still don't
work. Um, you know, no surprise there.
Dating apps don't work for, you know, heterosexual
um men like myself. So, I have no idea
why people still suggest them. You know,
to be honest with you, the only people
that benefit from dating apps are either
gay men or women, or I guess, you know,
there's an exception of a it working for
a heterosexual man if, you know, he's
extremely good-looking and he looks like
a model, but you know, generally
speaking, they only benefit um
yeah, gay men and women. Um so, I have
no idea why people still suggest them.
At the end of the day, I I feel like
they're that's that's the worst way to
try to get someone. You know, I'd say
it's even worse than, you know, trying
to meet a woman through approaching to
be fair. I mean, I I have no idea why
people still suggest them. They don't
work at all. But anyways, on to the main
point of this video. Right. So, I was on
Reddit earlier scrolling and
somebody uh I went on a few posts. They
were all sort of the same topic. They
all related to each other. And
basically, they were asking people and
asking women directly, you know, uh when
was the last time you had sex? How long
can you go without sex? Um you know,
before you get annoyed, Aggy, sexy,
frustrated. And you know, a lot of these
women were saying like, you know, a week
um two weeks, a month, two months, 3
months. You know, a lot of them are
saying how they've got friends with
benefits. And I might be a bit biased
here, but to me it was kind of like a
kick in the teeth because obviously last
week what happened when I got them 10
numbers, went out trying my best,
looking my best, spent a load of money.
Um, and out of them 10 numbers, I didn't
even get one single woman willing to
give me a chance, like even getting to
know me, my personality. I didn't even
get given a chance. Um, I didn't even,
you know, get, you know, I didn't even
stand a fighting chance. I didn't get
any of them numbers even willing to, um,
go on a date with me and see how things
go. So, I mean, if that in itself does
not tell you that there's no hope, um,
you know, I I don't know what possibly
will, you know, like. So, yeah. And it's
mad to think that like a woman doesn't
even need to leave her house to get her
satisfied, to get her needs satisfied.
You know, she can get a date whenever
she wants. She can get sex whenever she
wants. She can get, you know, a
boyfriend whenever she wants. Like I
said, she can get her needs satisfied
without leaving the house. Now, my
problem with this is not the fact that,
you know, the dating game is easier for
women because it's always been easier
for women. Even before social media, the
dating game has always been easier for
women and it will always be easy for
women. You know, back in the day before
social media, how do you think people
met? You know, men still had to approach
when, you know, most men are scared to
approach. Most men won't approach. You
know, I'm not scared because I've been
doing it for years. But, you know, men
still had to take the league, you know.
But the difference is is back then, you
know, there was hope because obviously
there was no simps, there was no white
knights, you know, um, you know, giving
women inflated egos, making women think
they're better than they actually are,
then them giving them an attitude, then
them thinking that they're better than
you. And hence why the dating game's
[ __ ] you know, it all stems from
social media and simps and white
knights. That's where the problem comes
from. Um, you know, so that's that's how
it is. But like the point I'm trying to
make is it's always been easier for
women, you know, and that's that's fine.
It's always going to be that way.
Always. And and and to be honest with
you, I'm I'm not complaining about that,
you know. There's there's no problem
with, you know, you having to try harder
to get what you want or you having to
put effort in or you taking a league cuz
that's that's part of being a man.
That's not my problem. My problem is is
that even when you go out looking your
best, you know, trying your best, being
confident, um, you know, spending money,
doing everything you possibly can, that
doesn't even lead you a date. I think
that's something, you know, that is is
mad. How you can literally do all of
them things and still get nowhere. It's
not like, you know, hold on a minute,
you do all of these things that women
don't have to do because that's the way
it is and then you get these things.
It's like you can literally do all of
these things. You can do your best, work
on yourself, work on, you know, your,
you know, you can get your money up, you
can look your best, you can do your
best, you can, you know, get 10 numbers.
You can literally do everything and you
still won't even get a date. Like that
to me is insane. Like, honest to God.
Yeah. I spent £600 last week and the
most money I've ever spent before on a
night out was £700. Yeah. £700. And I'm
thinking at the end of the [ __ ] day,
right? There is a cost of living crisis.
You know what I'm saying? So, I mean,
what is some what is a man supposed to
do? Go out every single week spending
£400, you know, getting a haircut every
week trying just to get nowhere in the
end? Like, when you know, all a woman's
got to do is just not even leave a house
and she can get a guy come to her and
she can get sex. Like that's the whole
problem with it's not that you need to
do X Y and zed to get what you want.
It's even it's even when you do [ __ ]
zed X Y and zed, you still won't get
anything. Even when you work on
yourself, even when you you know you
spent a lot of money, you've put the
work in, you've not, you know, stayed at
home moaning and winging, you still
won't get anything. So it's like they
don't have to do anything
to get what they want. But even when you
do everything, you still can't get
anything. What a [ __ ] kick in the
teeth. And at the end of the day, I
think like I said last week, maybe I
might be a bit biased with this, but
last week it really it was like [ __ ]
rubbing [ __ ] salt and alcohol in the
womb because it's like I spent a lot of
money. You know, I tried, you know, I
looked my best as well. I looked good as
well and I didn't even have a date
scheduled for the following week, which
was last week. So, I mean, what hope
actually is there? And then, you know, a
woman can just jump on a dating app and
get get a guy, whereas you could
literally go out every single week and
get nothing. You could do your best, be
your best, wait around, try and not try,
and you still won't get anything. It's
[ __ ] It's so [ __ ] to think that
like even when you put the necessary
effort in, you still won't get anything.
Cuz it's never It's never ever been like
that. It's always been like you put
effort into things, you get something
out of it. But with this, even when you
put effort in, even if you spend a load
of money or you do whatever it is you
need to do, you still won't get anyone
even give you a chance. It's It is a
proper proper madness. Like the dating
game for men truly is a mug's game. Like
at at this point, yeah, it's not even
saying that, oh, it's it's stacked
against men. It's literally a mug's
game. like how you can look your best,
do your best, be confident, spend that
money, you know, willing to do all the
necessary requirements and still don't
get anything. That is just a mugs game.
You know, at the end of the day, you
know, they they call gambling a mugs
game, but bro, at least with gambling
sometimes you win. At least with other
things that are generally considered a
mugs game. I bet you a lot of the times
you win. But with baiting, you can do
your I mean last last week I know I've
had like [ __ ] in the past and that but
it's like you literally have to look
your best, do your best, be confident,
have to continuously put up with their
[ __ ] and their mind games and you still
don't get anything at the end of it.
Like it's it's insane. Like I've never
ever heard of anything else in my life
where somebody would put effort into
something and then not get anything out
of it. It just doesn't life doesn't tend
to work that way. It's normally you put
the effort in like looking your best,
looks maxim, going out, being confident,
smelling good, spending money, and then
you eventually will get like a date. But
even if you do all of them things, you
still don't get anything. It's the same
as like if I was to go out um you know
uh this week say for example I went out
on Saturday this week I'd probably go
through a couple of hundred pound my
best doing my best and it would be the
same story get a couple of numbers [ __ ]
me around probably wouldn't even get a
date like it's it's mad you know the
dating game is truly a mug's game for
men you know that's what the date that's
what the title of this video is going to
be you know
I wouldn't fine if you actually put the
effort in and got something out of it.
But with this, it's like even when you
put the effort in, you look your best.
You know, you can be good-looking, you
can try your best, and you still won't
get anything no matter how hard you try
or how many times you try or, you know,
it's like you still literally will not
get anything. You know, last week proved
that. You know, that was like a months of
work. You know, 10 numbers. Yeah. I
normally used to get about three numbers
a week. So the the dating game truly is
a mugs game for men.