Okay, so I know I said I was done with
this shitty community just repeating self-reflecting
mongaloid mongified community and I am
but I just got cooked a lovely pork
roast dinner and it just reminds me how
like a certain person's never had
>> this cooked before by his mama his mom
used to starve him. Imagine your mom
starving you would been having and then
someone else's mom cooking him a lovely
pork dinner. I'm having beef as well.
It's it's in the oven, but it's not
quite ready yet.
>> Some people
>> being starved by their mother
>> can never relate.
>> Just certain things to you. Just just
certain things in life you can't relate to.
You went after the real