Yo. Okay. So, I'm just lying in bed um
playing a bit of Franklin and I thought,
do you know what? Yeah. Let me test this
experiment out um 3 months later cuz I
got some new women's numbers. And I
thought, do you know what? Yeah. Some of
them didn't reply. Some of them stopped
replying. Some of them replied and then
said they were on holiday. And I said,
oh, were you off on holiday? And then
they didn't reply. So, I thought I me
let me message all of these numbers
saying that I hate women. They literally
all replied back in like less than 2
minutes. Like the last time some of them
replied back and it took a little time.
I can safely say all of those women that
ignored or started ignoring or didn't
get back to me, best believe they were
somewhere to be seen when them negative
messages were sent. And that just goes
to show how [ __ ] up these women
really, really are. How they can ignore
normal and nice messages, yet as soon as
a negative message is sent, bam, they're
there. Trolling, trying to take the
piss. It's funny cuz no one on the
internet tells you any of this stuff.
Like, women are trolls. They're
[ __ ] Um, they only reply to
negativity. Like, you find this [ __ ] out
for your [ __ ] self. And you know, it
was winding me up that much that bro, if
I knew where one of them lived, I'd be
on their door now. Like that's how much
it was like generally annoying me. Um,
you know, the fact and some of them are
trying to troll me as well, ask me for
money. And it feels like I generally
think once you've met one woman, you've
met them all. They're all the same. Like
just that, right? They all reply to negativity.
Um, they all lead people on the same
way. um they all try to victimize
themselves, you know, like by that I
mean, so when you write, for example, I
hate women, and they reply straight
away, um they will use that as an excuse
as to why they didn't reply to your last
message when we both know they had no
intentions of ever replying to your
normal nice message. And the negative
message is what got them to respond in
the first place. So it if they generally
weren't all the same, they do a lot of
the same stuff for people that aren't
all the same. That's that's just how I'm
going to leave it. And yeah, like I had
one and a lot of the conversations that
I had, I felt like I'd had them a
million times before. Like, and that
just goes to tell you that it's never
ever going to change. Like, you know,
you get these people that say, you know,
you don't know what the future holds.
You never know who you're going to meet.
Um, but think about it. They were
probably saying all that [ __ ] to me
about four years ago and I'm still
dealing with it. You know, four years
ago when I was a lot younger when I, you
know, started this approach and [ __ ] and
I bet you they were telling me exactly
the same [ __ ] You know, you're still
young. You don't know what the future
holds. Well, I've got a pretty good idea
what the future holds in this country
when it comes to women. I've got a
pretty good idea so far what my um
experiences have been showing me. It's
not looking great. Um, so I mean that's
that's a [ __ ] fact. And do you know
what's so [ __ ] up is it's not like
we're 18, 19 years of age anymore. We're
[ __ ] adults, you know, 27. A lot of
them are a lot older than me. And
they're still playing these silly um
immature games, you know, only replying
to negativity straight away, leading
people on, [ __ ] with people, trolling
people. Surely to God, it would have
ended by now if it was going to. You
know, you hear all of these people that
say, "Oh, you don't know what the future
holds." But I mean, four years is is a
long time, you know, to give to give
this a chance to change. And it's
generally generally all the same [ __ ]
And I'm so surprised. And they were
replying back being like a [ __ ] as
well. Like they weren't just saying,
"Oh, why are you saying you hate women?"
Or they were generally just being a
[ __ ] Like an awkward trolling
[ __ ] Like I swear to God if I knew
where any of them live, bro. I'll be on
the door right now. I'm not even joking.
Like they they actually get you like
that. Um I'm glad I gave up with this
whole like approaching them this dating
thing. And do you know what? To be fair,
a part of me was like, do you know what
you should do? You should just approach
every day and just [ __ ] use one of
them for their body because one of them
is eventually going to say, "Yeah." Um
and then just [ __ ] them off and just
like ruin their life and not care about
them. But then I was like, "Uh, we're
not low like these women. We're not scum
like these women, you know. We we we're
not narcissists like them, which is what
they do is actually a trait of
narcissism where they try to victimize
themselves. That's a trait of
narcissism, which is why I explained
earlier. It's like we're better than
that. You know what I'm saying? We're
better than people that can only reply
back to negativity, you know? Um, and
try to play the victim and troll people
and [ __ ] asking me for [ __ ] money.
You know how many times I've had that
conversation before where someone's
tried to ask me for money? They
generally generally are all the same.
Like I get nothing out of saying
something that I don't believe. I get
nothing out of saying it. They genuinely
if I didn't believe it, they genuinely
are all the [ __ ] same. Like I of all
people would would would [ __ ] know
it. I genuinely would say that I've
approached in them few years 4,000
[ __ ] people. And you know, simps can
say, "Oh, you don't know all women." And
you know, but put it this way, these
people that defend women are probably
still [ __ ] virgins. They probably
never even [ __ ] been with a woman. I
just find it's so [ __ ] up how they're
so fast enough to reply to negativity.
Why do they do all the same [ __ ] if
they're not all the [ __ ] same? I
think that's that that is a a valid
point. If they're not all the same, why
do they do the same [ __ ] as one another?
If they're not all the [ __ ] same, you
know what? How can someone even answer
that? You know, we get people that say,
"No, they're not all the same. Why do
they do all the same [ __ ] then as one
another?" [ __ ] pathetic.