Okay, so this is going to be a response
to um Timmy. Yeah, it's funny how you
said that I'm the ma. Timmy, have you
actually looked at yourself? You're
literally a 41-year-old virgin. Like
you're you're 11 years older than the
Kent virgin, and you're and he's he's a
virgin as well, but you're both virgins.
Um and you're saying that I'm I'm the
ma. Uhhuh. Okay. How many times have you
been seen with a woman?
Huh? On YouTube throughout your whole
time on YouTube? Never. How many times
has Peter Belly been seen with women?
Several several times. I think that that
ends it. So, you were saying about how
um uh why am I so obsessed with money
and ret. Now, at the end of the day,
man, I liked what you was actually
saying in your video. It was actually
quite good. But you're you're saying it
to the wrong person, Timmy. You and
other people on here, all you talk about
is money. Money, money, money. This
person's skin, that person's skin, this
person's skin, that person's skin. And
then whenever you got whenever you get
beaten at the money game, then it's
like, ah, well, who cares about money?
So, you sort of backtrack what you say.
So it's like you skint people come on
here every day calling other people what
you are yourselves which is skint put
two and two together and then as soon as
somebody beats you at the [ __ ] money
game right you then say oh well who
cares about money like make it make
sense don't start something you can't
finish because it just makes you look um
very very silly I mean who's the one
that came on here started saying that
people are this and people that let me
tell you something to me do you want to
know how skinn these people really
really really are. It took 18 months for
somebody to show me 10 grand. They made
it so impossibly difficult to show me
that 10 grand, which is crazy because
they sit on it every day and they call
other people skimp. Yet, it took 18
months for somebody to show me that
[ __ ] 10 grand because they ain't got
it. Um, you know, for all of them 18
months. So, I mean, Timmy, you can't
really do that. You can't come on here
every single day calling people skin and
then when somebody beats you at the
money game, you then start saying, "Oh,
well, who cares?" Uh um you know, money
uh you know what I'm saying? It's it's
you can't do that. Like you started it
and a lot of the times I finished it.
You know what I'm saying? So you can't
backtrack what you are saying. And then
you're trying to say about how um I'm
jealous. Jealous Timmy. I've never ever
been jealous of anybody in my whole
entire life. never have been and never
will be. And anybody that's got more
money than me, I literally do not care.
Like, I mean, think about it. I think
I've said this a few times, but I don't
think you've you've heard me say it. I
could have £300 in my account and I
would have a better life than 99% of um
people in this community. Money, money,
money. All we hear about is money,
money, money. So, do we hear about who's
got the better life, but let's start
showing who's got the better life. Oh,
you remember all of them places that
I've gone to? Are you forgetting all of
those experiences that I have? And even
this month, I've had probably done more
than these people, bro. Why would I be
jealous of middle-aged old wrinkly men
that don't even leave the house?
Why would anybody be jealous of any of
those people? Think about it, right? I'm
27. I can do what I want. I've got money
to do what I want. whether I've got more
money than them or not, I have a life
and and I've shown that on YouTube. Why
would I be jealous of anybody on here?
They're low lives. They sit on YouTube
every single day trying to find people
to [ __ ] with from the time they go to
bed to the time the time they wake up to
the time they go to bed. All they do is
come on here and try to [ __ ] with
people. They live. They live to do this.
Like they live and they don't even get
paid for it. Like it doesn't matter
whether they've got money or they don't
have money, whatever. I mean, obviously
most of them don't have money because
they wouldn't be sat on here every day
doing what they do for a living and they
don't even get paid for it. They're
doing this every single day for a living
free of charge. Do you think people with
a better life and people that's got
money would be doing, you know, the
stuff that these people are doing on
here like Red Star, Smokeoky B, do you
think somebody with a better life would
be sat here wasting all of their life
away trying to [ __ ] with somebody and
not even get paid for it? Just just just
think about it. No. So, I mean that's
it. I've never been jealous of anybody
in my life. Never have been. And I never
ever will be. And to be honest with you,
mate, I don't know why you were even
making videos of me. You had nothing to
say when I was in Birmingham. I had to
listen to you and Monty's [ __ ] for the
better part of about 3 months. And then
when I finally went to Birmingham, you
was nowhere to be seen. And don't say
you didn't see it. And don't start
making excuses cuz I'm not going to go
round and round in circles with you. You
have nothing to say in person when I was
in your city. So why are you making
stupid little videos? It's just
ridiculous, man. I'm not I'm not going
to go round and round in circles with
you. Jealous. Bro, let me tell you
something. These people in this
community are nothing to be jealous of.
They're old, wrinkly, low lives that
ain't got a life. Money or no money.
That's that's irrelevant. Think about it, bro.
What what makes the person a something
to envy? A good life, good looks, their
youth. It ain't all about money, bro.
These people are nothing to be jealous of
like at all. So I I don't get I don't
understand what you are making videos
for. But yeah, that's my response to you, man.