Yo. Okay, so time for a new dating
video. Um, I was supposed to do this uh
a couple of days ago, but I just didn't
get around to doing it. Um, but I'm
doing it now. Um, so yeah, I'm going to
title this video as trying to date in
2025 is toxic and vile. Like, yeah,
literally, I don't think there's any better
words to describe it other than that.
Um, so yeah, uh, quick disclaimer before
I get into this, um, video. Um, that I'm
not a s. I'm not a white knight. I'm not
an incel. This is completely me just
being unbiased and, um, talking about my
experiences because I feel like anyone
that does a video like this um, should
be unbiased, you know, to make it fair.
So, this is just me um, talking. So, um,
yeah, about basically what's um,
happened recently. Um, so
yeah, like even like when I was
approaching the last time I went out,
which was last Friday, I was thinking
like, damn, this is really really vile.
So I'm going to start with um what
happened [clears throat]
two weeks ago and then I'm going to talk
about um what happened um last time I
went out, which was last Friday. So two
weeks ago was the first time that I went
out approaching and going for a drink in
6 weeks. Yeah, literally six weeks. I
actually think I broke the record of um,
you know, not going out for the longest.
And simply because, you know, six weeks
prior to this, right, I literally went
out, I looked my best, I got 10 numbers
and I didn't even get a single date. I
mean, I got one person that replied and
we were supposed to meet. We arranged it
and then on the well the day before they
came up with an excuse as they as as to
why they caught me. Tried to reschedule
it and never heard from them again. Even
to this day I've still not heard from
them. So at the end of the day it's like
if you can go out looking your best
getting 10 numbers that's that's a lot
of numbers, you know. It's not even like
it's three numbers or even four, you
know, and not even get a date. There
isn't hope in this country. Um and I
think that that really done it for me.
Like I was like, there is literally no
hope. Because you've got to think about
this, right? A date isn't really a big
thing. You know, I would go as far as
saying that, you know, eight times out
of 10 a date doesn't go anywhere. Um,
you know, like how many dates do you
think people go on before they meet the
love of their life or they meet somebody
that they um stay with for the rest of
their life? Quite a lot. You know,
obviously there might be some people
that get lucky the first time and the
first date they go and they stay with
that person. Um, but normally they,
especially nowadays, people constantly
go on dates before they find Mr. Right
or Mrs. Right. So, the fact that you can
look your best, get that amount of
numbers, and not even get a date,
there's no hope in this country. Um, and
basically, I just lost the desire to to
want to try again after that as and I
spent a lot of money as well. That's
another thing is when you're when you're
going out, you know, trying to date,
you're dealing with women that have got
attitude problems. You're dealing with
mind games. You're spending a lot of
money as well. Um, and there's a cost of
living crisis um going on. Um, actually
um what I noticed was um last Friday um
just to add this in here, a lot of
people are not going out as much now in
in central London. like it you it was
always everywhere it happened where like
pubs would be empty or you know not a
lot of people going but now um you know
even in central London this is happening
because people just simply don't have
the money to go out um you know things
are expensive people have to pay rent so
it's even hitting central London now um
which was the only place it didn't hit
because obviously you know people that
go there obviously have money so a lot
you know even the like clubbing scene
and the drinking scene is is dying a lot
now so um that's another thing I just
I'd add in there. But yeah, um basically
uh that's how I basically just lost the
desire and and hope to want to try
again. And you know, when I didn't go
out for them 6 weeks, um I didn't even
feel bored. I was just so happy to not
have to deal with the mind games, the
excuses, the attitude, all of the
toxicity that that came with trying to
um date women. Um and another thing is
um I felt so much better. you know, when
I gave up, I actually felt like I
changed as a person. Um, you know, and
I'm not even joking. Like, I feel I feel
like my personality changed. I changed.
Um, because obviously naturally it
would, you know, you're no longer
dealing with all of the toxic stuff that
comes with dating. Of course, you're
going to be, but not not in the first
two weeks because the first two weeks I
was still depressed from what happened
two weeks before that. Um, you know, how
you can get that that many numbers and
not even get a date. So I was just like,
"No, that is that is mad." But then by
two and a half weeks, the third week, I
just felt so much better. Um, that just
goes to show how toxic the whole thing
was in the first place that, you know,
as soon as you give up, you feel so much
better. Um, and yeah, so and I have uh
not had a date since April. Um, I've
only been on three dates this year and
um, it was in April. Yeah, all three of
them was in April. I think they were all
within the same week or two weeks. And
I've been out a lot since April, as you
can imagine. And not even got a single
date. So, I don't think there's much
hope in this country. Um, despite what
people say. And quite frankly, I was
sick of dealing with, you know, you you
get all of these people that will sit
there and and swear to their blew in the
face that, you know, all women are
aren't the same and all women are
different, but yet every single time you
go out and you try to meet a new woman,
it's always the same stuff. Mind games
or they pretend they've got boyfriends
or they give attitude or they give you
their number and lead you on. It's never
any different. So, I mean, I would love
to know um where all of these different
women are hiding because it must be not
on planet Mars because every single
woman that I come across, they all seem
to be the same. Um, so that's another
thing which I'll touch on to that a bit
later because this will tie in with
something else I'm talking about. Um, so
anyways, uh, yeah, that's that. So,
finally went out again after 6 weeks
again, which was two weeks ago. And I
literally remembered why I gave up. I
was like, "Oh, this is why I gave up."
It was so toxic. Like I was trying to
like speak to a woman and then her just
as we were about to exchange numbers, um
her friend would get involved and tried
to like draw attention and be like, and
it happened a couple of times to be
fair. Um it wasn't only one time. Um so
it happened a couple of times and then
uh yeah, it was like it was just they
just had attitude problems. Um as usual,
just bad bad attitude. um which is a big
thing with these with these women and
they've got a lot of really bad
attitude. Um so yeah um dealt with that
got into a couple of arguments. What I
don't understand is that it's this I'm
just going to add this in here is that
these people want to try and say that
you're a bully as soon as you stand up
to yourself. So because I wouldn't let a
woman shout in my face and tell me what
to do um you know all of a sudden I'm I
quote bully. So, I mean, it's like it
literally is the same as you will get
like, for example, narcissistic women
that will habitatly seek out people to
mess with um because that's that that's
what they do. And then as soon as they
meet their match, they will say that,
"Oh, you're a stalker." Or um you know,
they will try to play the victim. And
it's a bit like these women like they
will go around giving attitude problems
and you know being rude and then as soon
as somebody stands up to themsel all of
a sudden they're a I quote bully. Um and
yeah it was just pretty much the same
thing. Um and attitude problems people
saying that they had boyfriends. Um what
another thing that happened um was I was
in this um club and I met this guy and I
was like oh you know we should go out
and we should go and approach these um
these women. So, we went over and we
approached them, right? And one of them
said to me that, "Oh, um, you know, I
have a boyfriend." Um, typical, isn't
it? Um, so, okay, well, can you can your
friend maybe talk to my friend? And, um,
she turned around and said, "Oh, he
might want to sort out his big forehead
first before, you know, um, you know,
coming over and talking um to to to to
women." I'm thinking that just gave me
the ick, bro. Like even though they
weren't saying that to me or about me,
um that's disgusting, you know, because
you get all of these people that sit
there and say, "Oh, women go for
personality. They like guys with a good
attitude." Yet you will come across
these women that have absolutely no
problem verbally abusing somebody. No
one has a problem with that, you know.
But then when if you was to stand up to
yourself, just stand up for yourself.
You're bullying women. That's that's the
logic that they go by. And it's and it's
so insane. And it's not even that. It's
like even other examples where they've
got really really really really bad
attitude. It's like they're allowed to
walk around with attitude. They're
allowed to verbally abuse people. If you
went into a club and you started
verbally abusing women that you did not
know, mate, they would have a big
problem with that. You'd probably have
people chasing you with axes. But if a
woman wants to give attitude or try to
talk about someone's appearance or be
passive aggressive, there's no problem
with that. Absolutely no problem. But
people scream and shout that they want
equality. But how can it be equal?
Because you stand up to yourself when
someone's trying to be rude to you.
You're a I quote bully. Yet women are
allowed to talk about someone's forehead
being big and try to knock their
confidence down and try to insult them.
Absolutely no problem. So it just
doesn't really make any sense. Um, so
anyways, that night uh which was a
Saturday, I got I think I got four
numbers and only one replied and they
were from France. Um, and uh, then I
messaged them again and then they didn't
reply, which was strange because there
was somebody that I had a conversation
with from Manchester and they seemed all
right. They seemed down to earth and
whatever and then I went to message them
and absolutely no reply. Um, which which
was strange to be fair. I did think they
were going to reply. You know, normally
when you approach someone, you can kind of
guess um which is going to reply and
which is not going to reply. You have a
rough idea. Uh usually um so that was
shock. That was it was a bit bad to be
honest. So that's 14 numbers and only
two replies and not a single date. Um
and bear in mind dating apps don't work.
So that's that out the out the way. So
14 numbers, two replies. Well, 14
numbers in the space of the two two
outings that I've gone out and only two replies
and no dates. Um, which is a crazy
amount of number because I imagine if I
had to think about another guy doing
what I've done and it happening to it
would just be insane. And then that
brings me on to last Friday uh which was
so I've been out quite a bit you know so
I went out last Friday. Um, I was
supposed to go out the Saturday, but I
went to the dentist on Friday. Um, had
to get a filling in. I thought, "Oh, do
you know what? Yeah, I might as well
just stay out um now and um just just go
out basically. Um, why not?" Um, because
yeah, um I don't want to just like just
lie around and do nothing. So bear in
mind, I didn't have any expectations um
when I went out and approached because
generally deep down I know that there is
no hope. Now, before I get into this,
it's that people want to sit there and
say to you that, you know, there's hope
and you're going to find someone and
you're going to meet someone eventually
and tet, but what these people fail to
realize is, brother, you're you're not
even getting any dates with all of the
effort that you put in the approaching,
looking your best, doing your best,
there's no minor successes along the
way. None at all. So it's not very
likely that all of a sudden it's going
to change and also the the time frame
that it's been happening for. I mean
this has been happening for years. So
generally if you are going to find
someone eventually you've got more
chance of winning the lottery because if
it was anything less than that you would
have already found someone or you'd be
going on dates or something would have
happened something would be happening.
Um just a disclaimer to put out there
but there's nothing and this has been
going on for years. So anyways, I went
into central London um done some
approaches and the first person that I
approached literally just nod nodded
their head at me. Yep. I'm thinking,
"Oh, that kind of contradicts the whole
women go for personality then, doesn't
it?" Because when you try to speak to
someone, I mean, they don't even look at
you. Um so that was one out the way and
I've done quite a lot. Um there was one
from uh Amsterdam. Yeah, I I approached
this um this woman from Amsterdam and we
was talking and they said that they were
visiting and um they said basically that
oh do you have any recommendations?
Obviously I gave them recommendations.
They wrote it down. Then I turned around
and said to them, oh uh let's exchange
numbers and then um she said oh I don't
exchange numbers. I've got a boyfriend
but if I see you later I'll have a drink
with you. So, you'd have a drink with
somebody, but yet you have a boyfriend.
Bit strange. I mean, this is partly uh
it got really really bad. I mean, I had
to approach about 50 people sober to get
one number. Um and there was one that
said that they, you know, were looking
for someone. Um same old. Um and then
apparently about how like they will see
me later if they see me. Another thing
that they all seem to say for people
that are completely different, they all
seem to have similar sayings and similar
man similar similar mannerisms for
people that are completely different. I
mean, what are the odds? And there was
um one that stuck their thumb up at me
and basically there was a lot of
attitude problems. A lot like it was
bad. So, at the end of the day, I I was
just thinking to myself, like obviously
I was just doing it because I was doing
it, but I'm thinking, Jesus Christ, is
is this what people really have to go
through to try to find someone? Bear in
mind, dating apps don't work. I mean,
damn, that is that is really, really,
really bad. You know, you have to hear
the boyfriend excuses, um, the passive
aggressiveness, the sarcasm, the piss
taking, the attitude. And there was a
lot of people with attitude, bro. Like
like I said, it took me 50 approaches to
get one number. I mean it was about 50
sober as well. Like my back was killing
me by the end of it. Um so and there was
one tried to speak to them, they said
straight away not interested. Um so it's
like you get all of these people tell
you one thing on the internet and then
when you go out and you test the theory,
most of the women that you come across
are just people with attitude um simply.
And then I was like, do you know what
would be a good idea? If I actually
recorded 3 hours footage of me actually
approaching these women, but then
there'd be absolutely no point because
people would just dismiss your struggles
as usual anyways. So, I don't know why I
thought that, but anyway. So, yeah, in
the end, I got one number um and uh one
Snapchat um from the sober approaches.
Now, this is the funny thing, right? So,
I was I approached this woman right in
Snapchat on um in Oxford Circus and I
got her Snapchat and we was talking all
like the other night and whatever and
yeah, she was saying that um she's the
only one that didn't seem stuck up even
though she was from London. So, I mean
that's that's a needle in a haststack
when you find someone other than
yourself from London that doesn't have
an attitude problem. Um it's always nice
to be fair. Um especially a woman. So,
um yeah. Uh she basically said to me, I
was talking and I said to her, "Oh, like
do you want to hang out on Thursday?"
Then she turned around and said to me,
"Oh, you know, you're really nice.
You're a sweet guy. Thank you for
approaching me. Ret,
but um you know, um I'm busy with this,
that, and the other." And to me, it just
it just sounds mad because I'm always
constantly out there trying to find a
woman that is different, that don't
pretend they've got a boyfriend, that
don't lead people on, that don't have an
attitude problem. Like, I've made it my
life at times to try to find these
people that are out there and I can't
find them. Despite what people say, they
will sit there and say that women aren't
the same and but you can't find anyone
that aren't the same. um no matter where
you go, what you do, how you act, you
generally can't find one that's
different. And then you will get these
women that will, you know, say that they
can't find a normal guy, can't find a
nice guy, can't find someone that's not
like a, you know, an abuser because, let
me let me just say this to you, right?
Although they might have options, they
don't have genuine options. Like people
that are not creeps or not simps or they
don't have genuine options. So it's like
when I use it from when I base it off my
experiences is like hold on. You've got
a guy that's approached you. You've even
said that they're sweet and that they're
nice and ret but yet wouldn't you want
to give that person a chance? Now again
I'm I don't care. I don't have any
expectations, but you know, if you're
playing, you know, if you want to play
two sides of the coin of the coin here,
you would have thought that if a if if a
woman, right, was was decent looking and
they've come up approaching you, you
would give them a chance, you know? I
mean, these women constantly probably
have to, you know, filter out these weirdo simp.
And then they've come across someone
that by their own words is is a good
person. And I'm probably the most
genuine person they'll ever meet. but
they still don't want to give you a
chance. So, I mean, they don't really
deserve any sympathy then. If they ever
want to moan and complain about men ever
again, you know, that's on them. They
have no um they have no they don't
deserve any sympathy because think about
it, we're we're going out trying to find
someone different. Someone different has
very much come their way. Someone very
genuine has very much come their way,
but yet they're still not interested.
So, you know what? what what is it these
people actually want? So anyways, that's
that. So anyways, then I went to some
bars and clubs. Had to deal with the
I've got a boyfriend about six million
times. Um which is um which is weird. So
in the end I got uh I think I got seven
numbers and yeah, one number replied and
that Snapchat replied and basically
didn't get anywhere with any of them. So
that's three different outings and I
think I'm at 22 23 numbers now and not a
single day. So I generally don't see how
this is ever going to get better in this
country to be honest with you. Um and
it's like and obviously when I was going
out um approaching uh Friday, this is um
similar to what I was just saying is
that like [snorts] it's okay. Yeah, it
might be nice to find someone and
whatever, but is it really worth going
out every day disrespecting yourself,
dealing with women's lies, dealing with
their attitude, dealing with them being
stuck up just in order to find someone?
It really, really, really, really isn't
worth it. Um, it really really isn't.
Um, just to find someone that's well,
you know, it's just crazy. Unless like
someone's a virgin or they really want
kids, I don't see why people would
continuously go out and deal with the
disrespect, the attitude, the lies, the
games, the mind games being led on cuz
that's all that ever happens and that's
all that will ever happen um when you
deal with women. So, it's like why would
somebody really want to keep putting up
with that, you know? Like I said,
Friday, I had no expectations. I just
done it because I've done it, as mad as
that sounds. But there's a lot of women
with bad attitude. Um, again, you never
hear about this on the internet. So, um,
it is strange to be honest. Um, so
that's where we're at. 22 numbers, 23
numbers, and not a single date. Um, I
don't possibly see, um, how this is ever
going to get better. Um, but people
still seem to think I'm going to meet
someone, so I mean, that's that. Um, so
that's where we're at. So that's the
little video done.