So, I was just uh reading Rickster's
comment and all I've got to say is
cheers Rick. Um even though he's
probably going to um delete your comment
and ban you um and pretend that you're
me. Um that's the thing. Anyone that
disagrees with this skin virgin um he
will literally just yeah block them and
say that they're me. Um he's very scared
of dislikes as well. So, if somebody
writes a uh comment and he get, you
know, um agreeing with me or disagreeing
with him and it gets loads of um thumbs
up, he'll pretend that it's me that's
thumbsed up because he's so obsessed
with me and he's scared of likes and dislikes.
Um and yeah, like I said, anyone that
disagrees with him, he'll he'll ban
them. Um so, expect to be banned um when
uh when when he comes back on. Yep. He
he doesn't let anyone in here. only
people that uh agree with him. [ __ ]
loser. Copycat. No mind of his own. But
anyways, cheers Rick stuff.