Showtime. I tried so many times to
diffuse this situation with this [ __ ]
[ __ ] So many times and he wouldn't do
it. He wouldn't listen. I tried ignoring
him. Wouldn't listen. [ __ ] this, bro.
[ __ ] this [ __ ] bro.
[ __ ] that [ __ ] bro. Yeah. One second.
Yeah. I'm serious now. Yeah.
Try and get there as fast as you can, please.
Right. We're doing this now. We're doing
this, bro. Come on.
Go, go, go, go. Let's go. It's show time.
Just hope old Bill been called. It's my
friend there. I fancy see my friend on
my way to a confrontation.
But I'm on my way to a confrontation.
That's Imagine that. Sickening. You got
Can you just stop here? Yeah. >> Yeah.
>> Stop it. Stop it. Stop it. Stop it.
>> Are you paying cash?
>> Huh? Cash your card. >> Card.
>> Right. I send it over to that back machine. >> Yep.
>> When it comes through. >> Yeah.
>> Just push the red cross.
>> Okay. Hurry. Hurry. Hurry.
>> On the Hang on. Wait till it comes through.
>> Right. Just push the red cross on the
bottom left of the pin pad.
>> Open the door. Open the door.
>> No, I'm doing this one. >> Yeah.
You little [ __ ] [ __ ] Yeah.
You better not go in that camp. You
better not go in that t.
Where's this [ __ ] Where the [ __ ] is
Where the [ __ ] is this [ __ ] Where is
he, bro? Where the [ __ ] is this little Timmy,
come on, bro. Come on. Don't let us down
now, big man. Come on. Come on. Come on to me.