Yo. Okay, so um yeah, this is going to
be a video to Virgin Boy or anyone else that
feels like they may be able to um answer
this. But yeah, I was just sat here
thinking, you know, you always hear the
word socially acceptable and that's not
socially acceptable or this is socially
acceptable. Um you know, I was thinking
today because um yeah, something
happened. So yeah, I remember when I met
uh Virgin Boy a few times, he always
used to um try to dictate to me um what
was, you know, not socially acceptable.
He always used to say that's not
socially acceptable. Um and I think I
used to say back to that, I literally
don't care what is socially acceptable
or not. I literally don't give a [ __ ]
Um, I would happily go to the [ __ ] um
go to the [ __ ] North Pole and live
live with the [ __ ] penguins. Um,
because I literally don't care. Um, and
yeah, I mean, what better way to um ask
somebody what is socially acceptable
than, you know, a diagnosed autistic
person? You know, I'm sure they'll know
the um answer. So, yeah. Um I was on a
bus yesterday with my mom and we was on
the priority seat because uh there was
no other um there was no other seats
available. Obviously you can't relate
cuz your mom disowned you at a very
young age. Put you into care. But um
nonetheless I I was sat um with my mom
and um this this man tapped um my back
and said um yeah can you give this uh
seat up for uh this lady? And there was
nothing wrong with her. She wasn't
pregnant. She wasn't very old and she
wasn't disabled. And I said, um, no. And
I think it's a bit rude, you know, you
you telling people to move, you know,
especially when the person is not a priority.
And then, uh, he started getting rude. I
got rude back to him and I said, "If you
want to take this further, we can get
off the bus." and ret
um and yeah, you could probably guess
that he just completely shat it um and
went um you know to the back of the bus
which you know it's always what happens
with these entitled um [ __ ] in this
country. They will be in a bad mood,
right? They'll start on someone um then
they'll be even in more of a bad mood
because of that. They'll put you in a
bad mood just to not finish what they
started. It just doesn't make any sense.
And you know, if the person was a
priority, like pregnant or old or, you
know, disabled, then obviously it it
would have been a different story. But
they wasn't. Um, and it just brought
back a lot of like what used to happen
when I used to do the Uber deliveries.
You'd get these entitled [ __ ]
right, that make these stupid sly
comments to people that they don't even
know cuz they feel like they can cuz
they're entitled. And then you you park
up your bike and say, "Come here if you
got something to say." and then they
just don't finish anything they start.
They're such [ __ ] Like I actually
forgot like how many [ __ ] they
actually are in this country. Um it's
unbelievable. There's so many [ __ ]
all so many [ __ ] just in one
country. It's it's it's uh it's a it's a
[ __ ] madness. But anyways, so my
question to you Virgin Boy is is that
socially acceptable? You know, I is that
socially acceptable? People starting to,
you know, be [ __ ] to people that
they don't know. Or what about people
that are glued to Tik Tok all day every
day? Is Is that Is that socially
acceptable, mate? Or what about when
your dad who was 43 and he got with your
mom when she was 14? Is is that socially
acceptable? How about you being 31 and
being skinned in a bedsit? Is that
[ __ ] socially acceptable? What about
that time you [ __ ] stalked that girl
in Canada for [ __ ] 3 years cuz she
didn't want you? Was that [ __ ]
socially acceptable, mate? You know,
like you need to tell me in a video or
[ __ ] um you know um a video or a post
um what is socially acceptable. Um you
know, I've actually seen videos where
you know, people have approached women
and they've been outrageously rude. I'm
pretty sure that's not a silicable
as you used to say. You're going to
[ __ ] sit there, mate, in your skinn
virgin [ __ ] bed suit with no bed in
it and try to dictate to me what's
[ __ ] socially acceptable, you silly
little [ __ ] when you can't even [ __ ]
function in normal environments. You
can't even go to a normal pub with
normal [ __ ] people. That's why you
had to go to the [ __ ] club every week
and find a [ __ ] girlfriend. again. Is
that socially acceptable? Silly little
[ __ ] You know what I'm saying? Um, you
know, all of these things don't seem
socially acceptable to me, mate. What
about dressing like you're in the 1960s?
You know, is that socially acceptable?
Is that [ __ ] socially [ __ ]
acceptable, mate? You know what I'm
saying? No, it ain't. So, don't [ __ ]
try and tell me what's socially
acceptable, you [ __ ] virgin. Yeah,
I'm pretty sure I'm not the only one
that will [ __ ] uh tell you that. [ __ ] virgin.
Go get laid and answer my uh video as well.