Yo. Okay. So, uh, merry Christmas to,
uh, all the good people out there, um,
who's watching this. Now, I'm going to
prove that these people on YouTube have
got absolutely nothing in life. Um, and
it's always been themselves. They're
talking about when they're calling
people skin or when they're telling
people that their family hate them or
all the self-p projection [ __ ] that they
come on here and do every day cuz
they've got absolutely nothing in life.
And that's why they feel the need in the
first place to come on here and hate on
strangers, people that they don't even
know every day. So, it's currently
3:52. My sleeping pattern's a bit
[ __ ] And I am going for a lust roast
dinner today with family. But I'm going
to go live at 9:00 in the morning for
literally 5 minutes. Um, so I'm doing
this video um before I um do this. I'm
going to literally go live for 5
minutes. I'm going to go downstairs,
make a tea. I'm not even going to say
anything on the live stream and then I'm
going to go back up the stairs. Um, and
you will see that these people on
YouTube even Christmas day. Um, you
know, and that's just, you know, me
going live for 5 minutes and not even
saying anything. I will prove that these
people are the ones with no family, no
money, no life. It's always been these
people. No one else. It's always been
these self projectors. So, like I said,
yeah. Um, I'll be live 9:00 in the
morning. Um, and I'll be like 5 minutes,
won't say anything. I won't even be near
the phone. Go downstairs, make a tea, go
up, and I'll quickly end it and I'll
save what I have to save and add it to
my little evidence pack. And if these
people have really got a life and
they've really got family, they won't be
on here. [snorts]
Um, so yeah, time will tell, eh? So
yeah, I'll upload this uh after um I've
uh done the live stream. It's only going
to be 5 minutes and I'm going to end it
quickly cuz I've got stuff to do. It's
Christmas Day. So, uh, yeah, we'll see.
We'll see what the
what the results will be.