Look at this little [ __ ] He's still on
YouTube. AIN'T GOT A LIFE. AIN'T GOT NO
MONEY. Sat there being a little keyboard
warrior all his life. But he will never
meet anyone cuz he knows what's good for
him. Now, like I've said many times,
nobody can ever ever say that to me
about I can't meet them because I know
what's good for them. But Red Star, you
do as you're told cuz you're a good
little boy. Even though you know my
address, you know where to find me, but
you'll do nothing cuz you're a good
little boy. Isn't that right? Just
wanted to put it out there that nobody
could ever say the same thing to me. And
you said that I was calling the grape of
women and it's pathetic. But you'll do
absolutely nothing but be a keyboard
warrior. Skint online, no life, stalking
another man because you've got nothing
along with your 40-year-old [ __ ] simp
follower of virgins. Just wanted to say
that, mate. You'll do nothing.