Cool. Lovely sight. So, I've got the
jeans on. Obviously, they're a bit loose
until you wash them for the first time.
Got the lovely trainers on. Got the
stony on. Right. And now, I'm going to
put some of this on my hair. It's called
Gorilla Powder. Yep. I think I may have
mentioned it before. Maybe a couple of
people thought I was taking a piss, but
um I wasn't taking the piss at all,
mate. No, it's uh serious stuff that is
it helps your hair. But how can I forget this?
My favorite after save. I generally
don't feel like I could live without this.
Yeah, some kind had it away on me, so I
had to buy a new one. Oh, this is lush.
I could cover myself in this all day.
New pair of jeans, newest trainers, nice
Stony. I mean, it doesn't matter if the
Stony's brand new or not. I mean,
um, that doesn't really matter, does it?
Because stonies last forever. So, yeah,
I'm going to put this away, do my little
hair, put the bedding in the wash, and,
um, yeah, I'll uh do a video of the um
of the food when I uh when I'm there.
So, it's just a day of fun stuff today.
I don't really have days of fun stuff
anymore. I'm just chilling. So, I'm
always excited when when I finally do. So, yeah.