Yo. Okay. So, this is going to be a
video to um The Virgin. Um so, I was
watching your um live stream back
yesterday. Um and to be honest with you,
I don't know what's more uglier, your
face or your clothes?
Is it your face or your clothes? Your
ugly face or your ugly clothes? I mean,
I've never had to make such a harder
decision in my life which one's more
uglier because to be fair, they're both
pretty ugly. So, I mean, let's just let
the viewers um decide on that one. Now,
I didn't think it could get any worse
than the fact that you literally went to
Amsterdam just because I went to
Amsterdam. You literally copied my
holiday. Like, hear me out here. It is
literally, you know, less than a 1%
chance that people's first trip um is is
is is Holland. You know, that's not
where people normally go the first time
they go abroad. Um but because I went
there, you somehow ended up there.
That's a bit strange, isn't it? That's a
bit sus to say the least, how I went to
Amsterdam and all of a sudden you're in
Amsterdam. There's a bit It's a bit
dodge. You can see where I'm coming
from, mate. You understand? And I mean,
yeah, I can understand you. You know,
you could be scared of flying. You could
have a phobia flying, but I mean, you're
in a relationship. I mean, even though
she's a dwolf [ __ ] I mean, you are
still in a in a relationship. Um, you
could have went to Paris. I mean, when I
couldn't go to Amsterdam,
um, my second choice was um, Paris
because I couldn't go to Amsterdam
because of the restrictions due to the
pandemic that was currently going on.
So, I said, you know, you know, let me I
was speaking to Izzy at the time and I
said, "Oh, we should go to Paris."
You ended up in Amsterdam. That's a bit
that's a bit dodgy because because I I
went to Amsterdam as well and I know
there's a bit of a delay in the time
that I went and you went, but that's
simply because your skin and you
couldn't afford it and you had no money
to go cuz cuz you're skin. But I mean,
as soon as you could copy the exact
holiday I went on, you did and you went
back. And then let's just say the fact
you know that maybe you genuinely wanted
to go to Amsterdam. Of all places yet
you're in a relationship, all of the
places in the world that you wanted to
to go to, you just somehow picked Amsterdam.
I went to Amsterdam as well. Don't know
people's forgetting. That's why he went.
Um, I mean, let's just say, yeah, you
just wanted to go there. I mean, you was
literally going on about me all day
yesterday on your live stream. You was
going on about me. You literally paid
[ __ ] money to go on holiday
to talk about me. You You not only
copied my holiday, but even when you got
to the [ __ ] destination,
you literally somehow ended up talking about me.
Yeah, you you didn't go just because I
went. Nah, nah, you you generally wanted
to go to Amsterdam of all places. Yeah.
Yeah, of course you did. You keep
telling yourself that. Um, so and then
you was walking around, right, saying
about how, you know, when I went to
Amsterdam, I can only uh I could only
afford to um stay in a uh hostel. Now, I
would answer that, but I just think it's
a bit cheeky how you can try and tell
people what they can and can't afford
when it took you until 31 to actually go
abroad. You didn't go abroad until you was 31.
And you're trying to tell me what I can
and can't afford. I went abroad when I
was 23. I was literally 23 when I first
went abroad. Yeah. So, what you're doing
at 31, I done at 23. Yeah. And you're
trying to sit there and tell me what I
can and can't afford, mate. You couldn't
afford to [ __ ] go abroad 8 years
[ __ ] after me due to the fact that
you're skinn. So I don't know what
you're getting at, mate. I really don't.
So um yeah. And then you was going
around trying to convince yourself that
I'm ugly again cuz you know that I'm a
million times better looking than you
will ever be. That's why you come on
YouTube doing this whole [ __ ] every day
saying I'm ugly and I'm this and that.
all of the things that you are yourself
and you will always be and you take it
out on me the fact that you are the ugly
one and you are the skint one and
because you know deep down I'm better
looking than you and you're obsessed
with me. It literally kills you. That's
why you're walking around in another
country calling me ugly. That's cuz
you're ugly yourself. And another thing
is I like the fact that um I liked what
you you said about um how
um I like the fact that you said what
was it now you were saying about how a
woman has got to be out of her mind um
to go anywhere near me because I'm so
ugly. I know. That's why literally
you've never been with a normal woman
and you had to resort to disabled
because what you mean is no woman will
ever go near you because you are the
ugly one. That's why you had to go with
a disabled girl. So that I love that
little bit of projection. I know Peter
Belly is so ugly that no woman a woman's
got to be out of her mind to get with
me. Bro, women have been out of their
mind. That's why none of them ever got
with you and that's why you're with a
disabled girl. Peter Bell has been with
normal women though. Isn't it mad how
Peter Belly is so ugly but he's had all
the women that non legs wish he could
get with and he has to be with a
disabled girl but I'm so ugly. I don't
know how I'm possibly going to sleep at
night. I seriously don't. I mean you're
you're talking about yourself. I mean a
woman would have to be out of her mind
to ever get with someone as ugly as you.
You ain't even got teeth in your mouth.
That's why you're with a disabled girl.
That's literally you. You're talking
about yourself. Everything you say is
about yourself. Ugly. You skin you.
Everything that you say is literally
about your own life. You know, you are
talking about yourself. You are the one
with a disabled ugly girl because no
[ __ ] normal woman will ever go near
you. You're just self projecting. Now,
I'm going to leave you with this. Now, now
I know that I'm better looking than you.
I know that you're an ugly bastard. I
know that you're skint. I know that you
are all of these things. So, I'm not
going to waste my time on you anymore
because you coming on here saying all of
these things about me. The more you do
it, the more it shows it's about
yourself. Because from my understanding
is if you knew you was better than
someone, you wouldn't waste your life on
them. Whether that's having more money,
better looking, just better in every
way, you wouldn't waste your time on
them. You waste every second of every
day talking about me. You go on holiday
and you're still talking about me.
That's because you are jealous of
something. That's because you need
validation and you try to validate
yourself every single day that I'm as
ugly as you. That I'm as skinn as you.
That I'm as [ __ ] unlovable as you.
That's why you have to go with a
disabled girl. All of these things just
shows that you you're talking about
yourself. I I already know you're
talking about yourself, bro. I know
you're an ugly skinned bastard that
looks like a rat. I've been know you're
an ugly bastard, but the fact is is that
you will show yourself more. You'll show
yourself up more on YouTube the more you
do this cuz I'm not responding to you
anymore. I'm not going on your video um
ever again because I'm better than you
and you're the ugly skin virgin and I
know that. So, I'm not going to waste my
time on you. You are going to continue
to waste your time on me because
everything that I'm saying about you is
the truth. And that's why you feel the
need to try to self- project your [ __ ]
onto me, you ugly virgin. Um, now before
you sit there and say, "Oh, my
girlfriend's not disabled. My
girlfriend's not disabled." Now, [ __ ]
the talking. This is the last thing I'm
going to say. Um, because I'm not
entertaining you anymore. So, the last
thing I'm going to say is that it's not
about whether she spoke or the fact that
she's not spoke. You went around
messaging all of my sloppy seconds
trying to get wank material. She had no
problem with that.
You paid money to go on holiday and in
that holiday all you're doing is talking
about me. She's got no problem with
that. That shows that she's disabled
because any normal woman would have a
problem with their partner going around.
Um, I mean to be fair, she has she has a
bit to blame for it cuz if she actually
gave you sex and she took your virginity
um that you still have, then maybe you
wouldn't be doing it. But I mean, you
know, a normal woman would not let their
partner go around um trying to get wank
material um from other women and they
would certainly have a big problem of
somebody going on holiday. And in that
holiday where they're supposed to be
enjoying, they're sat there talking
about someone else. That's how we know
that she is literally disabled. So yeah,
a woman has literally got a normal woman
has got to be out of her mind to ever go
with you. That's why you've never been
with a normal woman and you're with a
disabled girl. That's yourself you're
talking about. Everything you say is
about yourself. So I'm done with you
now, Virgin Boy. I'm not going to be
entertaining you again. And the more you
do this on YouTube, the more it shows
how jealous you are of me, which I
already know. Because if you're not, and
I'm all of them things, then you would
just move on with your life and just
change up your content. So that's my
last words to you anyways, Virgin Boy.
Get a life, get laid. I'm not
entertaining you no more. I'm better
than you. I'm better looking than you. I
got more money than you. And I'll prove
it by never ever mentioning you ever again. Facts.