Oh my god. I'm just on Reddit here
reading this. And how [ __ ]
hypocritical is this, right? You you you
know where I'm where I'm going with
this. A few months is way too long to
just be talking. You got to be asking
girls out within a few days of texting,
not weeks or months. They start to see
you as I quote just a friend when you
don't make a move.
Huh? Literally, when I've got numbers in
the past and I've tried to meet a woman
within a week, you get all of these
white knights saying, "No, you're coming
on too strong. It needs to be a month.
You You need to wait. You're coming on
too strong." Um yet, uh when a woman
wants to meet me within the first
message, oh, that's completely fine.
That's completely okay. Um but you
trying to meet a woman within a week,
I'm calling the bomb squad on you, mate,
cuz that's a crime. And then you've got
a woman right in here saying that you
you need to be meeting them within a few days.
But then when you take their advice,
they tell you that you're wrong and then
you should be speaking to them longer.
So which one is it? Do we speak to them
a few days or a week or or do we wait
months? Because you can't do right for
[ __ ] doing wrong, can you? You try to
meet somebody within a week, they say,
"Oh, you're trying to meet them too
fast. You're trying to meet them too
fast. You're coming on too strong.
You're desperate. But then on the other
hand, they're saying that you do need to
meet them [ __ ] as soon as possible.
So which one [ __ ] is it? Jesus
[ __ ] Christ. You know, they'll
they'll keep up with their [ __ ]
hypocriticalness one day, won't they?
[ __ ] me. You know,
that's madness. That's crazy. You try to
meet a woman within a few days, a week,
they'll tell you that you're coming on
too strong, that you're you're trying to
meet them too fast. Um, and that's
apparently such a problem. But then on
the other hand, they're telling you that
you do need to meet them. So, which one
is it? Make up your mind. Is it do we
speak to them for a few days or a week
and then try to meet them or do we speak
to them for months? Because whenever you
do one, they tell you otherwise, no
matter which one you do. So, which one
is it? Please. Please. Which one? Damned
if you do. Damned if you [ __ ] don't.