Right. So, this is to the skin virgin.
Um, so I was just talking to uh Isabute
and she was basically asking me why does
this [ __ ] ugly rat looking balding
[ __ ] with skin ugly charity shop clothes
keep saying that he's had sex with me.
Um cuz obviously I've told her um you
know you keep saying that you've you
know had sex with her. You went nowhere
near that girl. Um absolutely nowhere
near that girl. uh you didn't have any
sexual contact with her. Um you didn't
kiss her at all. You met her three times
because she wanted to use you um for
money and then when she realized that
you were skint um you know she she she
stopped meeting you. You did not have
sex with her. The most you had was a
friendly hug. Stop saying that you've
had sex with her on a park bench. You
haven't had sex with her on a park
bench. A [ __ ] girl sitting on your
lap does not mean you [ __ ] stuck your
dick in them. You went absolutely
nowhere near that girl. And Aisha is a
Muslim. So I have you know that Muslims
right are not allowed to have sex before
marriage. Yeah. She did not sleep with
you. Yeah. Keep her name out of it. She
did not have sex with you. And before um
you tried to say that I'm jealous, bro.
All of the women I've been with is is
has been better than Aisha. In case you
try and say that it's jealousy. You know
this. I even said to you, you know,
years ago when we um when we met that
you would be a good author because the
stories that you tell are crazy. Like
you'd be good at writing books. Like you
had sex with somebody. But by the way,
the area that he went to is where I was
brought up, where I lived, and you did
not have sex with a girl on a park
bench. It did not happen. So stop lying.
She's even confirmed it's not happened.
Um, and another thing is, um, you know,
uh, what was it? Um, could you imagine
walking around [ __ ] Leighton and
seeing some ugly rat looking [ __ ]
right? Skint bastard with a broken dick
trying to stick up someone on the park
bench. I don't think so, mate. I don't I
don't think so. So, stop saying that you
had sex with her. You You remain a
virgin. Um, and you're going to die a
virgin in my opinion, unless you buck up
your [ __ ] ideas. So, yeah, stop
saying that you slept with Aisha. You
went absolutely nowhere near that girl.
Um, and she even says that you haven't
slept together. So, yeah, that's that.
Uh, a park bench. You did not have sex
with a girl on a park bench, you [ __ ]
idiot. Doesn't even sound believable,
you know? That's [ __ ] made up. Um,
you know, I I the weirdest thing I think
I've had is like a [ __ ] in it.
Anyway, that was at night though and
that was a [ __ ] You had sex in in in
in in in broad daylight on a park bench.
Really? I I [laughter] I I don't think
so. Keep keep dreaming, kid. Keep
dreaming. You went absolutely nowhere
near that girl. I was speaking to her
[ __ ] you know, early on Facebook.
Look, I've been speaking to her for a
couple of days and yeah, you didn't
sleep with her. Stop these lies. Stop
these madeup sex stories. Just like you
made up [ __ ] Hannah Nolles [ __ ]
gave you a [ __ ] [ __ ] She's never
gave you a [ __ ] You're a [ __ ]
virgin. You know, the only thing you've
ever had is is a kiss. At this age now,
the only thing you've had is like a
kiss, like like a peck on the mouth.
You've never slept with anyone. You've
never had oral sex. You've never done
any of these things. Leave Aisha alone.
and she doesn't want you. She doesn't
want to know you. Um, you know, he was
even trying to find out what [ __ ]
college that she went to. And I was
like, just leave her alone, mate. She
doesn't want nothing to do with you. I I
think she said that to you at the time.
She doesn't want nothing to do with you
in life, you know? So, just just leave
her alone and stop, you know. This is
past is the past. You know, she met you,
you know, three times. She didn't like
you and that's that. You know, she
wanted something that you couldn't give
her. That doesn't mean you need to make
up stories that you [ __ ] had sex at a
park bench. You know,
she wasn't interested in you. She gave
you a try. She gave you a hug. You
didn't You didn't I think you might have
held hands, I think she said. But you
absolutely did not kiss her and you
absolutely did not sleep with her. You
absolute virgin. And I said this to you
as well [ __ ] when I met you. You went
absolutely nowhere near Aisha. She
didn't want anything to do with you in
life. Keep her name out of it. She's
getting pissed off now.