Oh, so I've just come back home and look
what's come. My new Lego set. Can't wait.
Lo's got some new friends now.
Oh my god.
This cost me £120, by the way. He's my
favorite. He's cute, too. Oh, that's
that's Jedi Vader. I was about to say,
why is he white and not black?
One second. I grab that. I think I need
a knife because I don't want to ruin the
the box if I can help it. Yeah, I think
I've done a good job. The only thing I
cut was this slightly, but apart from
that, I didn't want to make the same
mistake as I done with that one. Oh my god.
I'm going to go straight for
the little characters.
Wait, where's Jar?
Looking for a judger.
As you can see, this one's quite um
quite bigger than the last one.
Okay, I'll come back when I've uh built the characters. Yeah.
Okay. So, I built some some characters.
Oh, Blair. Georgia, do you want to do
Did you want to show Georgia your new spaceship?
Yeah, I want to see a spaceship. Georgia
can also sit down.
Go on, show me your spaceship.
Oh, get on my spaceship. Get out my
And then look, he gets involved.
They're they're friends. See?
Here we go.
Blair, he's got some new friends now. Oh, Blair.
Straight him up like that. And they also
they also come with little little capes.
Look at these lovely little characters. Char spaceship.
Time out for you. You got a noise. Yeah,
there's one more I need to do, but I
couldn't find him, so I'll continue it another time.