Okay, so this is going to be my last
response to Ricky Millington. Um, so I
saw your reply um on the video of me
replying um to you and you said that you
watched two minutes of my video and you
didn't watch anymore because it's
boring. Um, it's repeating and I'm
talking rubbish now. Boring and
repeating. Don't you go on a a boring
repeating channel every single day and
talking rubbish on it. Um, so I I don't
understand. You literally go on your
boyfriend's channel every day talking
[ __ ] rubbish. I mean, I don't know
how many times I've caught you on the
most boringest repeating channel talking
rubbish. So, I would have thought them
three things would have been up your
street. No, I mean it's it's that
channel that you go on. Nobody goes on
it except people that are obsessed with
me. like not many people go on it. If he
goes live, only two people will go on it
maximum. So boring and repeating I I
would have thought would have would have
suited you. Now nothing was boring and
nothing was repeating. The video that I
done to you in response I had never said
any of the things before. You started on
me. So I done a video responding
pointing out where you contradicted
yourself. How could have I I've been
repeating myself when I've never
mentioned said things before. So, get
your facts right. I wasn't repeating
anything in them um messages. And what I
don't in a video, what I don't
understand is why did no one else have a
problem going on the video and agreeing
to it and thumbs up in it. But Ricky,
when he knows he's wrong and he can't
win an argument, it's boring. It's
repeating because he knew that he
contradicted himself. I.e. Should have
said that before. Um, so at the end of
the day, right, um, you said that you
watched two minutes of the video. Now,
you would have heard what I mentioned
about, um, the lover hearts, and you
were saying that the reason that women
was leading me on and playing games is
because I was putting love hearts on
their messages. Now, you still didn't
answer as to why a woman can put love
hearts on my messages. But if I put a
love heart on their message, I'm a
weirdo. That gives them every single
excuse in the book to lead me on and
play games. Because I'm pretty sure I'm
not the only one on YouTube that would
love to know why you can't love a
woman's message on WhatsApp, but they
can love yours. I don't think we'll ever
know. I think that woman will remain a
mystery. Um, I think you realize how
stupid you was even saying something
like that. Now, before I carry on,
Vicki, I just wanted to um read out a quote,
I wanted to read out a quote um by you
from a year and a half ago. So,
you said, "PJ, you're good-looking. It's
not you, it's the women that are picky."
Now, that's what you said, bro. That's
the So unlike a lot of other people um
if people was to go on go for me on this
community, you know, they haven't said a
quote that's contradicted everything
they've said in the past. Now that's
what you wrote. So you can't play two
sides of a coin. Is it heads or tails?
Is it the women that are the problem or
is it me? Cuz two years ago you were
saying it's the women and that I'm
good-looking and their standards are
unrealistic. But now you're saying that
it's not the women, it's me and how I'm
acting. So which one is it? Are you
heads or are you tails? And then you
said that you have no problem getting
women. So if you've got no problem
getting women and you get women, why was
you saying two years ago how it's the
women that's picky and I'm I'm not the
problem. Make it make sense. It's very
unbelievable to think that in two years
now only societyy's gotten worse. You
are somehow getting women. Yet two years
ago you weren't get you weren't getting
women and you was blaming women. So, are
you blaming women or are you blaming me?
Because it doesn't make sense. And
please don't say that I'm boring and I'm
repeating because you can't answer it.
Um, you know, please don't do that
because it's it's ridiculous. Um, so
what I don't understand is I went on
your comment and you got 14 thumbs up.
Now, I don't know how. Now, here's the
thing. I'm not like your boyfriend. I
don't need to um delete videos where
people have thumbmed up with someone
else, thumbs up someone's message or,
you know, disliked the video. I I don't
care about thumbs up because here's the
thing. Although it might seem very
delusional that I'm saying that 14
people thumbs up in your comment is uh
wrong and I'm right. The difference is
I've put the evidence out there in black
and white where women have led me on,
where they've played games. So there's
no argument. Whether it was a million
people liking your comment, evidence
shows that women have led me on and
women have played games. And if anybody
watched that video, which I assume the
people that, you know, gave you 14
thumbs up didn't, um, if they, you know,
they wouldn't be liking your comments
because your comment is contradicting
itself, which is what the videos show.
You're saying that there's a problem
with me loving women's messages, yet
they love my messages. You're saying
that I can't send a woman a voice note
who I've who I've never Who I don't
know, yet there's women that I didn't
send voice notes. You're saying that I'm
asking women to meet me multiple times.
I haven't asked every single woman to
meet me multiple times. So, if anybody
actually went on the video, Ricky, they
would realize where you actually
contradicted yourself and you've been
proven wrong. You know, it's not up for
debate. I mean, yeah, sure, people could
have said, "I'm wrong on some things. I
could have done this better. I could
have done that better." But the fact
that you got 14 thumbs up, yet being
proven wrong, it's not even up for a
debate. That tells you all you need to
know about this society. They're never
going to stop defending women at the end
of the day. Like it doesn't matter what
you show them, how you show them, what
you tell them, how many times you tell
them, they're always going to defend
women. It's obvious. Now, if these
people can't even shown different, then
there's no hope. I mean, there there's
generally no hope. I mean, I'm pretty
sure um I've put approaching videos out
there where I've tried to start a
conversation with a woman and she's not
let me finish my sentence before saying
she's not interested, which again
contradicts a lot of things that people
say, which I'm going to get on to that
in a bit. But to be fair, some people
did agree with me, which also proves
that obviously I am right, you know,
because there's an account called Tiger
Tiger, who I've not seen for years. Um,
he doesn't like me. Um, he's not a yes
man. He even [ __ ] agreed with me
saying that, "Oh, I see what you mean
now." Yeah, they're leading you on. And
three people, four people thumbmed it
up, including me. So, three people,
that's not me. So, three thumbs up. He
agreed. Somebody that's completely
unbiased. And I got likes on the video.
Um, because at the end of the day, I am
right because I have put the evidence
out there. And I hate saying that
because I don't want to seem like
someone that always thinks they're
right. But how on earth are you arguing
with [ __ ] evidence? It doesn't make
sense. It's like going to court, right,
and and and and the judge showing that
you've killed someone and they're
saying, "Nah, it never happened. We'll
dismiss it." It it generally that what
I'm showing like evidence what I'm
showing is is is it could be the
difference between convicting someone
and not convicting someone in court.
that what I've shown, what women have
done, you know, is is evidence. How are
you arguing with it? I don't understand.
So, but yeah, like I said, I'd rather
take six people that are genuine genuine
and agree with me than 14 people that
didn't even bother watching the video
because if they did, they wouldn't have
thumbmed up your um comment because they
knew that you're contradicting yourself.
Anyways, so do you know what? It's not
even that. It's not even the fact about
them dismissing my struggles or, you
know, um, when it's to do with me and
women, they're always sticking up for
women. It's not even just that when even
when Oh, no. What I wanted to mention
was, okay, let me give you my honest
opinion. Yeah. Say that I didn't make
the video and um, you know, I'm watching
somebody else make the video, right? And
a completely unbiased opinion. My
opinion would be that the women that
didn't reply back to you, you might have
come across as weird or they might have
gave you gave their number to get away
from you. Um, or they're just not
looking or whatever it is. That's what
it is. There's certain things you
shouldn't have said. Do not double text.
But there's no doubt in my mind that
there's no way I would have dismissed
the amount of women that was playing
games with me and led me on. There's no
way in earth if them 14 people weren't
biased and watched that video. um they
they would know that you are not right
by what the messages are saying. It
contradicts everything you are saying.
So how can it be right? You understand?
So that's that. Um but obviously you
could and the fact that they're not even
agreeing with some of the things that
I'm I'm showing. It's like they're
saying no, they completely dismiss it.
That's how you know they're biased
because you know there's messages where
they could have said, "Oh, you was right
here. You was wrong here." But they
haven't done that. They've dismissed
everything that you have shown them
actually shown them which is what how
you know they're biased because how can
you argue with what you shown you know
because we all know if we was yeah it's
a madness but so then I've come to the
realization that they're never ever
going to stop defending women they're
always going to defend them like I
generally feel like a woman could go out
and murder someone and people would
would still make excuses for them like
generally from my experiences of showing what they've
and people still agreeing with with
them, you they're always going to defend
women and dismiss your struggles cuz
that's the thing. They don't even
critique and say, "You've done this
right, you've done this wrong." They
dismiss everything. That's what I'm
trying to say. So, um also, um it's not
even just that. Like, even when I'm not
involved and I see something online,
they're so anti-laming women for
anything. Like, okay, let me give you an
example. So when a woman does a shitty
thing, people will say, "Oh, they don't
owe you anything. Oh, they don't owe you
nothing. Oh, they don't owe you
anything." And I mean, like, it it's
like they use that to very much cover up
the shitty behavior that they that they
display or the shitty things that they
do or like, you know, when you never
hear about a man not owing anyone
anything. So, it's like, and another
thing is when they say, "Oh, it's not
about looks, it's about personality."
They will try to take away anything
physical that they go for as much as
possible. when we all know that it is
about physical appearance with women and
by physical I don't mean like looks like
you could be good-look and because you
got a beard they won't go with you
because you got you know green eyes they
won't go for you they're more shallow
than men yeah people will sit there and
say yeah men are shallow men are picky
but if you try to say about oh a woman
you know she will she will turn somebody
down for having a beard she won't even
give them the chance to get to know
their personality you'll get a bunch of
simps after you with an axe
um for speaking the truth and I've
actually I actually have like evidence
of this you know where like you know
depending on your heritage and stuff how
well you do you will do with dating you
know but they tried to say nah nah nah
it's all about personality they seem to
want to live in this fantasy land where
women don't go for for appearance but
the thing what I mean by that is even
when you look good and you look and
you're good-look just because you're not
their exact preference
that would be the difference between
getting with you, giving you a chance,
and not getting with you and not giving
you a chance. But no one wants to admit
that ever. Um, which is strange because,
okay, let's just say for argument sake,
I'm going to do this with you now, Ricky. Yeah.
You're saying that it's me and how I'm
acting. I'm going to show you a couple
of my approaching videos where I have
tried to start a conversation with a
woman and she has said straight away
that she's not interested. And I'm going
to leave the comments open and it's no
hold bars. Again, you can say what you
want. You can have your opinion. How are
you going to get your way out of that?
Huh? How when you try to speak to a
woman, she will say straight straight
away, I'm not interested. There's
literally conversations where I've had
there's literally times where I've
approached women completely normally and
they've said straight away, not
interested. Would that not contradict a
lot of what you're saying? Because if it
didn't, wouldn't they be giving you a
chance going on a date with you, seeing
your personality and and stuff like
that? Like it generally if what you're
saying is true, why is it that I've got
so many videos where I've tried to talk
to a woman and she said straight away
not interested and I will put them up.
I'll put a couple of them up for you and
I'll put one up where I've had a
conversation. Do feel free to try to
critique them, please. Um, now I'm going
to put them videos up. So, all of these
biased 14 people that have thumbmed up
your message, I would love you to tell
me what I'm doing wrong, how I'm acting
wrong when a woman is not even giving me
the chance to finish my sentence before
saying I'm not interested. Please do.
Now, before I know what you're going to
say, Ricky, I can almost read your mind.
You're going to sit there and say,
"Well, you know that that's not going to
work approaching women on the street.
You need to use dating apps." Now, I
would agree with you. It's not the thing
nowadays where people go out on the
street and approach women. It's very,
very outdated. I do agree with you. So,
I don't always think that I'm right.
Believe you me, I don't always think
that I'm right. However,
dating apps don't work and they've not
worked for a very, very long time. So,
there is no alternative. So, just to
clarify, there's no alternative than
approaching women on the street or a bar
or a club. Oh, that's another one. I'm
going to add a club one there just in
case you try and say, "Oh, well, you're
approaching women on the street."
Whether it's right or wrong, which I
agree with you that it might not be the
done thing nowadays,
it will show you that the only thing you
can do is approach women because the
dating apps don't work. Now, before I
put these videos up there about of me
approaching women and them not giving me
the chance to see how I'm acting, you
know, all of the [ __ ] that you come out
with, I'm going to I'm going to show you
my dating apps because people like to
tell people that they need to go on
dating apps to get laid and dating apps
work and use dating apps. Um, so I'm
going to show you the dating apps not
working and then I'm going to show you
how um I've had to approach women and
then when I've approached women I'm
going to show you their response. So
yeah, we'll start with the dating apps. Yeah.