Yo. Okay, so time for a new dating
video. Um, so in this video I wanted to
talk about how, you know, there's
absolutely no hope um, you know, trying
to find a girlfriend or, you know, if
you're trying to get laid or if you're
trying to get anything from a woman. And
not only that, I wanted to talk about
the whole expense of dating. Um, and
what I mean by that is, you know, when
you go out, you know, over a weekend,
you know, going for some drinks, getting
your haircut, um,
going out, you know, to eat, um, how
ridiculous it is, um, how much it costs
and stuff. So, yeah, I'm going to talk
about that as well. So, I know I said I
was going to go out approaching
yesterday. My bad. Um, I woke up, I was
exhausted and just burnt out by the
whole thing. Um because you know I went
out last week and I got 10 numbers and I
didn't even get a single date out of any
of them 10 numbers which is absolutely
disgusting. Um but you know I thought
you know I just want to chill. Um let me
do it tomorrow which is today which is
Friday. I'm going to go out today. Um
and the reason is is because my hair
still looks good. Um, and my, you know,
the haircut cost me a lot of money, and
I just want to get my money's worth
since I spent a lot of money over that
weekend, which we'll get on to in a
minute. But, um, yeah, it's I'm I am
dreading it. Like, I am not looking
forward to going out and approaching at
all because at the end of the day, I
shouldn't have to be going out again.
You know, I went out last week. I got 10
numbers. I looked my best. I smelt my
best. I was confident. And the fact that
I did not even get a date for this week,
not even a date, which a date basically
is just the first steps of, you know,
getting to know someone, you know,
seeing if you're compatible with said
person. And the fact that I looked my
best, smelt my best, was confident, and
I don't even have a date this week,
that tells me a lot. That tells me
there's no hope in this country, you
know, despite what, you know, people try
telling you. um you know um it there is
none because at the end of the day it's
it's been a very long time since it's
been that way. It's not like you didn't
look your best and you got four numbers
or you looked your best and you got
three numbers. You looked your best and
you got 10 numbers. Um think of all of
the other women that I approached that,
you know, didn't give me their number.
And the fact that you have not come
across one person that's even given you
the chance, um it says a lot. There's no
hope in this country. Um, you know, it's
it's so obvious. Um,
and you know, you you get people that
come on my live stream when I go live
and they'll say, "Oh, well, you know,
the past doesn't dictate the future."
It's been dictating the future for 5
years. Um, you know, at the end of the
day, a lot of people say, "Oh, yeah, the
past does not dictate the future." But
with this particular thing in dating,
it's the same old thing every time you
go out. You know, you try to meet a
woman, you try to speak to a woman, they
say they've got a boyfriend, they say
they're not interested, they walk away,
or when they give you their number, they
play games with you. That's all that
ever happens. How does the past not
dictate the future when the same thing
has been happening for years? And you
know, not only that, right, um there's
been no sort of leadup to any success.
Now, this is another thing I was
thinking of. Um, and what I mean by that
is my last
date was April. So quite a while ago,
April. And how many times I've been out
since April? I've been out a lot. I've
done a lot of approaches. And I've not
had like it's not like I've had dates,
you know, two dates a month or a date
every week or whatever. and oh, I've had
this or oh, I've had this or maybe I've
had the one odd one night stand or some
sort of progress along the way. There's
been nothing. There's been absolutely
nothing. And I went out last week and I
didn't even get a date scheduled for
this week. There is literally no hope. I
don't know why people seem to think that
there's still hope in this country
regarding, you know, finding someone. I
mean, if there was really hope, you
would have found someone by now. And if
there was hope, you would have been on a
date this week from last week's
approaching session. You know,
approaching all of them people, looking
your best. If there was generally hope,
A, you would have found someone by now
or B, you would have been on a date this
week. You know, it's it's obvious, you
know, there's no I know people like to,
you know, dismiss my struggles and
things that I've tried in the past, but
generally if there was hope, you would
have found someone by now. You would be
going on dates. you would be getting,
you know, successes along the way. A
date or the odd one night stand or the
odd kiss. There would be things going like
like up, down, up, down with your hand.
Not just straight, but there's nothing.
But yet, people still seem to think
there's hope. People still seem to to
live under, you know, you know,
delusional thinking that one day you're
going to go out and it's all going to
change. It's never going to change. It's
obvious. Um, and to make it even worse,
right, is when I went out on that Friday
to that Sunday, I spent £600. I'm not
even joking. Drinking, haircut, food,
you know, messing around, having fun. I
generally spent £600. Now, that is a lot
of money, right, to just throw away.
And, you know, imagine you done that
every single week, you know, and it's
like you can go on holiday with £600.
You could definitely do other things
with £600. And trust me, right, not a
lot of things scare me. Um, but the fact
that you can literally look your best,
do your best, be confident, and throw
away hundreds of pounds. Yeah. Over the
weekend and not even be given a date at
the end of it. That is scary. That is
very, very scary. You know, it wasn't
like it was 200 pound or£300. Oh, good
weekend. you know, it was hundreds. Um,
and oh, I didn't even gamble either. So,
I mean, if you gamble, you know that
most of that money went on gambling. It
just went on drinks and food. And yeah,
it tells me that there's no hope in this
country. Um, you know, for me anyways.
And luckily enough, um, I won the money
back and a little bit more. I just
played some roulette and won the money
back, but that's not the point. Um, it's
not it doesn't mean I'm just going to
waste it again because I won money, but
yeah, it's it's disgusting, honestly.
Um, you know, it's lucky I've got
savings and stuff, but it's not the
point. It's like it just goes to show
that what is this what we have to deal
with every single time you go out. You
know, the risk of getting 10 numbers and
not getting a date and spending hundreds
potentially just to go out drinking.
It's just not worth it. You know, at the
end of the day, there's just no hope in
this country. Like, tomorrow when I go
out, that's going to be the last time I
go out until my birthday, which is in 3
weeks time because it's it's mad how you
can look your best, do your best, be
confident, and not even get a date,
which is the first step to everything.
And the fact that you can go through all
of that money, that same money that you
could book a holiday for is insane.
Like, it's bad. But you get people that
still seem to think there's hope and
you're going to meet someone, it's
they're living in denial. Like they they
really really really are. Because if you
can look your best, do your best, do so
many approaches, and not even get a
single date, not even somebody willing
to give you half a chance, what makes
you think one day you're randomly just
going to meet someone and be in a
relationship and have a love life and
have a sex life? It just it doesn't ring
right. It just doesn't. But I guess so
many people are just in an eye and they
just seem to think one day you're going
to go out and societyy's going to change
for you and me. It's never going to
change. Never. It's been the same thing
for years and now there's not even any
progress along the way. So it's
it is generally insane. But that's all I
wanted to say. So yeah.