Yo. Okay, so time for a new dating
video. Um, I'm going to title this video
dating in 2026. And uh, yeah, this is my
first dating video of this year. And
yeah, I wanted to do it uh, a little bit
ago, but I just was waiting for the time
for the right time. And after what
happened today, uh, it was shocking, by
the way. Um, yeah, it's definitely time
for a new dating video. Um, it has
definitely gotten worse. Um, you know,
at the end of the day, I want to talk
about, um, in this video, I want to talk
about like the double standards, why I
gave up, uh, you know, how they always
try to blame, you know, the man as to
why women flake and, um, ghost and lead
people on and all of the crappy things. Um,
let's face it, most of them do. Um, you
know, people people can say it's
generalizing, but let's be like, let's
be so real right now. you know, you're
you're you're talking to me, someone
that's approached and and dealt with god
knows how many women. I wouldn't even
like to put a number on it. I've lost
count. But, you know, like anyways, um
so I'm going to start from 6 months ago
right up until well today pretty much.
So, 6 months ago, right, I literally was
like, I'm done with this dating thing.
Um people give up for different reasons.
Uh different things annoy different
people. Um, and I just in my the logic I
had right is that I've tried more than
enough. I don't need to keep going out
and, you know, dealing with people
saying that, you know, uh, they've got
boyfriends or getting numbers and people
leading me on and getting numbers and
people, you know, playing games and then
flaking. And do you know the the the the
two things that used to really annoy me
the most um, with this whole dating
thing? Um, it wasn't really even the
boyfriend thing or the people saying
they're not interested. The thing that
used to annoy me, right, is when I used
to get people's numbers and then they
would just lead you on and play games
and the excuses they used to make. Um,
you know, like, I can't date you because
you're too old. I can't date you because
you're too young. I don't uh I can't
date you because you're not a Muslim. I
can't date you because you live too far.
I can't date you because you don't know
enough about Palestine. I mean, [ __ ] me.
All of these examples I'm using have
been used in the past and more. And then
you come to think of it, it's like, bro,
you've really got to have like no
respect for yourself if you're going to
continuously keep putting up with this.
Um, you know, at the end of the day,
it's just like it it's mental. It's
absolutely mental. You know, you're not
fat, you're not ugly. There's no reason
for it. And, you know, as I said, what
the logic that I went with is the fact
that you've tried more than enough. you
shouldn't have to go out and keep
trying. You should have found someone.
You know, you have all of these people
that say, you know, people have found
their partners at this age and that age
and that x y zed. But what these people
fail to realiz is I've approached more
women than probably 95% of the people in
the world. Not fat, not ugly. So
logically, for my mo for my own mental
sanity, I did I I wanted to stop
experiencing bad experiences. And it
made sense. It's logical. You know,
obviously a lot of people might not be
able to relate to it if they haven't
tried or they might have met someone um
years ago or whatever the the case is,
but I was quite frankly getting sick of
it. Um as most people would. I mean, I
feel like most people got sick of it
before me. Um and I just would rather
just like think of it like, yeah, okay,
maybe having someone might be nice,
maybe whatever, you know, it's a bonus,
but it is not worth it. Cuz think about
it, how how long are you going to keep
doing it for? How many years are you
going to keep going out every week
getting the same experiences, hearing
the same excuses, dealing with the same
bogus? I mean, who's to say you're not
going to be 45 and dealing with the same
thing, you know? And, you know, and I I
do get what what people are trying to
say when they're like, you know, you
don't know what the future holds, but
realistically, if you want to be, you
know, theoretical about this, you would
have already met someone. If there was
someone generally for you, you would
have met them. There's no reason why you
have not met them. You put the effort
in. You're not fat. You're not ugly,
which there's nothing wrong with fat and
ugly people, whatever, but like that's
the way society judges people nowadays.
That's what that's the point I'm trying
to get at. So, completely washed my
hands with it. Um, until I went out
because I actually planned to go out um
with um someone and I would have never
heard the last of it if I didn't go out.
So, I went out and basically um yeah, I
was in a bad mood. Like someone had to
basically force me to go out. I was I
was done. I told you I've been done for
a very very long time um with this whole
like um dating thing. So, anyways, I
went out and then obviously drunk and I
was like, "Okay, I'm in a better mood
now." Literally, I approached a couple
of people. It wasn't about collecting
numbers. It was just about finding
someone who appeared to be different. So
approached this person um and they were
showing like really good vibes. Oh yeah,
drop me a message where it's it's not
like they just gave their number to get
away from you. They were proper like
enthusiastic about giving the number,
enthusiastic about saying, "Oh, drop me
a message." So I'm thinking, "Okay,
cool." Got one number, enjoy the rest of
my life, rare. Um first number I got for
a long time. And you know, uh then she
literally didn't even reply to the
message. And I'm thinking in my head
like at the very least they're going to
at least reply to the message since
they're very enthusiastic about giving
me their number and then they never
replied. So I'm thinking oh god same old
crap. Um and then I think after that I
think I did go out once. I think I went
to Liverpool Street. Um bear in mind
these are months months a away from each
other whereas I used to go out like
twice a week. So you can understand.
It's like now the only time I go out is
if I'm bored out of my head and
someone's getting on my nerves and
trying to stress me out, which I get
I'll talk about that. But I think I went
to Liverpool Street before that or after
that. But anyways, I went to Liverpool
Street by myself. Um I think I got a
couple of numbers. Same thing happened
again where I got led on uh by one of
the free numbers and I'm thinking no
that is I am done. Um and and I'm going
to add this as well. Um
you when you're getting these bad
experiences, right? Be it someone
leading you on, being someone having a
bad attitude, being someone having a
abrupt body language, whatever it is,
the only thing that's coming in my mind,
right, is you are getting men pretty
much defending these people, defending
this behavior just for just for the sake
of doing it. Like it's it's kind of mad
because I mean I would generally say you
know even if there are good women out
there let's face it like I was saying
earlier most of them are toxic most of
them are you know are going to do these
things. So the fact that you've got so
many men nowadays defending these women
that do these shitty bad things
completely baffles me. Um it really
really does. You know it's not like
they're an animal or or a child or a
baby that are genuinely innocent.
They're women that do toxic, bad, mean
things. Um, pretty much. And you're
getting people that are defending them
just for the sake of defending them.
They're defending them very biasly.
They're not getting their purse stolen
or they're not getting attacked on the
street and then someone's just, you
know, getting involved. They are
defending them just for the sake of
defending them. And it doesn't pop up
all the time, but maybe after about four
or five different bad experiences,
you're thinking, "Oh, damn. you you you
know people are defending this kind of
behavior and it's just like it's just
it's mad because coming from somebody
that's not biased and completely
unbiased who's been with women I'm not a
virgin I've been with women I don't
understand why people would want to
defend people that are doing these
horrible things but they they still do
and I've got evidence I've got like I've
put the evidence up there and and even
when I was on my break for months and
months and months I was watching a lot
of kick streamers I moved on to kick
and the attitude from a lot of these
women towards these men. I'm thinking it
got to a point where even watching it
was annoying me. Um, you know, even even
some of these things on Instagram and
it's and I don't understand how
people can keep defending this uh uh
behavior, you know, the leading on the
the playing games, the dishonesty, the
the the the stuckupness. It's like it is
it is it's crazy. And then it's Yeah,
it's just crazy. So, I missed all the
events. Uh, didn't go out Boxing Day,
didn't go out New Year's Eve. I was
like, I'm completely completely
completely done. However, I was on
Instagram and like a few like other
different little um apps. See if
anything changed on the dating apps. It
appeared that Tinder was just full of
bots and fake profiles. And then I was
on Instagram and I thought, you know,
yeah, if I come across someone that
proves to me that they're different and
they prove to me that they're a good
person, right? I'll give them the
chance. Like, I'm not going to
completely say, "Okay, no, you're a
woman. I'm not going to go with you."
Like, whatever. Like, if someone proves
that they're different and they give me
a better experience and they come along,
that's fine. But as far as me going out,
get my haircut, going out approaching,
dealing with people that's got bad
attitude, I'm not I'm not doing it. And
that's and and that's my that's that's
my own choice at the end of the day. So
um and there was this one woman right
who was I think she lived in Wil
Wilshire. Yeah. And she was like saying
how she can't meet me because of
distance. Um when me and we both know
that if I was her next door neighbor
she'd come out with another excuse. Oh,
you're too young for me. Oh, you're too
old for me. And to me, the thing that
they're trying to do doesn't work. At
the end of the day, I prefer somebody to
be honest with me. Oh, I don't like
people with black hair. I don't like
people with green green eyes. You know,
when when somebody is blatantly lying
and just coming up with excuses, it's
very very worse than just being honest
in my opinion. I don't know how other
people's brain works. Um, but you know,
and and you'd get these things again. I
mean, I was talking to a woman like
every day um for like a whole day. We
was talking about things and she was
saying about how she defends men and
then she just turned weird the next day
and then just completely ghosted. Never
heard from her again. Which I thought it
was a bit weird. Um but then I thought,
okay, you you've not met them that
you've only spoke to them for like a day
and then you're thinking, okay, yeah,
then it really really really gets worse,
which what brings me up right to like
this point now. Um, and so I went out
early February. Um, basically somebody
owed me money. They were stressing me
out. And you know, sometimes when like
you got like a lot of stress going on.
Um, and you just want to go for a drink
and forget about it in a healthy way, in
a in in a in a very non-alcoholic way.
And just clear your head, you know,
clear your head, something to do. So I
thought, you know what? I'm going to go
out. Um, I'm going to get my haircut. I
need to get my haircut as well. Like my
beard was like looking very Yeah.
terroristy. So, I had to I had to groom,
had to do my hair, do my eyebrows, and
I'm thinking, right, I need to clear my
head. So, I literally went out um I
started doing these sober approaches.
This is the last time I went out. And
then I'll get on to the numbers I got
and why we're here today, basically. So,
I went out, I was approaching, and I was
getting a lot of bad attitude from these
women again. Uh it got it got it gets
worse. Like I said, I always say to
myself, a few years ago, it was hard. It
was hard. It's always been hard, but it
was possible. Nowadays, it just seems
it's impossible to even get as much as a
conversation from someone. You know,
they're so glued to their phone or
they've got a bad attitude or you get
what I'm saying? And a lot of them were
like very very rude. Um, and not like
swearing you or cussing you, but their
whole like body language. And I'm
thinking like it was it almost annoyed
me, but I thought, okay, this is not
normal, but it is normal because it's
not normal because you should be able to
just go out and meet a woman and not
have to deal with this. But at the same
time in 2026, unfortunately it is
normal. Um, if that makes sense. So, you
know, you watch these kick streamers,
they get it. Everyone else, you know, a
lot of people get it and it shouldn't be
normal. But unfortunately, it is normal.
So, that's I just tried to like say just
keep telling myself that, but it does
get draining. You know, when you're
dealing with people that's got bad
attitude and whatever, it does get
draining. So, then I hit this club. Um,
I stayed in it. It was a Thursday
because I go out Thursdays. the rare the
very rare time I do go for a drink. I've
done a few approaches um and I got
got five numbers I think and I got one
reply. So, I got one reply, but it
doesn't matter, you know, if one reply
is somebody that's replying and they
want to meet you and they're genuine,
then it doesn't matter how many replies
you get, you know, one person is is
enough. We don't, you know, is So,
messaging this woman who was a Christian
and we was going back and forth, back
and forth, u getting on, talking about
hobbies, whatever. And
here's the thing, right? Ah, this is
what my main point is that I remember
specifically um it's happened a few
times, but spec specifically a couple of
people in this community, they would say
to me, "Oh, you're trying to meet the
woman too fast." My whole thing has
always been if you get a woman's number,
you want to be meeting them within 4 to
7 days. Obviously, there are some
exceptions. you know, someone could be
out the country or whatever, but they
would need to have a really really good
reason to not be able if they want to
meet you. I'm not saying that obviously
people don't have to meet you. They
don't have to, but I'm saying if they
would have to be have a really good
reason not to meet you, um, and be be so
busy that they can't meet you, if that
makes sense. So, obviously work is not
really good enough. So my whole thing
was I meet people on the Thursday. I
approach someone on the Thursday, get
their number on the Thursday, try to
meet them by the Sunday. Or if they said
next Thursday or they were busy, okay,
next week, yeah, you schedule next date
for next week. And there was always a
reason why I've done this. Even though
people would come and say, "Oh, you're
coming on too strong. You need to speak
to them longer." Um, you know, there's
all there was always little excuses.
They have different rules for men than
they do women. Basically, you can never
do right even when you're right or
wrong. You try to meet them faster, they
um they mess you around. You speak to
them longer. Oh, you're just delaying
the inevitable. They mess you around.
You know, you're just delaying it. So,
with this woman, I took it very very
very slow. And the only reason I didn't
um try to meet her like very very fast
is cuz obviously she told me like she
had like some anxiety issues. Um she
told me like a bit personal stuff about
her ex and stuff. So, I'm thinking,
okay, whatever. Just play it cool,
whatever. You know, I've got nothing to
lose, but I keep speaking to this
person. and she she had exams and she
told me the dates of her exams and we
would speak every single day and
obviously I wanted to kind of like get
her to trust that I'm not like these
other people that have done this that
have used basically the same
manipulation tactics in the past. So I
took it very very slow, very very steady
and yeah the conversation was going I I
don't I don't think I've ever had a
better conversation every single day
with somebody than I had with this
person. And I'm thinking, okay, we might
be in a bit of luck now. 2026,
um, you know, everything happens for a
reason. It is technically a new year.
It's the first time me trying this year,
so whatever. And we was talking and
talking and she'd messaged me saying
that she's stressed and she's studying
and where she had showed me her studying
and she gave me the dates. I wanted to
give her the benefit of the doubt. Maybe
I was being a tad gullible. Maybe I was
being a tad delusional, but I just
wanted to basically just cling on
anything that was positive at this
point. you know, I've got somebody
responding every single day. Um they're
they're messaging every all day every
day. So, I thought so then we're talking
and we're talking and we're talking and
we're talking and um this is another
thing um why I say to people that you
should meet people like as soon as
possible because the more you speak to
them, the more you start getting
invested. I don't think the tax is the
right word. I'd say invested. So,
obviously it got to a point where like
I'm thinking, "Oh [ __ ] I hope they
don't ghost me. I hope they don't start
like ignoring me. I hope they don't
start doing all of these all of these
things. Um because obviously I'm
investing now. I've been speaking to
this person longer than a week. So, and
it's that's another thing. It's very
very stressful. Um the whole thing is um
stressful. And then they did get back to
me or whatever. Talking never said
anything weird. Um yeah, nothing nothing
weird. It was all cool. It was all
whatever. Um and obviously this is a
point of this is what happens even when
you speak to someone um you know uh
longer. You would like to think that if
someone spoke to you every day for so
long, they would have the decency and
dignity not to ghost you or or I thought
at the very most the very worst I'd get
friend zoned or just didn't get
anything. I weren't expecting anything.
I was just expecting to basically keep
talking to someone and meeting someone.
I didn't have any expectations in my
mind, bro. Lit literally went on my
phone um today. I went on my so last
time I spoke to him was the 17th. Uh
they said, "Oh, I'll get back to you
after the exams or send me voice." Went
on the lit literally went on the
messages earlier and the picture
disappeared. So they've deleted my
number. They didn't block me. I found
that they deleted my number. They didn't
care the fact that I spoke to them for,
you know, 3 weeks. Um and I tried like
supporting them. I said, "If you ever
need to talk to anyone, talk to me. Like
you can talk to me anytime you want."
You know, we was just like getting on
and stuff. I was like, "So this person
didn't care about ghosting me." Um, so
that just proves to me and everyone else
that even if you speak to people for
long periods of time, they will still
mess you around. They will still ghost
you. They'll still [ __ ] you over. Um, so
anyone who is dating, obviously you
don't have to take my advice, but I
would strongly advise anyone. I'm done
with it. Try to meet these people as
soon as possible. Um, and and and that's
it. And that's why we did you that's why
we went through that strategy because
even if you can speak to someone for
three or four weeks um you know uh they
can still ghost you. They can still mess
you around. I don't know why she did it.
Um you know at the end of the day. So
yeah she she said that she'd never ghost
and stuff. We had loads and loads of
chats like normal chats and stuff. So
this just goes to show that like I mean
there's no hope. I mean that's that. And
then I mean obviously that's a big
middle finger to people that say, "Oh,
you need to wait. You need to speak to
them longer." We've spoke to them
longer. This conversation couldn't have
got any better and they ghosted me. Um,
you know, it's not even like they they
they they were your friend and whatever.
They they ghosted you, you know, after 3
weeks. And who's to say that will happen
again? It would happen again. It will
happen. It has happened again, you know,
but obviously this is the one that
sticks out. So even when you speak to
them longer, they will still ghost you.
So, it doesn't matter if a man's trying
to meet a woman the next day or 10 years
later, they're still going to get
ghosted. They're still going to get
messed around with. It's a bit similar
to when it's like they're trying to put emphasis
all on the man. Like, think about like
this. Yeah. It's like when they say to
you like, "Oh, you need a job. You need
a car. You need this. You need that."
Bro, there's so many people in the world
that's got that and they still don't
love a woman. You know, it's like,
"Yeah, people should go to the gym.
Yeah, people should make more money.
Yeah, people do need to like work on
themselves." Yeah. This video is not
saying that don't do anything because
this is the way dating is. But if you're
these people, I don't respect these
people that say, you know, you need to
get money, you need to do this, bro.
I've lived by myself. I've worked. I have had
[ __ ] tons of money and it never ever
made a difference. So that is also
another way to kind of blame men because
obviously they'll just say oh well you
live with your mom or you haven't got
money or you know it's just another
excuse just like when you know you try
to meet a woman with you know within 7
days which I think is fair dudes to be
fair they will make excuses like oh well
um you're trying to meet them too quick
okay well what about this woman who
ghosted me today after 3 or 4 weeks what
was the excuse then no weird talk
conversation was perfect um they They
they don't want to admit in their head
that, you know, these women do lead
people on. They do do it for fun. They
they do have the capacity to do these
things. Um even though they, you know,
they seem to think because they're
women, they've got to be angels. There's
no way a woman would would ever do
anyone over. Now again, if it was a
child we was talking about, if it was a
baby we was talking about, I' I'd be
nodding my head like a dog agreeing. But
I'm sorry, a pretty uh a grown woman
knows exactly what she's doing and she
knows exactly when she's leading someone
on and she knows exactly when she's
playing games. Um, gender does not
discriminate here. Men can do it and
women can do it. Um, but they would just
come out with all of these excuses. So,
it got to a point where it's like now
you couldn't even ask for advice. No man
should, could, or ever from now on ask
anyone for advice because there's always
going to be that biasness. There's
always going to be that, oh, well, you
need to do this, you need to do that.
Oh, we've done this, we've done that.
Now, what's now? Now, what's the next
excuse? There's always going to be that
biasness. Just like when I used to show
text of me being led on and people
playing games with me, there was always
the excuse, oh, you're coming on too
strong. Oh, you need to speak to them
longer. Um, which again, like I said,
they're not going to feel no way about
ghosting somebody um just because
they've spoke to someone for 3 or 4
weeks. Um, and I tried with this woman.
I tried supporting her and everything.
Um, I said, you know, you know, if your
anxiety is bad, call me. And she still
didn't give a [ __ ] um about ghosting me.
So, I mean, this is the this is what
we're dealing with now. And now we're in
the same sailor boat. So, moving
forward, what are we going to do? What
could we what could what could you do?
Do you understand what keep going out
every week dealing with the same old
same old same old same old same old for
how many years? When's it going to stop?
When are you going to break the cycle?
And that's why I gave up. You know, it's
it sucks. To be fair, I would say with
this person, I would say I wasn't
expecting it, but I was prepared for it.
Um, I was expecting them to just be like
very very the way they were for very
long because of their ex and stuff and
you know, even if you weren't going to
get with them, but I didn't think I
didn't think they'd ghost. I didn't
think they'd ghost. Um, because I'd be
waking up to 23 messages. Um, and you
know, you'd think you'd think you tried
to think like them after a while. You'd
think, "Oh, would you would you go to
someone if you spoke to someone for 3
weeks?" And then you'd say to yourself,
"No." So, you would think the same thing
would go for them, but that's it. Like,
it doesn't matter what you do in this
day and age.
Try and meet too fast, try and meet too
slow, go out approaching, you're always
going to have this problem. Um, and
that's why I gave up. It reminds me of
just a mugs game, a complete and a mugs
game. But yeah, that's my video in 2026. And
yeah, um I think the only way I'd ever
get with anyone now is if a miracle
happened and someone reached out and
they proved to me they were different,
which let's face it, I think got more
chance of winning the lottery if you
don't mind me saying. But yeah, that's it.