So this is a video to um Monty man.
Yeah, cuz I just watched his live
stream. Now he was talking about these
people being single and lonely and
retire. So that's their business to
stand up for themselves. Then he started
bringing me up. Bro, don't bring me up.
Yeah, I would rather be [ __ ] single
than be with that ugly fat slag STD
ridden [ __ ] that you're with. Yeah. And
you're sat there saying about how, oh
yeah, well, she could have chose anyone
in this community. Monty, I could have
been with Natalie G before you if I
wanted to. Yeah, that is not a flex.
Getting with a [ __ ] fat ugly slag
that's been ran through on YouTube is
not a flex. So if you are about to talk
about people, yeah, don't talk about me,
I'd rather be single than be with that
[ __ ] [ __ ] dumpster STD ridden [ __ ] in
with in your words that's got black
flaps, bro. Yeah, I could have been with
her way before you was even with Kaye,
bro. So don't [ __ ] sit there and try
and say you will use your single like
PJ, bro. I could have had your [ __ ]
before you was even with [ __ ] Kaye. I
don't want that stinking fat [ __ ] with
black flaps. Yeah. Yeah. You [ __ ]
idiot. Don't bring me into your [ __ ]
[ __ ] I'd rather be single. I'd rather
[ __ ] be single than be with [ __ ]
that. And I proved it by turning her
[ __ ] down years ago when I was 20
[ __ ] two. You [ __ ] idiot. Get a
[ __ ] grip yourself, you [ __ ] pathetic [ __ ]