my football bet coming and I thought you
know what what better way to uh
celebrate it than with a uh chicken vindaloo basically. Um
yeah, I got a double scar node ra
coming. I never thought I'd see today.
So usually I get a lamb vindaloo but
today I wanted to get a chicken one cuz
you know winner winner chicken dinner.
You know how it is. You absolutely know
how it is. I'm surprised the [ __ ]
virgin didn't copy my football bet. He
not saying that he can't have a Vindaloo
because he [ __ ] it's too much for
him, but you know, I'm surprised he
won't run into the bookies. He'll do
anything to fit in. That's why he's why
he copied the Shervel Cole trend to make
himself look good cuz he's a little
copycat. So any of you, if you copy
today my football, you little copycats,
you would be having the same thing. bit.
I thought I'd celebrate with a I never
thought I'd get a double both teams to
scar. No jar.
Like I said, I prefer the um
I prefer the that but obviously
winner winner chicken dinner. Now, if I
was L or the virgin, that would be gone,
mate. That would be [ __ ] gone. But
not big strong Turkish men. M.