Yo. Okay, so I'm going to get I'm going
to tell you a little um story. Um I woke
up today and yeah, this actually pissed
me off. Um this is one of the reasons
why I gave up with women and dating. Um
because of how toxic it was. Um and
yeah, I've not been in a bad mood for a
very long time um since I gave up
dating, which was weeks ago. Um I've
almost broke my record to be honest. So
yeah, I haven't approached women or um
drunk for yeah 6 weeks because you get
to a point where you say to yourself
like enough is enough. Like these women
are clearly all the same. You know, I
don't know how many more times you're
going to keep giving them the benefit of
the doubt um to prove that they're
different or to prove that they're good
only for them to do exactly the same
thing. Um play games, lead you on, have
the same [ __ ] attitude. Um, you know,
it's like it gets to a point where no,
they are all the same. Like despite what
all of these, you know, other people
want to say about, oh, they're not all
the same, retrieve
another. So, at the at the end of the
day, actions speak louder than words.
And at the end of the day, it's not like
you've been in a 10-year relationship
and you've split up with a person and
then you've suddenly started to
generalize all women or you've been
trying for a month and then you've
suddenly started generalizing all women.
This has been going on for [ __ ]
years. So, at the end of the day, the
question is how many more years you have
to keep giving women the benefit of the
doubt to prove that they're not all the
same only for them to prove that they
are all the [ __ ] same. So I think a
big thing is this in this is actions
speak louder than words. And another
thing is right um I felt so much better
when I've when I gave up with dating you
know no makebelieve boyfriends no mind
games no attitude no leading on you know
when you finally give up you feel so
much better like you I generally feel
like you change as a person like but
that that goes with anything that's like
toxic and bad for you like you could be
addicted to like drugs or gambling um or
and and as soon as you stop obviously
not straight away it takes time you
change as a person. Like I felt like I
actually changed as a person when I gave
up. Um that's how toxic it was. You
know, it got to the point where, you
know, you'd go out every week, you'd get
numbers, they'd lead you you'd lead you
to [ __ ] on or they wouldn't reply. That
with the [ __ ] you know, the the way
the drink would make you feel as well,
you know, and then when you finally give
up, you you feel so much better. Like
you don't even feel bored. Like my
friend said to me like, um, do not feel
bored. And I was like, nah. Because
where I've been dealing with their [ __ ]
for so many [ __ ] years, more than
anyone in the world, when you finally
give up, it's like a it's like a relief.
It's like a weights been lifted off your
shoulder, bro. It's it's it's madness.
So, yeah, this gets me onto this story,
right? And yeah, like
um I have been saying for the past 4
weeks that um you know, I'm going to uh
go out and try I'm going to try again.
But whenever it comes to the day, I'm
like, nah, there's no point. The more I
think about my bad experiences with them
and even the odd one that I come across
from Instagram um or any social media
platform, the more I realize what these
women are like and why I don't even
waste my time on them. Um, which gets me
onto this [ __ ] Um, excuse my French,
right? So, I met this person on Reddit
uh about a month and a half ago, and
they were talking normally at first.
They live in a different country. It's
just an example of what these women are
like. Um, that's another thing that I've
not mentioned uh before is that you will
talk to a woman, right, and have a
normal conversation. Um, and you'll be
like, "Good night." They say good night.
Then you'll message them the next day
and it's like they've completely
switched. It's like they're a completely
different person or they'll like they
will write a last message to you and
then when you respond the next day when
you wake up, you'll never hear from them
again. Like they're they're it's where
they're so fake and phony, right? They
um they can only keep it up for so long.
Um and that and that's what it is, you
know? They it's like you speak to one
person one day and then it's like
they're a completely different person
the next day. It's [ __ ] madness. Oh,
they Oh, that or they just [ __ ] ghost
you. Um, but anyways, so I was speaking
to this person uh who I met a month and
a half ago and one day they were typing
right normally typing normally and then
suddenly they stopped replying and it's
not like they blocked me or they said
they had a boyfriend or anything like
that because they said they were single.
Um, and they just kept ignoring and
ignoring and ignoring and ignoring and
and and at the end of the day, like
normally when people ignore, I don't
really care, but they were doing it on
purpose to be a [ __ ] Like, they must
have like clicked on 200 of my messages.
And I was like, you are not going to sit
there and [ __ ] keep ignoring me. Um,
this is what I mean where it's toxic.
When you enter the dating arena and you
deal with women, it's the same toxicness
again. This is why I gave up. But
anyways, um, and I was like, "You're not
going to you're not going to sit there
and keep ignoring me." Um, because I
wanted them to block me. The whole point
of it was I wanted them to just to block
me. They lived in a different country
anyways, and you're not going to sit
there and ignore me. I feel like a lot
of these women, they need telling about
themselves. Like, they all think their
[ __ ] don't stink. They think they're
better than everyone. And I feel like a
lot of them, they need telling about
themsel very verbally. Um, but the
moment you do that, they play victim,
which we'll get on to anyways. Um, so I
was like, "Okay, I'm just going to start
sending you pictures on my dick. I'm
going to do everything now until you
[ __ ] block me. You're not going to
sit there and [ __ ] ignore me, you
stupid cunt." Right? And then they still
was keep clicking on the message,
clicking on the message, bro, about 300
times. And I started spamming all their
pictures like, and then they finally
they said, "Oh, you need to get
therapy." And blocked me. I said, "No,
you're the one that needs to get
therapy." Sat there [ __ ] ignoring
people like you're better than them, you
[ __ ] stupid stuck up [ __ ] Um, and
then she blocked me and then, oh, the
irony was I got I got uh banned. Um,
they are they are [ __ ] [ __ ]
aren't they? The more you think about
this. This is what put me off wanting to
go out Friday. Um, this Friday. This is
why I'm not going out now. Probably
won't go out now. Don't think I can
stomach it. Um, so where they uh
reported me, I got banned on Instagram
for seven days. Oh, and then we had some
white knight messaging me. I said,
"Don't even think about coming on my
[ __ ] inbox, you [ __ ] white knight
cunt." That's what I said to him. I
swear to God, bro, if this guy lived in
England, I'd be meeting him today. Like,
bro, your [ __ ] ass [ __ ] girlfriend
blocked me for a reason. Don't message
me, bro. You're barking up the wrong
tree. Yeah. And I feel like that's what
it is with a lot of these women is that
they're they're they're very
narcissistic. Um, and you know, as soon
as someone gives them a taste of their
own medicine, they play victim, call you
a stalker, report you to Instagram. They
can even they'll even report you to the
[ __ ] police. Um, so at the end of the
day, she didn't tell me she had a
boyfriend. She was very, very much
single. And that's not the point. I
weren't trying to get with her. You are
not just going to sit there and ignore
me. You're going to block me. Simple.
And this is why I gave up with the whole
dating thing. Um, they are clearly all
the same. like it's it's it's it's it's
obvious now, you know?
So, I said, "You're not going to sit
there and ignore me. You're the one that
needs therapy, you stupid cunt." And
then she's got some [ __ ] And this is
what I don't understand with these
women. Why do they get other guys to
message you? Do they not have a voice of
their own? Like, they're big enough to
be ignorant, stuck up [ __ ] And we're
talking verbally now. We're not talking physically.
They're big enough to be [ __ ] stuck
up egoistic [ __ ] all their [ __ ]
life. But soon as it's to do with
standing their ground, they won't do it.
They will not do it. They're cowards.
This is what I mean with them. They are
[ __ ] cowards. It has pissed me off so
much this morning, bro. I swear to God,
if this guy lived anywhere in the UK, I
would have made a [ __ ] example out of
him, bro. Don't come my [ __ ] inbox,
start whiting some [ __ ] stupid
[ __ ] [ __ ] cuz you're barking up the
[ __ ] wrong tree. I told him about
himself as well and then he said, "Oh,
nothing." He couldn't say anything. Like
they're big enough and [ __ ] ugly
enough to be egoistic [ __ ] But
when it's to do with actually standing
their ground and argue, you know, you
know, with someone, they won't do it.
They'll get some [ __ ] stupid white
knight that you don't know to start
messaging you. They're [ __ ] absolute
[ __ ] That's what they are. Dick
[ __ ] heads. Yeah. They're not so big
when they meet their match, are they?
These women. I've noticed that with
these entitled [ __ ] women. They're
not so [ __ ] big when they meet their
[ __ ] match. And I mean verbally. I
mean very much verbally here. I don't
mean physically. I mean verbally. Um and
in that in that sense we're all equal.
So at the end of the day like they're so
big, aren't they? When they think
they're dealing with a [ __ ] or a
white knight. But as soon as you match
their energy, oh you're a stalker. Oh,
we'll get the white knight to defend us.
I told that guy more than about his
[ __ ] self, mate. Yeah. And he's lucky
that he lives in [ __ ] South America,
bro, because I've been meeting him
today. And this is the toxicity that
people don't need. This is why I gave up
with dating. This is why I gave up with
women, because it's the same [ __ ] with
them, you know. And yeah, that's a
that's a little story for you all. Um
Yeah. And how many times has that
happened where, you know, they act like
[ __ ] and then as soon as you give
it back, they report you to Instagram or
they uh report you to police or they get
some white knight to to fight their
battles. A very verbal battle, mind you.
You know, they're [ __ ] [ __ ]
I'm so glad I gave up.