Yep. So, I'm out here with the old
drink, mate. You know what I'm saying?
And uh smash about four approaches. No
good. But uh yeah, we're getting on it.
The boys will definitely get some under there. [Music] Definitely. Excuse me.
>> What's your name? What's that?
>> Pizza. What do you think? [Music]
>> Every time I go out eastondon [Music]
I went last year and I was this first
time in like 10 years. the chainsaw.
>> Yeah, even for me. [Music]
>> So, do you like Friday? players.
>> It's the big game. [Music]
>> I don't to be honest. I don't
>> I don't go out like Thursday or
Saturday. Thursday. Have you ever been
out on Thursday? Be so good. It's like
sometimes it's better than
>> I mean
so like what tomorrow
but like drinking or One day
another time I would like to thank you
for your boyfriend.
Nice to meet you anyway.
Santa had a boyfriend. [ __ ] off, man.