Yo. Okay, so I'm going to be live at um
5:00 PM and this is going to be a panled
um live stream. I'm really going to rip
into these people, you know, the [ __ ]
that they've been doing for years. You
know, the jealousy towards me. Um I'm
going to put the link up. I want them to
show their face. I want them to show me
money. All of the things that they try
to call other people all of these years,
I'm going to put a stop to it. Um you
know, and I'm just going to keep putting
a link out, putting a link out, putting
a link out. And the title of the um live
stream is going to be you people are
jealous of Peterbelly and you can't
prove otherwise. And proving otherwise
would be showing your face to be better
looking than me. Showing your money.
I've got money here by the way. So I'm
I'm more than happy to play the money
game today um with these people. So
yeah, we're really going to dig into
these people today and we're going to
spoon nothing but facts. Like I'm going
to rip into that [ __ ] so bad that
they're going to need another [ __ ] Um,
what what even was that? But yeah, I'm
going to be ripping into these people,
tearing them apart today. Tearing them
away. You know, as someone used to say.
So, yeah, I'll be live at 5:00 p.m. um
with the Hangout link. And I want these
people to turn their camera on, show
their face, and try and tell me that
they're not jealous of anyone, which
they won't be able to do because they're
ugly mongos, fat with no life and no
money, which is what we're going to be
getting into later on um today. So yeah,
I'll be live at 5:00 p.m. Title is going
to be You People Are Jealous of Peter
Belly. That's what it's going to be. And
after this live stream, I'm going to be
off YouTube for a couple of weeks and
stuff because I've got things to do. But
yeah, I really want to rip into these
people, do you know? Cuz it's like, you
know, when you read these little [ __ ]
comments, yeah, it [ __ ] just annoys
you and like you feel the need to rip
into them. Like, bro, I'll play the
money game. I'll play the looks game
today. I'll play every single game that
these mongos won't beat me at. Yeah.
Simple. So, I'll be live at 5:00 p.m.,
bro. I want to see looks. I want to see
money. I want people to have a debate. I
want debates. I want to, you know, ask
these people why they do what they do.
You know, it's going to be a bit like
politics, to be honest. I want people to
join. I want people to show their face.
I want to see money. I want to have
conversations. I want them to really
prove that they're not jealous of
anything. And if they if they aren't
really, they'll put their camera on and
they'll show their face. Um, and they'll
have this debate. And if they can't do
that, then it just goes to show that
they're jealous. So anyways, live at
5:00 PM. So yeah, you better join.