Yo. Okay, so this is to London Taylor.
Yeah. Um because I am losing my [ __ ]
patience. Um I I can't lie. Now, I did
say to Greasy that, you know, I'm
waiting. I'm still waiting. I'm pretty
much waiting longer than the guy in the
Little Britain shop, you know, the the
the awkward shopper. Um so, what I done
was I emailed him cuz, you know, I
wanted to um keep this off of YouTube
because I don't want to, you know, wind
people up and, you know, whatever. So,
I've messaged him and he's not replied
back and it's been a couple of hours and
I've just basically stated that you're
nothing but a biased [ __ ] Um,
basically, um, and the fact that like
I'll explain why in a minute, but and
it's been a couple of hours. He's still
not um, emailed me back and I figured,
you know what, he might not check his
emails. So, I'm just going to do a
YouTube video. So, he's definitely
definitely definitely um, going to um,
you know, see this and he says that he's
got a degree and that he's intelligent.
So hopefully he will be able to be the
one to answer this. Now, you know, the
past like week, 2 weeksish, I've been
thinking like I'll put my tea bag in a
in a tea. Yeah. And I'll be like, "This
guy is a biased cunt." Like this LT.
Yeah. He tries to act like he's like
he's not one of these people. He's not
biased and he's completely fair. And I'm
thinking, okay, bro, let's let's get
this started again. Now, hold on a
minute. I've gone on this guy's channel
where he has um you know, been calling
me a virgin. We all know the skint
virgin in the shitty bedset. And then
he's been calling me a virgin. And I've
scrolled down again and he's been
calling me a virgin. Now the only thing
I'm thinking at this point is hold on a
minute. Where's London Taylor talking
about um you know me having a [ __ ]
me sleeping with Sig, me sleeping with
that girl that I had, you know, a friend
with benefits with. You know, there's
multiple different occasions and things
I've shown to actually fully um fully uh
defend the fact that I'm not a virgin
other than showing a fat ugly girlfriend
that you keep going on about. And what I
mean by that is two weeks ago, right,
when I was calling him a virgin, LT was
straight to his rescue. He's got a
girlfriend. He's got a girlfriend. He's
got a girlfriend, which is not proof
that someone has had sex. What is proof
someone has had sex is someone like me,
bro. Yeah. Someone that's shown a
[ __ ] Someone shown me in bed with
women. Show I've put a porno, bro, that
got about two people's YouTube channels
banned because of it. They can't even
log back on it. And then you're trying
to tell me how me calling someone that's
got a fat ugly pig girlfriend a virgin
is ridiculous. But but some calling
someone like me a virgin is not
ridiculous. Really, bro? And then you
started and then you were saying, "Oh,
well, you're being immature. I'm being
immature, bro." You did you not remember
what you literally said them two weeks
ago? You said that, oh, having a [ __ ]
is not proof that you've had sex. Okay,
bro. So, someone that's proved they've
had a [ __ ] someone that's shown them
in bed naked with several different
women, someone that has met a single
woman multiple times in hotel rooms and
have admitted to sleeping with me.
That's not proof. No, that's not proof
that someone having a fat, ugly, stinky
girlfriend is somehow more proof than
what I've shown. Really, bro? Like,
you're you're supposed to be
intelligent, bro. you're supposed to
have a degree, but bro, I'm starting to
really really doubt you, bro. I'm really
putting you in the same um category as
as these people. I can't lie to you,
bro, because that does does not make any
sense. And obviously, I understand like,
you know, you could you could generally
believe that, you know, me saying that
someone has a girlfriend and being a
virgin is is ridiculous. And you you are
in your rights to think that, but
wouldn't you think it's more ridiculous
for somebody to be calling me a virgin?
But with that one, you let it slide,
don't you? You have nothing to say about
it. I mean, I've said I've asked Joe
this before, but obviously the guy is a
[ __ ] so um he couldn't um couldn't
really answer it. And he was saying that
basically he knows that I'm not a
virgin, but he doesn't need to say
anything. Oh, okay. So, you don't need
to say anything unless it's me talking
about the skin lanky virgin that then
you need to say something. Okay, mate.
Really? Really? Do you not see how you
kind of like these people? I don't know.
That has just been annoying me the past
week, bro. In my head. Um because it's
blamed in biasness. I mean they've done
it with they've done it with um they've
also done it with money as well. Like
when I've shown money they made
different rules for me. I had to show
exactly the same money again even though
I showed it millions times and if I
didn't I was skinned. I mean they are
generally generally generally biased. I
mean how they can seem to think that me
calling somebody with a fat ugly
girlfriend that he's got no proof of
[ __ ] um a virgin is ridiculous. But
people calling me a virgin isn't. when
I've when I've shown a bit more than a
fat ugly girlfriend. And then they and
then oh this is another thing LT said as
well. He said, "Oh, it doesn't count
because I paid for it." Bro, them women
that I got with, they was not all paid.
And secondly, even if I got with one
woman. I Let's just say I only showed
one woman and I paid only her. Brother,
I've still banged a woman on camera.
I've still been with a woman in a
woman's bed. It would count more than
showing a fat ugly girlfriend. I mean,
bro, like that would count as someone
losing their virginity. Now, I don't
count it as a body count, but I mean,
even if you was to go out right now and
you was to pay an escort, you've lost
your virginity if you're a virgin in my
book. But it doesn't count as a body
count. So, if someone says, "Oh, what's
your body count?" Obviously, you exclude
the escort. So, what you're you are
biased to the max, bro. If you really
really think that it's ridiculous me
calling someone a virgin that's got a
fat ugly girlfriend but someone calling
me a virgin when I've literally proved
I've had sex. I've had people's channels
banned because of it. You got something
wrong with your head, bro. You're a bit
cucku. Like you generally generally are.
And you'll notice that as well. A few
people have done it. Every single time
I've called this nonslegs a virgin.
They're straight to his rescue. And to
be honest with you, he hasn't even
proved he's had sex. Let me tell you a
story, bro. I shouldn't even be telling
you this, right? I know a couple and
they didn't have sex because the guy
couldn't get his dick up. There's people
in relationships that's got no dick. I
mean, bro, no matter how what percentage
that you want to put on it, bro, there's
a big bigger bigger bigger chance of him
being a virgin than me being a virgin.
It's like it's it sounds ridiculous,
bro. I know what you're saying. The
whole thing is immature, but bro, it's
to show how biased you are. If we have
to we have to we have to talk about this
to show how biased you are, it is the
truth. You don't. And and think about
what you're saying, bro. If someone
having a [ __ ] is not proof that
they've had sex, then someone having a
girlfriend isn't proof that they've had
sex. Because a [ __ ] is showing more
than a fat, ugly girlfriend. Um, you
don't know their love life. You don't
know if they've ever had sex. You do not
know them. What you do know is I have
shown I've had sex. I have shown me pull
multiple women. Everyone knows my
history with women. So, I just want to
kind of know why you are also nowhere to
be seen when someone's calling me a
virgin. And another thing is I don't
want you to defend me. I don't need you
to defend me. So don't try and reverse
the psychology now and say, "Oh, oh, I
need you to defend me." I'm asking you
why you're not because you are biased.
You know, and you know, the same thing
would happen if I [ __ ] got a
girlfriend tomorrow. They'd be like,
"Oh, uh, well, you haven't proved you've
had sex with her." And that's exactly
LT. You're really, really no different
than one of these people. As much as you
claim that you are, trust me, trust me,
trust me, trust me, you're not. You
know, if you really, really, really,
really think it's ridiculous me calling
someone with a girl a girlfriend a
virgin, why do you not find it
ridiculous someone calling someone like
me a virgin when there's literally no
chance of me being a virgin? There's
like no chance. And you don't seem to
have the same energy. You don't seem to
have the same energy when people calling
me a virgin, but you seem to have all
this energy when I'm calling legs a
virgin. You're straight away like, "He's
got a girlfriend. He's got a
girlfriend." like you will literally
defend him till you're blew in the face
and it's not even proof that he's had
sex. It's way less proof than what I
have provided. Um so it's kind of like
and that's what that's what you call an
agenda and something that's not suiting
your narrative, you know, and and you
know, and even if even even if the roles
even if the the roles were reversed and
I had a girlfriend and he's the one that
was having sex, they would they would
take e side. Um, so you know, I'm trying
to say it doesn't really make any sense,
you know, and and even the things that
you were trying to come out with. Oh,
well, you paid them. Oh, it was just a
[ __ ] Really, bro? You're saying all
of these things and you're trying to
make up excuses as to how I'm how the
things I've done has not counted, but
yet you're you're defending someone with
a fat, ugly girlfriend, and you don't
even know their sex life. You're not
even that [ __ ] fly on the wall, bro.
I don't possibly know how somebody could
have [ __ ] sex when they're on YouTube
stalking someone 24 fucking7 and they're
[ __ ] messaging every single [ __ ]
hookup that I bloody been with. Mad. You
are biased. And this is not a video to
defend you. You are biased. Simple.
Thank you. It's all I wanted to say. Had
to get out of my system. You know, I
really really been gunning to do this
for days. You're biased. Simple.