actually turned into a Monday session
with the person that I'm with. My first
first drink in 2026 and I am fat.
Um, yeah, I done an approach earlier and
this is for Grevy by the way. I done an
approach earlier on one first one of
2026 and the first drink is 2026 to be fair. Um,
yeah. Um, yeah. I don't know how many
Guinnesses I am down, but I'm going to
Should I do one of them now?
>> Yeah, just for grievy because we have we
have deprived the poor [ __ ] of content
as of late. So, why not? Nah.
Damn. Just let you know,
I haven't drunk today. I haven't ate
today before drinking.
I stopped watering it out. Look, it's
gone. Greavves is gone. Little drables.
It's like mouthwash.
Yeah. Can't leave Grezy without content
for too long. Packer. He's been with us.
He's been with us. He's been with us
since day one. Man,
>> I am fat. How many last time I got drunk
on a Monday, you know, but don't feel
like a thick to be fair. It feels more
like a Wednesday, Thursday than a Monday.
I am [ __ ] [ __ ] though. I'm not even
joking. Drinking all day, playing some
pool. I played a couple games of pool
earlier with someone. Yeah, last stairs.
it is what it is, man.
Know what we're going to eat later. Who knows? Yeah.