Yo. Okay, so this is going to be my
reply to um Virgin Boy. Um yeah, do you
know what? I'm going to start calling
you S Legs. Yeah. Or should I start
calling you Simpleton Legs? Get it? Simp
Pin cuz you're a S and you're also a
Simpleton. But yeah, maybe. But
obviously the number one name for you is
is always going to be the virgin because
you're big virgin, you know, biggest
virgin going. Um but yeah, I'm going to
title this video um simplex. So I went
on your uh channel and I saw your little
um simp comment um saying about how um
yeah, well done for bullying a uh poor
innocent woman. Now I don't think we're
watching the same video. like can't be
you can't be watching the same video as
I made that I'm watching um because my
video is uh giving a woman a taste of
her own medicine, you know, bit like
what they've done to people over the
years, leading people on, taking the
piss, standing people up. So, as soon as
you give somebody the tiniest dosage of
their own medicine, you're all of a
sudden a bully now. So, what does that
make these women all of these years? I
mean, Jesus [ __ ] Christ. I mean, I
read your uh comment um uh someone sorry
uh someone's comment on your um
community post saying that they hate me
even more now. They hate me for doing 1%
of what women literally do all day every
day to other people. Like, think of all
of the guys that we don't know that
they've done this to. I mean, I've been
stood up. Um I I got stood up in London
last year. I was supposed to meet
somebody. They didn't come out. The year
before that, I went all the way to
Nottingham when there was a train
strike. It was an absolute [ __ ] trying
to get up there and the woman literally
didn't show up. Now, obviously, I went
on a night out there anyways, but she
didn't know that. Like, she was
prepared to leave me completely [ __ ]
So, giving somebody a taste of their own
medicine um does not make them any kind
of bully. It's giving somebody a taste
of their own medicine. Um because what
does that make these women even
marvelably? Do you know what I'm saying?
So like it's it it's it's crazy how like
women can do whatever they want whenever
they want and then as soon as you give a
tiny bit back you get all of these simps
chasing you with a [ __ ] axe. It's a
madness. Um absolute madness. Um it
really really really is. Like I'm
surprised um you know simp legs tried
calling me a bully. Normally they call
you a stalker. If you literally meet a
woman and she tries to take the piss out
of you and tries to be a [ __ ] and you
give her what for, normally they they
they will victimize themsel and then
call you a stalker to try to victimize
himself. But being called a bully. Yeah,
that's definitely that's definitely up
there with a new one because I've never
been called that before. Or are you
referring to the fact that I said that
she needs to gain weight and get a boob
job? I mean, she started it. I mean, she
she tried giving me a lecture about my
appearance. you know, when I met her,
she was saying about how I need to go to
the gym and, you know, go and lift
weights when there's nothing wrong with
my body then and there's nothing wrong
with my body now. And she was trying she
was saying I need to change my hair. Um,
she was giving me a manipulating lecture
about my appearance in in hope and
anticipation she was going to make me
insecure. She's a [ __ ] which is why I
stood her up. Yeah. Which is what
they've done to other people before.
stood people up. Fun fact, I um remember
a story that uh Fraser told me before
where he went to meet this um woman in a
train station and she didn't show up and
uh he his phone died and he was
completely [ __ ] He had to stay there
overnight because the train stopped
running. I wonder if that woman got
called a bully. Nah, she wouldn't, would
she? The double standards wouldn't allow
it. Um fun fact for you all. Um, so
yeah, that does not make somebody a
bully for giving somebody a taste of
their own medicine, matey. Um, not in
the slightest. And the reason I spoke
about her appearance is cuz she tried
giving me a lecture about mine. And you
know, it's not even like she was trying
to give an opinion or give a preference.
She was literally trying to make me feel
insecure. Um, I know the difference. You
know, I'm an adult. You know, I'm way
too smart for these women. I know
exactly what they're trying to do.
um when you've been dealing with them
for so long, as I always say, you know
what they're like. So, there's nothing
innocent about them and there's nothing
a that's a bully about me. Me giving
somebody a taste of their own medicine
is far from bullying someone. So, get
your facts right um before um making
community posts about me. Now, you were
saying about how I need to I'd like to
see you try to bully a man. Now, you do
realize you just opened up a can of
worms for yourself. Um, now firstly, I
wasn't bullying anyone. Like I said, I
was giving somebody a taste of their own medicine.
But I do know also that I have gone to
your area three times and you have not
come out. Instead, you've run to the
police screaming how you're not a
fighter. Now, I know people on here like
to forget the L's that they took and
they like to forget um W's that you've
took because people love forgetting. you
know, I went to your area three times
and you literally did not come out once
despite being the biggest keyboard
warrior that's ever existed probably on
the internet along with your boyfriend
Red Star whose dick you like to suck
every day. Um, and you know, same with
Mark Samson. Went to his area two times,
didn't show up. Went to Trevor Dawson's
area, didn't show up. Went to Tererry's
area, didn't show up. Went to Bomb two
times, didn't show up. Isn't it funny?
Simple legs. how you are the biggest
keyboard warrior on here as long along
with your boyfriend whose dick you like
to suck every day. You know, you two
have never ever tried meeting anyone.
You've just been a keyboard warrior.
You'll always be a keyboard warrior. You
got your boyfriend sat on YouTube
stalking men all day every day cuz he's
a sad fat baldy skint loser with no life
stalking every single day. We've got you
being a [ __ ] virgin every day in your
channel, but you'll never ever meet
anyone. And it always goes to this
again. It's like, okay, yeah, I might
have took some L's. Yeah, I might have
run up my mouth on YouTube a lot, but
bro, I've met people. I've put myself at
risk. I'm meeting Prime on Monday. If
Prime comes to London on Monday, I'm
going to smash his [ __ ] face in, you
know. There's no doubt about that. You
know, and I've and I am meeting him and,
you know, at the end of the day, I've
tried to meet other people as well and
I've met other people and I've, you
know, I've put myself in danger on this
website. You along with your little
boyfriend, Red Star, you will never ever
meet anyone. How many times have I gone
to your area? How many times have I
called you out and I've called Redshot
out? And all you'll do is do nothing but
sit online every day being stalkers.
Which is one thing, but then what makes
it even more interesting is that then
you'll then beg London Taylor. You'll
beg the black man to come and do this to
me and come and do that to me. It's a
madness, isn't it? How you and your
boyfriend Redar, right, are the biggest
keyboard warriors ever, like I've ever
come across. You'll never meet anyone.
You'll never say anything to anyone's
face. You know, you just want to be a
little loser on YouTube every single
day. And then you think you've got the
cheat to tell me, right, in your [ __ ] skintset
that I need to go and try and bully a
[ __ ] man, mate. Why didn't you bully
me when I went to your area three times?
Why didn't your boyfriend Red bully me
when I called him out a million times?
And another thing is, you knew where I
lived as well. You knew where I lived.
Redstar knew where I lived. So, why
don't you ask yourself the same
question? Why didn't you come out when I
was in your area three times? Why didn't
you come to my address? Why didn't Red
Star show me where he is the five or six
times I called his ass out? So, you
might want to practice what you [ __ ]
preach before [ __ ] coming on YouTube,
making community posts, trying to [ __ ] simp
woman that just got a taste of her own
medicine. Just got a taste of her own
medicine. Didn't defend myself. didn't
don't need to exaggerate all of these
things. I just gave her a small dosage
of her own medicine. Simple as that. She
spoke about my appearance. I spoke about
her appearance. She wanted to be a [ __ ]
I was a [ __ ] back. You know, it's like
that's just the way it is. That doesn't
mean somebody is a bully. You know, it's it's it's
madness. Bullying is what you and your
little boyfriend Red tries to do on
YouTube every day. But you don't bully
anyone. You just make a tit of yourself,
you know, like it's but you know that's
you're ridiculous. You need to practice
what you preach. You know, I've I've
I've tried to meet a man. I've gone to
your area three times and you hid under
the [ __ ] bed. Gone to [ __ ] Mark's
area [ __ ] two times and [ __ ] he he
hid under the [ __ ] bed. I've called
Red Star out a million times.
[ __ ] he would never meet anyone.
Yeah, he will stalk and record
everything all day, every day on YouTube
like the fat 40-year-old skinned virgin
he is like you. Pathetic, man. You need
to practice what you [ __ ] preach, [ __ ] virgin.