Yo. Okay, so I am going to this
Brazilian restaurant again. I went a
couple of days ago, but for some reason
I just didn't record any of it. And
yeah, so basically it's like a buffet
set price. So you can pick what you want
and then they literally will bring meat
to you and they literally have
everything. pork, beef, lamb, and like different
like by pork they'll have like pork
belly, pork, you know, loin, they'll
have gamin, beef, lamb, like they
literally have everything. Whereas if
you go to like an Indian, they'll do
lamb and for example, not the beef here
has everything. So, um yeah, and you can
literally and the meat that they bring
to you, um that's a set price as well.
So you can have it for as long as 2
hours. So yeah, it's really lush. So I'm
going to go again. It was that nice. I'm going again.
Feels like it's going to snow, you know.
So yeah, that's what I'm doing. But I'll
pause and resume.
Okay, so this is the buffet bit. So I've
got some uh pork ribs, some beef, and
mushroom. Right. This is not the [music] main bit.
>> Hello. You like pork belly and chicken sausage?
>> Pork belly, please. All right.
>> So, I can put chir. >> Mhm.
>> No sausage. No sausage. That's fine.
>> And they'll carve it in front of you. It's lush.
>> Yeah. I wasn't expecting it that fast.
So, that's pork belly. And then they'll
do lo beef that you'll see. And the
reason they give you this is whilst
they're cutting it, you have to sort of
hold it whilst they're slicing it.
Nice bit of lemonade as well.
Nice bit of pork belly. Pork ribs. Pork belly. [music]
>> Lovely. [music]
Absolutely lovely this place. I had to
come back. It was so nice. So good.
>> From Yes, please.
>> This the one the tong one, please. The tongue.
That nasty beef. So good.
I didn't realize that one. Yeah.
>> So, you obviously hold it whilst they slice it.
>> Yeah. They just brought over chicken
wings, but I didn't want it because I
saw what these
pork ribs. I don't really fancy chicken
to be fair. Mhm.
Lush. This is the chicken.
>> Oh, that's lush. [music]
The pork ribs are nice. All right.
>> Right. And this is the gammon. Oh,
this is what this was one of my
favorites over there. Yummy. M. That's lush.
cut in front of me.
>> So nice.
It's honestly got to be the best curry
I've ever had. Oh, lush.
>> Absolutely lush.
>> It gets better, trust me. Right.
Some more beef. Had to wait a while for
it. Um the chicken came around a couple
of times, but I didn't want the chicken.
So, yeah. Had to get some more rice, by the way. Lovely. Should
be lamb next or pork lo.
This is lush. [music]
Here we go. Got the lamb now. Oh, look at that.
Peter belly is getting stuffed.
Oh my god, that [music] is yum. I
>> tell you what, yeah, this would be good
before getting on the drink and the day
after getting on the drink when you're
like hung over. Oh my word. Oh man, that's delicious. So succulent. >> Wow.
I'm getting there, you know. I'm getting there.
Yeah. I'll pause and show you the next
one. Should be pork loin next. 100%. Should be.
And that is the pork loin. So, it's
basically pork chop because a pork
chop's called a pork loin. This is very
nice. Very nice. Anyways, I'm going to
end the video here and uh yeah, just
stay here and enjoy some more food until
I'm absolutely full. So, yeah, there you
go. That's the Brazilian restaurant.