Okay, so this is going to be a video to
Smokey Be. This is going to be my last
response to you, man, because I got to
be honest with you, it's it's getting
kind of sad now. Um, it's looking a bit
dodge. Um, and it's getting weird. Um,
at the end of the day, right, um, when
someone's obsession gets as bad as the
skin, lanky, ugly virgin with the ugly
disabled girlfriend in the bedset, um,
you know, that's when it's time to
think, yeah, man, this is kind of this
is this is a this is this is time to
step back. But to be honest with you,
yeah, um I was thinking about this
yesterday when I went for a walk and I'm
thinking like Jesus Christ, like these
people on YouTube are never ever going
to stop their jealousy towards me. Um
which I I will explain what I mean um in
a minute. I'm not just going to say
something and not explain it. Come on,
Smokey B. I'm not like you people on
YouTube, you know, starting something I
can't finish. Bear with me. It's like
it's it's mad. Like they they spend
every second of every day being obsessed over me.
It's clear as a sunny day that it is
jealousy. Because if someone's not
getting paid to do something and they're
doing this every single day for years
and they don't stop,
what is it? Like, have you ever heard
like the saying, bro, like time is
money. And it's like kind of like I
shouldn't even be on here entertaining a
bunch of people that are just jealous
like that have got no life. Like I
should just be living my life. But I did
come on today because Smokeoky B I did
say to Greavesy and Stephen Howard, I'll
go live for the football. But you know,
it's like you and the Virgin and a few
other people, you actually live to do
this for free. Like you don't get paid
by YouTube. You don't get paid by
anyone. You waste your life away on me
every second of every day. And you've
been doing it for years now. Have a
laugh at yourself. Now, you know that
you know the last um thing that you
wrote in the paragraph saying that
you're going to have a laugh about me,
bro. Laugh at yourself. You know, if you
packed that [ __ ] in, yeah, about 5 years
back, you probably weren't too old to change
your life, but obviously you're in your
40s now. You're a bit of an old [ __ ]
There there's no going back. But if
you'd actually stopped all them years
ago, right? Um you would have actually
like you would you could have actually
changed and you was writing about how
you know I say that I've got the better
life than everyone and how I'm skinn and
I live in a bedsit and uh I live in a
spare room. You said a better life. Uh
bro, didn't you see what I learned in
two years? All of them places I went to,
all of them women I've been with, all of
the friends, all of the hotel rooms.
What the [ __ ] was you doing in them
[ __ ] two years, [ __ ] You're
trying to say that that's not a better
life than yours. Like, that wasn't even
me being offensive. That was the truth.
You in them two years, you know what
you're doing now, right? Sat on YouTube
projecting, calling other people the m
when you're the M yourself, which we'll
get on to. I was out there living life
and you're still on here. Think about
it, bro. So, I mean, I don't know. And
the thing is, I'm not skimp. I don't
live in my mom's spare room. What the
[ __ ] How the [ __ ] would you know how
much money I have? Boy, listen to
yourself. How much How would you know
how much money I have? And listen,
right? Um, even if I was skin and I
lived in my mom's spare room, guess
what? I'm not like you in my 40s, an old
wrinkly man that's probably too fat to
see his own dick that can't get off of
YouTube. Because at the age of 27,
guess what, bro? I could actually change
it. I can actually get some money, still
live with my mom, and my life would be
100 times better than yours. So, I mean,
that doesn't really narrow it down, does
it? And bro, listen to me now. Yeah.
Now, I'm not just saying this. I don't
think that what you're showing is your
money. Bear with me now. Anyone that's
watching this, don't think, oh, like if
I ever show money, if I ever show money,
he's going to say the same thing to me.
How many times has somebody put a bank
statement on that was fake. Come on,
bro. Like, it's been done quite a few
times. But I'm going to give you the
benefit of the doubt when I ask you to
to do the next video and not show the
exact same amount of money. But here's
the thing. You said that you're going to
laugh at me with your wife. Bro, you
need to laugh at yourself. You You Bro,
do you know what? The only thing your
wife, your makebelieve wife probably
laughed at is the fact that you got
called out two times on YouTube and you shat it.
And also the fact that you've known
where I've lived for 5 years and you
ain't done [ __ ] all about it. Your
makebelieve wife, bro, probably laughed
at how much of a beta male you are. No
one laughed at me. No, bro. I've shown
my face. I've proved many times I'm
better looking than all of you people on
here. I'm not saying I'm good-look. I'm
not saying I'm average, below average,
ugly. I know one thing though. I'm
better looking than everyone on here.
And that's exactly why people like you
don't show your face because you are the
manta. And remember that conversation
that I always used to have with Bob? I'm
sure you watched it. He'd always make
all of these excuses. I can't show my
face because someone's going to find out
who I am. And to this day, no one's
found out who he is, by the way. So,
bear bear that in mind. Um, yeah.
Someone's going to f know uh what I uh
what I look like, and then they're going to
And did you notice something, Smokey B,
that all of the things that he was
trying to call me over the years, it was exactly himself.
bit like you. That's literally a prime
example of what you are. You're the
manta. You're the fat, ugly, low life,
which is why you do what you do on here
every single day. And that's and that's
literally what it is. Because at the end
of the day, bro, if I'm all of those
things, why are you sat there wasting your life
obsessed and stalking me every second of
every day free of charge? How are you
going to are you going to answer your
way out of that one? Come on, bro. It
was a good try, but you're never ever
ever going to beat me. Now, what I am
going to ask you to do now um before I
ever ever give any thought into giving
you another reply, right, is you know
how you say that I'm the monto and I
don't believe that is even your money
because come on, bro. [ __ ] fridge
repair man done the same [ __ ] about a
year ago. How about this? How about you show everybody
your face? Why don't you come on YouTube
and show everybody what you look like?
And that's where I'd always have you by
the bollocks. Literally, I that's how
you always get these people like the
bomb and all of these other people. Cuz
think about it, there's been a history
of this [ __ ] Smokey, man. Come on.
Remember Gay Cat that used to talk about
Kayle's looks? She was probably the
ugliest thing I've ever seen in my life.
Bomb. Few other people. If you're not
any of these people, and I'm really
really am, why don't you show everyone
your face? You know, you're fast enough
to show money or fake bank statements
rather. Why don't you show everyone your
face, bro? Why don't you show everybody
what you look like and it will be the
same fat ugly manta. And that's it. So,
bro, it's very easy to do, right? Show
your face and show six grand in cash.
I'm not going to ask you to show 10 or
whatever because, bro, you you know,
you're just going to say you don't have
that cash. You said that you gambled
three grand the other day on roulette,
right? Okay. Show us six grand and show
your face. And when you've done that,
come back to me and try to say that I'm
the monto and I'm all of these things
that you're not. Cuz let me tell you
something, bro. If I stumbled across the
new community today and I was talking
about someone's looks for even one second,
let alone four years, and they turn
around and say to me, "Oh, well, I'm
better looking than you." I'd show my
face and prove that I'm better looking
than them. The fact that you and these
other people can't do it, it's as clear
as day who the real monties are,
yourself. So yeah, come back to me when
you got that six grand in cash and come
back to me when you finally got a pair
of balls and you can actually uh show
your face t now.