Yo. Okay, so this is going to be um my
response to Virgin Boy. Um this is going
to be a one-off, by the way. So don't
start expecting videos of me um you
know, replying to you every day or
whatever because you are the one that's
obsessed with me. I'm not the one that's
obsessed with you. And as I stated, um,
the reason I don't entertain this guy
anymore is basically because he comes on
YouTube every single day saying that I'm
skin and I'm ugly apparently. Yet he
doesn't fail to waste every second of
every day of his life, stalking me,
talking about me, doing videos on me,
doing community posts on me, which then
contradicts everything that he says
about me. And all of the things that he
tries to say about me is about himself.
and it just shows he's obsessed and
jealous. Sorry if that's a bit too
intelligent for you, but I mean it's
we're dealing with me here. But anyways,
on to the point of this video. So, I
went on your community post and um you
put up a quote from um is his name Mr.
Skinners or Principal Skinners? I can't
remember. Anyways, that the teacher from
the Simpsons and it was a sarcastic piss
taken uh quote saying that uh it's women
that are the problem, not me. It's women
that are the problem, not me. Now,
the problem with this is did Principal
Skinners show you what I showed you? you
know, me approaching women normally and
them saying they're not interested
straight away before getting to know me,
getting to know my personality, which
then contradicts the whole they go for
personality quotation mark. Um, because
how could they possibly if you know they
just say straight away they're not
interested. Um, they dismiss you
straight away. Um, what about when I've
got numbers and they've led me on, took
the piss, agree to meet, then flaked
when they were supposed to meet? What
about numbers that replied back and put
a love a heart and then blocked out of
nowhere? I don't know. I'm pretty sure
it was them women and not me. I mean,
I've showed enough evidence. See, the
diff see the thing with this is I can
back up everything that I say. I can
show my approaches. I can show my
messages. I can show the experiences I
have had with women. Um, which proves it
is these women. Now, I have never said
once that I've never been wrong and it's
always been them. Um, but it's not been
me for a long time. And trust me, I know
when I'm wrong. Um, and I've never said
that I'm not wrong. I admit when I'm
wrong, but all of this shows that it is
them. It's It's not about debate. Oh,
I'm wrong. You're wrong. T I have got
normal approaches. I have got messages.
I have I have where people have led me
on. I have had where people have tried
to take the piss out of me. It's there
in black and white
like the black and white cat. So your ar
your whole argument does not make any
[ __ ] sense when I've got the evidence
to back up what they have [ __ ] done.
Do you understand what I'm saying? So
and like the approaches they've even
been rude before, you know, in
approaches. So it's it's it's it's
quite simple to be honest with you. Um,
and um, I've seen where you've wrote
about how I need to work on myself. Now,
the irony of somebody that's got no
teeth telling somebody else that they
need to work on themselves, that doesn't
even make any sense, mate. Because if
you actually worked on your [ __ ]
self, you'd have some [ __ ] teeth in
your [ __ ] mouth. You know what I'm
saying? So, how you can try to tell me
that I need to work on myself, yet you
don't have any teeth? Like, what? I need
to work on myself because I've showed
these women being stuck up time wasters
taking the piss leading people on. That
means that I need to work on myself even
though I can back up everything that I
have said about them. I can literally
back it up in black and white. So I
don't understand the whole point of your
argument. It makes no sense. And you
know when you were saying that I need to take accountability.
Um, now do you actually know the
definition of accountability? Taking
accountability is when you've done
something wrong, when you've maybe stole
from a shop or maybe I don't know, you
might have cheated on someone and you
need to take accountability for your
actions. I don't need to take
accountability for me going around
trying to meet a woman and her acting
stuck up. I don't need to take
accountability for me getting a woman's
number and her leading my ass the [ __ ]
on, which I can prove. I assure you,
mate, there's no accountability for my
end that needs to be [ __ ] took. And
all of the times that I have been wrong
in the past, I've admitted I'm wrong.
When I'm wrong, I admit I'm wrong. I'm
not stubborn. But actually, watch what
you shown for [ __ ] once. Because I
feel like a lot of these people that
will continuously defend women the way
they defend women, they dismiss all of
your struggles. Like I've literally
shown people what they have done, you
know, like several several several times
and they still sit there and defend
them. It's it's [ __ ] crazy. Um, so I
mean that's I don't need to take
accountability for trying to speak to a
woman normally and then being stuck up a
lot of the time or them leading me on. I
don't need to take accountability for
being [ __ ] normal. Um and and I'll
have you know right that you know when
you were saying about how I need to work
on myself and ret.
Now fun fact a lot of when these
experiences happened I was going to the
gym. I had money have money had my own
house was traveling. I had my [ __ ] well
and truly put together probably more
than these more than most of these
[ __ ] women. Probably more than most
people to be fair. But that was just
because I was just in a fortunate
position to to to to be in. So I mean,
was I perfect? No. Was there room for
improvement? Yes. Because no one's
perfect. There's always room to [ __ ]
improve. But mate, I had my [ __ ]
together. I've got my [ __ ] together now,
that doesn't change the fact of these
bad experiences with [ __ ] women. Just
because someone does two more push-ups
in the gym than they're supposed to. It
doesn't mean these women in this country
are going to stop being stuck up
[ __ ] So, at the end of the [ __ ]
day, that's that's that as an example.
And you were saying about how you
getting a beard trim and you getting a
haircut is is not working on yourself.
Well, mate, let me tell you, it
definitely [ __ ] well is a form of
working on yourself because you, right,
working on your appearance is part of
working on yourself. It's like a [ __ ]
fat person, an obese person, right?
going to the gym and getting in shape.
They've worked on themsel. Yeah. Not
fully, but it's a form of working on
yourself. Just like when you work when
you work on your looks, it's a it's a
form of working on yourself, the inside,
your mental health, financially. There's
different parts of [ __ ] working on
your [ __ ] self, you [ __ ] idiot.
Um, and another thing is right um you
say about how um
you know if you failed with women over
and over and over again for years you
would think that you are the problem but
that's not quite correct is it? Because
I mean every single woman that I've got
with you have tried it on with. So, if I
really failed with women over the years,
right? How comes you've tried to get
with every single woman that I've slept
with? Like, you literally have stalked
every single woman that I've been with.
I have been with more women than you
have. Yeah. I have had sex more times
than you have. Just because I complain
about women and I don't lick their ass.
And I'm not a I I don't follow the trend
of licking women's asses for the sake of
licking women's asses, it doesn't mean
I've never had a woman, mate. Everyone
on women, everyone on YouTube has seen
me with women. I've been with more women
than you, right? Better looking women
than you and I've had sex more times
than you have. That's facts. Like, I'm
not even trying to sound immature.
That's facts. So, what reason would I
have to sit here and lie about women all
being the same? Because they are.
They're all the [ __ ] same. And if I
didn't think it, I wouldn't say it. And
if it wasn't true, I would have been
shown a long time ago it wasn't true. So
the whole argument does not make no
sense. You've got nothing to prove to
back up anything that you're saying is
right. I have got evidence to back up my
struggles and the [ __ ] I've gone through
with these [ __ ] which is why I'm
leaving, you know. So it's it's it's
that simple. And and again, you were
saying about how I've never had these
struggles with women. Yes, you have. You
have never been with a normal woman.
You've always been with disabled women.
And the fact that you've never ever
[ __ ] met a woman outside of a [ __ ]
[ __ ] dating app. Yes, you have had
these problems with women multiple
multiple multiple times. You are with a
[ __ ] disabled girl. Yeah, you
literally was on five dating apps. What
do you mean you've never had problems
with women? you're literally with a
disabled [ __ ] girl, you know, and and
like I said, don't even try to sit there
and say that you are happy with her and
reta t because you're [ __ ] not.
Because if you was happy with her,
you've tried to get with every single
woman that I have been with. So, it just
goes to show how insecure and unhappy
you really really are. So, don't even
try that [ __ ] Um, you know, so
you've you've never even been with a
normal woman ever. You've never even
been with a normal girl. What the [ __ ]
And you're saying about how you've never
struggled with [ __ ] women, yet you
was on five dating apps. You've
literally stalked all of my sloppy
seconds cuz you've never had sex
yourself. But no, you've never had
problems with women.
Okay, mate. Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah,
yeah. That that what a way to prove it
than you being with a disabled girl and
having to be on five paid dating apps,
but yeah, you've never struggled. So at
the end of the day, mate, before telling
people that they need to work on
themselves, you might want to work on
yourself and you might actually want to
learn the definition of accountability.
Yeah, it'll get you far in life. So
yeah, that's it. Done now.