Look at this. Greavves is going to
[ __ ] love this. Right. So, I was
speaking to this woman on Reddit from
America. She was the same age as me. And
I basically shared her uh I shared my
experiences with her and whatever. And I
said, you know, do you want to share
your experiences? Ret.
Literally, as soon as I showed women
leading me on, bam, she went at me
writing paragraphs, making excuses,
started being aggressive.
Accountability is a woman's worst
nightmare. Like we are literally
literally going to go back to that. And
this woman was completely fine.
Completely fine until I started showing
where women was in the wrong on purpose.
Yeah. These kinds of people exist. Look
at this [ __ ]
>> So, um I'm going to be straight with
you. Um you can [ __ ] off.
>> Look at that. They don't like
accountability. Look, I was showing her
multiple screenshots even though people
even, you know, where people on YouTube
didn't see it, right? And look, same old
excuse. Change their minds. Change their
minds. Change their minds. See, they
hate being wrong. They hate being
[ __ ] shown, right, that they've led
someone on or they've done something on
purpose. It's their worst nightmare. I'm
going to do a video, right, um, on this
[ __ ] later. Look at this [ __ ] All
because I showed women leading me on.
Bam. This feminist started attacking me.
An undercover feminist, right? She
masked it well at first, you know,
acting like she was, you know, um,
normal and whatever, mate. They did not
change their [ __ ] mind, [ __ ]
Yeah, I'll put the whole screenshot on
YouTube again. They didn't change their
[ __ ] mind. People that have not
met someone don't change their [ __ ]
mind, bro. Yeah. [ __ ] absolute feminist. [ __ ] loser.