Yo. Okay, so this is going to be my last
response to Joseph Ferrar, and I
absolutely mean it. Um, unless uh he
agrees to uh meet me, which let's face
it, he can't even talk on the panel.
He's that petrified. Um, so anyone who's
watching this, I wouldn't uh hold your
breath on the idea that this guy is ever
going to say anything to anyone's face.
Um, yeah. What makes me laugh is he
can't talk on a panel, but then he tries
to tell me that I will do nothing and
how people can't take my word serious.
Strong, strong dose of projection. That
is definitely definitely definitely. Um,
and somebody went on um his community
post earlier and said about how um yeah,
PJ wants to meet you in January and then
he turned around and said that sounds
gay to me. What? Somebody telling you
about your nonsel loving ugly self to
your face is is gay. I'm not so sure.
And why are you making fun out of the
word gay? I mean, you are gay. Uh
nonslegs is your boyfriend. Um I
literally said this to you um yesterday.
Uh you've got the same similarities.
You're both obsessed with me. You're
both jealous of me. You're both keyboard
warriors that will never ever meet
anyone. You both have got a lot of
energy behind a keyboard. And let's not
forget you both have got fat, ugly,
stinking misses. Um, which let me tell
you one thing right now. In the 28 years
of me being alive, I have never ever
resorted to anything as fat and ugly as
what Joseph Ferrar was with and what not
is with. So they they definitely
definitely definitely are boyfriends.
Um, and they definitely need to get
married so they'd know all about being
gay. Um, and also, um, the other thing
is, uh, whenever I used to go at
non-legs, um, for, uh, you know, being
the virgin that he is, you'd always get
Joseph Ferrar to his rescue. Oh, he
can't be. He's got a girlfriend. He done
it multiple times and we're like, all
right, bro. Jesus Christ, get out of his
[ __ ] [ __ ] hell. So, I mean, you
are gay with your boyfriend. Um, so
that's another dosha projection right
there. So, anyways, we'll get into this.
So, I was live yesterday morning. Um,
and basically I was in a bad mood as it
was. Uh, because believe it or not,
these self-reflecting fat, ugly people
on here that was lonely this Christmas,
they don't bother me. I was I was in a
bad mood from something else. And this
Joseph Fer commented and I said,
"Listen, mate, if you've got anything to
say, right, say to my face, uh, I've
caught you talking [ __ ] behind my back
um, multiple times. Uh, last week I was
on my mom's phone. LJ was live. Laney's
sub to LJ. big up Laney and I see this
Joseph Fro saying that I'm this I'm a
sad bastard. I said, "Listen, mate. I
will make it easy for you. I will travel
all the way to Yorkshire today and I'll
give you the chance to say anything you
want to say to my face." Um, and I gave
him the same offer last week also. And
he weren't having none of it. He tried
changing the subject. Uh, he tried
bringing money up again even though I
beat him beaten him at the money game
multiple times. So, what he really means
with this evidence is he will do nothing
ever. Um, I mean, [ __ ] me. I' I travel I
I I literally offered to literally
travel four or five hours away. Um, but
to be honest with you, think looking
back on it now after all of these years,
it seems a trend with these Northerners,
Bomb, Trevor Dawson, Kevin Murphy, all
fat, all ugly, all whenever you go to
them, they never show up. It seems to be
a a a common thing with these
northerners which makes me laugh because
Joseph Farra always used to say you know
if that poster thing about someone being
a nons happened up north um the people's
windows would get smashed their houses
would get broken into. I don't think so
mate going by your activity being scared
of talking on a panel scared of meeting
me even though I gave you several
several uh opportunities that I would
travel up there and you didn't want any
of it. I think you northerners are a
bunch of [ __ ] houseses if if I must say
so myself, but I mean don't don't take
offense to that. Um and then yeah, I
just wanted to say uh that that's that
basically and then I went on your um
your channel and uh you were saying
about how uh we laugh. Um I assure you
you fat ugly people on this community
don't laugh at anything. I mean you
people was lonely this Christmas. You've
got no friends outside of YouTube.
Joseph Fro, you and these other people,
this whole YouTube is your bummy [ __ ]
life. I assure you, you don't laugh at
anything because in your in your case,
in in your situation, there is no
laughing matter. So, I mean, you can
keep pretending that you laugh at me,
but I mean, I I don't think someone
that's younger, better looking than you,
is anything to laugh at. I mean, you
would laugh at yourself if you was to
laugh at anyone else. Being a [ __ ]
house, not being able to talk on a
panel, um, showing fake wins. And
another thing is you were saying about
how um, you know, I shouldn't get
jealous and jealousy is not a good look.
You need to tell yourself that you're
the one that's jealous of me. You're the
one with 30 jeans. You're the one with a
200lb phone. You're the one showing off
a pension that you can't even touch.
Trust me, everything points to you being
jealous of me. I am not jealous of some
fat, ugly, wrinkly slob that shows fake
wins. Now, let me make this clear to
you. Uh, one more time, I have got more
money than you. Yeah. Yeah. I've got
more money than you. Yeah. Just because
I have caught you being a bullshitter
and showing fake wins does not mean I'm
jealous. I'm younger than you. I'm
better looking than you. I've got more
than you will ever have in life. I've
got more money than you. Right? Someone
can go on a gambling channel. And then
you were saying about how why does why
do why do I have to show losses? Because
it's a gambling channel. Your channel is
a gambling channel and you're not
showing any losses cuz apparently you
don't lose. Uh because it's a gambling
channel to answer your question. Um I
have got more money than you and I can
call you out on your [ __ ] if it is
[ __ ] and that does not mean that I
am [ __ ] jealous. You know, you are
putting up fake wins. Yeah, that's
that's what you are doing. Simple. Like
that's does not not does not make me
jealous telling you what you're doing.
I'm younger. I'm better looking. I don't
need to be jealous of a fat 40-year-old
slob that can't talk in the panel. It
doesn't doesn't make sense. It doesn't m
does not make any [ __ ] sense at all.
You know, how does that make sense? Why
would I be jealous of some old wrinkly
fat [ __ ] fart? It It does not make
any sense. You're probably not even
[ __ ] mobile, you [ __ ] geek, you know.
So, um yeah, no one's no one's jealous
of you, mate. I I I I assure you. Um
people can tell you about you being full
of [ __ ] and only putting um you know,
fake wins up and not be jealous of you.
Um, that very much can happen, mate. I'm
pretty sure there's loads of people that
tells stop and step that he doesn't win
all the time and they've probably got
more money than him. A lot of these
people. So, how does that make sense?
So, anyone that calls you out on your
[ __ ] is jealous. What? Jealous of a
what? 250 win, bro. I've got more money
than you. I don't know how many times
I've had to say to you that I've got
more money than you and it doesn't
process in your [ __ ] brain. Then you
try to tell other people that they're
jealous. Jealous of what? a wrinkly old
slob with no life. Come on, bro. Come
on. Where Where would the jealousy
really come from? You know, you showing
fake whims trying to get other people to
gamble, mate. I know what you're about.
It's so obvious what you're about. You
know, it's you're boring, mate. You're
really, really boring. Anyways, right.
If you've got anything to say further,
right, we can arrange a time and a place
to meet. Until then, I'm done with you.
Simple. You're not going to get another
response out of me. Um, and that's it.
[ __ ] off. Get a life. You and your
boyfriend nodd legs, right? It's almost 2026
and yeah, that's it.