Hey madness.
Yeah, I'm back, bro.
Timmy just motivated me to come back.
Okay, that's okay.
I need to fill this. Most my mugs are up
here to be fairy.
It's not good, is it, lad?
Was I expecting it?
To be honest with you,
I kind of was to be fair, bro. I kind of
I kind of was,
but I already like didn't really care at
the end. Anyways,
but kind of
50/50, bro, because
yeah, is what it is.
I think this is the worst day I've ever
had for a very, very long time, bro.
Bad, bad, bad. Hey baby.
Bro, what the [ __ ] is that all about?
Bro, leave you on Instagram.
I kind of did expect it. I kind of did. But
yeah, I know what uh you know,
people are kind of like, you know, so
we got [ __ ] royally today.
We got [ __ ] royale like in like in
Burger King, bro. It
What the [ __ ] bro?
What the actual [ __ ]
I messaged them saying, "Listen, if you
don't want to talk to me anymore, just
say you don't want to talk to me in it."
As simple as that. I don't I don't
really give a [ __ ] You know what I'm saying? Like,
you know what I mean?
I just say, bro, that like basically
Yeah, that's the same thing. So, I've
been [ __ ] royally, bro.
So, now we're back. Now we're actually
back in we're actually in a worse position.
You know, I was actually saying to my
friend in the Netherlands, I was in such
a good mood yesterday, bro.
I was in a sick mood yesterday. Like, a
good mood. I was actually in a good
mood, bro. I made my bed, done my
washing and [ __ ]
[ __ ] man. That's not good, is it?
What? Oh my god. Am I supposed to know
everything to do, bro?
Am I supposed to know everything, bro?
Am I a magician, bro? on my [ __ ]
Yeah, my friends like, "Oh, it's exams."
No, it's not. Cuz they would have
deleted your number, Greasy. They
wouldn't have deleted.
Now, you understand what I'm saying now,
ain't it, bro? About like people. You
you you understand what I'm saying about
people ignoring this joef and stuff. Are
you actually you are you listening to
what I'm saying?
I can get I can get into it so much,
bro. Now, now something now something
else is over with this guy that made me
money. Do you see why people don't
bother with people, bro?
Do do you kind of see now, lad? So,
my point's been proven again, lad. Yeah. Um, yeah.
Glad you find it funny, Greasy, cuz I [ __ ] don't.
I'm glad you [ __ ] do, but cuz I [ __ ] don't. [ __ ] man. Sure
would have probably made a difference if
my phone did get [ __ ] robbed to be fair. So,
do you think all the disappear on someone?
Nah, he doesn't know who she is.
Nah, he doesn't know who she is. And
that person in the picture isn't her. N
he doesn't know who she is. He doesn't
even know her name, lad.
He doesn't know her. Doesn't know her
name. Doesn't know anything about her.
So, wouldn't possible. And she hasn't
blocked me either.
H this person I was speaking about, bro.
By stick, that person isn't her in the
photo, bro. No one knows what she looks
like. No one knows her name. So, they
would have never found her. And she
didn't block me either. So, she hasn't
blocked me. She would have blocked me,
but she hasn't. So, um yeah. Yeah.
Nah. Nah. No. It doesn't add up cuz she
would have blocked me. He doesn't know
her. He doesn't know her. He doesn't
know her name. He's never seen a picture
of her. Impossible, bro.
No, it doesn't add up cuz he doesn't
know her name. He doesn't know what she
looks like. cuz she's not on social
media. He would have never found her.
No, he hasn't. They don't know her. They
don't know who she is.
No, she hasn't even blocked me either,
bro. She's um
No, she hasn't even blocked me either.
No, I just went to [ __ ] I scrolled down
and she's [ __ ] deleting my [ __ ] number
like Oh, they blocked me in it. No, I
messaged them. They didn't block me, bro.
No, they ain't blocked me. They just
like the profile picture is gone, but
like there was two ticks. I'm thinking
like, are you good? Like,
what's going on, man? Like, call me in
it. They don't mind. We've been speaking
for like [ __ ] god knows how many
days. They ain't blocked me. They would
have just blocked you in it.
No, they don't know who she is. Trust
me, they don't know her name. They don't
know what she looks like. Yeah, she
deleted my number. Yeah, that's what I'm
saying. And I'm thinking, "What the [ __ ] bro?"
No, she didn't. She doesn't know me, bro.
She didn't know my name. She didn't know
nothing about me. No, she hasn't blocked
me. And she would have blocked me. If
she Google my socials, she would have blocked me.
I got [ __ ] royally, bro. Today.
Seriously, fire stick. I got [ __ ] royally.
No, she didn't search up nothing, bro.
She doesn't know my name. She doesn't
know me. Just like most of these people,
they don't know me. WhatsApp's inc WhatsApp's encrypted. So,
um, yeah, we got [ __ ] Roy. I think
it's funny to laugh at, lad,
but he doesn't know her, bro.
Bro, he doesn't know her. He doesn't
know her. He doesn't know what he she
looks like. He doesn't know anything
about her. No one knows her. Just like
no one knew that 19year-old.
Yeah. He doesn't even know who she is.
Bro, that person. Listen, bro. No one on
this community has ever found anyone
since USA is he. And that was years ago.
And that's cuz I doxed her. Anyways, so
yeah, Fire Stick. I basically said, um, yeah.
I could get drunk today, bro. I'm not
going to lie to you, bro.
I've actually got anx I've actually got
anxiety today, bro. And I don't normally
get anxiety, bro.
I really, really don't. But I have it today.
Is it Tim? Is it? Yeah.
Yeah. I think today I do, bro. Yeah.
See, so this is the thing. Fire stick.
Like this is what I was trying to
explain to you. Yeah. When we was
talking for 6 hours, like me personally,
like it has annoyed me a bit, but kind
of like cuz I knew the situation, I
stopped caring. But you got to
understand, brother. Like it's like what
we was talking about. Like it's like
what we was talking about before,
brother. Yeah. Like you can't do right
and you can't do wrong. You try to meet
them too fast, there's a problem. You
delay it, they [ __ ] you over anyways.
Like me personally,
uh I didn't think I didn't think they
were going to [ __ ] me over because of
the way that they were messaging me. But
like at the same time, I was prepared
for it at the same time.
But I just thought because obviously
sending me 23 messages and stuff, they
weren't going to [ __ ] me. I thought like
at I thought I thought at like the very
um at the very like most they were just
going to friend zone you which it would
have been fine. Well, it would have been
fine but [ __ ] better. I didn't know
to be didn't expect it but I was
prepared for it to be fair. The last
message I sent was well I messaged her
today. I said like what's going on? But
before that, it was just, "Oh, I'm doing
this. I'm doing that." Uh, she asked me
what I was doing. I told her what I was
No, V hasn't spoke to any girl. He
doesn't know her,
bro. Bro, V doesn't know any girl I'm speaking to.
He doesn't know any girl I'm speaking
to, bro. Hand on my heart. Even
Greavvesy doesn't know her. No one knows
what she looks like. No one knows her
name. No one knows where she lives. He
doesn't know anyone. If he did, he'd put
her up. Simple as that. He's not
speaking to anyone, bro. You can't find
people on something that's encrypted
like that. But anyway, it's fine.
It's fine, bro. It's all good, man. No worries. Yeah,
he hasn't posted proof of anything.
Let me have a look.
Let me see.
No, they're not talking to her. They
don't know. Anyways, let me see. I'll
tell you if it is her
and she would have blocked you anyways.
Where is this guy?
Nah, they're not speaking to her. They
don't know her.
They don't know her. This woman on
Instagram he's put up, I don't even know
who the [ __ ] that is. So, they can't
even find people on my Instagram,
you know? Trust me. If they if they if
they found her five sticks, she would
have blocked me, bro. There wouldn't
have been no two ways about it. I would
have just been blocked.
I would have been blocked, lad. Just
like straight blocked. Um,
yeah, that's not her in the picture.
No one's ever found um people from my
WhatsApp, bro, ever.
So, yeah. Um, but seriously, lad.
Um, she hasn't blocked me. She's deleted
my number, but she hasn't blocked me. No. Baby Cakes,
I've already messaged her. She hasn't blocked me.
Anyways, we know she hasn't blocked me
anyways. So, we're not we're not getting
into this, bro. Because we already know
she hasn't blocked me and we already
know V. So, just stop talking [ __ ]
Yeah, just stop talking [ __ ] bro.
Um, but yeah, uh, fire stick, lad. Um, yeah. No.
Yeah, bro. It doesn't matter how long
you speak to um someone fire stick.
They'll [ __ ] you over anytime, bro. Anytime, bro.
It's just sad that, you know, this is
the society that we're living in. But
that's the way it is, I'm afraid.
No, I thought they would have just maybe
like friend-zoned you. Maybe.
Of course he's not ruining my life, bro.
He doesn't know anyone I speak to. And
I'm not repeating it again. I've already
said he doesn't know anyone I'm speaking
to. If you want to think he does, then
keep thinking that, bro.
We know what it is. You know what it is.
You know what's happened. So that's it.
We're not getting into these stupidness.
We're not getting into this stupidness, bro.
He doesn't know anyone I'm speaking to.
So it's as simple as that. So anyways, um
I just don't understand it. Fire stick
to be honest with you bro
said they were busy
I was going to message them maybe next
week and I just see their pictures gone
I'm thinking oh [ __ ] I've been blocked
message them there's two ticks what the
[ __ ] bro what's even a point you know
it's just um
so that's enough evidence now to suggest
that you don't need to speak to people
for pe for long periods of time they're
not going to think twice about [ __ ]
your ass over
so I mean that's that is solid.
That is solid, bro.
That's solid evidence now.
I mean, they could get back to you, but
okay, whatever, Smokey B, bro. We're
ignoring you anyways, lad.
Okay, bro. Whatever. We're ignoring you,
bro. We're not doing this keyboard
warrior [ __ ] We're talking serious [ __ ] here. But what
they're saying is uh
yeah, people could just be busy and
whatever and stuff, bro. Yeah. Yeah.
Okay. Whatever, bro. You've said all of
this. No one knows any woman I'm speaking to.
You don't know any woman that I'm
speaking to. But yeah, keep telling
yourself that you do. keep putting fake
women up. We're going to time this guy
out anyways. Yeah. For a little bit.
So, I don't I don't understand five
stick what would have caused it
to be to be honest with you, bro.
Oh [ __ ] I need to reset my [ __ ] phone now.
are close to packing up, lad.
Um, I think that'll be the full thing, Grezy.
And then we can say we've actually been
[ __ ] Literally 2 minutes to midnight.
This phone's going to pack up
and it will be [ __ ] four things
instead of three.
Imagine, bro. You just open the phone
and it splits in half.
It will happen one day. Hopefully not
today, though. I don't think my heart
could take any more [ __ ] today, lad.
Yeah. So, um, what I was saying, bro,
is, uh, yeah, they're not going to
message back cuz if they were going to
message you back, they would have
deleted your number, but then at the
same time, they haven't blocked you.
No, hopefully my phone doesn't break.
They wouldn't have blocked They would
have blocked you.
Fire. What do you What's going on, bro?
I was nothing but nice to this person.
And look, I've been [ __ ] over again.
I don't know why someone would [ __ ]
someone over, bro.
Like that. But yeah, I've been [ __ ]
Yeah, [ __ ] man.
That is weird, bro. Yep.
Yeah, pretty much.
This is why I don't date, lad. Why
stick? This is why I don't date.
Someone was going to message me. They
would have deleted your number.
I kind of I kind of saw it coming, bro.
But I thought it was going to be more like Friendzones
days ago, bro. Days ago. She said, "Oh,
she was busy and [ __ ] like with exams
and that and she has exams." She told me
the date she had exams and whatnot.
So, and she messaged me depressed and
that. So I thought, "Oh, I don't think
they were lying. I don't think they were
they weren't genuine. I don't think they weren't genuine."
So I just kind of thought, "Okay, [ __ ] it." Yeah, man.
So, we got [ __ ] a lot today, didn't we?
But that was meant to happen. All that
[ __ ] that happened today was just meant
to happen. I feel like it's meant to
happen. You know what I mean? Stuff like
that. Fire thing.
I reckon, yeah, it's meant to happen.
That kind of [ __ ] man.
I know. I don't know because
they just broke up with someone and whatnot.
They probably got back with their ex.
Typical, isn't it? No, I said I think
that's the worst that would have
happened, but no, they've
they've uh done it. They've done me dirty. So,
no, I think that's the worst that would
happen. But yeah,
stop there, didn't it? Oh, well,
I woke up to like 23 messages.
They said, "Oh, we're not I'm not going
to ghost. I'm not going to ghost. I'm
not going to ghost. I'm not going to
ghost. I'm not going to ghost."
And you did. Yeah, probably.
And I'm not even going to tell you what
she told me. Um um
that's what happens. You see,
I'm not going to tell you what her ex
did. She told me what her ex did, and I
was like, "Oh no." Here we go again. Yeah.
Yeah. It's got to be that X, mate. I reckon. Yep.
Nah. Nothing to do with rape. No, it's not that.
Cheating on her and had a kid with someone else.
It's probably worse to be fair. Yeah.
It's all good anyways, bro. Like, stay
lost at the end of the day.
You just got Yeah.
Yeah. Like most of them do, bro. Most of
them talk about their ex.
Most of them do. I don't think I've ever
met someone that doesn't talk about their ex.
Yeah. So, we did get really [ __ ] today. Agree. Yeah.
Yeah. And they've I've I've had it
before where I'm touching just USA
Izzy's boobs and she said, "Oh, my ex
said I had nice boobs, too." What a turn off.
I've had it where I've approached a
19year-old. Oh, my ex was called Peter.
Yeah, it's happened many times. I don't
care about your [ __ ] ex. Yes.
I took out on Laney today cuz she's kind of selfish.
She's kind of selfish, bro. If you think
about it, she didn't show no remorse
when I've been scammed out of [ __ ] money.
Yeah, I know. I know.
I've had it before where I said, "Oh my
I've had it millions of times. I just
can't remember exactly the exact
points." Like with the X thing. I've had
it multiple times.
I've had it a few times, bro.
You just said try ring up the bank. I
tried to ring up the bank. They weren't having it.
What can I do?
No, they've definitely deleted my number because
their Christian symbol's gone.
Unless they put everything per private,
but I don't know.
Yeah, obviously. Yeah. Um,
that is weird to
Oh, [ __ ] hell, bro.
I ain't even going to give any of that money back.
Well, what I can say
what I can say, Grezy, I can I can
confidently say what a [ __ ] day I've had.
Just like Zippy in it.
Ah, I try to not laugh, but you just
have to, bro, if you're saying stuff like that.
What a [ __ ] day I've had.
It's true though, is it, bro? If you
think about it, he woke up, bro. He woke
up like by the cereal box in it. He
lifted his head up and he was like,
"What a [ __ ] day I've had."
Kind of relieved that it's over and I
don't need to stress anymore about this
person if they're going to reply and
whatever. Like, I'm kind of relieved it's over
to be fair. It's kind of like a relief
cuz it was a lot of stress, you know,
wondering if people was going to reply
back and if I was going to get [ __ ]
over again. It was kind of a relief.
Yeah. I don't know why they would have
deleted my number though.
Just doesn't make sense.
How much you How much money you got?
Fire stick. You got any money, bro?
Nah, I've got pictures of her. I'm not
putting her up. So,
that man's going to love this. I
messaged him. I told him what happened.
He's going to love it. You just know he is.
Maybe like£1,400. Maybe
1.4. Maybe something like that.
This isn't good.
600 until when?
Don't you think it's kind of shitty what
they done though, bro?
Why is the point even speaking to me for
that long if you was just going to do that?
I can tell you exactly how long I've
been speaking to them for. Since the
6th of February. Yeah.
Yeah, she was all right. Yeah, she was
she was actually Yeah,
I just said if you want to talk, just
tell me you want to talk and [ __ ] Like
we can call if you want, man. Like, do
they suffer from anxiety and [ __ ] but
really done me dirty like that, bro?
Really done me dirty.
Yeah. Christian is he [ __ ] us. Steven
Howard [ __ ] us royally, bro.
But I wonder why though. This is the
whole mind. This is the whole mind game thing now.
I want answers, bro.
This could get dangerous, lad.
No. [ __ ] I went down my contacts cuz
obviously I messaged her. Her pictures
disappeared. I thought, "Oh, she blocked
me." But she never she just deleted my
number. I said like, "What's what's
going on, man?
There's no way there's coming. There's
no way there's You're coming back from
that, mate. Someone's lead your number.
They've deleted your number. It's as
soon as that. They've obviously deleted your number.
No, he doesn't know who I'm speaking to.
I'm I'm going to say this one more time, bro. Um,
no one knows who who, bro, no one knows
any woman I'm talking to. That's the
last I'm going to say that, bro.
Otherwise, I wouldn't be confused, would I?
Bro, he doesn't know anyone I'm speaking
to, bro. All the women I speak to are on
WhatsApp, an encrypted site. Bro, no one
knows her name. Not even Greavvesy knows
her name. Me and Greavvesy speak on
Instagram. He doesn't know anything
about her. He doesn't even know her. He
doesn't even know the first letter of her name.
Yeah, it's been really bad today, bro.
What do you think? What do you think it is, bro?
just doesn't make sense.
Yeah, it's hopeless, bro. In this
country is proper hopeless.
It's proper proper proper hopeless in it.
Never sent her a dick picture. Never
spoke about sex. Never said anything weird.
Didn't do anything wrong, bro. That's
what I'm saying. You might as well do
things wrong. This what I'm trying to
say to you. You might as well do things
wrong. you might as well be a weirdo, bro.
Cuz you're going to get treated the same way,
whether you're normal, whether you're um
you might as well just be a [ __ ]
freak, bro. You probably you probably
get more respect for it to be fair.
But we there's such a problem, bro.
There's such a problem with us trying to
meet someone in four or five days. Well,
look, you spoke to someone for almost a
month. They have no problem with [ __ ]
you off, [ __ ] you over.
I'm going to call them tomorrow, bro. If
they haven't responded by tomorrow, I'm
going to call them.
And you know what annoys me about these
women? Fire stick. I didn't mention it yet. Now,
you know, I don't know if this is just
you, bro, but she was saying about how
she wants her man to be this, she wants
her man to be that, she wants her man to
be this, she wants the fairly high standards.
But I'm thinking, bro,
was any of your exes like that? Do you
have all of these high demand demands
when it was your exes?
Why all of a sudden now
you're having these? And it's and it's a
lot of people. I've I've noticed that as
well to be honest. They they have these
expectations. I'm thinking was did you
have them same ones for your ex? Clearly
you didn't, bro.
You know what I'm saying? Do they have
to be this? Do they have to be that? Do
they have to be this? Do they have to be that? You're just
You're just [ __ ] bro. It's as simple as that. >> Yeah.
>> I don't know if it was only me.
cuz I said no dick pictures. I just told
you I didn't send dick pictures. I
didn't do anything wrong.
I didn't say anything wrong. I didn't do
Grieves seen the conversation. He seen
most of this, bro. I can send you more
if you want, Grievy.
I can send you more. Nothing out of line. Um,
nothing. Nothing out of line. No sex
talk, no nothing, bro. Cuz I weren't
interested in that. Uh but anyways,
[ __ ] her, bro. It
she said she's just going to be focusing
herself and that,
but she said that she's going to meet
me, bro. She said she'd never ghost. And
then she said she was going to meet me and
but she never. So there you go.
You really think I'd go into bookies and
smash coke on machines? Greasy.
>> Yeah. Everybody knows that you're a crazy [ __ ]
Yep. That was scaring me as well to be fair.
But why would you go back with your ex
when he's cheated on you and had a kid with someone?
No. No. She still ghosted me. No, no,
no. She did still ghost me because she
said that we was going to be talking
properly after her exams. So, she did
ghost me. She deleted her number and she disappeared.
No, she's she was she the last thing she
done was ask me a question. She ghosted,
bro. It's as simple as that. She ghosted.
She ghosted, lad.
She did ghost.
Yeah. Nah, it's too late, bro.
Go back with your ex that treats you
like [ __ ] and has a baby with someone else.
No, she ghosted. Um, Grezy, she ghosted.
Oh, we're going to be talking. I didn't
message her again. The last time the
last messages were uh
the last time he messaged was the 17th
and I thought oh I don't want to message
her again. She might be busy with her
exams and her picture was still showing.
So I was going to message her the next
week and say oh let's meet up now on it.
But then when her picture disappeared
I'm thinking what the [ __ ] Yeah.
Bro, she ghosted.
Yeah. Simple as that. She ghosted. Oh, yeah.
So, is there any point going out even
speaking to anyone anymore? Me thinks
not. Me thinks not.
No, me thinks not, lad.
Is there a point in even speaking to anyone anymore?
Look at this woman. She hasn't replied
to my message, but she's changed her photo.
Oh, no. She didn't change her photo. But yeah, still.
Is there a point in even speaking to
people anymore? I don't really think so, lad.
No, obviously I don't.
Just the same old [ __ ] then, is it? I
can't believe I got scammed by that
casino though, bro. Yeah.
Yeah, that X thing has been brought up a
couple of times.
Yeah, it has happened quite a few times
to be fair.
I can't remember exacts, but it has
happened. It's definitely happened.
I just wait for that Lad Brooks account to reopen.
I got scabbed.
You got £600. Until when? Buy a stick.
Until when, lad?
In love with somebody that cheats on you
and has a child with someone else. Huh?
These people never learn, bro, do they? Yeah.
I can't believe I scammed that.
Nah, Mr. B. Them army [ __ ] were
laughing at us, mocking us.
Oh, yeah. I tried to go to the cinema
today to get a pickix and they wouldn't
let me up. Yeah.
No, I'm I'm just going to change the
password on it. You can't ban You can't
ban your account. They won't close it.
Um, I'm just going to have to change the
pot. I won't play on it ever again.
Clearly, bro, they scam me.
They scam me, bro. So,
yeah, I tried to get a pick a mix today.
They won't let me up. I just got [ __ ] royally today.
Yeah, this message again. I said, "Yo,
what the [ __ ] Still a block me [ __ ] bro."
>> Yeah, exactly. But don't worry, I'll
never go back on anyways. I'll change
the password. I'll get my mom to change
the password. Yeah, I'll ring her tomorrow. Bro,
she's getting a [ __ ] lot. Remember
when Casside Mark said that? You know, you
you're getting a [ __ ] lot, mate.
You're getting a [ __ ] lot. Remember that?
Yeah, I do. Don't do Do you know
remember that Seaside Mark video? years
and years and he was he was clenching
his fist. He said, "What you done to me?"
Monty was on Timmy's today, ain't it? Um, Grezy,
what do you think is a decent amount of
money you should have? buy stick like 1,00100 1200.
Yeah. And I'm trying to support her and
I want to support her.
Yeah. And that's why I was supporting her.
Yeah. She's got anxiety and she's an
emotional wreck, which is why I was
supporting her and trying to help her.
We're laughing at you. Mocking you.
Was laughing at you. Ma.
Yeah, she's she's she's she's an
emotional wreck and I'm trying to
support her. So why what the [ __ ] bro?
I said if you ever need to talk to
anyone, you can talk to me.
You know I'm here and [ __ ] bro. Yep.
How much do you get a month? Fire stick.
I get about 1,200.
I'm on some money if I'm even going to
get it. Probably not.
Think we just need to put today behind
us, bro, and just kind of move on.
We got [ __ ] royally, bro.
Royale today. I think we just put it
behind us now, bro. What st?
See, I'm upset cuz I got scammed. It's
not cuz I lost 100. If I lost it, then I
would have been like, I lost it. I got scammed, bro.
What am I kind of thinking, why have
they reversed it? And £150, bro, is £150.
I would have paid for a light out, nice haircut.
But I said to her, "If you ever need to
talk, message me and stuff." I weren't
even expecting anything from her, bro. I
really wasn't greedy.
Look at all of these messages. [ __ ] me, bro.
Yeah, that's a bit annoyed me that they scam me. Yeah.
Do you don't you think it's a bit unfair, Grezy? Yeah,
bro. There's nothing weird in the messages.
There's so many messages, bro.
There's like so many messages. So many
bro. There's so many messages, bro. It's
probably the longest conversation I've
ever had. So, you know,
bro, there's so many, bro. There's so
many. But it's just normal chat. Most of
it is just normal chat.
Most of it is just normal chat, bro.
It's just like
I can't read.
I didn't freak her out, bro. I don't
need you to assess anything, lad. Right.
I've been talking to people for years,
and if I knew I'd done something wrong,
I know I'd done something wrong, bro.
They're so long, bro. These messages are so long.
No, didn't ask about baby. She said,
"Oh, do you like kids?" This was when we
first messaged. The first day we
messaged the first day. And then she
said, "Oh, do you like kids?" And I
said, "Yeah." And she said, "Oh, do you
want kids?" I said, "Maybe." I said,
"What do you think our kids would look
like?" She said, "For [ __ ] sake,
probably you. You've got great
features." That was the first day. And
then we spoke for like 3 weeks after
that. So that's the only thing that was
said. That was three weeks ago.
And then we speaking like every day at
one point all day every day and nothing
weird was said.
Nothing sexual at all.
Nothing sex. Bro, you don't need to ask
me if I've done this. I've done nothing
wrong, bro. Otherwise, I would tell you
I done something wrong.
Why are you trying to make this about me, bro?
They're [ __ ] They're [ __ ]
Whether you was weird, whether you was
normal, whether you tried to meet them
the met the same day, whether you tried
to meet them a month later, they're
[ __ ] They're just [ __ ]
You need to stop putting emphasis on me, bro.
Yeah, but I know. I get what you're
saying, bro. But like, you don't need to
ask them questions, do you, bro? Come on.
You don't need to ask questions, bro,
because it's silly. Because why would
anyone do that?
It's okay if you're just messaging a
random person on on Instagram and not
someone you've approached, bro. Why you
Why would you do that? Why would you
[ __ ] it up? It don't make sense. So,
yes, she was just saying, "Oh, like
you're good-looking and shit." Um
we were just like um
we were just talking mad like stuff in it
pretty much. Yeah,
I'm going to we'll speak more next week. Yeah, right.
I said that you were I said that you're cute, too.
I just said, "Oh, you're cute as well." basically done.
She asked me my body count as well.
She's asked me stuff like my body count.
I said my body count was three
obviously cuz I'm not going to tell her
it's [ __ ] seven, am I? Six or seven.
Well, excluding the escort. So, I just
said, "Oh, free in it." People don't
need to know that stuff, lad.
And that's another thing, Grevy, they
should if they're not interested in like
dating that, why they asking your body
count and [ __ ]
Why are they asking your body count?
Why they you understand what I'm saying, bro? Like,
you know, why are they asking your body count, bro?
I know they don't count. So, my body
count is seven.
There you go. So, my body count is seven.
So, why they asking your body count, you know?
Yeah, but but if she's not looking to
date me, why is she asking me questions?
That's what I'm saying.
Well, I'm not like her ex, but
obviously it's over now, isn't it?
That is [ __ ] up, bro.
Imagine that fire sticking and going out
and repeating the same process.
[ __ ] that for Game of Soldiers.
No, I'm good, bro.
I'm actually good, bro. Nope.
I did. I was knocking on the head, bro.
I was She was the last like result. This
was from weeks ago, bro. This person was
from weeks ago. I have I already knocked
it on the head, bro. I I been gave up.
I had been gave up, bro.
This was from weeks ago in it. And I
thought, oh, cuz they're talking and
stuff, I'll just give them the benefit
of the doubt. I I've gave it up, bro.
Cuz now it's getting worse, you know? I
can't remember the last time I've spoke
to someone this long and they've [ __ ]
me over again. I can't remember, bro.
Very long time.
So, that's why I gave up. That's why I
got away from it, lad.
That's why I gave up.
Then I was I had mood swings every day
for a long time after I gave up, you
know. And then I then it went away. Then
Antman's friend was doing my head in. He
owed me money. He was [ __ ] around. So
I went out for a drink. And then that's
how that this come about. This whole thing. Yeah.
So, I'm not I'm not looking to uh I'm
not looking to repeat the process again.
I'm not looking to repeat.
But that's what I'm trying to say to
you. Fire. You get people like Joe F and
Ricky Millington. Oh, you need to speak
to them for longer. Do I? Do I need to
speak to them for longer? Do I? Yeah. I
No, I'm not interested in an escort, bro.
This whole thing weren't about sex. It
was trying to meet someone that was normal.
I didn't even really care about the sex. So,
I was even about the sex, bro.
Yeah. The thing is, Fire Stick is you
got to understand, bro, is that they're
always going to make excuses for these
women. They're always going to think of something.
Talk longer. Oh, you're talking too
fast. Oh, you're coming on too strong.
You will never ever ever ever win. never
win. Whether you're right, whether
you're wrong, they'd always come up with
Cuz what's the excuse for this then?
I didn't send no dick pictures.
I was being [ __ ] normal, nice,
everything. So what? So what do you want
me to do? Go out again and repeat the
process? Nah, [ __ ] off. You can [ __ ]
right off, mate.
So yeah, that's that's that. You know
what? Maybe they'll message back tomorrow.
Doubt it though. Yeah, maybe.
But are your ex is your ex all of these
things that you're expecting from me?
Does he have to study? Does he have to
go to church? Clearly not. Clearly [ __ ] not.
So it just annoys me, bro. just talking
about it and all. This is why Ant-Man
left a long time ago.
This is why Ant-Man left.
Yeah. I said to her like, "Why have you
like deh Why have you deleted me?" I
said, "Like, what's up? Are you good or
like you stressed? Like
um like what's going on? If you don't
want to talk anymore, just stay basically."
Yeah. I said, "Why have you delete?" I said, "Yeah. No.
Yeah. I changed her name to Christian
Izzy, didn't I? Greasy.
So, you didn't know her name? Yeah. Yeah,
but then why are you giving your number?
Why are you giving people your number?
You are you are kind of indirectly you
are kind of indirectly leading people on
cuz you must know that you're never
going to get with me. You must knew that
if you if you was really off of dating,
right? You must knew that like if you
was into dating. Yeah.
Like you would have went back with your ex
even if that was a thing. You knew you
was never going to get with me. So they
are still kind of indirectly leading
you. They're playing games and
indirectly indirectly leading you on.
Yeah. All the people I meet is from approaching.
But yeah, it does seem to be the only
way. And it's not even about it being
the only way. Is how do you really want
to keep putting up with this [ __ ]
Do you really really want to keep
putting up with this [ __ ] for god knows
how many more years? That's a question
you got to ask yourself.
But yeah, I don't know why she's done
that, bro. You would have thought
somebody would have just blocked you in it.
No, you can't go for a week, mate. You
need to go for at least two weeks.
No, you need to go for at least two
weeks, lad. Not a week. Jet lag and [ __ ] in it. Yeah.
[ __ ] hell, bro. That's pissed me off
a little bit, bro.
Maybe her phone broke. No,
I'm going to I'm going to call her tomorrow anyways.
I said to Ant-Man, they they they don't
say they have a boyfriend here. And I
said I said to Antman, "They say they've
got a boyfriend here." He said, "I know
they [ __ ] do. That's why I left."
He said, "That's why I left."
It's true though, ain't it? Yeah.
And this guy was [ __ ] scared of flying.
Like so scared of flying, he said he
would never fly again.
That's how you know it was the right
thing to do. He was he swore he'd never
fly again. Coming back from Spain, he
said, "I'm never flying again." So, I
mean, you know, it's not even just him
as well. Loads of people live out there
now or they're living in Dubai and stuff.
It's bad. But people on Reddit say it's
easy. Fire stick.
They say dating is
I just kind of expected this person to
kind of be different and stuff, but no.
What do you think of the eyes? Where's it? [ __ ] Yeah. Cuz
it's kind of like a thing of now five
stick is [ __ ] even if you go out and
you get numbers, you know you're going
to get [ __ ] over.
You know you're just going to get [ __ ]
over. It's going to happen now, bro.
You will never know. You can't see if
someone's different unless you've met
them multiple times now. It's to a point
where it's like it doesn't matter who
comes across like this or who comes
across like that.
You are going to get [ __ ] over.
>> It's as simple as that. So, it's kind of
like it's just a waste of everyone's
time at this point, isn't it?
>> So, I don't know, bro. Yeah.
Do you want me to put nonsle legs as
bullies up? Greavves. I found them on
Facebook. Jackary and Miles from Glasgow.
You want me to put, you know, the bullies?
Well, the college bullies.
I was thinking of doing a community post about it.
See you later, Timmy. Hey, bro. We're
not entertaining Timmy, bro. We're not
entertaining Timmy anymore after the [ __ ]
what he done and [ __ ] No, I don't care,
bro. I don't watch his channel. He's
gay, lad. I don't care about him and
these gay little videos, bro.
I don't care about my stalkers. These
little weirdos. They need to come out
the closet, bro. I don't need to watch them.
[ __ ] them, lad. I don't give a [ __ ]
Nah. The only person I was up to was Timmy.
So, if I gamble on this Lad Brook site
when it reopens Fire Stick, I assume
they're not going to try and not pay me,
right? But I'm still kind of scared. I
think like they're not going to pay me again.
I reckon they might like but I don't
think they can in it.
No, I use my sister's account.
I use my sister's account on Ladbrooks.
No, I use my sister's account on Lad Brooks. [ __ ]
If this person doesn't mess me back, I'm
going to call them, bro.
I'm going to call them maybe tomorrow or something.
I'm Tibet. Nah,
no. I'm a [ __ ] wave in Tibet, bro. No.
No. Obviously not, lad. Yeah. Nah.
The [ __ ] were laughing at us. [ __ ] us.
Yeah, you're going to do all your money
in I reckon. Fire Stick, you're going to
end up doing all your money in, lad.
I can see it.
Guess what? Guess what? We are [ __ ]
bro. We are [ __ ]
I can't believe they I can't believe
they were able to just scam me like that.
Why? Fire stick. Them army [ __ ] were
laughing at us.
Them army [ __ ] were laughing at us.
Yeah, I'm just going to stay single now,
lad. Gave up with a date in here.
Like, do you watch Kings Clean's Fire Stick?
I kind of like I don't even like get
sex. I don't even get like horny
anymore, bro. I don't really care about
like the dating [ __ ] But obviously if
someone comes your way and they act they
could be normal and stuff like you're
not going to say no are you? But
I gave up properly like a very long time ago bro.
Yeah he can do that then can't he?
Oh you watch Kings clean five stick
you know who it isn't it?
Yeah, I'll put my camera on there. [ __ ]
Yeah, I will never run into that [ __ ]
lad. No, he will never he will never
give me trainers, bro. He will never
give me trainers cuz uh my trainers are fresh.
Oh, sorry about this.
My trainers are straight up fresh. Hey,
look at my top, bro. Big up.
What you call a sexy top l dad?
Kings clean. The guy that stops people
in the street and off and buys them trainers. Yeah.
laughing at you, Dusty. Mocking you.
Yeah, he did. Yeah,
probably I've been led on again. Yeah. damaged.
Nah, she might be asleep.
I can't see when she's online. She's
deleted my number. Um, no.
That's so weird. People don't normally
delete your number and then not block you.
Them [ __ ] were laughing at you. Mocking you.
That's so catchy, bro.
Laughing at you. Mocking you.
Remember that fight sick? Them army
[ __ ] were laughing at you, mocking you. fire stick.
They were laughing at you, mocking you.
What do you reckon the chances of
finding someone in this country? Fire stick.
Ah, very slim, lad. Very slim.
Bro, if it was a Thursday today or
Friday, I think I would have got on the piss, lad.
I don't really drink anymore. But I
think I would have
walking about. What? Nottingham. Yeah.
What we're losing Nottingham. Yeah, man.
So, yeah. Fire stick. But imagine that
was £500 I put in and I got it to 1,800
and they wouldn't let me take the money.
They're scammers, lad. scammers.
How can they do that, bro?
Yeah, those were the good days, bro.
they were good days. They were good
That football's a bit [ __ ] is it?
Can't believe that, bro. Yep.
I don't know what I'm going to do in the future, lad.
You know what I mean? Fire stick. As you
get older, you think of what you're
going to do in the future more. Is it
If SL was playing at home, that would
have been him, bro. That would have been him.
It would have been a nice cash out as
well if id bet online.
Hopefully this is a dream, bro. Put the
link up so if any want to join. Um
[ __ ] hell, bro.
You have to wager your own money.
Imagine having to wager your own money, bro. [ __ ] hell.
I'm really and truly [ __ ] in it.
It's only It's only down from now, lad.
It's only down from now. Yeah.
Them [ __ ] were laughing at you,
mocking you. Fire stick [ __ ] you.
You remember that account Steven that
used to come on and said Peter B don't
let them [ __ ] women win.
Don't let them [ __ ] women win.
There's account that used to come on
fire stick and used to say that. Don't
let them [ __ ] in women win. Yeah.
Hopefully this Christian Izzy messages
back tomorrow in it.
Wonder why she gone weird, bro.
No, she ain't removed the No, she
definitely deleted my number cuz her
stat her status had has been removed. Yep.
Yeah. Go away.
What do we do in life? What do we do in life, lad?
Where do we go?
What are we doing live? Yeah,
the people on Reddit say it will get
better. Steven Howard,
they say it gets better.
They say life gets better. Yeah.
Lady was sleeping all day. Yeah, bro.
Oh, I got [ __ ] over again, Tiger, by
another woman, bro.
I was speaking to someone for weeks.
They said they were busy with their
exams. We was voice noting every day.
And they just deleted my number. Didn't
block me deleting my number. Said, "Oh,
what's going on? You good?" Or like,
"Call me, whatever." Done.
Yeah. So not good, lad.
>> Yeah, it was really bad, bro. Yeah.
And uh I got scammed out of money today
from a casino. Yeah.
Uh, they owed me money and they didn't
give me it. They scammed me out of
money. I lost a football bet. What a
[ __ ] day I've had. Tiger.
What a [ __ ] day I've had, mate.
No, I've give up dating in this country,
bro. I'm done with it. I was already
done. I've already done I was already
done with it from months ago, lad.
I was already done with it from months
ago, lad. I'm I'm all right, bro. I'm good.
I don't want to deal with any more of
their [ __ ] They're all the same.
They'll never change.
No, I'm good, lad.
No, I'm good, bro. Rather you than me.
I'm not doing that again. I should have
to should have to go out and try again
to get lead on again. I'm not doing it again, bro.
And you can [ __ ] off, you virgin. You're
not coming in my hangouts. Bye-bye. So,
yeah, I'm not doing it again.
That's the worst thing. Why am I Why
would I want more bad experiences mixed with alcohol?
What's that going to achieve? The same
old the same old. The same old.
Be hung over.
What? Why am I going to do that, lad?
I won't do it again.
See, even though I'm depressed and that
I still brush my teeth cuz I kind of
have to. I don't want another cavity and [ __ ] So,
no, I gave Bro, Dusty, the last time I
went out before that was 3 months ago.
I gave up for 3 months. I missed all the
I missed all the events. Uh, New Year's
Eve, Boxing Day. I missed all of them, bro.
I'm [ __ ] done. There's a reason why I
went out last time and it's not an
excuse. Ant-Man's friend owed me money.
He was pissing me off. I thought, "Fuck
this." The hair was coming down my
ankles. I thought, "Let me just go out."
It ain't happening, bro. Trust me, it ain't happening.
So, yeah, you you don't want to go out
and meet a new girl. You want to you you
want to give the [ __ ] up, which is what
I already done. I already gave up to get
away from this. When I've given up when
I gave up with stuff in the past, I gave
up to get away from it.
I gave up because of these reasons, you know. So
that's that, bro. It's all good, man. a year.
Yeah, I think a year, which was last year.
No, I'm done with the dating in this
country. I gave her the benefit of the
doubt cuz she seemed normal, bro. And I
thought, okay, whatever. She's normal
and that, whatever. I just thought, [ __ ]
it. And then they just turn out to be
the same. So there's nothing left to
prove here. I've shown what they're like
and good luck to anyone that wants to
late in this country
and that's that.
So yeah, I've done my I've done what
I've had to do now. So that's it. Yeah.
And it's so mad because it was so good
yesterday. I had a good I was in a good mood yesterday.
But when they say things can happen at
any moment, things could also get bad at
any moment as well.
You could also things bad things could
happen at any moment.
I was going to save this 150. I was
going to go out next week or something
and then I would have well I had plans I
had was going to go cinema and then [ __ ] but
so I had actually planned what I was doing yeah
you trying to date in this country is
your self harming
All you're doing is self harm and trying
to date in this country. No good is ever
going to come out of it. Never has and never will.
So that's that.
I'll be ringing them tomorrow.
I will be ringing them tomorrow. So,
yeah, I'm being serious. UK asylum. You
think I'm a troll? I'm not a troll, bro.
There's nothing about me that's trolling, lad.
Nah. Never in this country.
Never in this country will anything ever change.
Not in this country it won't.
No. Not in this country, lad.
Not in this country. It won't. Cuz why
hasn't it already?
Why hasn't it already?
It will never change.
Only you can change your life by leaving this country,
by doing what Ant-Man done or creating a
life for yourself somewhere else.
Um, you know,
that's the only way your life will change.
So, it's very scary now that people
could speak to you for that long and
spend all that time and still [ __ ] you
over. It just gets worse and worse and
worse and worse and worse.
Yeah, you don't need to try anymore, lad.
You know, you get to a certain age,
which is normally about 28, 29, you just
don't care anymore.
You see memes on it all the time. I
don't give a [ __ ]
I started to kind of like the person,
but then after a few days, I was like, I
don't really care anymore.
But it's still not nice getting [ __ ] over.
H Samuel, nobody knows about my YouTube.
Stop making excuses for why they do the
stupid shitty things that they do. They
don't know about YouTube. They don't
know about things that I've said. They
don't get sexual remarks made about
them. They're just [ __ ] Simple as that.
Stop making excuses for the [ __ ] Simple.
They're [ __ ] They're [ __ ]
I was speaking to this person for like 3
weeks. Nothing weird was said. Nothing
abnormal was said.
And look, they still had no problem
[ __ ] me over. So, I don't know what's
all of this. You need to speak to people
longer for what? to get [ __ ] over.
What? To get to for the inevitable to get delayed?
Why would you want to delay the inevitable?
Doesn't make any sense. Why would you
delay the inevitable?
It just doesn't make any sense.
There's no point delaying an inevitable
that's going to happen. You're going to
get [ __ ] over. That's exactly what's
going to happen. That's what's been
proven to happen. So that's it. Yeah.
But now things will never change and
they will never change.
They would never change that cuz it
would have already in 5 years. And
that's another thing you need to
remember that if something really was
going to change regarding this,
it would have already changed,
you know. That's the way I see it.
Why hasn't it already changed,
you know? So,
So yeah, so even um
even religious people play the same games.
So now there's no point going to church, is there?
Yeah, there's no point going to church, is there? Mad. Yeah.
What do you think? UK asylum.
I'm not a troll, lad. Nothing about me
is a troll, lad. Hello. Stupid.
>> Yeah. So, like, why do you think I'm a troll?
Why would I troll, bro? All that [ __ ]
happened today, bro. Yeah,
these memes are funny, bro.
These memes are funny. UK asylum. [ __ ] bro. Yeah.
I guess I'll be on YouTube tomorrow then. Yeah.
I'm going to go lads anyways. Yeah. See you.