Hey, so this is going to be um my last
video to the bedless toothless skin
manta rat face virgin. Um I was just
thinking here. I don't know what the
[ __ ] I was playing at, you know,
yesterday making that video to you. I
mean, Jesus Christ. Like that's a
madness, bro. What the [ __ ] was I
thinking? I had you running to the
police crying. And it's it's it's it's
not even just that as well. you you you
were literally crying to the police cuz
you got owned on YouTube. And and it's
not even that. It's like, do I really want to
look back in 10 years and think, I've
wasted all this time arguing with a
skint virgin that ain't even got a bed.
And then I feel like, no, I don't know
what the [ __ ] I was playing at
yesterday, even responding to your ugly
virgin ass. But um it's mad though. It
is. It is mad cuz I feel like it's not that bad.
um you know once a month, twice a month,
even an hour every week. But this is
actually your whole life, isn't it? You
and Red Star, cuz you're both ugly skin
monitors. You literally have nothing but
doing this every single day, do you?
Like I think you generally don't
understand when somebody doesn't want
you. Um I mean, let's use a few
examples. Britney never wanted your ugly
ass. She made that clear. Your mom
didn't want you. This is why you're so
salty about other people having um
relationships with their mother because
your mom put you in hospital. Um and I
don't want you. It's It's mad. Like you
you literally spend all Well, you ain't
got a life cuz you're skin, but I mean
you spend all your time um on YouTube
doing this every day. What a loser. Like
I was actually I just came to the re
realization that bro I'm not going to
sit and argue with some virgin loser and
at the end of the day yeah um it got to
a point where um also uh the thing is
you're just a keyboard warrior like your
boyfriend. I mean I've already owned you
enough times. And another thing is um I
don't want to be responsible for the
fact that I stayed on YouTube and you
died a virgin because of me. Like I'm
not gonna I am not going to be hold held
responsible for that because obviously
if I come because you're so obsessed
with me. All you do is do videos
convincing yourself that I'm as ugly as
you cuz you're sad skin bastard. And if
I stay on here, I'm going to literally
waste all of your time being triggered
by me every single day. And then that
way there's no way you're ever going to
get laid. You're never going to lose
your virginity. And I'm not going to be
responsible for the fact that I stopped
you finally getting laid, losing that
virginity that's been holding you into
your body for 31 years. So, I decided
I'm going to come off of uh uh YouTube
today. So, yeah. Well, a bit later on,
maybe come back in a couple of weeks.
But it's mad how you literally do this
every day for a living.
You and you literally have nothing but
doing this every single day. It's mad.
Like that's all you have in your virgin
skin life. It's mad. That is a madness,
bro. Like occasionally it is. It is
funny. But you do it every day. Yet
you'll never meet anyone. Yet you'll
never say anything to anyone's face and
you'll cry like a little [ __ ]
That is that is insane. Like even for me
to say that like for a straight face,
you're you're a [ __ ] loser. I'm not
going to spend my life arguing with some
little [ __ ] skinny 6' nothing loser
that's scared to meet me. Um, but at the
end of the day, if you ever change your
mind, um, and you want to meet, well,
you got more chance of winning a
lottery. Yeah. You know, I am anyways.
So, yeah, I will not be entertaining you
anymore. Um, you need to really learn
when people don't want nothing to do
with you. Didn't you learn that from
free people like Britney, um, your mom,
me, like, why are you obsessed with
people that don't want you, that never
wanted you? It's It's [ __ ] crazy.
Like I can go on about so many [ __ ]
stories about how you got bullied in
college because people thought you was
gay, which is where the whole Chevel
Cole thing come from. You was just
copying people and how these black guys
throw [ __ ] at you and then but you're
just some little obsessed virgin. That's
what you are. You just live in the past
because you ain't got a life. Like it's
actually just dawned on me all of this
YouTube [ __ ] is because you're the
you're a skin that ain't got a life.
That's that's literally what it is.
That's why you spend you spend all your
life on YouTube doing this because you
literally are skin. That's why you and
Red Star spend all day every day on
YouTube cuz you're low life skinned
little mutters. Yeah. That's what it is.
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. I'm not entertaining
you anymore anyways. Yeah. [ __ ] you.
[ __ ] that. Wasting my time on some
[ __ ] virgin that can't even get a
girl that ain't disabled. I don't want
that on my [ __ ] deathbed. And like I
said, I don't want the fact that I'll be
responsible for you dying a virgin. I'm
not having that on my [ __ ] death bed.
So yeah. Um, you're not getting
entertained anymore, you little [ __ ]
So you can keep making videos. You can
keep typing. No one cares. No one wants
you. [ __ ] virgin. Get off of YouTube
and get laid as soon as I go. It'll do
you good, mate. Do a world of good.