Yo. Okay, so I just wanted to um do a
video and I'm going to title this as
don't talk about people that you don't
know. Um I've said this about a million
times. Um again, I've not took my
medication, so I'm a bit fit bit uh
ADHD, biter, but yeah. So reading this
comment, I've got the money for
trainers. No, you don't, PJ. Don't I?
Cuz I just ordered them 5 minutes ago,
so I'm pretty sure I do. Um, are you
have got them? He's so skinn it's
incredible. Sits in his mum's bedroom
all day on Reddit talking to nobody. Is
Is that true, mate? Cuz I've spent over
£400 on two items in less than a couple
of days. I don't think you know how much
money I have. Um, this is what I mean
with these people in this community. Um,
they can't see outside the bubble. So,
their life is skin, no life, YouTube
every day. Um, and they live in that
bubble and they don't seem to think that
anyone else can be outside of the bubble
that they're living in. Mate, I just
bought the trainers. They cost me £210.
They're coming tomorrow. Yeah. Yeah. You
don't know how much money people have.
So, you along with seven other people
have just been proven wrong. So, yeah,
I'm going out sending it tomorrow cuz I
got a new pair of um jeans. My trainers
are coming tomorrow. It would be
absolutely rude not to go out tomorrow
and send it. It'd be it'd be almost a
crime to not go out on the pool
tomorrow, you know. So, stop talking
about people that you don't know. You do
not know what money people have. You do
not know what money people don't have.
You only know about your own skin life,
which is why you come on here every day
calling people [ __ ] skin. Um, so cuz
you're Skint yourselves. Um, so, uh,
yeah. Uh, with that said, um, the reason
I didn't buy them yesterday is because
Greavvesy wouldn't let me. And and and
if you didn't know, Grezy is the boss
and I have to run things by him first
before doing things. And he he wouldn't
let me out to buy the trainers. I
ordered them because they're a specific
type of trainers that I like, ones that
you can never afford. Um, but he
wouldn't let me. He wouldn't let me. And
I saw this comment and I was like, "Fuck
it. I'm going to prove you along with
seven other people wrong that you don't
know what money people have and you
don't know what people have and what
they don't have. And I do need a new
pair of trainers. Um it was going to
happen anyways. So yeah, maybe uh when I
do this video tomorrow, right, because
they're coming tomorrow, um you can maybe,
you know, take a leaf out of my book and
stop talking about people that you don't
know. We're not all skintike you people.
We're not all sat on YouTube all day
every day like you people. There's other
people out there that have got different
lives than you. Believe it or [ __ ]
not. Jesus. Anyways,