Yo. Okay, so this generally is going to
be my last reply video. Like I am done
with these fat, ugly, self-p projecting
losers that ain't got nothing in their
life. Um, they're not even worth the
time a day. Um, which is why I I haven't
responded to them like 99% of the time
until the past couple of days. But
anyways, I was on Timmy's channel,
right? and um he put Red Stars video up,
so I just clicked on it and he's showing
money and he's saying that he's shown 2.5 grand.
Are you a [ __ ] [ __ ] or are you just
like just plain stupid? Like I'd like to
think that, you know, you're just plain
stupid because I wouldn't want to think
somebody is actually as [ __ ] as you.
But saying that,
you actually are [ __ ] aren't you?
Like, think about this, right? Go into
the bathroom right now, Red Star. Yeah.
Look at that booty, fat, ugly head of
yours and that ugly face and that fat
belly of yours. Right. And just say to
yourself, don't even think to yourself
that you've been on YouTube
every single day from the time you've
woke up to the time that you've gone to
bed stalking me, right?
And you ain't got paid a penny to do so.
What? What a loser. I think this is
actually what like prompted me to want
to come off this [ __ ] Like I'm done
with this community now. This is
actually my last reply. But that just
goes to show like me like as a as a
normal person and other normal people
that are watching this. If somebody
right was a skint ugly this that and the
other, would you waste every second of
every day of your life for 5 years
trying to troll them
and not get paid for it? No, you just
live your life like a normal person
knowing that you're better than them.
That's how everybody knows Red Star that
it's jealousy because there's literally
nothing else. It it it it could actually
it could actually be you know what I'm
saying? You would just live your life.
Like you you've done it for years and
you haven't even got paid for it. Like
you laugh at it. Like I know what you're
saying. Like when um people mention the
word jealousy um you laugh at it and be
like, "Oh, what's there to be jealous
of?" But you you have to understand that
the only thing it could actually point
down to is is jealousy. That's the only
way it would it would possibly make
sense for you to waste your precious
life where you're good-looking and
you've got all this money on a I quote
skin manta every day of your life and
not get paid for it. The only thing it
could be is jealousy. So, I mean, it's
it's it's nothing to laugh at. It's it's
the truth. It's what the evidence shows.
You've been doing this for years. Um,
you know, it's all because you're a
lonely, fat, insecure,
ugly bastard. You've been alone on
YouTube for years doing this. Triggered.
Like, even your videos that you do,
right, responding to me, you can see how
triggered you are. Like, with the
exclamation marks and the capitals,
like, you really really are a bully
victim, bro. Like, you you live with
your mom in your 40s. You got no life.
You got no friends. That's why you stalk
me every day on YouTube because you're a
fat ugly nobody. And what's worse about
it is you're also a coward. Like, bro,
listen. You're the one that had to keep
begging London Taylor to come on my door
and go to the pubs I was in. But listen,
you know that you can never ever do even
1% um you know, of the stuff that you do
online to anyone's face. You're just
you're a loser. You're honestly a loser.
And if the people that um didn't watch
you was was
such yesmen, they would tell you that
you're you're a loser. Like the last
thing I would be doing is wasting my
life all day every day stalking somebody
that's a skin bunter and not get paid
for it. And I'm pretty sure most people
agree with me like you're you are
clearly I think what you're what what
you hate is the fact that I'm younger
than you. I'm better looking than you
and I'm not hopeless like you. That's
why you come on YouTube every day
triggered at the world because you're a
[ __ ] Like you've been a [ __ ] since
birth and you're definitely jealous of
something. Like think about it. Look at
your boyfriend. [ __ ] lanky ugly
string of [ __ ] pissed virgin with a
disabled girlfriend. Now you see when I
say that I'm not going to waste my life
every day stalking them from the time I
wake up to the time I go to bed. You
know why? because I know I'm better than
them. How can you call me all of them
things yet waste all of these years
stalking me and harassing me, right? And
you don't even get paid for it. And do
you know what? You've done it for 6
months and I didn't even reply the first
6 months. Do you think anyone would believe you
that you're living your best life when
you have to come on here doing this
every day? No, bro. You're a fat, ugly
virgin [ __ ] It's obvious to everyone
now. You know, you're a lonely, sad,
jealous bastard full of hatred on the
tubes because you ain't got a life.
That's what it is. Bit like a lot of the
people that follow you. Now, we're going
to get on to the money thing now. And
I'm going to explain this to you one
more time. And I want you to listen and listen carefully.
I've come to the realization that me
keep saying that I've shown money. I've
shown money. I've shown money. It
doesn't suit a lot of the people because
the problem is is when you come on here
and you're better looking than people
like yourself and you're younger and you
kind of got hope and a little bit going
for you, these people don't like you.
These fat ugly people in their 40s that
have got nothing. They they hate on
anyone that's that's got a better life
than them. So what they then have is
they have selective memory. Just like
when, you know, I've tried to meet
Trevor Dawson and he didn't meet me,
people will pretend it never happened.
Or when I've gone to meet the bomb,
people will pretend it's never happened.
Just like when I've literally explained
that I have shown you and other people
money time and time again, people will
just pretend it never happened. Bro,
come on now. You should know how the
game works. You invented the game. You
you skint [ __ ] ugly bastard with no
life and the other people that follow
you. You literally invented the game.
Somebody shows you money, you double the
money. You got shown 5.7 grand, right? And
you are showing me three grand less.
That means ultimately you lose the money
game. Think about it, bro. You and your
skin [ __ ] sad rejected followers have
been coming on here for [ __ ] donkeys
years, you know, calling people skin and
reta t. Bro, how many times have you
been shown money more than anything that
you've shown? You got shown more than
anything that you've shown for [ __ ]
almost 2 years and none of you showed me
anything, bro. That's why people don't
show you money anymore. Not because
they're skin, not because they don't
have it, because bro, I've got a history
of what you do. Every single time you
get shown money, you can't show nothing
yourself. Think about it, bro. You're
coming on here trying to say that you've got £20,000,
bro. If you had £20,000,
how comes your [ __ ] ass did not show
anything when I kept showing you money
multiple multiple multiple multiple
times, bro? It doesn't make any sense
whatsoever. And the only people that
will pretend I've not shown money is
just people that follow you and just
Yes, man. Like you're all biased. You've
got selective memory. Like and like I
said, it's about the meeting as well.
Like everybody knows that I have shown
more money than you you ever will, you
know, and that's and that's and that's
and that's what it is. You know, you
have been shown thousands. You know, the
only people that think that you've won
by showing less than what I've shown you
is the yesmen that are the biased
people. You know, that that pretend I
didn't go to meet Bomb and pretend I
didn't go to meet Trevor Dawson. Bro,
you've got nothing. Yeah. You want
everyone to believe that you've got all
of this money? No, no, no. Bro, you're
sat on YouTube doing what you do all
day, every day for [ __ ] years. like
you get asked to show where you are, you
can't meet anyone, right? And you know,
then you then beg the black man to to to
to fight your battles. You're nothing
but a coward. You know how you could
have all of that energy for 5 years
being triggered on YouTube the way you
have and not get paid for it. Bro, that
would depress the [ __ ] out of me. If
someone had five years of my life
triggering me every day for five years
like I have with you and not get paid
for it and not even do a damn thing
about it like come on my door because
you're too much of a [ __ ] to I would I
would be raging, bro. I think that would
actually tempt me to actually then start
going on people's doors. Like you're
you're a [ __ ] loser, bro. You're a absolute loer.
You really really are like bro. We all
know people have got selective memory
but I know which is all that counts that
you have been shown thousands and
thousands and thousands and none of you
you your virgin gay lanky boyfriend
couldn't show anything.
Not even anything for two years. Bro,
have a word with yourself. You didn't
win anything. You've never won anything.
Bro, you've been you've been losing
since you've come out of your mom's
[ __ ] You know what kind of loser what
kind of freak of nature sits on YouTube
for five years in a row every single
day, right? Um
stalking from the time they've woke up
to the time they've gone to bed and not
get paid for it. What actual freak does
that, you know? And then you're showing
less money than I've shown, pretending
that you've won.
Really, bro? Come on. Have a word with
yourself. All the unbiased people know
that none of you people, right, had
anything to show when I was showing you
that money, anything to [ __ ] show.
Like, you lost for almost two years. You
couldn't show nothing, you know? And Joe
made a point that
um you know well maybe they didn't have
it or but I mean what all of them people
calling other people skimp didn't have
money to show for 18 months. Wouldn't
that then mean that they are the skint
ones you know? So it's Yeah, man. Like
and that's it. That's my last say. I'm
never going to entertain you again. I'm
done with this community. So have fun
loser. And guess what? Do you know what?
If you've really got anything to say,
Red Star, come and say to my face. You
know where I live. You have my address.
I mean, I'm saying that because I'm
never going to watch any of your videos
again. Um, I'm never um going to go on
your channel again. You do realize I
used to go on your channel once every 6
months. Think of that, loser. Whilst you
was wasting your life away on me for
free, right, every day. I wasn't even
going on your channel. you weren't even
being mentioned. You're a [ __ ] loser.
But hey, if you ever do change and you
ever do grow a pair of balls, um you
know where I live. So yeah, but yeah,
just to clarify, you showing £3,000 less
than what I've shown, that's not you
winning. And but the only reason nobody
would agree is because you're all
biased. You pretend things don't happen.
You believe what you want to believe.
Um, so that's that's why you say, "Oh,
well, yeah, that was years ago." And no,
you you're being shown thousands. Like,
it's not even a joke. Your boyfriend,
the virgin, has been shown thousands.
And there was no 14 grand being shown
then. So, at the end of the day, bro,
get a life. Get off of YouTube. Sort
your jealousy issues out because I am
done. And if you ever change your mind
and you really have something to say,
well, guess what, [ __ ] You know where
I live. So yeah, get a life. You don't
want to waste another five years of your
life being jealous and stalking and not
being paid for it, man. Come on. You're
better than that. So yeah, and like I
said, if you ever change your mind and
you got a pair of balls, um, and you,
you know, you want to do something
yourself instead of begging a black man,
um, you know where I live, you [ __ ]
loser. Have a good life, loser.