[snorts]
Yo. Okay, bringing it back old school.
Yeah. Um, time for a new jambling video.
I actually lost 250 the other day. And
gambling is a little bit out of control,
but I thought, do you know what? [ __ ]
it. Because we put real gamb videos on
this channel, don't we? We do, don't we?
[snorts] Yeah, man. Oh [ __ ]
This is so dangerous.
I shouldn't even be playing this to be fair. Yeah, man. [snorts]
Roulet is bad. Do not gamble, people. I
was doing 120 spins the other day. Madness. [snorts]
The one that would be nice.
Nope. Zero section. [clears throat]
Basically need one of them. >> [snorts]
>> basically here. Come on. 5811
21. It's [ __ ]
Needed to. Really?
Yeah, that is [ __ ] man. [snorts]
Come on. 811. [snorts]
We just some money off here, didn't we? >> [snorts]
>> I think I'm going to double up after this. [snorts]
[ __ ] 16. [ __ ] off. [snorts]
24 would have been good, man.
There we go. >> [gasps]
>> This isn't good, man.
Stay away from the zero section.
20 is good. TW is lovely.
I'm sure it is. It [snorts] is. He's [ __ ] lovely.
[ __ ] lovely cat.
All right, [snorts]
give us another one, mate.
It's just [snorts] what it does. It
gives you wins and it takes it back off you.
Hopefully that's not going to happen
with this one.
Give us [snorts] another little hit. [sighs]
If it hits 30, it's technically a loss.
Nah, I knew it. [snorts] Every time,
bro. [clears throat]
Does it every [ __ ] time.
Here we go.
Oh, [ __ ] me.
Is that getting in the old nerves now?
[laughter] Is that getting in the old nerves? Jesus Christ. [snorts]
Any one of them will be mega 811. Come on.
[ __ ] 19 every [clears throat] [ __ ]
time. It's so fixed. It does the same
thing as soon as you up the annity. It
It misses every single number you do.
Every single time. It does it every
single time. It was doing it the other
day as well where it will give you a
win. Gives you a certain amount and as
soon as you rebet, it [ __ ] you every
single time without failure. As soon as
you up the ante is what I call it. It
was doing it the other day as well when
I got it to 250. As soon as you up the
ante, you get [ __ ] in the ass every time. Yeah.
Yeah. We're [ __ ] bro. Proper [ __ ]
Yeah, it knows. It knows where the money
is. Well, at least nothing changes with
rigged ass rulet online. As soon as you
up the ante,
uh, nothing changes there. So yeah, I
just thought I'd do that little