Hey, this is going to be a video to um
Jo that I was live earlier, sorry, just
had a hiccups. And you know how I was
saying um all women are literally
exactly the same. Um this is what I was
trying to say to Virgin Boy um you know
years ago, but I think he thought by
defending women he was going to finally
lose his virginity and not die a virgin.
Um but obviously he is still a virgin.
he's going to die a virgin. But this is
exactly what I mean. Um Joe, like they
literally are all the same. They say
exactly the same stuff. They've got the
same mannerisms. They all do the same
[ __ ] which makes me generally believe
that they are all the same. And I think
anybody with a brain would would think
the same. They literally are all the
same. So when I go on Instagram,
um there's this guy in America. There's
a few channels, but this is like one of
the main ones. And his [ __ ] always pops
up. Like whenever I open the Instagram
app. Yeah. He does approach him like
what I used to do. And it's literally
it's like once you've watched one,
you've watched all of them. It's just
it's just the same [ __ ] And it's like,
how could you possibly have hope when
even someone that's completely different to you,
um, that lives in a completely different
country than you, that looks different
than you, is getting the same [ __ ]
[ __ ] So, anyways, I'll play some of them, right?
>> I don't.
>> Oh, you don't?
>> [ __ ] You're so beautiful.
>> Thank you.
>> Yeah. Yeah. It's cool if I grab your number.
>> No, I have a boyfriend. boyfriend that's
never with them.
>> It's kind of Russian.
>> Oh, it's Russian.
>> I don't know.
>> Oh, is this a magazine? >> Yeah.
>> Okay. Well, I was wondering if I get over
>> I mean two two saying that. I mean, that
doesn't really mean much, right? But it
gets worse. Trust me.
>> Where you from?
>> I'm from Dallas.
>> Oh, you're from Dallas? >> Yeah.
>> Oh, okay. What's your background? You
cut I don't know. Your eyes kind of
throw me off. I'm Colombian.
>> This is a different god by the way.
>> Are you Colombian?
>> Oh, were you born here or?
>> No, I was born here.
>> Are you okay?
>> Well, I was born I was whenever I get your number.
>> I have boyfriend.
>> Third one.
>> Excuse me.
>> You would have thought, right, if these
if these women generally weren't all the
same NPCs, you would have thought they
would have said no and maybe gave
constructive criticism or a bit of
feedback or just in general use another
excuse. They do and say all the same
[ __ ] Like they've got the same look in
their eyes. And you know, like even
watching this annoys me. And I would say
these guys here were more confident than
me because I I I don't really do it
anymore. You know, I've for a couple of
weeks. I would say they're even better
than me at this. And they're still
getting the same [ __ ] Like surely to
God, it's got to be these women being
all the same. Like it it has to be. What
else could it be? Right. We'll continue.
random, but I just saw you and I thought
you really pretty.
>> Thank you.
>> Yeah. What's your name?
>> Sorry. Thank you. I have a boyfriend. >> Random.
>> Isn't that mad though? They say that
they go for personality and tet yet when
you get normal guys like these. I'm not
even talking about myself now. They
don't even get given a chance. [ __ ] me.
>> I just saw you walk by and had to come
approach you cuz I thought you're really pretty.
>> Oh, thank you. Y >> Heather.
>> Heather. Nice to meet you.
>> Nice to meet you. say compliment.
>> Where you from?
>> Yeah, I live here.
>> Oh, you live here? Oh, okay. Oh, well,
>> that's also another NPC thing they say.
I live here. I'm from here. Like just
like flat out that with no enthusiasm,
but apparently they're not all the same. But anyways, >> um
>> Oh, you've heard that one before.
>> see, none of these are any different.
None of these [ __ ] ones are any
different. They're all the same.
>> These are just some I recorded.
>> Nice to meet you.
>> Well, I was wondering if I get your number.
>> Yeah. Well, yeah.
>> You said she had a boyfriend as well if
you didn't hear it. She's from the Netherlands.
>> Sorry to bother you. I I think you look
really cute and I'd love to take you out sometime.
>> Thank you so much. You're so sweet. I
actually believe that.
>> Okay, no problem.
Yeah. Isn't it so funny how all of these
women claim that they've got boyfriends,
right? When there's more single men than
men in relationships. A B their, I
quote, boyfriends are never ever with
them. Isn't that a bit sus? But they've
all got these boyfriends that are never
with them that, you know, most of my
friends that I know, like people that
have got no connection, no correlation
to each other, most of them are single.
Like, yeah, I know people in
relationships, but more people I know
were single than than have girlfriends.
Um, and you also get a lot of women that
are single and a lot of, you know, women
that hate men, but they claim they've
all got boyfriends.
When the maths don't add up, the maths
don't add up. You know, [Applause]
>> I really appreciate that. Thank you.
>> Have a good one. Thank you. Have a good
day. Appreciate it. Okay. Oh, you got
here. Thanks, man.
Hey, I'm so sorry to bother you. I don't
normally do this, but I thought you were
really cute and I was wondering if I
could get your number.
>> Oh, thank you. What's your name?
>> I'm I'm Connor.
>> Nice to meet you, Conor. Unfortunately,
I do have a boyfriend, but honestly
>> Oh, dited
and I probably
>> Thank you. I I really appreciate that.
Have a great one. You too. [Applause]
>> Hi. Um, my name is Connor. What's your name? >> Jessica.
>> Nice to meet you, Jessica. Um,
>> I thought you were really cute. I was
wondering if I could take you out sometime.
>> No, sorry. I have a boyfriend.
>> Okay, no worries.
>> Oh, Jesus Christ. They're looking to be
all the [ __ ] same. It's the same
>> Oh, this is this is this is the funniest
one. Yeah, this is the one I showed
Antman. Right. So, she's from London.
So, they're they're they're in Chicago,
right? In America. The guy
>> Oh, I actually spoke on this one, so you
can just listen.
>> Chicago, right, in America. The guy
approaching is American and she's from London, right? >> Norway.
>> Sorry. Hold on. Hold on. >> Norway.
>> Oh, no. London.
>> London. No way.
>> Have you noticed they've all got the
same attitude, the same mannerisms, the
same look in their eyes, but somehow
they're not all the same. Makes you
wonder, doesn't it? [ __ ] makes me
wonder. I don't know about anyone else
who's watching this, but it makes me wonder.
Sorry, I didn't realize how
>> they all have the same attitude, the
same mannerisms, the same attitude.
>> Oh [ __ ] I said exactly the same thing
on that. That's how you know I'm right, bro.
>> They all have the same attitude, the
same mannerisms, the same attitude. They say ex
>> And bear in mind, this is not even me um
approaching and it and it just winds me
up just watching it. It just annoys me
just watching them and it ain't even me.
That's the maddest thing about it. all
have the same attitude, the same
mannerisms, the same attitude. They say
exactly the same stuff. Look,
>> I just
can I grab your number?
>> Um, I'm actually going to see my boyfriend
>> right now.
>> Go to see your boyfriend. So, you've
come all the way to America to see your
boyfriend that lives in Chicago. I mean,
what's what's the chances of that?
They're just all the same. I feel sorry
for people that generally think one day
it's going to change. I generally feel
bad for them, bro. [ __ ]
>> That's also another thing they like to
say is, "Oh, I'm going to meet my
boyfriend." That's that's another NPC
thing they say. If one has said
something, they've all said it. That's
how you know that they're all the same.
>> My classes are
>> um So,
yeah. And it's mad how like
one day someone
thinks they're going to wake up and all
of a sudden it's going to be different.
How's it going to be different? How is
it going to be [ __ ] different? You
know, this was the red flag here. Yeah.
There's some guy in London that does it
as well. Isn't it mad how all of the
people that you watch doing this, they
get exactly the same [ __ ] It's exactly
the same [ __ ] as I I used to get as
well, you know? But you hear about, "Oh,
other guys do it. Watch out for the
other guys." Well, I'm watching other
guys, bro, and they seem to be getting
exactly the same [ __ ] So, what the [ __ ]
is going on?
>> Oh, so you're a freshman?
>> Yeah, I'm a freshman.
>> Okay. So, maybe I could like help you
find your classes sometime. >> Blanca.
>> Blanca, can I grab your number? >> No.
>> In a friend way? Like in a friendly way
or like boyfriend?
>> No, I have a boyfriend. Yeah.
>> Yeah. No, I didn't.
>> Bored as [ __ ] Ah, I want you. >> What?
>> I can't hear you.
>> Got you, [ __ ]
>> You drink coffee >> sometimes.
>> So, we should go out for coffee.
>> You're not a surfer. >> What?
>> I know. I still can't hear you.
>> Are you Are you speaking English
correctly or is this just me?
>> This is another guy. by the way.
>> Oh, [ __ ] this. I'm not listening to this
anymore. It's just the same [ __ ]
[ __ ] [ __ ] this. And yeah, it just goes
on and on and on and on and on and on
and on and on and on and on and on and on.
>> Thank you. Appreciate that.
>> Are you drunk? My bad.
>> Hey, that's a crazy question.
>> I I
got black on.
>> Yeah, but real [ __ ] I just wanted to
give you like get your number or whatever. [Music] [Applause]
>> You got the points.