Okay, so Greezy, um when I went out the
other day, right,
I was so hung over that I actually
thought I was going to die. Um I bought
a takeaway and I couldn't even eat the
takeway cuz I kept being sick and you
know, then I thought to myself, yeah, I
need um a new hobby, you know. So I got
myself some Lego. I used to love um Lego
Star Wars um as a child and I feel like
it's one of them things you can you know
still like as a um as a adult. So look,
you got Yoda, you got um I forget his
name, but the the robot and yeah, just
lovely little characters. Um this cost
me £40. Um and obviously I'm going to
add to it. Um and yeah, just start
collecting um Lego Star Wars. Um because
they're lovely little characters.
They're lush. They're lush characters.
Oh, wow. Look.
There we go. See?
Wait, where's the uh
Oh, he's there. I was about to say I
thought separate. So yeah, I am going to
um try to build this [snorts] and um yeah,
go from there basically.
Okay. Right. I'm going to I'm going to
build the characters first cuz obviously
um that's what [snorts] that's how you always start. Yeah.
Right. One second.
Right. So, I'm back. I made the uh characters. Yoda.
Put him there with a spare
light sab and the the bot. That's what
you call lovely characters.
Lovely little characters.
So, now I've got to build this. Oh, when
I build it, I'll show you and I'll tell
you how long it's took me
to build this. H
I've got a feeling it's going to be a
good couple of hours and then yeah, I'll
buy some more Lego and just build up
from there basically. So,
yeah, just put that there. So, yeah.
Right, let's get started. >> [sighs]