Okay. So, I'm going to do that approach
you wanted uh using that pickup line cuz
yeah, you've been asking me to use it.
So, I haven't approached for a month. It
will be I've done two approaches just
before. I'm going I'm about to do this
one, but this is the first time me out
doing this in a month. But yeah, I
wanted to warm up a little bit. So, you
wanted me to use that line on someone.
Okay. Let me find someone that I like
the look of.
>> So, she's all right. Okay. Let me do her.
Yeah. Oh, no. You think I was overreacting?
>> Excuse me. Excuse me. Sorry. You I just
wanted to say where did you get that? >> Sorry.
>> Where did you get that? >> What?
>> That beauty.
>> What's your name? >> Sorry.
>> There we go. >> Done.
>> All it takes is two before doing this.
>> Amazing. And
>> you can't even get a conversation out
someone like two I done two approaches
before this. And I didn't even get a
conversation. No, no, I done free
actually cuz I done one at a train
station. Couldn't even get a conversation. Um,
>> what did I get? Um, I got
>> What did I get? What did she say? I
think she said she was engaged. She gave
me like really bad attitudes. She gave
me an attitude about it. So, look like
by the way, all fresh, face waxed and
everything. So this is how hard it is in
this country to you can't even get a
conversation out someone.