Yo. Okay, so this is going to be my last
video um for a couple of weeks. I'm not
going to go live for a couple of weeks.
Um and yeah, I want to do this video to
um to the copycat. Um now, I went on the
Copycat's channel earlier and Red Star's
channel earlier, and this has literally
been the first time I've gone on it in 3
weeks cuz I don't really go in anymore
because it's just the same obsessed
people repeating keyboard warriors. Um,
and it was again today the same old
repeating little fat, ugly, low-life
people. Um, what it is with these people
on here, um, is they're fat, ugly people
that have got no life. Um, so they just
try and take it out on people that are
younger than them, better looking than
them, and have hope that they don't.
That's the number that's the number one
thing with these people. like you know
these haters on Red Star channel and you
know even L J's they're just fat ugly
people that never made it um that hate
themselves. Um it's cool but it's it's
the truth. Um you know and sometimes
you've got to be cool to be kind.
They're literally life's losers. I mean
they can't even take a day off of here
without hating on people that they don't
[ __ ] know. Is that really people
living their best life? I I I don't
think so. Um I would beg to differ on
that one. Uh anyways, um before I get
into this video to um uh the the
copycat, um I wanted to um ask you um a
couple of questions is that um why do
you feel the need to be a copycat? Um
you know, I don't know what you have
asked Santa Claus for Christmas this
year, but have you tried asking him for
a mind of your own? Um because you know,
since I've known you, you absolute
virgin. Um, you've made it a thing
where, you know, you don't copy people.
Um, you hate people that copy people.
You've got a mind of your own and that's
why you dress like an absolute virgin.
Um, dress your way. Sorry. I mean, um,
because other people don't dress the way
that that you dress. Um, and you went
with that, but then you started saying
that I was gay because I don't find
Cheryl Cole attractive.
I mean, really, bro, really? you you you
say that you've got a mind of your own,
but um now at at the start I didn't
really think much of it because
obviously being new to college or school
or a new workplace um people will do
things to fit in and obviously he was
doing this to fit in and to be honest
with you now there was quite a bullying
uh problem with him um in college as
well which is why he stopped attending.
Um he was um he was studying lamb
landscaping um but because of the
bullying um he stopped going into
college which is why he didn't finish it
because why else would he finish it and
I think I think it was two people that
was bullying him over the way that he
dressed or something. It wasn't
physical. They did beat him up but they
were calling him names and stuff. Um and
then all of a sudden one day he was like
sh she's attractive. She's good-looking.
You're gay homo. if you don't like her.
And I'm thinking, bro, where the [ __ ]
has this come from? Um, that is being a
copycat. Um, you know, pe, you know,
you're not a copycat because you find
the person attractive. Um, you're being
a copycat because you're saying that if
that person does not like that person,
they're gay. That's not what gay means.
Okay, let's go by your logic then. So,
if somebody doesn't find Cheryl Carl
attractive, but they find, you know,
black women only attractive, would that
make them gay? What if they don't find
Shervel Carl attractive, but they like
blonde women with blue eyes and big
boobs? Would that make them gay? Or
would that still very much mean they
like certain [ __ ] women? You know, I
mean, it it doesn't make any sense. I
can assure you, mate, just because
somebody doesn't find Sher Cole attractive,
um, it doesn't mean they like Dick. It
doesn't it doesn't mean they like Dick.
I know it might be hard for you to
believe. Um, but yeah, you definitely
definitely meet, you know, I wouldn't
like her because her boobs are not big
enough and I don't like her color hair.
I mean, at the end of the day, that's
that that that's me. Everyone's allowed
their, you know, women have got types.
So, why can't men have types, you know?
That that is definitely definitely
copying. Um, because if anyone goes on
the student room form, you will see a
bunch of people said exactly the same
thing to each other. Oh, Sher Cole's
hot. She Cole is attractive. Gay. they
all they literally all copy each other.
Um it's a trend that went on a couple of
years ago and obviously he wanted to he
started saying it to fit in with the
crowd because he didn't want to feel
left out and he wanted to stop being
bullied in college. I guess um I think
it did stop after that but there was a
bullying problem. um he used to tell me
every time we meet he used to say this
this these two guys were bullying him
but I can't remember the exact story but anyways
and then you start copying people's
[ __ ] holidays you bloody copycat now
me I'm going to Amsterdam because I I
wanted to go abroad the first time I
went abroad was when I was 23 so I
thought you know what let me let me go
to let me go to Amsterdam and um you
know I went to went to Amsterdam
just thinking nothing of it. Couple of
years later, I see some [ __ ] lanky
[ __ ] ugly rat looking [ __ ] with his
downy girlfriend being exactly the same
place as me. And I'm thinking, what? You
absolute copycat? You know what's the
[ __ ] chances that I've gone somewhere
and you've suddenly ended up in the same
place as me the first time? Now, if it
was your third trip or fourth trip or
fifth trip and so on and so forth, then
yeah, the fact that that's the first
place you went to, you [ __ ] rat ugly
bastard. Um, just goes to show that
you're nothing better than a copycat.
Um, you know, that's like what, one in
247 odds. I think there's like 247
countries, but the odds are mad that
you've just ended up there that I went
there. You're a copycat. You're an
undercover copycat. like you're one of
them little cats, right, with the spies,
little copycat. And I remember um
before, you know, you've actually um
said um that you're f, you know, you
prefer cats and I prefer dogs. I mean,
of course you would prefer cats. You are
a cat. A [ __ ] big copycat. Um so
little copycat. That's so like that's so um
so catchy that is. Um but yeah, so
that's you actually copied my holiday.
I'm seeing I'm seeing some [ __ ] ugly
rat looking bastard in the same [ __ ]
place as me. I'm thinking what the [ __ ]
Weird. So, um I went on your uh your
response to Red Star. Um you responded
to this autumn woman. What is it with
you and these women? You absolute
virgin. I mean, you've stalked every
single woman um that I've been with
convincing yourself I've not had sex
with them. You go, you reply. What is it
with you and women? I generally think
it's because of your erectile
dysfunction, which is why you're still a
virgin. Um, you I think you're a bit
jealous that like I've had sex and you
can never or something something weird.
You always seem to be around women.
You've got an obsession with women I've
been with and even other women. It's
weird. I went on your channel earlier
scrolling up and you've been doing it
for years. You absolute virgin. We
definitely know Sarah has never given
you any sex, mate. Um, so anyways, um,
so you were saying about how, um, I was
projecting and you were saying that I
project my ugliness onto people. No,
that's you. Uh, you've got a channel
being mentally obsessed with me every
single day trying to call me ugly. Um,
that's that's you. And you were saying
that I'm I'm projecting when I'm calling
you a virgin.
I'm projecting when I'm calling you a
virgin. Bro, your channel got banned
because I put a video up of me sticking
my dick in a woman's mouth. I don't
think I'm a virgin. I really, really
don't think I'm a virgin. Now, you can
go on all you like to the cows come home
that you're not a virgin because you're
with this disabled girl for a few years.
And you can say that all you like, but
I've proved I've had sex and and there's
no getting out of that. But you're still
saying I'm a virgin. Yeah, I got your
channel banned with my porn video,
but you're still calling me a virgin.
That doesn't even make sense at this
point. It it does not even make sense.
You're an absolute virgin. Like, it
really really really is ridiculous now.
And you know, you and and at the end of
the day, um I know a virgin when I see
one. and and the way you stalked the
women that I've been with and the way
you kept dismissing all of the sex
stories that I told you that were real.
You're the biggest virgin going. I
didn't know that back then cuz I was
[ __ ] 17, 18. I don't [ __ ] you
know, I wasn't fully, you know, grown
then. But a few years later, I was
wondering, I was thinking to myself, why
the [ __ ] does this virgin um keep saying
that I've not had sex with Escorts when
I've literally told him the story a
million times? And I was like, It's cuz
he's the virgin. It's cuz he's never had
sex. He's the big virgin. And you didn't
want to feel left out because you lost
your virginity before him. It might have
been with an escort, but um yeah. Oh,
it's cuz he's the virgin. That's why I
was saying to myself, I I get it now.
You know, like when the penny drops, um
I clocked on in the end because he get
my mom to like
um agree with these things and have to
agree with these things and stuff and
it's weird. It's like, "Oh, it's cuz
he's never had sex." The penny dropped.
He's the virgin. [ __ ] It took me like
21, 22. I was like, "Oh, it's cuz he's
the virgin." It made sense in the end
because you've never had sex and you
never will have sex. And then you were saying that
you were saying to her that I've never
had a girlfriend. Bro, I've had more
women than you will ever have and I've
never ever resorted to disabled. So, I
don't know why you keep repeating the
same thing over and over again. We've
been over the same thing over and over
and over again. So, I mean, it's it's
it's ridiculous. And then I went and
this is the thing that made me laugh as
well. Um, you really really really are
an absolute [ __ ] loser. Now, I've
seen you um say this a few times on
YouTube trying to call me a loser, but
no, no, no, no. All all jokes aside, now
you are the definition of a [ __ ]
loser. Now, I went on your um community
post where you're saying that um you
know you're going to call the police and
ret. Now, before I get into this, you
got 13 thumbs up.
You got 13 thumbs up. That's mad because
all of the thing the only thing that
comes to my head is that think of all of
the times Monty said that he was going
to call the police and other people have
said they're going to call the police.
Dereass a grass. Dereass. Darag of
grass. But yeah, when the copycat virgin
says that he's going to call the police
on me, everyone praises him. These
people in this community are proper
biased nons lovers. It's [ __ ]
obvious. And by the people, I mean
obviously the haters. There are genuine
people on it, but I mean like the
haters. He got 13 thumbs up. Now, if I
turned around and said I was going to
call the police or Monty or anyone, we'd
get a bolican for it. They are nons
lovers on here, mate. Um, they must
absolutely see themselves in the copycat
virgin every time they go on his
channel. But um what I just wanted to
say is um that you are an absolute
loser. You literally come on YouTube
every [ __ ] day being mentally
obsessed with someone like you're some
kind of big man in your shitty little
bedsit. Giving it the big I am giving it
the big man. And any opportunity that
you get to try and call the police on
people, you take it. Mate, you're a
loser. Everyone knows you're a loser.
Even the people that follow you would
tell you that you're a loser if you're
not biased. Like you're a proper proper
loser. And it's not even just that. It
shows how you are so obsessed with me.
Because anyone who's watching this Yeah.
to make police reports and do what he
does every single day. He his life is
dedicated to trying to [ __ ] with me,
grass on me. He's mentally obsessed
loser. That generally generally
generally what he is. He's a mentally
obsessed little cretton. And at the end
of the day, right, I feel bad for the
police. There there's people out there,
you know, getting their phone snatched
or someone could be getting killed or
[ __ ] knifed up or whatever. There's
actual serious [ __ ] happening. And then
they've got some little rat ratoui rat
looking [ __ ] right? Belling them up
because they've lost an argument on
YouTube. What a loser. What an absolute
loser. Like if I was so much of a loser
that I had to run to the police over
somebody owning me on YouTube is mad.
It's crazy. Like you live to [ __ ] with
people and then you go running to the
police. You're a loser. It shows that
you got no life. You are a low life
virgin little loser. And let me tell you
something. As far as this police thing
goes, you're never going to win. You
know that you're never going to win. So
why waste your time? You know, even if
it takes a day, five days, 10 years,
you're never ever ever going to win
because the amount of [ __ ] that I have
got on you, you know, the only reason
the police have done stuff is because
you went crying to them, you little
narcissistic virgin, saying, "Oh, he's
bullying me. He's bullying me. He's
bullying me. He's bullying me." But
trust me, in the end, you're not ever
going to win. Believe you me. Um, and I
wouldn't say believe you me if I wasn't
honest, you know, about it. Like you're
you come on here trying to [ __ ] with
people and then you go run to the police
because you're a [ __ ] loser that
can't take it. An absolute loser. You
think that's winning? You think that you
crying to the police, right, being a
little loser is winning. That's not
winning. That's you being owned. Since
you like that word, Since you like that
word so much. That's a vindaloo, by the
way, coughing up.
Since you like the word so much, that's
you being owned. You literally have to
run to the police over YouTube. You
haven't won anything. And in the end,
you're not going to win. You will not
win in the end. Believe you me. So why
why not, right?
If your life is not tragic and you're
not all of these things and all of these
things I'm saying about you is false,
why don't you [ __ ] off of YouTube and
get a life? You low life. Why don't you
make that low life a high life and and
get a life? In other words, because you
can't do it, you're mentally obsessed
little weirdo. You are obsessed with me.
Even my solicitor said it as well when I
went to see her um couple months ago in
the summer. You are obsessed.
You generally generally are. You've got
a channel, right? Dedicated to me. Your
whole life revolves around me trying to
get me nicked, doing videos. You are a
obsessed little loser. I feel sorry for
the police as well. There's actual
things going on in like, you know, in
the world. Um, serious things, you know,
ser things are a serious matter. But,
you know, and then you got some little
skin little virgin cuz you got owned on
YouTube cuz he's obsessed running to
them playing the victim. It's [ __ ]
mad. It's mad. You're not such a big
man, are you? When you're when you're
[ __ ] with a grown man, are you little
[ __ ] Um, but you know, I've met plenty
of people like you now, mate. You know,
it's it's it's not it's not a big thing.
Um, but yeah, that's that's me. You you
seriously need to get a life. You're an
absolute loser. You're the biggest loser
I've ever come across. How someone the
fact that someone can be older than me
and that's the cry to the police over
YouTube and think they've won is is is
mad. And all of the people that agree
with you are just biased, genous nons
lovers. That's why they're like you. You
know, at the end of the day, like I
said, let me let me let me let me step
it back a bit. you got 13 likes promoting grassin. [laughter]
If that does not tell you about this
disabled autistic um community, I I I I
don't know what will. But yeah, anyways,
Virgin, you need to seriously seriously
get a life. You you need to get laid
before it's too late. You know, you're
almost 31. Um and yeah, you need to get
a life. And the police thing, you're
never going to win with it. You will
never ever ever ever ever ever ever win.
No one's seen what you've done yet. I've
got a harassment folder that's over 160
pages long of what you've done. So,
you're never ever ever ever going to
win. So, at this point, you might as
well just stop wasting the police time.
Get off of YouTube and and get a life.
Um and and and and that's it. So, yeah,
that's my video to you.