Yo, so this is a video um responding to
Timmy because he's done a couple of
videos on me. Surprise, surprise, you're
coming with money, Mike. It's typical.
Like everybody knows what you do. Like
you will never ever ever meet anyone.
And if by the very low chance that you
do meet someone, you're always with
another person. Like, let's just put it
this way. Yeah. If you was really going
to come to me, you would have got in
that taxi. It's as simple as that. You
agreed to it. People didn't pull pull it
from the cow's ass and just ordered you
one, right? We You literally said that
you would have got in the taxi. Then it
was another excuse and another excuse
and another excuse and Wednesday it's
going to be another excuse. Um and if
you do by the 1% chance come like like
you said, you always need backup. Timmy,
when are you going to stop this? You're
not a hard man. Um I don't know why your
disability seems to like make you think
that you're some kind of hard man. You
are an actual [ __ ] There's literally
nothing hard about you. You've never won
any fight. You've never ever turned up
anywhere by yourself. And yet in 2026,
you're continuously right coming on to
YouTube acting like you're some kind of
big man when you're just a [ __ ] who's
as weak as anything. Like it's it's it's
crazy. Like it honestly honestly is. And
like it doesn't matter, bro. Like, I
really do hope you do come on Wednesday,
which is not going to happen because you
started it and I'll finish it. Like, I
know why you do what you do, right? All
it is with you is you know that you're a
gambling addict. You know that you're
ugly. You know that you're skintto
me. That's what you do. Or if some or if
people are giving you [ __ ] on YouTube,
that's why you bring up my name. You've
been doing it for years now. Think about
it, Timmy. Yeah. I showed you £1,300
last February. You ran away. You got
shown different amounts of money and you
ran away. Timmy, you're the kind of guy
that was living off of bread and water
for a month and you want to talk about
me doing my balls in. You want to talk
about me doing my balls in? Like, you're
talking about yourself, your skin,
you're a gambling addict. You're a
[ __ ] virgin. You've never been seen
with a woman unlike me. And another
thing is, I'm not even saying this, bro.
Yeah, we were saying it [ __ ] other
day, bro. If I look like you at Money
Mike, I'd kill myself. Like, especially
you. You're ugly. You're disabled.
You're a virgin. You've never had a job.
Bro, no wonder you go for me, bro. It
makes it makes perfect sense why you
would go for someone that's younger than
you, that doesn't have an addiction,
that isn't a [ __ ] virgin, you know,
that's got more in life than you, that's
better looking than you. No wonder you
always deflect and reflect on to me, you
know, when you're doing your little
videos. It makes sense. Like, your life
is completely over. You're finished.
Like I would honestly if I was you, I
would kill myself. And I'm not even just
saying that. And then you're and then
you want to go for me. Like you're
you're a self projector. That's
literally all you are. You're a gambling
addict. You're a [ __ ] virgin. You've
pawned all your [ __ ] in. Um you know,
because you're skint. And then you
gamble the money that you get from
pulling. And and that's why you go for
me. That's why you talk about me cuz you
know I'm none of these things. I'm not
ugly like you. I'm not a virgin like
you. I'm not addicted to gambling like
you. Yeah, I might gamble every couple
of weeks properly, you know, and I
always have money. You've got an IVA.
Like, you're you're [ __ ] Like, you're
honestly [ __ ] And that's why you go
for me. I understand it. Yeah. Just like
your boyfriend Nons legs, who's as skint
as you are. Um, you know, it's a pattern
with you people. And especially you,
right? When the heat is on you, you like
to bring up my name and try to start
fake drama. You want to try and make
people believe that you're fighting
people when you're not fighting people.
Because if you really was going to meet
someone, you would have you would have
got in that taxi just like you said you
was going to. You would have got in that
taxi like you agreed to, right? And
okay, then you made an excuse for that
and then well, you would have been to
London by now. But no, you want to do it
for a week's time, which is Wednesday,
and then you're gonna come up with
another excuse. And then when you've
done your balls in again, you're gonna
start fake drama again. Try and act like
you're the big man again. And and and
look at you, mate. Anybody would think
you're the [ __ ] rock. The way you
come on here. Yeah. Act like you're some
kind of bad man. Like you're some kind
of strong man. Like anyone would think
this guy is like Hulk Hogan or some
[ __ ] I swear to God that all he is is
just a little ugly spasticated virgin
from Birmingham that selfreflects his
life onto people that are better than
him. It's it's as simple as like it's as
simple it's it's similar to people from
Lord J's channel. You know the ones that
say, "Oh, you're a M. You're this.
You're that. You're this." But they'll
never show themselves. You're similar to
that except except that you actually do
show yourself and you're [ __ ]
[ __ ] You got missing teeth. Like
look at you and look at me, bro. No
wonder you go for me. No wonder I'm the
first person you mention cuz you're a
jealous little [ __ ] And you know deep
down your life is pointless. You know,
there's like no point being you. You're,
like I said, you're ugly. You're
[ __ ] You're a virgin. You're an IVA
mong. There's not one thing that you say
about me that doesn't apply to yourself.
So, and as usual, you said that you're
coming Wednesday with backup. You're so
predictable. Do you know what everyone
needs to do? Yeah. When this [ __ ] makes
excuses on Wednesday for not turning up,
everybody just ignore him. Anytime he
tries to act like the big man or calls
people out, just laugh at him. Don't
don't go him. Don't do anything. just
laugh at him. And if you're into
gambling, then you can just watch his
gambling videos. But anything to do with
drama and videos, just laugh at him.
He's been doing this for years now and
years now. And you know, it's like what
Tom Tom Wood said, right? Arguing with
Timmy is like playing chess with a
pigeon. Even if you beat it, it's just
going to strut around the chessboard and
[ __ ] all over it and pretend it's one.
I.e. him not getting in a taxi and
changing the rules. I.e. the fact that
he's not already in London. I.e. the
fact that he said he's going to meet all
of these people and he hasn't. He's a
[ __ ] that that that creates fake beef
for attention on YouTube is and that's
it. Because where he knows people are
not liking him and he knows that, you
know, whatever, he's trying to look good
by creating fake drama and then when
Crunch comes to crunch like ordering the
200 taxi, he shits himself. He's a
laughingtock. The excuses on Wednesday
is going to be laughable. I can't wait
to hear it.