Yo. Okay, so this is going to be my
video to uh non legs. I was going to do
this the other day. Um but yeah, I just
couldn't be bothered. Um so uh I just
wanted to start with this. Yeah. Before
I get into like the main bit. Um I was
going on a couple of your community
posts and you were saying about how um
cuz normally I don't um respond to your
community posts because it's just
self-projecting. You know, when you're
saying I'm ugly skin and incel, like
you're just talking about your downbeat
self. Like, that's all you're talking
about. You're not talking about me, lad.
You're talking about yourself. Like,
speaking of incels, like you're so much
of an incel that you had to start
targeting disabled dewism women [snorts]
because you can't get anything normal.
You're too ugly. You're too disabled.
And somehow I'm the incel. someone
that's been with more women that never
had disabilities that were better
looking than that woman that you're
with, but all of a sudden I am the
incel. Bro, name me one woman that
you've been with that isn't an ugly
spasticated girl and then come back to
me and then just start talking about
who's an incel and who's not an incel.
And what I don't understand is um you
were saying about how um uh what was it?
you were saying about how, you know,
there's, thank God that there's not guns
in this country because I'm going to be
the next um Elliot Roger and Reta t um I
don't know if you know this nonslegs,
but people can have a different opinion
and not be a sing
like you and not be a serial killer.
Like, bro, just because I'm not a s that
licks women's asses and be like, "Oh,
women are this, women are that, they
can't do no wrong." like just because I
don't think women are angels does not
equal a serial killer. And next time you
um try and say that I'm the next Elliot
Roger, uh just remember I've not had to
target disabled women because no normal
woman would ever have to deal with me.
Like look at my past women and look at
yours. You're with a [ __ ] [ __ ]
that can't even talk. So I just wanted
to get that out the way. Um and you're
still calling me a virgin in 2026 even
though I got your channel banned for
pornography. Like I've actually got your
channel banned for pornography and
you're still calling me a virgin. Do you
not think that you're maybe just talking
about yourself? Like maybe just a little
bit like with with these community
posts. But anyways, on to the main bit, right?
Okay. So, I went on a couple of your
community posts. There's about four of
them. And you're really trying to [ __ ]
stir stuff between me and Timmy
Eldridge, saying that I'm a [ __ ] that
I can only go for women and not men and
this and that. And like you're proper
trying to [ __ ] stir. You've done it
between me and the neighbor as well, the
next door neighbor. You've tried [ __ ]
Like you've done it with a couple of
people. You've done a lot of [ __ ]
storing. Now, can I suggest one thing,
right? And that's you get a MRI scan.
And if you don't know what MIR scan is,
it's basically a uh it's basically a
head scan. Um because you are suffering
from se severe uh selective memory nons
right I have been to your area once you
did not come out and face me a man you
know the same thing that you're accusing
me of not doing um which to be honest
with you could have beat me there's no
there's no way there's no way way anyone
can say that you definitely wouldn't
beat me I'm not trained in fighting I'm
not a fighter um I've never done boxing
I literally don't know how to fight you
never come out you never said anything
to my face despite bad mouthing me on
YouTube for plenty of years and you
continue to do so. Second time tried
meeting you. Same thing again. You did
not come out was live in your area. You
went running to the police. So this is
what you've done despite trying to say
that I will never meet a man. I will
never say anything to anyone's face. And
then that's them two. Fair. Cool. The
third one. I went to your area. I
[ __ ] put up posters that you was a
[ __ ] nons which could have got you
killed. Like that. That's not even a
joke, bro. that could have got you
killed. Now, there's a certain line that
you don't cross, and I crossed it pretty
much how you did when you tried to get
my money stopped. So, then I went to
your area, pull up posters of you, and
bro, when did you once get me back? Did
you try to meet me after that? Did you
come on my door after that, considering
like I was living by myself like in the
old house near to where you used to go
to your events? Um, did you do my
windows in? Did you put up posters of
me? Like, there was various different
ways that you could have got me back.
Like you got violated probably more than
anybody on this community. Like that's
probably worse than what LT done a
couple of years ago to be fair or on par
with it. Like you got up you that [ __ ]
could have got you killed and you did
not once try to get me back ever and and
you're talking about people not not
being able to face men. I mean Jesus
Christ. Like I think even though the
people out there that are about it the
least if you cross a certain line that's
it. and I crossed that with you when
I've done them posters and you never
tried to get me back once. I had you
stopping going to your event for a
month. Um, I had you stop coming on
YouTube for two weeks. And to be fair,
you probably had to, you know, walk
different directions. Don't say you
didn't cuz you did, right? At the end of
the day, lad, anyone can come on YouTube
a couple of months late, um, a couple of
years later and say, "Oh, that never
happened." When it's calmed down, when
the heat's gone, you know, when time
passes, lad, we all saw what happened
when them posters got out there. So
don't try and tell people about them not
facing men. You have got to be some kind
of coward to allow that to happen and
you not do anything back. See the thing
is with LT, LJ, Terry, whoever wants to
have an opinion on whether Timmy beat me
or he didn't beat me. These people have
actually tried to meet people in the
past or have met me. You will never meet
anyone. You will make sure that you will
never ever meet anyone. It's the same
thing when you used to do them little
coward um videos um in your little gay
little virgin events um and then two
seconds later you jump on the train and
then when somebody would come to your
area, oh big bad nod is running to the
police. Like bro, everybody knows what
you are. So how you try to tell other
people that they're a coward when you
have allowed a man to humiliate the [ __ ]
out of you in your area with them posters?
I bro, you get a head scam because
you're not you're not thinking straight.
Like you generally generally are not um
thinking straight and and that's it. And
like it's the same thing with the Timmy
thing, right? I ignored it. I be I I'll
be real. I ignored it cuz I thought he
was going to go away. I thought he was
just going to get bored. Whatever. I was
trying to do it for my mom's sake. Now
nonslegs, the difference between me and
you is that as soon as I see him try to
badmouth my mom, I was straight in that
taxi. And I must have missed that [ __ ]
by about 20 sec seconds. I was going to
knock him out. Yeah. In front of
everyone. Yeah. Went live in the house.
He wasn't anywhere to be seen even
though he was around the area. Okay.
People told me to go to a pub. Went to
the pub. He wasn't there. You You
understand what I'm trying to say? But
bro, there's no way anybody would have
got away with putting up posters around
me saying that I was a nons all around
the area posted if I knew where they
lived. You knew where I lived. It was It
was next to your events that you stopped
going to. you never ever once tried to
get me back. So, at the end of the day,
lad, please look closer to home before
trying to talk about other people not
facing men. Um, you know, at the end of
the day, that's
that's a valid point. I tried to get
Timmy and I tried to meet him after that
as well. I went to the pub everybody was
telling me to go to. So, I mean, at the
day, at the end of the day, bro. And
then let's look at let's look at the
history, right? I've met Terry. I've
tried to meet Mark Samson. I've tried to
meet Bomb. I've tried to meet Trevor
Dawson. I have I have put myself in
danger on this community multiple times.
Whereas you, you lanky virgin [ __ ] you
let people put up posters about you and
you still haven't got me back. You will
never get me back and you will never
ever say anything to my face ever. So,
you know, you're not about that life to
start [ __ ] stirring. If you want to keep
keep being on YouTube and being
obsessed, then that's on you, bro. Like,
no one cares about yourself projecting
[ __ ] That's no one cares about that.
But when you're trying to [ __ ] stir when
you are the biggest coward going is
beyond me. Like you're not you're not
thinking straight. You'll never meet
anyone ever. People can pull up posters
of you and you allow it to happen. All
you do is go crying to the police. So
how can you like me? That's one thing
I've never done is [ __ ] stir. Even when
Monty and Timmy was arguing all them
times, I would never [ __ ] stir. You will
[ __ ] stir constantly but will never meet
anyone. You will allow people to violate
you time and time and time again. then
you're back on your [ __ ] storm. And how
does how does that even make sense? How
the [ __ ] does that even make sense? And
then you're that much of a coward
because you know that not only will you
not meet anyone that people are beating
you badly on YouTube, you have to get
the police involved. You're a coward in
every single way. Not only do you get
owned on YouTube to the point where you
can't even meet anyone, you then have to
get the police involved every time and
follow stuff up like you're a loser,
lad. You can't you can't talk about
anyone. So when you start when you get
me back for the posters that I've done
of you and you know you whatever then
then come back and start [ __ ] stone coward.