So yeah, just having a vindaloo. I
haven't had a curry in ages. Absolutely
ages. And I just wanted to say to Virgin
Boy that you might be able to um copy my
holidays, you'll copycat and go
Amsterdam and copy me in every single
way possible, but you you can't copy my
tasting food because a you can't afford
it cuz your skin and b you can't handle a window. Yeah,
the corn is more your thing, mate.
more for white
lanky skinny [ __ ] with no muscle.
This is for um
big strong Turkish men. So you might be
able to copy my holidays like I said and
other things. You can't copy my taste of
food, mate. This would send you into
[ __ ] A&E, mate. For me, I'm used to it.
been strong turmo. Man,
you never cop my food, man.
Cuz you have to [ __ ] some night. You
can't handle everything to do.