Yeah, pretty
good. There you
go. So, I was doing something uh Yeah.
I'm not going to lie, bro. I actually
feel like going back with a [ __ ]
hammer, bro. I'm not even
joking. I'm not even joking, bro. I
literally feel like going back with a
hammer. I swear to God,
bro. I'm getting these mooch moves again
over gambling. I swear to God.
put me [ __ ] the whole tendencies up
again, bro. You know what I'm saying?
Yeah, I swear down, bro. And if this was
only £100 as well, this is this is clear
signs of gambling. This was only £100 as
well. Didn't put any more in it. Didn't
lose all my money. Didn't This was only
£100. It's a good telltale sign, you
know. This is why I leave all this stuff
up so people know what how it actually gets
people, you know, and not this [ __ ]
secular flop saying playing, oh well,
you win some, you lose
some. Gambling, gambling, gambling. You
can win. You got garments before. I
literally I was doing that for ages, bro.