So, I'm back at this again. Call it
Saturday. Just done one. Um,
not interested. Just done another one.
And she literally said like in these
words, "I'm not interested." Sorry, I'm
not interested. Sad, sad, sad. Uh, it
seems that it really does. Your past
really does predict your um future when
it comes to dating in this country. It's
literally impossible. And it's got worse
100%. I haven't even started drinking
yet. I'm completely sober and nah.
No chance whatsoever. It's crazy, isn't
it? But you have people that try to
convince you that all of a sudden it's
going to change one day.
>> Change for the worse maybe, but not for
the better. Um, yeah. So,
sad sad sad.