Okay, so now it is Friday and I am going
to do um some sober approaches.
Um I'm literally going to do this one right here. [Music]
>> Don't be like looking for a face. Right,
we'll do another one because it's going to see this one. Excuse me.
>> I had to say that. Beautiful.
>> Thank you.
>> What's your name?
>> My name is >> Peter.
>> Peter. My name is Peter.
>> Nice to meet you.
>> What country are you from?
>> I'm from Albanian.
>> Albanian. Albania. >> Yeah.
>> A lot of people say to me that I look
Albanian, but I'm not. I I
>> Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. When you somewhere. Um,
>> I know he's Albanian, but he's trying to speak.
>> Maybe you can teach me the Albanian
language because I don't know because
people always say that I like Albanian.
>> So, what made you come to London places?
>> I come to study.
>> You come to study? Oh, nice. What do you
>> Business and accountancy. Never heard.
>> Sounds very I've heard accounting. I've
never heard someone studying business.
>> Yeah, business accounting is in business
as well. So
>> that sounds very that sounds very interesting.
>> Check it out.
>> What are you up to today?
>> Well, I have a trip to go with my
student for my class.
>> Okay, so in a bit of a rush. >> Yeah. >> Okay.
>> Have a great day.
>> Cuz if you if you wasn't in a rush, I
would have said I'm very very hungry
from yesterday. So if you wanted to get
Nando, we could go to Nandos. But since
you're in a rush another time,
>> huh? We didn't know that.
>> I I asked you on WhatsApp and and
another time since you're in a rush today.
>> Have a great day. But I really
appreciate even the comments on
everything and even that you even try to
to talk to me. But I even I really
appreciate have a great day. Have a great life.
>> Have a great time. Bye.
>> See you later.
>> There we go.
Told you I didn't want to tell her I was
drinking from all last night. I
absolutely smashed it. Literally. I
actually thought she was actually going
to give her a number there, but nope.
Completely sober as well, mate.
Oh, I like her, man. Um,
[ __ ] it. I wouldn't be right. >> Yes.