Well, it's not that busy cuz it's Tuesday, but
we will still make it work.
Got to find somewhere. Uh,
>> yeah, [ __ ] it. We'll do this one. Excuse
me. Sorry. I just wanted to come over
and say that I thought you looked really beautiful.
>> Thank you.
>> What's your name?
>> I'm Nia.
>> No, Peter.
>> Nice to meet you.
>> Where are you from?
>> Uh from London.
>> London. Fair enough. What's your plans for today?
>> I'm just meeting one of my friends. Literally.
>> Yeah. The weather's nice there, isn't it?
>> Yeah, it is very nice. Getting hotter tomorrow.
>> Yeah. So, where else in London are you from? >> West. >> Chelsea.
>> Okay. And the rich area.
>> The rich area. Well, yeah. >> Yeah.
>> The nice area.
>> The nice area. I remember I went there
once to pick up my passport.
>> Where are you from then?
>> Um I live in Stratford from East London.
So I live my first year accommodation.
>> Yeah. And what do you what do you prefer Stratford or >> Chelsea?
>> Yeah. So
>> Chelsea, there's more to do in
Stratford. Like that was Statford is a
great place to like live for like
location. Like you can get anywhere in London from
>> But there's nothing.
>> I mean you got Westfield and West Stadium, right?
>> Yeah. But
>> I'm not a West fan.
>> No, I hate I don't like football. People
go there and Westfield and stuff, but I
never drink locally.
>> I like,
>> you know, I've never been on a night out
there. Never. I've heard about it, but
I've never been. But whenever I go out,
I never I never stay locally. Like I
always go central or like a different city.
>> How old are you?
>> I'm 20. Fair enough.
>> Lovely to meet you.
>> I was going to say another time. Do you
plan to go in?
>> I actually have a boyfriend.
>> You have a boyfriend? Okay. Have a good
day anyway. Yeah. Thank you.
>> Take care.
>> There we go. Wife friend.
>> I feel like my friends. >> Sorry.