Okay, so I'm going to do an approach in
Costa coffee shop. This is bad.
Sorry, I'm just about to walk past MS. I
saw you and you look nice, so I thought
I just come and say hi to you.
>> So, where are you from?
>> Um, just London.
>> Just London. Oh, just London or
>> I've never heard a place called Just
London before, but uh I have now.
Just unenthusiastic vibes. I was
actually going to do the one. That was
[ __ ] hard, bro. So, it gets harder
and harder to do the more it doesn't
work. And obviously, that's like in a
place where there's loads of people.
It's not like some just walking past and stuff.
So, um, yeah, that was
that was it, bro. [ __ ] Um, just London.
Unenthusiastic from the start. Just
London, bro. What? Any of you that do
this, you'll start understanding what I
mean. Like, you you'll sense the vibes.
It might sound crazy to people that
haven't done this
yet, but yeah, that one was pretty uh
pretty difficult. Not pretty. It should
be like 2 minutes. one one of the bits
do it cuz it's like like I said it's in
a coffee shop. It's a bit embarrassing,
isn't it? Um but yeah, just London. Just
Like cuz even if you said different
things and then you say to them like
something about whatever I don't know
what they're wearing or whatever it may
be then they're just going to say that
they have a boyfriend at the end of it
or they're going to bring up their
boyfriend or that's not going to work at
all. I've not sort of uh
I done my hair as well. I I done my hair
life and clean my face and uh yeah cuz
obviously had to uh
you know but yeah
had to sort of I guess had to do a few
errands so I thought let me knock an
approach out whilst doing so and yeah I
think I'm going to do one more and
that's it. So, I'm going to do I'm going
to do two for today.
No more. Even though I can get addicted.
Uh but yeah. Same.