Wales here. I'm going to do this approach.
Get on the sand.
>> How you doing? You good?
>> How you doing? Are you good?
>> Yeah. You
>> What's up there?
>> I'm going home.
>> Where you from? Exhale.
>> What's that?
>> Where are we from today?
>> From London.
Yeah. What's What's card like?
>> Yeah. Last night.
>> Good. What new place is there to go?
>> Um I'm not really sure.
>> Nobody sure?
>> No. I've got to go. I got a train. I'm
going to check. Thank you.
>> Can I Instagram?
>> I got to find me. I'm joking.
>> There you go.
Even in Wales, mate. even in Wales. But
to be fair, it is on the street and [ __ ]
um just it is on the street to be fair.
So she had a proper W accent. That's
proper Welsh. That is
uh right. Okay.
I feel like I need to do another one cuz
you need that that pump. You know what
I'm saying? That pump, bro. I can feel
my heart beating pounding out my chest.
literally. But to be fair, we will get
something at night. Trust me, 100% you
will here. I'd be very surprised if you
don't get a few numbers here
cuz obviously again it is it is the
daytime and you know, but at night we should definitely
get somewhere and these little ones on
the street will help you be able to
do more at night if that makes sense.
>> Um so yeah. Um anyways, I'm going to get
something to eat and then yeah.
Go back to the hotel, chill for a little
bit, have a bath, get ready, and then go out.