Okay, so I just done that one. I'm not
sure if you heard it
or not, but this is a music just in case you never
see. I think I might do that one there.
>> Actually, there's one there. She's
actually a lot better. He doesn't look >> excited
to have you. Yeah,
>> just visiting friends.
>> Yeah, quite a bit.
>> Yeah, just seeing friends of the day.
Friends of the day.
anyway as well. I was going to say hi on WhatsApp.
>> I have a boyfriend. Sorry. Thank you.
Anyway, but yeah, I'm a boyfriend.
Sorry. Thank you.
>> [ __ ] hell. Help me out here, bro.
Trying to get a girlfriend in this
country is impossible.
You f Honestly, you you start a
conversation with someone
>> and they say straight away they got
boyfriend. You you literally can't even [ __ ]
>> I don't know how people get in relationships.
I don't I mean that they must have got
lucky on [ __ ] dating apps or maybe
through work or maybe years ago, but now >> busy.
>> Even two even before like 2 years ago,
even from 2 years ago, it seems to have
gotten a lot harder than it was then.
But is what it is, man. What's your name, bro?
>> I'm a
>> Peter, man. Nice to meet you, bro. Have
a good day. Yeah,
>> thank you.
>> There you go. I was chatting to one of
the guys want to hear about it.