Yo. Okay, so time for a new video. And
I'm going to title this video as a woman's
worst nightmare is taking accountability
cuz I feel like it's uh very relatable to this
um topic that I'm just about to talk
about. So yeah, um I was on Reddit
yesterday and I uh stumbled across this
woman and we was talking about like
normal things at first, you know, um
finances, cost of living and meta tet
and just normal life stuff, you know, as
you do. And me being me, I couldn't help
but, you know, show her um my approach
in videos where, you know, I've
approached women and they've said
they've got a boyfriend or they've said
no or they've gave attitude or they've
said straight away they're not
interested without even getting to know
you or your personality. Um you know um
and it's it's crazy all the things that
like I've said in previous videos that
makes you think like what hope do you
actually have? you know, you try to
start a conversation with a woman and
it's straight away, you know, I'm not
I'm not interested or they say they've
got a boyfriend when in reality, I hate
to break it to you, but 90% of them
probably don't. Um, and it's like that's
it's just absolute madness. Um, how
anyone would think that you've got hope
of of ever finding someone in this
country. I mean, they're very
optimistic, you know. I don't even think
I could have that hope, you know, after
all of them bad experiences. But it is
what it is. But the main point of this
video is not that the main point of it
was that with that I also showed her
like messages um you know between me and
like different women like some that I
met in the club, the bar, the pub, the
street um you know various different um
places. And um there was one where this
woman and I was speaking um you know
every day for a week and you know only
in the end for her to say oh I didn't
feel the spark and I'm not interested in
dating. Now at the end of the day right
if if that's the case then you know you
shouldn't give your number reply every
single day keep somebody on that string
along to then cut them off the string in
the end. That is somebody doing that on
purpose. Now, the reason I didn't I said
that and not just if they feel this way,
they shouldn't give their number because
obviously the excuse is always going to
be cuz people have got tons of excuses
for women. I don't know why they do, but
they do. Um the excuse is always going
to be well they gave their number to get
away from you or they gave their number
to um because they felt uncomfortable is
one thing but then the other thing being
is them giving you their number
stringing you along every single day
only in the end for them to just say
they're not interested in dating. I mean
they they literally done that on
purpose. I mean, it's it doesn't take
Einstein um you know, to work out. And
she she just weren't having any of it at
all. No matter what I was showing her,
she was dismissing all of my struggles.
She didn't care. Um all she cared about
is victimizing women. Sad re sad reality
we uh live in nowadays. And then I show
her another one where you know I was
speaking to this woman for 2 weeks and
when I mentioned up me when I mentioned
meeting again again she was keeping me
on that white string along. Um all of a
sudden oh we can't uh we can't meet
because we live too far away when in
reality we didn't live far at all. Um,
and then what made it even worse is I
was showing her like women that agreed
to meet me, then on the day they were
supposed to meet, one of them said, "Oh,
I want to get back with my ex." Or, you
know, one would block me or one just
wouldn't reply back. Yeah, these women
done that on purpose. There's literally
no denying that. They never just
randomly changed their mind like she was
trying to make out or decided against
it. They literally done it on purpose
because at the end of the day, if
somebody changes their mind that
quickly, a few different people, I would
probably want to go to the to a
psychologist and see what uh undiagnosed
condition I've got if I'm changing my
mind that quickly. Of course, it was
done on purpose, just like if a man was
to do it, it would be done on purpose. I
don't know why people seem to think
women can't do things on purpose the way
men can. They're not newborn babies.
They know exactly what they're doing.
Um, and she wasn't taking any
accountability for it. It's not even
like she said, "You know what? I thought
you was wrong on two of them and I
thought you was right on two of them."
She's just done nothing but continuously
defend them and continuously make
excuses for them. Um, and what's so mad
is what a lot of you don't know is that
even though some people are good at
approaching, there's not a lot of people
that are good at texting. I'm good at
approaching and I'm good at texting and
I actually arranged to meet with some of
these people and they still come out
with their [ __ ] Um, you know, I've
been dealing with this for [ __ ]
years. You know, I I tried explaining
this to her and she anything I would
show her, she would dismiss and twist it
twisted it to what suited herself. Um,
because it was as if my struggles didn't
suit her. Um,
it's insane at the end of the day. Um,
and then another thing was um, um, yeah,
and then she was trying to say um, about
how I've I was coming on too strong. And
then that's a bit weird to say because
if I was coming on too strong, why did
they arrange to meet me and then you
know bottle bottle out last minute with
some [ __ ] excuse? You know, it's
always excuses. And do you know what? I
would love somebody one day to explain
what that means. Coming on too strong. I
would love one day for somebody to
explain that to me. Um because it it's
to the point now where you hear it so
much it doesn't even make any sense. I
mean, I've I've had a one night stand
before. um you know with a woman that
come on to me and then she was trying to
say that I'm the one that come on too
strong. I mean I feel like it's just a
thing people say now just like when
people say women don't owe you anything
in the wrong context you know they use
that word to justify their shitty
behavior. Um try to justify their shitty
behavior rather but you know it's like
that whole coming on too strong thing.
It's weird because it's like all of
these women will tell people that they
want they want confident men and they
want people to be assertive and
assertive basically means forward and
flirty and very forward with your
intentions. Then as soon as you are, oh
you're coming on too strong. I mean it
doesn't even make sense. Like there was
nothing too strong coming on my
messages. They were completely fine. You
know it was just normal normal talk but
she weren't taking any accountability
for the fact that they were just doing
it on purpose. Um, you know what I'm
saying? And it's crazy. And then I would
say to her about, oh, like they'd reply
to negative things, but they'd ignore
normal messages. Um, and then she
twisted it saying, "Oh, well, no wonder
they don't want you if you're if you're
um, you know, saying negative things."
Again, twisting things to what suits
herself. Typical trait of narcissism.
Um, no, they ignore normal messages and
then as soon as you write negative
things, they reply straight away. Um,
they literally have no accountability
whatsoever for their actions. Like, they
really really really don't. Um, it's
it's crazy. And I'm not going to lie to
you. Right in the end, she was winding
me up so much because she was completely
ignoring what I was showing her and
showing these women that were clearly
taking the piss out of me. I started
getting quite rude and I started getting
quite nasty. And at the end of the day,
right, she was giving examples about
like, "Yeah, but people have had this
done to them before and people have had
this done to them before and they don't
act like that." But the the big
difference is is no one's had it like
me. No one's had it nowhere near 10%
that I have had it with these [ __ ]
women, you know, and you know, I've said
it once and I've said it before. If
anybody went through even 5% of what
I've been through, they would have ended
up killing someone. So in the end of the
day, right, at the end of the day, I'm
not normal because a normal person does
not have the amount of patience that I
do, which is a good thing. You know,
they might want to say, "Oh, you know,
what you're saying is a bit bad and what
you're saying sick." What about all of
the things these women have done, you
know, in the years, the piss taking, the
leading on, the wasting your time, you
know, considering how much you've tried,
you know, to make it work. At the end of
the day with these women and with a lot
of people, they're very fast to see it
from one point of view, which is their
own point of view or a woman's point of
view. But if you if they actually saw
the bigger picture and they actually saw
it from your point of view, they would
understand why you feel the way you do.
If they actually put if they literally
put themsel in your shoes for 10
seconds, they would know exactly why,
you know, you've said the things you've
said and you feel the way you do. It's
completely justifiable. I mean, at the
end of the day, right, how how would we
know if it is or it isn't? No one else
has been through what I've been through.
Nowhere near what I've been through. You
know, if if if it was a woman that had
been through all of this or a man that
had been through all of this, they would
have ended up killing someone. It would
even be someone saying stuff verbally.
So, at the end of the day, you know,
don't judge a m don't don't judge a man
unless you've walked a mile in these
shoes. Um because I don't think anyone
would be here now if they went through
half even, like I said, even 10% of what
I've been through. Um, you know, they
dismiss all your struggles and then they
go back to victimizing women. It's
insane. It is very, very, very insane.
And, you know, it's not like you're
these people making these videos and
you've never tried. You generally
literally have tried more than anybody
in the world. And that's something that
you'll always have going for you. Um,
you know, it's completely justifiable
why you feel the way you feel, you know,
and sometimes you say the things you
say. What would they be like if they
went through anything near what you've
been through? What? They would just be
fine with it. They would just be a
normal person. Of course, they wouldn't.
Do you know what I'm saying? So, um
yeah, it's strange how like they they
completely dismiss your struggles and
just just just
talk about what suit, you know, it's
just it's crazy. It's crazy. Like, it's
you've been through hell and back with
these women. Um, I would love to meet
somebody that's been through even even
half of what I've been through, right?
And see what they're like now. I bet you
they're mentally [ __ ] up in like a
mental hospital or something. It's
because of these women. They don't take
accountability for anything they do. You
know, at the end of the day, like I know
like people sit there and say they don't
compl like don't complain and a man
don't complain. But literally, like I
keep saying, if anybody went through
half of what I've been through, they
would end up going on a killing spree.
I'm I swear to God they would. You know,
how I never ended up going out and
killing anyone after all of these years,
I shall never know. Um, but you know,
people still give you [ __ ] People still
victimize women. People still don't hold
any accountability for what they've
done. It's [ __ ] madness. They just
try and say, "Oh, well, there they just
changed their mind." No, they've done
what they done on purpose. It's insane.
But yeah, women's worst nightmare is
taking accountability. It's It's 30 now,
bro. It's verified. After that today,
you can you can just you just know, you know.