This is the first solo approach I'm
going to be doing. I've l just had my
haircut. So, yeah.
>> Excuse me. Sorry. Sorry. I just wanted
to call over to say that I thought you look beautiful.
>> Sorry. I have a boyfriend.
>> You have a boyfriend? Um,
there we go, bro. Even looking fest as I
do, still can't even get anything. But
I've got a boyfriend. Looks like we're
in for a long day, bro. A long [ __ ] day.
Bad thing is it's like we're literally
just opposite the barbers as well. So
they probably just see me do it and
they're thinking what the [ __ ] So even
after like all the fms after shave, nice
hair, you still can't get anything. But
I've got a boyfriend. That's the first
one. Crazy isn't it, bro?
I think because it's been so long since
well, it's been like two weeks even. It
seems a lot longer that I've not gone
out and done it. It seemed it would have
been a bit different, but never change.