Yo. Okay, so this is going to be my
video to Joseph Fra. Um, like I said I
was going to do. Um, a little bit late.
Uh, I was live, you know, talking to
Dusty and yeah, man, just just time
flew. But, you know, better late than
never, as they say. So, um, yeah, Joseph
Ferrar, it is really, really about time
that you came out of that closet. Um,
and before you say it, I'm not trolling
you. I'm not taking a piss. Um, I'm not,
you know, trying to be funny. I
generally believe at this point that you
are a [ __ ] homosexual. Um, along with
your boyfriend, Nons, and Red Star and
Jamie Thompson. Because think about this
logically for one second. You know, if
they wasn't gay,
why have they been on YouTube for the
past four years stalking um, a [ __ ]
man, you know, from the time they wake
up to the time they go to bed? So I
don't think you are the only one that
hasn't come out the closet yet, Joseph
Ra. And I generally believe that this
obsession um you know with me and this
jealousy and this weirdowness or
whatever the [ __ ] you want to call it, I
genuinely believe that it's starting
well it's always come from within. But I
think it's coming with it's coming
within because you people ain't come out
of the closet yet and you hate yourself
for it and you don't know how to do it.
So, because you don't know how to do it,
um, you know, and the fact that you hate
the fact that you're gay, this is where
a lot of this is coming from. It It
really, really, really is. Now, hear me
out, Joseph Ferrar. Yeah, because I'm
actually going to elaborate and explain
what I mean. Um, something that you
can't [ __ ] do. You know, you say that
people are, I quote, jealous, but you
can't even explain how. You can't even
explain how they're jealous. So, I'll
explain um with you. So, I was on Laura
J's live stream um yesterday, and
believe it or not, I saw every single
one of your comment comments, and every
single one of your comments was about
me. And I'm like, "Nah, this guy's gay.
He's got to be a homosexual. There's
there's no way that this guy is is
straight. There's no way, mate. I am not
[ __ ] having it." Um because I kind of
thought, you know what? Hold on a
minute. Right. a straight man that is,
you know, obsessed and in love with a
woman wouldn't even act this way. I
mean, I can tell you right that, you
know, the women that I've met and, you
know, hooked up with and that, you know,
I thought, you know, at times I was
being a bit bad, but I am not nowhere
near, not even 1% bad um or was obsessed
as these people are with me than, you
know, with these women and I could never
be. And it was a case of where I feel
like even if that was to ever happen
eventually you would get you just get
bored you know whereas these people they
can do this year in year out day in day
out they have got to be gay and jealous.
There is there is just there's just
nothing else now. Like it's not it's to
a point now where it's not even up for
debate. And and that's the thing that
makes it so mad is the fact that a these
people have never met you and b they're
the same sex as you. And when you're not
acting this way towards women that
you've actually met and even if you did,
you would just get bored eventually, but they don't,
there's something seriously wrong with
these people and they do need to come
out the closet um and just do everyone a
favor. Um and themselves a favor also.
So yeah, I would advise you um Joseph
Farra that um you know, find a
convenient time to talk to your wife and
explain to her that uh you like dick. Um
and whilst you're at it, um tell me what
she thinks about you having a channel
dedicated to somebody 10 years your
[ __ ] senior whilst you're [ __ ] at
it. Um because I would love to know her
response um to that because I'm I'm
assuming she doesn't [ __ ] know. Um
that that's like I said if your [ __ ]
wife exists. So um you know that is is
very very very weird. It's very very
strange. You along with your boyfriends
definitely need to come out the closet
and like I said do you and the world a
favor. Um because there is no doubt in
my mind that you are gay now. Um so
that's it. And it's not even like you
know you know there's some people where
you know if you ignore them they will go
away. Um, with these lot, you could
ignore them for [ __ ] 15 years and
they would still do it every day. They
are they are gay. Simple as that. They
are jealous. There's no there's no
there's no denying that. Now, um, so
anyways, moving on. I want to get onto
your community post. Um, the second most
recent one, then we'll get on to the
recent one. So, you said how I've never
seen somebody decline so quickly in 10
days. And then you said, "Well, you've
got Lego and then your what are them
kids clothes that you've got?" They're
not kids clothes, bro. They're men's
clothes made for [ __ ] men. And the
fact that they're selling it and they're
still selling it suggests that [ __ ]
men are still [ __ ] buying it. Yeah, I
needed a couple of casual t-shirts. So,
I bought Simpson one, saw a Spider-Man
one. I love the fact that you think
that's pathetic when they're literally
made for [ __ ] men and you feel like
and you think that somebody, you know,
having a Lego collection is pathetic.
You're trying to take the mole high
ground than what you find, I quote, is
pathetic. Yet, you are literally on
YouTube stalking a man every day for
years. Do you not think that maybe
you're just a little bit more pathetic
than somebody having a [ __ ] Bart
Simpson t-shirt? Really? You don't think
so? I mean, you could be 70, 80 years
old and still like The Simpsons and
still like Marvel. I mean, Jesus [ __ ]
Christ. They're made they're made for
men. The t-shirts are made for men. [ __ ]
me, you know. Um, and then you and then
you was talking about how, you know, um,
uh, you can't um, find uh, meaningful,
you can't maintain meaningful
relationships and and and stuff like
that. Now, we'll get on to the friends
bit and then we'll get on to the women's
bit. Now mate, I have got loads and
loads of different friends. I've got
loads and loads of um associates which
I've made by myself associating with
them. So I'm not sure what you mean by
that. I mean I function in normal
environments and I've met normal people.
So how can't I then maintain normal uh
relationships with people now with
women? Um I mean I've been on dates with
women. I've had sex with women. I've
been [ __ ] I have had friends with
benefits. I've met the same w woman more
than once several times through me going
out approaching talking to them and not
any of these women was disabled like
your boyfriends. Um sorry if that hurt
but the truth you know does hurt. So I'm
not sure what what you mean by that. I'm
not sure what you mean by can't maintain
normal relationships. I've I've been
with several different women. I mean,
they were a bit mad. Some of them were a
bit mad, but they weren't disabled or
vulnerable in any way, shape, or form.
So, I don't know what you mean by that.
Now, then I want to get into your most
recent one. Now, now before I do, um I
wanted to touch on the word um I quote
jealous. Now, you said that I'm jealous.
Okay. So, um if I'm jealous of you, why
have you got the channel dedicated to
me? I mean, I habitantly on purpose try
to avoid you bastards. I ignore you
bastards and you carry on stalking me
and talking about me every day. But
you're saying that I'm the jealous one.
So why are you wasting your life on me
and I'm not wasting my life on you? You
have got the channel dedicated to me
along with your other boyfriends. I
don't have a channel dedicated to you. I
don't post about you. So how can I be
jealous of you? Make it make sense if
you are going to try and tell somebody
that they're jealous. and maybe try not
having a channel dedicated on that said
person that you're trying to accuse of
being jealous. Now, if you're talking
about the gambling, here's the thing.
I might be 10 years your senior, but
guess what, Joe? Um, you know, uh, don't
always take age as face at a face value
and think that because someone's older,
they've got more life experience at a
certain thing because think about it,
bro. Everyone's everyone's in a
different position in life. Now, I can
safely say that I have gambled just as
much as you have, if not more than you
have, bro. I've had loads of money. I've
not had to work. I've done a lot of
gambling. I've done a lot of [ __ ]
around. Yeah. You know, you know, put
two and two together. What does someone
do if they've got time and they've got
money and they're not working? Come on.
So, at the end of the day, just because
I point out your [ __ ] [ __ ] little
um you know uh community post where I
personally believe that you are putting
money in and taking the money out
doesn't mean someone's jealous. It means
somebody that sees through your
[ __ ] Now, when you got asked to
prove that you are winning as much as
you are claiming, what was the excuse
again? I can't go live in the bookies
because I'm going to get banned. Then I
done a video in the bookies recording me
playing roulette. Did I once get told
off? No. Did I once get banned? No. So,
actually prove that you are winning by,
you know, doing a live stream in a
bookies and then try to tell people that
they're [ __ ] jealous. Then you might
have somewhat of a point when you're
trying to call someone jealous. But,
bro, I can see through your [ __ ] I
win football bets. I've won a lot of
football bets. What have I got to be
jealous of? I mean, bro, come on. You
have got the channel being obsessed with
me. It's not the other way around. I
think you will find that you are
jealous. Now, I was wrong, man. You
actually showed yourself.
Congratulations. You showed yourself.
You still didn't show your face, but you
showed that you wasn't fat and you
showed whatever. So, you know, good on
you. You know, I admit when I'm wrong.
However, I love the fact that you were
saying about how, oh, it's so funny how
you think everyone's fat. This person's
fat. That person's fat. We're not all
fat. We're not all this. We're not all
that. Now, Joseph Raw, I didn't just
come with this community and started
thinking everybody was fat. I went by
the patterns over the years with these
people that was saying that you're a
skint and you're this and you're that.
And every single time they got doxed,
they were fat and ugly. It it became a
pattern over the years where hold on a
minute. This Joseph Ferrar is doing the
same thing. He's got fat hands, which
you do. You're probably the same. I
mean, bro, look at your boyfriend Jamie
Thompson. I have never seen anything as
fat and ugly in 28 years. In my 28 years
of living, I never have. So, it's
naturally to it's natural to think that
you are the same when you know there's
been Graycat, there's been bomb, there's
been Pat mustard, there's been several
other different people that's been doxed
and they've been fat and ugly. And the
people that aren't fat and ugly aren't
doing the [ __ ] that you're [ __ ]
doing. So, you know, at the end of the
day, it doesn't take back you being
jealous. Think about it. Joseph Farra,
who is the most jealous of me on this
community? Your boyfriend Nons legs. And
he's and he's lanky. So, I mean, he's
not fat. So, I mean, at the end of the
day, it's it's not one thing, Joseph.
You know, I've got better hair than you.
I've got a better beard than you. I've
got a better life than you and I can't
be bothered. I've got more family than
you. I've got a better voice than you.
I'm more confident than you. I You know,
there's so many little things, you know,
that that you are you are jealous of you
and your boyfriends. It's not just
looks, it's it's so many other things,
you know, and and and that's what it is.
And that does not take away the fact
that you're any any less jealous, you
know, you are jealous of me. You want to
bum me. Yeah. It's as simple as that.
You you want my ass, but unfortunately,
I don't swing that way. So, like I said,
you know, you you come out the closet
and you know, the world will be a much
much better place. You know, I said I
was going to do this video earlier and I
did. So, um, and to be honest with you,
all of the people that are on your
channel saying that I'm this, I'm that,
you know, the haters, the low lives,
they're probably closeted [ __ ]
homosexuals just like you and your
boyfriends are. Same as you, you know,
at the end of the day. And, you know,
even the people that are doing this,
bro, a lot of them are fat and ugly, you
know? You know, and and that that that
generally is the fact. What else would
you want someone to say if people have
been on the YouTube on this YouTube for
years doing this and they've been outed
for their looks multiple times
and even people that shown their face. I
mean, of course, it's natural to think
that you're going to be exactly the
[ __ ] same. Um, so come out of the
closet and get your life sorted because
you clearly clearly are
are not straight, you know, with with
with what you've been doing on YouTube
lately. And I'll still be going to
Nottingham soon and I will let you know
um, you know, when I am going um, what
time of you get more than you'll get
more than enough notice um, beforehand.
So do not worry about that. So yeah,
come out of the closet. Uh you
desperately need to.